"Egyptian President Hosni Mubarak is in the United Arab Emirates , the first stop of a regional tour to discuss the Middle East peace process .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ IN DT NNP NNP NNPS , DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN TO VB DT NNP NNP NN NN ."
Mr. Mubarak met Tuesday with UAE President Sheikh Khalifa bin Zayed al-Nahayan .,B-per I-per O B-tim O B-org B-per I-per I-per I-per I-per I-per O,NNP NNP VBD NNP IN NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP .
The Emirates official WAM news agency says the UAE president stressed the need to revive Middle East peace talks .,O B-org O B-org O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O,DT NNP NN NNP NN NN VBZ DT NNP NN VBD DT NN TO VB NNP NNP NN NNS .
"The news agency quotes Mr. Mubarak as saying his visit to the UAE is part of continuous consultations on issues , including the status of Palestinians .",O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O,"DT NN NN VBZ NNP NNP IN VBG PRP$ NN TO DT NNP VBZ NN IN JJ NNS IN NNS , VBG DT NN IN NNS ."
Peace talks between the Palestinians and Israel stalled after an Israeli moratorium on West Bank settlement construction expired in September .,O O O O B-gpe O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O B-org I-org O O O O B-tim O,NN NNS IN DT NNS CC NNP VBD IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP NN NN VBD IN NNP .
The UAE and Egyptian leaders also discussed ways to promote trade and strengthen diplomatic ties .,O B-org O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP CC JJ NNS RB VBD NNS TO VB NN CC VB JJ NNS .
Mr. Mubarak will also visit Qatar and Bahrain .,B-per I-per O O O B-geo O B-geo O,NNP NNP MD RB VB NNP CC NNP .
