Police say unknown attackers have killed at least seven police officers in central Pakistan .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNS VBP JJ NNS VBP VBN IN JJS CD NNS NNS IN JJ NNP .
"The attack happened early Saturday near the town of Mianwali , in Punjab province .",O O O O B-tim O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O,"DT NN VBD JJ NNP IN DT NN IN NNP , IN NNP NN ."
The outpost building was destroyed in the blast .,O O O O O O O O O,DT NN NN VBD VBN IN DT NN .
Security officials say it is not clear who is behind the attack .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NN NNS VBP PRP VBZ RB JJ WP VBZ IN DT NN .
