Police in southeastern Nigeria have clashed with separatist protesters demanding the release of their leader .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN JJ NNP VBP VBN IN JJ NNS VBG DT NN IN PRP$ NN .
Authorities used tear gas and fired live rounds to disperse youths who blocked roads in the city of Ontisha Monday .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O,NNS VBD JJ NN CC VBD JJ NNS TO VB NNS WP VBD NNS IN DT NN IN NNP NNP .
The separatist group MASSOB says three people were killed - a claim police have denied .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN NNP VBZ CD NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN NN VBP VBN .
"The group , which advocates independence for Nigeria 's Biafra region , had called for a two-day shutdown of business in the region to protest the detention of leader Ralph Uwazurike .",O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O,"DT NN , WDT VBZ NN IN NNP POS NNP NN , VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NN IN DT NN TO VB DT NN IN NN NNP NNP ."
"Millions of ethnic Ibos stayed at home Monday , with reports saying some supported the protest while others were fearful of trouble .",O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN JJ NNS VBD IN NN NNP , IN NNS VBG DT VBD DT NN IN NNS VBD JJ IN NN ."
An Ibo attempt to break Biafra away from Nigeria in 1967 led to a three-year civil war in which more than one million people died .,O B-org O O O B-geo O O B-geo O B-tim O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN TO VB NNP RB IN NNP IN CD VBD TO DT JJ JJ NN IN WDT JJR IN CD CD NNS VBD .
