South Korea says it hopes all parties to the six-nation talks on North Korea 's nuclear program will take active steps to ensure the success of the next round of negotiations .,B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ DT NNS TO DT JJ NNS IN NNP NNP POS JJ NN MD VB JJ NNS TO VB DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNS .
"South Korean Foreign Minister Ban Ki-Moon also said Wednesday in Seoul that his chief nuclear negotiator , Song Min-soon will visit China and the United States before the next round of talks with North Korea .",B-geo B-gpe O B-per I-per I-per O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNP JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP RB VBD NNP IN NNP IN PRP$ JJ JJ NN , NNP NNP MD VB NNP CC DT NNP NNPS IN DT JJ NN IN NNS IN NNP NNP ."
"In Washington Tuesday , the chief U.S. delegate to the talks , Christopher Hill , said Pyongyang 's agreement last month to abandon its nuclear programs could lead to regional peace and the eventual reunification of the Korean peninsula .",O B-geo B-tim O O O B-geo O O O O O B-per I-per O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"IN NNP NNP , DT JJ NNP NN TO DT NNS , NNP NNP , VBD NNP POS NN JJ NN TO VB PRP$ JJ NNS MD VB TO JJ NN CC DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN ."
Mr. Hill also said his staff has held direct talks with North Korean diplomats in New York .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-gpe O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP NNP RB VBD PRP$ NN VBZ VBN JJ NNS IN JJ JJ NNS IN NNP NNP .
