"The economy consists primarily of tourism , subsistence agriculture , and fishing .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ RB IN NN , NN NN , CC NN ."
The government is the major employer of the work force relying heavily on financial assistance from the US .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NN VBZ DT JJ NN IN DT NN NN VBG RB IN JJ NN IN DT NNP .
"The Compact of Free Association with the US , entered into after the end of the UN trusteeship on 1 October 1994 , provided Palau with up to $ 700 million in US aid for the following 15 years in return for furnishing military facilities .",O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN NNP NNP IN DT NNP , VBD IN IN DT NN IN DT NNP NN IN CD NNP CD , VBD NNP IN RB TO $ CD CD IN NNP NN IN DT JJ CD NNS IN NN IN VBG JJ NNS ."
"Business and tourist arrivals numbered 85,000 in 2007 .",O O O O O O O B-tim O,NN CC NN NNS VBD CD IN CD .
The population enjoys a per capita income roughly 50 % higher than that of the Philippines and much of Micronesia .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O,DT NN VBZ DT IN NN NN RB CD NN JJR IN DT IN DT NNPS CC NN IN NNP .
"Long-run prospects for the key tourist sector have been greatly bolstered by the expansion of air travel in the Pacific , the rising prosperity of leading East Asian countries , and the willingness of foreigners to finance infrastructure development .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN NN VBP VBN RB VBN IN DT NN IN NN NN IN DT NNP , DT VBG NN IN VBG JJ JJ NNS , CC DT NN IN NNS TO VB NN NN ."
