Friday 's attack in Dujail in Salahuddin province occurred when many people were on the streets just before the breaking of the fast during the Muslim holy month of Ramadan .,B-tim O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim I-tim O,NNP POS NN IN NNP IN NNP NN VBD WRB JJ NNS VBD IN DT NNS RB IN DT NN IN DT JJ IN DT NNP JJ NN IN NNP .
Some of the victims were policemen .,O O O O O O O,DT IN DT NNS VBD NNS .
"No one has claimed responsibility , but the attack resembled similar bombings carried out by al-Qaida in Iraq .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-geo O,"DT NN VBZ VBN NN , CC DT NN VBD JJ NNS VBN RP IN NNP IN NNP ."
"In other news , the U.S. military says Iraqi and coalition forces have killed two terrorists and detained 13 suspects during operations targeting al-Qaida in Iraq .",O O O O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-geo O,"IN JJ NN , DT NNP NN VBZ JJ CC NN NNS VBP VBN CD NNS CC VBD CD NNS IN NNS VBG NNP IN NNP ."
