Israeli rescue and police officials say one person has been killed near Tel Aviv by a car bomb that was apparently linked to criminal activity and was not politically motivated .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN CC NN NNS VBP CD NN VBZ VBN VBN IN NNP NNP IN DT NN NN WDT VBD RB VBN TO JJ NN CC VBD RB RB JJ .
Authorities say the explosion injured at least five bystanders Friday in the town of Rishon Letzion .,O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-org I-org O,NNS VBP DT NN VBN IN JJS CD NNS NNP IN DT NN IN NNP NNP .
"They say the bomb was placed in a car , and that the explosion killed the vehicle 's driver .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBP DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NN , CC IN DT NN VBD DT NN POS NN ."
Israeli security forces have been tightening security across the nation before the start of the Jewish holy day of Yom Kippur on Sunday .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim B-org I-org O B-tim O,JJ NN NNS VBP VBN VBG NN IN DT NN IN DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP NNP IN NNP .
Palestinian suicide bombers often have carried out attacks ahead of major Jewish holidays .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN NNS RB VBP VBN RP NNS RB IN JJ JJ NNS .
