A published report says the United States and Japan will declare for the first time in a joint agreement that Taiwan is a mutual security concern .,O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBZ DT NNP NNPS CC NNP MD VB IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP VBZ DT JJ NN NN .
"The Washington Post newspaper , citing a draft copy of the document , says the agreement will be announced after a meeting in Washington Saturday between Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice , Defense Secretary Donald Rumsfeld and their Japanese counterparts .",B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O B-per O B-org B-per I-per B-org I-org B-per I-per I-per O O B-gpe O O,"DT NNP NNP NN , VBG DT NN NN IN DT NN , VBZ DT NN MD VB VBN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP IN NNP IN NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP NNP NNP CC PRP$ JJ NNS ."
The Post calls the move the most significant alteration since 1996 to the U.S.-Japan Security Alliance .,O B-org O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-org I-org I-org O,DT NNP VBZ DT NN DT RBS JJ NN IN CD TO DT NNP NNP NNP .
It follows an assessment earlier this week by CIA director Porter Goss that China 's military buildup is tilting the balance of power in the Taiwan Strait .,O O O O O O O O B-org O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,PRP VBZ DT NN RBR DT NN IN NNP NN NNP NNP IN NNP POS JJ NN VBZ VBG DT NN IN NN IN DT NNP NNP .
