"The heaviest snowfall in five years has blanketed Japan 's capital of Tokyo , causing injuries and disrupting transportation .",O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"DT JJS NN IN CD NNS VBZ VBN NNP POS NN IN NNP , VBG NNS CC VBG NN ."
"In its first snowfall of the winter , downtown Tokyo had six centimeters of snow by afternoon Saturday , while neighboring Yokohama was blanketed by eight centimeters .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"IN PRP$ JJ NN IN DT NN , NN NNP VBD CD NNS IN NN IN NN NNP , IN VBG NNP VBD VBN IN CD NNS ."
The weather forced flight cancellations and bullet train delays .,O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD NN NNS CC NN NN NNS .
"The snowfall forced Narita airport , Tokyo 's main international gateway , to close one of its two runways for about an hour for snow removal .",O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD NNP NN , NNP POS JJ JJ NN , TO VB CD IN PRP$ CD NNS IN IN DT NN IN NN NN ."
Several people suffered injuries after slipping on the wet snow .,O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBD NNS IN VBG IN DT JJ NN .
"The Tokyo area had so far missed out on the season 's record snowfalls , which have claimed the lives of more than 100 people , mostly in northern Japan and coastal areas on the Sea of Japan .",O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,"DT NNP NN VBD RB RB VBN RP IN DT NN POS NN NNS , WDT VBP VBN DT NNS IN JJR IN CD NNS , RB IN JJ NNP CC JJ NNS IN DT NNP IN NNP ."
