Afghan government and security officials say Afghan forces have surrounded more than 200 Taleban insurgents in the south .,B-gpe O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-org O O O O O,JJ NN CC NN NNS VBP JJ NNS VBP VBN RBR IN CD NNP NNS IN DT NN .
Provincial officials say the militants have been trapped in Uruzgan province since Sunday .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim I-tim O,JJ NNS VBP DT NNS VBP VBN VBN IN NNP NN IN NNP .
"But an Afghan regional commander , General Rahmetullah Raufi , said there is no campaign to surround insurgents there .",O O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O,"CC DT JJ JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP , VBD EX VBZ DT NN TO VB NNS RB ."
And a spokesman for NATO said he has no information about fighting in Uruzgan .,O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O,CC DT NN IN NNP VBD PRP VBZ DT NN IN VBG IN NNP .
"Despite the opposing accounts , Afghan officials say a key Taleban commander , Mullah Dadullah , might be among the trapped militants .",O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-org O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NNS , JJ NNS VBP DT JJ NNP NN , NNP NNP , MD VB IN DT JJ NNS ."
"But a Taleban spokesman disputes this , saying Dadullah is not even in Uruzgan .",O O B-org O O O O O B-org O O O O B-geo O,"CC DT NNP NN NNS DT , VBG NNP VBZ RB RB IN NNP ."
"In a separate development in the south , General Raufi Tuesday said Afghan and NATO forces clashed with Taleban insurgents in Zabul province .",O O O O O O O O B-org I-org B-tim O B-gpe O B-org O O O B-org O O B-geo O O,"IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN , NNP NNP NNP VBD JJ CC NNP NNS VBD IN NNP NNS IN NNP NN ."
He said 11 Taleban militants were killed .,O O O B-org O O O O,PRP VBD CD NNP NNS VBD VBN .
He added that there were no casualties among Afghan or NATO troops .,O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-org O O,PRP VBD IN EX VBD DT NNS IN JJ CC NNP NNS .
