U.S. military documents show American forces in Iraq have detained the wives of suspected insurgents in an effort to pressure the suspects to surrender .,B-geo O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP JJ NNS VBP JJ NNS IN NNP VBP VBN DT NNS IN JJ NNS IN DT NN TO VB DT NNS TO VB .
The documents are among the thousands released under a court order to meet a request from the American Civil Liberties Union for information under the U.S. Freedom of Information Act .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,DT NNS VBP IN DT NNS VBN IN DT NN NN TO VB DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP IN NN IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP NNP .
They discuss two instances in 2004 .,O O O O O B-tim O,PRP VB CD NNS IN CD .
"In one , a secretive task force detained for two days a mother of three young children , including a nursing six-month old , to "" leverage "" her husband into surrendering .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN CD , DT JJ NN NN VBN IN CD NNS DT NN IN CD JJ NNS , VBG DT NN JJ JJ , TO LQU NN LQU PRP$ NN IN VBG ."
"In the second case , U.S. Army personnel discuss via e-mail an undisclosed number of female detainees , with one saying he believes the women had information or could lead the soldiers to their husbands .",O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN , NNP NNP NNS VB IN JJ DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS , IN CD VBG PRP VBZ DT NNS VBD NN CC MD VB DT NNS TO PRP$ NNS ."
"A Pentagon spokesman said it is difficult to determine what happened from the documents , but he added the military thoroughly examines allegations of misconduct or abuse .",O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NN VBD PRP VBZ JJ TO VB WP VBD IN DT NNS , CC PRP VBD DT JJ RB VBZ NNS IN NN CC NN ."
