Sources close to Iraqi Shi'ite leader Abdul Aziz al-Hakim say the cleric has died .,O O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O,NNS RB TO JJ NNP NN NNP NNP NNP VBP DT NN VBZ VBN .
"Hakim was being treated for lung cancer at a hospital in Iran , and those close to the man said his health was deteriorating .",B-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD VBG VBN IN NN NN IN DT NN IN NNP , CC DT JJ TO DT NN VBD PRP$ NN VBD VBG ."
"A family member and an aide to Hakim , speaking on the condition of anonymity , separately told reporters Wednesday that he had suffered a setback .",O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O,"DT NN NN CC DT NN TO NNP , VBG IN DT NN IN NN , RB VBD NNS NNP IN PRP VBD VBN DT NN ."
"Hakim was known for his close links with Iran , and he led the Supreme Iraqi Islamic Council , one of Iraq 's most powerful Shi'ite groups .",B-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-org B-gpe B-org I-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"NNP VBD VBN IN PRP$ JJ NNS IN NNP , CC PRP VBD DT NNP JJ NNP NNP , CD IN NNP POS RBS JJ NNP NNS ."
"In June , Iraqi President Jalal Talabani visited Hakim in Tehran , where the ailing cleric was seeking treatment .",O B-tim O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O B-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP IN NNP , WRB DT JJ NN VBD VBG NN ."
