"North Korea 's ambassador to the United Nations , Han Song-ryol , says Pyongyang is willing to attend talks over its nuclear arms program if the United States promises peaceful coexistence and non-interference in the North 's internal affairs .",B-geo I-geo O O O O B-org I-org O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"NNP NNP POS NN TO DT NNP NNPS , NNP NNP , VBZ NNP VBZ JJ TO VB NNS IN PRP$ JJ NNS NN IN DT NNP NNPS VBZ JJ NN CC NN IN DT NNP POS JJ NNS ."
"South Korea 's Joong-Ang newspaper quoted Mr. Han Saturday as saying Pyongyang would return to talks "" in any form "" if the United States drops its hostile policy toward the North .",B-geo I-geo O O O O B-per I-per B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP POS JJ NN VBD NNP NNP NNP IN VBG NNP MD VB TO NNS LQU IN DT NN LQU IN DT NNP NNPS VBZ PRP$ JJ NN IN DT NNP .
"Mr. Han singled out Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice 's designation of the North as an "" outpost of tyranny "" as representative of U.S. foreign policy .",B-per I-per O O O O B-org B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,NNP NNP VBD RP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP POS NN IN DT NNP IN DT LQU NN IN NN RQU IN NN IN NNP JJ NN .
"Beijing sent the head of the Chinese Communist Party 's international department , Wang Jiarui , to North Korea Saturday , where he is expected to urge Pyongyang to rejoin six-party talks over its nuclear program .",B-geo O O O O O B-gpe B-org I-org O O O O B-per I-per O O B-geo I-geo B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD DT NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP POS JJ NN , NNP NNP , TO NNP NNP NNP , WRB PRP VBZ VBN TO VB NNP TO VB JJ NNS IN PRP$ JJ NN ."
