"The U.S. director of national intelligence says the Venezuelan government continues to push an anti-U.S. , radical leftist agenda among its Latin American neighbors .",O B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"DT NNP NN IN JJ NN VBZ DT JJ NN VBZ TO VB DT JJ , JJ JJ NN IN PRP$ JJ JJ NNS ."
"In his annual report to the U.S. Congress Tuesday , intelligence director Mike McConnell said the gradual consolidation of democracy continued to be the dominant trend in Latin America over the last year .",O O O O O O B-org I-org B-tim O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O,"IN PRP$ JJ NN TO DT NNP NNP NNP , NN NN NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN NN VBD TO VB DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP IN DT JJ NN ."
"But he said that leaders in Bolivia , Nicaragua and more tentatively , Ecuador , have engaged in sharply anti-U.S. rhetoric inspired and supported by Venezuela and Cuba .",O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,"CC PRP VBD IN NNS IN NNP , NNP CC RBR RB , NNP , VBP VBN IN RB JJ NN VBN CC VBN IN NNP CC NNP ."
McConnell also said Venezuela has increasingly become a major departure point for South American drugs such as cocaine bound for the U.S. He said President Hugo Chavez 's lack of cooperation with international anti-narcotics programs has undermined efforts by neighboring nations by providing traffickers alternative routes .,B-org O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-org O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP RB VBD NNP VBZ RB VBN DT JJ NN NN IN JJ JJ NNS JJ IN NN VBN IN DT NNP PRP VBD NNP NNP NNP POS NN IN NN IN JJ JJ NNS VBZ VBN NNS IN VBG NNS IN VBG NNS JJ NNS .
McConnnell also said recent actions by Cuba 's Provisional President Raul Castro indicate he is looking to make modest reforms to Cuba 's Communist economy .,B-org O O O O O B-geo O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,NNP RB VBD JJ NNS IN NNP POS NNP NNP NNP NNP VBP PRP VBZ VBG TO VB JJ NNS TO NNP POS JJ NN .
