"Venezuelan President Hugo Chavez has lashed out once again at the United States , calling President Bush an "" assassin "" and a "" crazy man . """,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN RP RB RB IN DT NNP NNPS , VBG NNP NNP DT LQU NN LQU CC DT LQU JJ NN . LQU"
Mr. Chavez made the comments Thursday in a speech in Caracas after U.S. Assistant Secretary of State Thomas Shannon strongly criticized the Venezuelan government in testimony to a congressional committee .,B-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O B-per I-per O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD DT NNS NNP IN DT NN IN NNP IN NNP NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP RB VBD DT JJ NN IN NN TO DT JJ NN .
"Mr. Shannon told the committee Thursday that Mr. Chavez is a threat to democracy , and is a destabilizing factor in Latin America .",B-per I-per O O O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNP NNP VBD DT NN NNP IN NNP NNP VBZ DT NN TO NN , CC VBZ DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP ."
Washington denies any such plans .,B-geo O O O O O,NNP VBZ DT JJ NNS .
"Despite the harsh rhetoric between the two nations , Venezuela remains a chief supplier of oil to the United States .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"IN DT JJ NN IN DT CD NNS , NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN NN TO DT NNP NNPS ."
