"The Global Seed Vault opened near the North Pole on 26 February , and an Internet project aimed at promoting biodiversity went on line .",O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNP NNP VBD IN DT NNP NNP IN CD NNP , CC DT NNP NN VBN IN VBG NN VBD IN NN ."
"The so-called "" doomsday "" vault is in the remote Norwegian archipelago of Svalbard and is designed to protect millions of seeds from climate change and other disasters .",O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ LQU NN RQU NN VBZ IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP CC VBZ VBN TO VB NNS IN NNS IN NN NN CC JJ NNS .
The Encyclopedia of Life web site is just a click away and is meant as a source of information about all living things .,O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP IN NNP NNP NN VBZ RB DT NN RB CC VBZ VBN IN DT NN IN NN IN DT VBG NNS .
VOA 's Paul Sisco has more .,B-org O B-per I-per O O O,NNP POS NNP NNP VBZ RBR .
