The military said the vehicle was part of a convoy providing security for a road construction project in the area .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD DT NN VBD NN IN DT NN VBG NN IN DT NN NN NN IN DT NN .
Taleban insurgents and their supporters have stepped up attacks ahead of Afghanistan 's parliamentary elections next month .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,NNP NNS CC PRP$ NNS VBP VBN RP NNS RB IN NNP POS JJ NNS IN NN .
But Afghanistan 's Foreign Minister Abdullah says the insurgency will not hamper the vote and that local enthusiasm will ensure the polls are a success .,O B-geo O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC NNP POS NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT NN MD RB VB DT NN CC IN JJ NN MD VB DT NNS VBP DT NN .
"Mr. Abdullah made the remark Thursday in Canberra , where he was holding talks with Australian government officials .",B-per I-per O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O,"NNP NNP VBD DT NN NNP IN NNP , WRB PRP VBD VBG NNS IN JJ NN NNS ."
