Ukrainian Prime Minister Yulia Tymoshenko says she is ready to accept any conditions necessary to revive the pro-Western ruling coalition she shares with the country 's president .,B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ JJ TO VB DT NNS JJ TO VB DT JJ NN NN PRP VBZ IN DT NN POS NN .
"Ms. Tymoshenko says she will accept any ultimatum , if it will preserve her party 's alliance with President Viktor Yushchenko and avoid a protracted political crisis .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ PRP MD VB DT NN , IN PRP MD VB PRP$ NN POS NN IN NNP NNP NNP CC VB DT JJ JJ NN ."
But she also warned Wednesday in Kyiv that Mr. Yushchenko is doing everything he can to maintain the political deadlock .,O O O O B-tim O B-geo O B-per B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,CC PRP RB VBD NNP IN NNP IN NNP NNP VBZ VBG DT PRP MD TO VB DT JJ NN .
The Yushchneko-Tymoshenko coalition collapsed last month over differences on how Ukraine should respond to Russia 's military incursion into Georgia .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O,DT NNP NN VBD JJ NN IN NNS IN WRB NNP MD VB TO NNP POS JJ NN IN NNP .
"Talks to resuscitate the coalition have made little progress , and the president can call fresh parliamentary elections if no coalition is put into place this month .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS TO VB DT NN VBP VBN JJ NN , CC DT NN MD VB JJ JJ NNS IN DT NN VBZ VBN IN NN DT NN ."
Mr. Yushchenko and Ms. Tymoshenko were close allies during the 2004 Orange Revolution that brought the president to power .,B-per B-geo O B-per B-geo O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O,NNP NNP CC NNP NNP VBD JJ NNS IN DT CD NNP NNP WDT VBD DT NN TO NN .
"They have since disagreed , reconciled and fallen out again .",O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBP IN VBN , VBN CC VBN RP RB ."
