A Palestinian suicide bomber has killed three Israelis at the entrance to a West Bank settlement .,O B-gpe O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,DT JJ NN NN VBZ VBN CD NNS IN DT NN TO DT NNP NNP NN .
The Israeli military says the Israelis were apparently giving a ride in their car to a Palestinian hitchhiker when he blew himself up near the settlement of Kedumim .,O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT JJ NN VBZ DT NNS VBD RB VBG DT NN IN PRP$ NN TO DT JJ NN WRB PRP VBD PRP RP IN DT NN IN NNP .
Witnesses say the bomber was disguised as a religious Jew .,O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP DT NN VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN .
Media reports say the victims included an elderly couple and a young girl .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS NNS VBP DT NNS VBD DT JJ NN CC DT JJ NN .
"The Al Aqsa Martyrs Brigades , an offshoot of the Fatah Party of Palestinian President Mahmoud Abbas , claimed responsibility for the attack .",O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP NNP NNP , DT NN IN DT NNP NNP IN JJ NNP NNP NNP , VBD NN IN DT NN ."
The group said the bomber was a 24-year-old man from the West Bank town of Hebron .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O,DT NN VBD DT NN VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP NN IN NNP .
