Haitian-born musician and humanitarian Wyclef Jean is considering running for president of Haiti .,O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NN CC JJ NNP NNP VBZ VBG VBG IN NN IN NNP .
"Jean 's family released a statement Tuesday , saying that the Grammy Award-winning musician is "" committed to his homeland , "" but he has not formally announced an intent to run for president of the earthquake-shattered nation .",B-per O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NN VBD DT NN NNP , VBG IN DT NNP NNP NN VBZ LQU VBN TO PRP$ NN , LQU CC PRP VBZ RB RB VBD DT NN TO VB IN NN IN DT JJ NN ."
"In an interview with CNN , Jean , who grew up in the United States , said he has filled out the necessary paperwork in case he does decide to move forward with a candidacy .",O O O O B-org O B-per O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN IN NNP , NNP , WP VBD RP IN DT NNP NNPS , VBD PRP VBZ VBN RP DT JJ NN IN NN PRP VBZ VB TO VB RB IN DT NN ."
Presidential candidates have until August 7 to register .,O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O,JJ NNS VBP IN NNP CD TO VB .
"Jean is the founder of the Yele Haiti Foundation , a charity for Haiti that has been active in rebuilding efforts following the devastating earthquake in January .",B-per O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"NNP VBZ DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP , DT NN IN NNP WDT VBZ VBN JJ IN VBG NNS VBG DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
Current Haitian President René Preval is ineligible to run for a third term .,O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,JJ JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ JJ TO VB IN DT JJ NN .
