U.S.-based coffee chain Starbucks has announced plans to close 600 stores in the United States in the next year due to the weak U.S. economy .,O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,JJ NN NN NNP VBZ VBN NNS TO VB CD NNS IN DT NNP NNPS IN DT JJ NN JJ TO DT JJ NNP NN .
"The Seattle , Washington-based coffee seller announced the move on Tuesday during a conference call with reporters .",O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O,"DT NNP , JJ NN NN VBD DT NN IN NNP IN DT NN NN IN NNS ."
"The company says about 12,000 employees , or seven percent of its global workforce , will lose their jobs because of the closures .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ IN CD NNS , CC CD NN IN PRP$ JJ NN , MD VB PRP$ NNS IN IN DT NNS ."
It says it will open fewer than 200 stores in 2009 .,O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,PRP VBZ PRP MD VB JJR IN CD NNS IN CD .
"Starbucks ' Chief Financial Officer , Peter Bocian , said many of the stores being closed were located near other Starbucks stores .",B-org O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O,"NNP POS NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP , VBD NN IN DT NNS VBG VBN VBD VBN IN JJ NNP NNS ."
"Because of the company 's aggressive expansion practice , it is not uncommon in the United States to see two of the shops within blocks of or even across the street from each other .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN IN DT NN POS JJ NN NN , PRP VBZ RB JJ IN DT NNP NNPS TO VB CD IN DT NNS IN NNS IN CC RB IN DT NN IN DT NN ."
"The company also has been expanding worldwide , operating in 45 countries .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN RB VBZ VBN VBG NN , VBG IN CD NNS ."
