"Iran 's President Mahmoud Ahmedinejad has marked the 25th anniversary of the outbreak of the Iran-Iraq war with a warning that any nation attacking the Islamic Republic will face a "" destructive and fiery "" response .",B-geo O B-per I-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN DT NNP NN IN DT NN IN DT NN VBG DT NNP NNP MD VB DT LQU JJ CC JJ RQU NN .
"Speaking on Thursday at a military parade in Tehran , Mr. Ahmedinejad said Iran is serious about defending its security from its enemies .",O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"VBG IN NNP IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , NNP NNP VBD NNP VBZ JJ IN VBG PRP$ NN IN PRP$ NNS ."
"He did not name any country , but Iran regularly refers to the United States and Israel as its chief adversaries .",O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O,"PRP VBD RB VB DT NN , CC NNP RB VBZ TO DT NNP NNPS CC NNP IN PRP$ NN NNS ."
"The hardline president also insisted that Iran wants peace , stability and justice in international relations .",O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN RB VBD IN NNP VBZ NN , NN CC NN IN JJ NNS ."
"Thousands of troops and military hardware were on display at the parade , including six of Iran 's newest Shahab-3 ballistic missiles .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"NNS IN NNS CC JJ NN VBD IN NN IN DT NN , VBG CD IN NNP POS JJS JJ JJ NNS ."
Analysts say the 1980 - 1988 war - in which the United States backed Iraq 's Saddam Hussein - was fought to a standstill .,O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O,NNS VBP DT CD IN CD NN : IN WDT DT NNP NNPS VBD NNP POS NNP NNP : VBD VBN TO DT NN .
Up to one million people died in the conflict .,O O O O O O O O O O,IN TO CD CD NNS VBD IN DT NN .
