The International Criminal Court has ordered the release of former Congolese militia leader Thomas Lubanga following a delay in his trial .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN JJ JJ NN NN NNP NNP VBG DT NN IN PRP$ NN .
Prosecutors have been given five days to appeal his release .,O O O O B-tim O O O O O O,NNS VBP VBN VBN CD NNS TO VB PRP$ NN .
Lubanga is accused of using child soldiers in clashes involving his Union of Congolese Patriots militia during 2002 and 2003 in the Democratic Republic of Congo 's Ituri district .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org B-gpe B-org O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O,NNP VBZ VBN IN VBG NN NNS IN NNS VBG PRP$ NNP IN JJ NNPS NN IN CD CC CD IN DT JJ NNP IN NNP POS NNP NN .
Lubanga 's trial was suspended last month after the court ruled that prosecutors inhibited his defense team by refusing to share documents that could help establish his innocence .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NN VBD VBN JJ NN IN DT NN VBD IN NNS VBD PRP$ NN NN IN VBG TO VB NNS WDT MD VB VB PRP$ NN .
Some four million people were killed in conflict or by disease and hunger during Congo 's civil war from 1998 to 2003 .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,DT CD CD NNS VBD VBN IN NN CC IN NN CC NN IN NNP POS JJ NN IN CD TO CD .
"Militia and rebel groups continue to be active in parts of eastern Congo , mainly North Kivu province .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O,"NNP CC JJ NNS VBP TO VB JJ IN NNS IN JJ NNP , RB JJ NNP NN ."
