French smokers are savoring their last cigarettes in cafes as strict new smoking bans are to take effect in the country and much of Germany .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNS VBP VBG PRP$ JJ NNS IN NNS IN JJ JJ NN NNS VBP TO VB NN IN DT NN CC NN IN NNP .
"The French ban formally started with the New Year , but authorities say they are delaying enforcement until Wednesday .",O B-gpe O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"DT JJ NN RB VBD IN DT NNP NNP , CC NNS VBP PRP VBP VBG NN IN NNP ."
"French Health Minister Roselyne Bachelot on Monday rejected calls for last-minute changes to the ban , which covers smoking in all in public places .",B-gpe O O B-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP IN NNP VBD NNS IN JJ NNS TO DT NN , WDT VBZ NN IN DT IN JJ NNS ."
Some establishments say the ban will hurt business .,O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP DT NN MD VB NN .
"The French smoking ban applies to restaurants , bars , cafes and night clubs , and in February it will expand to offices , schools , airports and a number of other enclosed public spaces .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN NN VBZ TO NNS , NNS , NNS CC NN NNS , CC IN NNP PRP MD VB TO NNS , NNS , NNS CC DT NN IN JJ JJ JJ NNS ."
"In Germany , legislation requiring smoke-free areas in bars and restaurants has gone into effect in eight of 16 states .",O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,"IN NNP , NN VBG JJ NNS IN NNS CC NNS VBZ VBN IN NN IN CD IN CD NNS ."
"The law covers Bavaria , Berlin , Brandenburg , Bremen , Hamburg , Mecklenburg-Western Pomerania , Saxony-Anhalt and Schleswig-Holstein .",O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O B-geo O,"DT NN VBZ NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP , JJ NNP , NNP CC NNP ."
