Spanish police have arrested an Algerian man charged with providing logistical support to a suspected coordinator of the September 11 terrorist attacks on the United States .,B-gpe O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O B-geo I-geo O,JJ NNS VBP VBN DT JJ NN VBN IN VBG JJ NN TO DT JJ NN IN DT NNP CD JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNPS .
"Authorities say they arrested the man , identified as Tahar Izerouel , late Tuesday .",O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-tim O,"NNS VBP PRP VBN DT NN , VBN IN NNP NNP , JJ NNP ."
He was charged earlier this week along with seven other terrorist suspects .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD VBN RBR DT NN IN IN CD JJ JJ NNS .
The Algerian was still at large when formally charged and anti-terrorism judge Baltasar Garzon ordered his arrest .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O,DT NN VBD RB IN JJ WRB RB VBN CC JJ NN NNP NNP VBD PRP$ NN .
