"The United Nations top envoy on Burma has wrapped up a visit to India , where he says he had "" candid discussions "" with officials there about promoting change in military-ruled Burma .",O B-org I-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"DT NNP NNP JJ NN IN NNP VBZ VBN RP DT NN TO NNP , WRB PRP VBZ PRP VBD RQU JJ NNS LQU IN NNS RB IN VBG NN IN JJ NNP ."
"A U.N. spokeswoman said that during Ibrahim Gambari 's meetings , the two sides agreed to acknowledge the positive steps Burma 's military leaders are taking .",O B-org O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"DT NNP NN VBD IN IN NNP NNP POS NNS , DT CD NNS VBD TO VB DT JJ NNS NNP POS JJ NNS VBP VBG ."
They also agreed to encourage Burma to make further progress toward democratization and the respect of human rights .,O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP RB VBD TO VB NNP TO VB JJ NN IN NN CC DT NN IN JJ NNS .
"Gambari told reporters in India that he plans to visit Burma soon , but did not give a specific date .",B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD NNS IN NNP IN PRP VBZ TO VB NNP RB , CC VBD RB VB DT JJ NN ."
Gambari arrived in New Delhi earlier this week from Beijing where he also met with Chinese leaders to discuss Burma 's political situation .,B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-tim B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo O O O O,NNP VBD IN NNP NNP RBR DT NN IN NNP WRB PRP RB VBD IN JJ NNS TO VB NNP POS JJ NN .
Gambari is scheduled to travel next to Japan for further meetings .,B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN TO VB JJ TO NNP IN JJ NNS .
"Rights groups have criticized India and China 's continued investments in Burma , saying such ventures help support a government accused of human rights violations .",O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS NNS VBP VBN NNP CC NNP POS JJ NNS IN NNP , VBG JJ NNS VBP VB DT NN VBN IN JJ NNS NNS ."
