A one-day peace conference hosted by Indian Prime Minister Manmohan Singh has ended with assurances from the prime minister aimed at pushing the peace process forward in Indian-Kashmir .,O B-tim O O O O B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT JJ NN NN VBN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NNS IN DT JJ NN VBN IN VBG DT NN NN RB IN NNP .
The prime minister announced Saturday that his government may soon release detained political leaders who are not being held on serious charges .,O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBD NNP IN PRP$ NN MD RB VB VBN JJ NNS WP VBP RB VBG VBN IN JJ NNS .
Mr. Singh met in New Delhi Saturday with representatives of pro-India parties as well as minority Hindu groups from Muslim-majority Kashmir .,B-per I-per O O B-geo I-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD IN NNP NNP NNP IN NNS IN JJ NNS RB RB IN NN NNP NNS IN JJ NNP .
But Kashmiri separatist leaders boycotted the talks .,O B-gpe O O O O O O,CC JJ JJ NNS VBD DT NNS .
Some of them had demanded India first build confidence in Kashmir by releasing the political activists and reducing troop levels .,O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,DT IN PRP VBD VBN NNP RB VB NN IN NNP IN VBG DT JJ NNS CC VBG NN NNS .
Mr. Singh says he is confident that Kashmiri leaders who stayed away from the conference will eventually join the dialogue when they see the benefits of taking part .,B-per I-per O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ JJ IN JJ NNS WP VBD RB IN DT NN MD RB VB DT NN WRB PRP VBP DT NNS IN VBG NN .
"Some Kashmiri separatists are seeking independence from India , while others want to merge with Pakistan .",O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT JJ NNS VBP VBG NN IN NNP , IN NNS VBP TO VB IN NNP ."
