"The centrist party of outgoing Bulgarian Prime Minister Simeon Saxe-Coburg-Gotha has ended its efforts to form a new government , almost seven weeks after inconclusive parliamentary elections .",O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN IN VBG JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP$ NNS TO VB DT JJ NN , RB CD NNS IN JJ JJ NNS ."
"The centrists announced the failure of their efforts Thursday , two weeks after the Socialist Party also abandoned efforts to organize a new cabinet .",O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS VBD DT NN IN PRP$ NNS NNP , CD NNS IN DT NNP NNP RB VBD NNS TO VB DT JJ NN ."
The Socialists outpolled the party led by Mr. Simeon Saxe-Coburg-Gotha in the June 25 elections .,O B-org O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O B-tim I-tim O O,DT NNPS VBD DT NN VBN IN NNP NNP NNP IN DT NNP CD NNS .
"However , Socialist leader Sergei Stanishev could not muster enough support in the new parliament to form a coalition government .",O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , JJ NN NNP NNP MD RB VB JJ NN IN DT JJ NN TO VB DT NN NN ."
"News reports quote analysts as saying a lengthy political crisis could delay the implementation of reforms the European Union has declared necessary if Bulgaria is to join the bloc , as planned , in 2007 .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"NN NNS VBP NNS IN VBG DT JJ JJ NN MD VB DT NN IN NNS DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN JJ IN NNP VBZ TO VB DT NN , IN VBN , IN CD ."
