Pop singer Elton John and his long-time male partner joined hundreds of other same-sex couples in exchanging vows under a new civil partnership law that went into effect Wednesday in England and Wales .,O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,NNP NN NNP NNP CC PRP$ JJ NN NN VBD NNS IN JJ JJ NNS IN VBG NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN NN WDT VBD IN NN NNP IN NNP CC NNP .
"Mr. John and Canadian filmmaker David Furnish - partners for 12 years - took their vows in a ceremony at Windsor Guildhall , just west of London .",B-per I-per O B-gpe O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-geo O,"NNP NNP CC JJ NN NNP NNP : NNS IN CD NNS : VBD PRP$ NNS IN DT NN IN NNP NNP , RB NN IN NNP ."
"A large crowd turned out to see the couple , whose ceremony was held in the same building where Prince Charles married Camilla Parker-Bowles last April .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O B-geo I-geo O B-tim O,"DT JJ NN VBD RP TO VB DT NN , WP$ NN VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN WRB NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP JJ NNP ."
"The new civil partnership law gives homosexual couples the same property and inheritance rights as heterosexual married couples , and it entitles them to the same pension , immigration and tax benefits .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ JJ NN NN VBZ JJ NNS DT JJ NN CC NN NNS IN JJ JJ NNS , CC PRP VBZ PRP TO DT JJ NN , NN CC NN NNS ."
"The law took effect Wednesday in England and Wales , after becoming effective in Northern Ireland Monday and Scotland Tuesday .",O O O O B-tim O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O B-geo I-geo B-tim O B-geo B-tim O,"DT NN VBD NN NNP IN NNP CC NNP , IN VBG JJ IN NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP ."
