"Paul McCartney , one of two surviving members of the music group the Beatles , has arrived in Israel for his first concert in the Jewish state .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP , CD IN CD VBG NNS IN DT NN NN DT NNP , VBZ VBN IN NNP IN PRP$ JJ NN IN DT JJ NN ."
"Thursday 's concert is part of the musician 's series called "" Friendship First "" that features performances in cities McCartney has not visited before .",B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O,NNP POS NN VBZ NN IN DT NN POS NN VBD RQU NNP NNP LQU WDT VBZ NNS IN NNS NNP VBZ RB VBN IN .
The former Beatle says he hopes the concert will bring a message of peace to the Middle East .,O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT JJ NNP VBZ PRP VBZ DT NN MD VB DT NN IN NN TO DT NNP NNP .
"Organizers say McCartney will perform at an outdoor venue in Tel Aviv for a crowd of at least 40,000 people .",O O B-per O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP NNP MD VB IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP IN DT NN IN IN JJS CD NNS .
"In 1965 the Beatles were set to perform in Israel , but the concert was canceled after Israeli government officials said the band might be a corruptive influence .",O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN CD DT NNPS VBD VBN TO VB IN NNP , CC DT NN VBD VBN IN JJ NN NNS VBD DT NN MD VB DT JJ NN ."
The government formally apologized for the 1965 cancellation earlier this year .,O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O,DT NN RB VBD IN DT CD NN RBR DT NN .
