The European Union says Israel 's plan to raze Palestinian houses in East Jerusalem is illegal under international law .,O B-org I-org O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ NNP POS NN TO VB JJ NNS IN NNP NNP VBZ JJ IN JJ NN .
"EU foreign affairs chief Catherine Ashton said Wednesday the demolition of the 22 homes would be "" an obstacle to peace . """,B-org O O O B-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP JJ NNS JJ NNP NNP VBD NNP DT NN IN DT CD NNS MD VB LQU DT NN TO NN . LQU
"Israel plans to replace the homes , located in the al-Bustan neighborhood in Silwan district , with an archaeological park .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ TO VB DT NNS , VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NN , IN DT JJ NN ."
"Protests in the neighborhood have occurred repeatedly in recent months , but escalated after Jerusalem Mayor Nir Barkat approved the controversial redevelopment plan earlier this month .",O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN DT NN VBP VBN RB IN JJ NNS , CC VBN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN NN RBR DT NN ."
"U.N. Secretary-General Ban Ki-moon said last week the planned demolitions and further Israeli activity "" are contrary to international law and to the wishes of Palestinian residents . """,B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD JJ NN DT VBN NNS CC JJ JJ NN LQU VBP JJ TO JJ NN CC TO DT NNS IN JJ NNS . LQU
"Palestinian President Mahmoud Abbas and Jordan 's King Abdullah II also denounced the plans , and U.S. officials have warned the project could further threaten Middle East peace efforts .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O B-gpe O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP CC NNP POS NNP NNP NNP RB VBD DT NNS , CC NNP NNS VBP VBN DT NN MD RB VB NNP NNP NN NNS ."
