A senior member of Tajikistan 's Islamic opposition party has died after spending five years in prison .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-tim I-tim O,DT JJ NN IN NNP POS JJ NN NN VBZ VBN IN VBG CD NNS IN NN .
"The Islamic Renaissance Party ( IRP ) says the group 's deputy leader , Shamsiddin Shamsiddinov , died from cancer on Wednesday .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-tim O,"DT NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP RRB VBZ DT NN POS NN NN , NNP NNP , VBD IN NN IN NNP ."
"Shamsiddinov was arrested in 2003 , and sentenced a year later to 16 years in prison for a series of charges including illegal border crossing and polygamy .",B-per O O O B-tim O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD VBN IN CD , CC VBD DT NN RB TO CD NNS IN NN IN DT NN IN NNS VBG JJ NN VBG CC NN ."
The IRP says he was targeted for his political views .,O B-org O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP VBZ PRP VBD VBN IN PRP$ JJ NNS .
The IRP fought the former Soviet republic 's Moscow-backed government during a 1992 - 1997 civil war .,O B-org O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O,DT NNP VBD DT JJ NNP NN POS JJ NN IN DT CD IN CD JJ NN .
The party later entered a power-sharing agreement with the government .,O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN RB VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NN .
"In other news , Tajik security officials say more than 500 kilograms of illegal drugs were seized during a raid along the country 's border with Afghanistan Thursday .",O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O,"IN JJ NN , JJ NN NNS VBP JJR IN CD NNS IN JJ NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN IN DT NN POS NN IN NNP NNP ."
Officials say several smugglers have also been detained .,O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP JJ NNS VBP RB VBN VBN .
