"Three architects have unveiled plans for a trio of skyscrapers to surround the World Trade Center site in New York City , which is being turned into a memorial to victims of the September 11 , 2001 terrorist attacks .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O,"CD NNS VBP VBN NNS IN DT NN IN NNS TO VB DT NNP NNP NNP NN IN NNP NNP NNP , WDT VBZ VBG VBN IN DT JJ TO NNS IN DT NNP CD , CD JJ NNS ."
"Plans for the three buildings were unveiled Thursday , designed by Britons Norman Foster and Richard Rogers and Japanese national Fumihiko Maki .",O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-gpe B-per I-per O B-per I-per O B-gpe O B-per I-per O,"NNS IN DT CD NNS VBD VBN NNP , VBN IN NNS NNP NNP CC NNP NNP CC JJ NN NNP NNP ."
"The skyscrapers will flank the American-designed Freedom Tower , which will stand more than 540 meters high - the tallest building in New York .",O O O O O O B-art I-art O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"DT NNS MD VB DT JJ NNP NNP , WDT MD VB JJR IN CD NNS JJ IN DT JJS NN IN NNP NNP ."
"The rebuilding of the World Trade Center site has been repeatedly delayed by insurance and security concerns , as well as arguments over the design of the memorial .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NN VBZ VBN RB VBN IN NN CC NN NNS , RB RB IN NNS IN DT NN IN DT NN ."
Construction of the Freedom Tower is set to begin next year .,O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O,NN IN DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB JJ NN .
The entire site is expected to be completed by 2012 .,O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT JJ NN VBZ VBN TO VB VBN IN CD .
