"U.S. Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice starts a tour of Central Asian countries Tuesday , to promote democratic and economic reforms , while securing support for the U.S.-led war on terrorism .",B-org O O B-org B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT NN IN JJ JJ NNS NNP , TO VB JJ CC JJ NNS , IN VBG NN IN DT JJ NN IN NN ."
"Ms. Rice stops first in Bishkek , the capital of Kyrgyzstan , where she is to hold talks with top government officials , including President Kurmanbek Bakiyev , and participate in a panel discussion on democracy and reforms .",B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ RB IN NNP , DT NN IN NNP , WRB PRP VBZ TO VB NNS IN JJ NN NNS , VBG NNP NNP NNP , CC VB IN DT NN NN IN NN CC NNS ."
"She will also travel to Afghanistan , Kazakhstan and Tajikistan .",O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O,"PRP MD RB VB TO NNP , NNP CC NNP ."
"Monday , Ms. Rice said she also might visit Pakistan to show U.S. support for earthquake victims .",B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O,"NNP , NNP NNP VBD PRP RB MD VB NNP TO VB NNP NN IN NN NNS ."
The trip does not include a stop in Uzbekistan .,O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NN VBZ RB VB DT NN IN NNP .
"A top State Department official has expressed concern over recent decisions by the Uzbek government and a "" general climate of fear "" in the country .",O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNP NNP NN VBZ VBN NN IN JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN CC DT LQU JJ NN IN NN LQU IN DT NN .
