Iraqi police have found at least 10 more bodies in Baghdad - the latest victims of apparent sectarian violence .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN IN JJS CD JJR NNS IN NNP IN DT JJS NNS IN JJ JJ NN .
"In Geneva Thursday , Manfred Nowak said torture in Iraq is - as he put it - "" totally out of hand . """,O B-tim I-tim O B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP NNP , NNP NNP VBD NN IN NNP VBZ : IN PRP VBD PRP : LQU RB IN IN NN . LQU"
"In other violence Friday , a roadside bomb killed an American soldier in eastern Baghdad .",O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo I-geo O,"IN JJ NN NNP , DT NN NN VBD DT JJ NN IN JJ NNP ."
"A senior U.S. general in Iraq , Major General James Thurman , told reporters at the Pentagon Friday that he would like about 3,000 more Iraqi soldiers to join the effort to end violence in Baghdad .",O O B-geo O O B-geo O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-org B-tim O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT JJ NNP NN IN NNP , NNP NNP NNP NNP , VBD NNS IN DT NNP NNP IN PRP MD VB RB CD JJR JJ NNS TO VB DT NN TO VB NN IN NNP ."
"The general said currently there are 15,000 U.S. troops taking part in the security operation in Baghdad , but only 9,000 Iraqi soldiers .",O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O,"DT NN VBD RB EX VBP CD NNP NNS VBG NN IN DT NN NN IN NNP , CC RB CD JJ NNS ."
