"Venezuela has begun military instruction of civilian reservists who , according to officials there , would conduct guerilla warfare against foreign aggressors .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBN JJ NN IN JJ NNS WP , VBG TO NNS RB , MD VB NN NN IN JJ NNS ."
"About 500,000 civilians have begun training .",O O O O O O O,IN CD NNS VBP VBN NN .
They will train on weekends for four months of weapons and resistance tactics .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP MD VB IN NNS IN CD NNS IN NNS CC NN NNS .
Mr. Chavez has begun the civilian training program to build up a force capable of resisting a more powerful foreign force .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN NN TO VB RP DT NN JJ IN VBG DT RBR JJ JJ NN .
Washington has denied it has any plans to invade Venezuela and has warned that Mr. Chavez is becoming a threat to Venezuela 's democracy and regional stability .,B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN PRP VBZ DT NNS TO VB NNP CC VBZ VBN IN NNP NNP VBZ VBG DT NN TO NNP POS NN CC JJ NN .
