Two Britons have appeared in a London court to answer charges of leaking a sensitive government memo on reported comments by President Bush about bombing the headquarters of the Arab satellite TV channel Al-Jazeera .,O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,CD NNS VBP VBN IN DT NNP NN TO VB NNS IN VBG DT JJ NN NN IN VBN NNS IN NNP NNP IN VBG DT NN IN DT JJ NN NN NN NNP .
Civil Servant David Keogh and former government researcher Leo O'Connor face charges of violating Britain 's official Secrets Act that bans such disclosures .,B-org I-org B-per I-per O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP CC JJ NN NN NNP NNP NN NNS IN VBG NNP POS JJ NNP NNP WDT VBZ JJ NNS .
The court put off further hearings until January 10th .,O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT NN VBD RP JJ NNS IN NNP CD .
"Last week , a British newspaper , the Daily Mirror , reported that a leaked British government memo had described a 2004 meeting between Prime Minister Tony Blair and President Bush .",O O O O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-tim O O B-per O B-per I-per O B-per I-per O,"JJ NN , DT JJ NN , DT NNP NNP , VBD IN DT JJ JJ NN NN VBD VBN DT CD NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP ."
"The report quoted the memo as saying Mr. Bush discussed plans to bomb al-Jazeera headquarters in Qatar , but that Mr. Blair talked him out of it .",O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD DT NN IN VBG NNP NNP VBD NNS TO VB JJ NN IN NNP , CC IN NNP NNP VBD PRP IN IN PRP ."
"Monday , Mr. Blair denied receiving information about a plot to bomb the station .",B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP , NNP NNP VBD VBG NN IN DT NN TO VB DT NN ."
"The White House has dismissed the report as "" outlandish . """,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN RQU NN . LQU
