U.S. Treasury officials have arrived in South Korea to discuss ways to stop North Korea 's alleged illegal financial activities .,B-org I-org O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNS VBP VBN IN NNP NNP TO VB NNS TO VB NNP NNP POS JJ JJ JJ NNS .
"Daniel Glaser , deputy assistant secretary for terrorist financing and financial crimes , will stay in Seoul until Tuesday to discuss North Korea 's counterfeiting of U.S. currency and money laundering .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O,"NNP NNP , JJ NN NN IN JJ NN CC JJ NNS , MD VB IN NNP IN NNP TO VB NNP NNP POS NN IN NNP NN CC NN NN ."
"Glaser visited Hong Kong and Macau from Tuesday through Friday as part of a larger Asian tour that also includes stops in Beijing , and Tokyo .",B-per O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O,"NNP VBD NNP NNP CC NNP IN NNP IN NNP IN NN IN DT JJR JJ NN WDT RB VBZ NNS IN NNP , CC NNP ."
"The United States has slapped sanctions on companies it suspects of aiding North Korea in counterfeiting , money laundering and the drug trade .",O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNPS VBZ VBN NNS IN NNS PRP VBZ IN VBG NNP NNP IN VBG , NN NN CC DT NN NN ."
U.S. officials have also blacklisted eight North Korean companies in connection with weapons proliferation .,B-geo O O O O O B-geo B-gpe O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBP RB VBN CD JJ JJ NNS IN NN IN NNS NN .
North Korea says it will boycott six-part nuclear disarmament talks until the sanctions are lifted .,B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ PRP MD VB JJ JJ NN NNS IN DT NNS VBP VBN .
