Former U.S. President Bill Clinton will meet Taiwan President Chen Shui-bian as part of an ongoing Asian tour .,O B-org B-per I-per I-per O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP MD VB NNP NNP NNP NNP IN NN IN DT JJ JJ NN .
"A Taiwanese foreign ministry spokesman told the Reuters news agency Mr. Clinton will deliver a speech on democracy and security after arriving in Taipei Sunday , following stops in South Korea and Japan , then have dinner with Mr. Chen .",O B-gpe O O O O O B-org O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O B-per I-per O,"DT JJ JJ NN NN VBD DT NNP NN NN NNP NNP MD VB DT NN IN NN CC NN IN VBG IN NNP NNP , VBG NNS IN NNP NNP CC NNP , RB VBP NN IN NNP NNP ."
"The visit is likely to anger Beijing , which views Taiwan as a renegade province of China and objects to any participation by the island in international affairs .",O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ JJ TO VB NNP , WDT VBZ NNP IN DT NN NN IN NNP CC VBZ TO DT NN IN DT NN IN JJ NNS ."
"Mr. Clinton visited Beijing earlier this week , where he praised efforts to combat the deadly AIDS virus , and pledged his foundation would donate drugs and offer training to doctors .",B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD NNP RBR DT NN , WRB PRP VBD NNS TO VB DT JJ NNP NN , CC VBD PRP$ NN MD VB NNS CC NN NN TO NNS ."
"During visits to China as president , Mr. Clinton reiterated the U.S. policy of recognizing Beijing as China 's sole government .",O O O B-geo O O O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O,"IN NNS TO NNP IN NN , NNP NNP VBD DT NNP NN IN VBG NNP IN NNP POS JJ NN ."
