"Texas Governor Perry says thousands of refugees now sheltering in New Orleans ' Superdome arena will be moved to Houston 's Astrodome , some 500 kilometers west .",B-org B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNS IN NNS RB VBG IN NNP NNP POS JJ NN MD VB VBN TO NNP POS NN , DT CD NNS RB ."
"Some 23,000 people took shelter at the Superdome to escape the hurricane and rushing floodwaters .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT CD NNS VBD NN IN DT NN TO VB DT NN CC VBG NNS .
Refugees have complained about worsening sanitary conditions there .,O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP VBN IN VBG JJ NNS RB .
Governor Perry told reporters his state will to do whatever it can to help victims of Hurricane Katrina .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD NNS PRP$ NN MD TO VB WDT PRP MD TO VB NNS IN NNP NNP .
The governor said the children being temporarily housed in Texas will be able to enroll in local public schools .,O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD DT NNS VBG RB VBN IN NNP MD VB JJ TO VB IN JJ JJ NNS .
"He says he also spoke with Florida Governor Jeb Bush , about coordinating relief efforts .",O O O O O O B-geo B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O,"PRP VBZ PRP RB VBD IN NNP NNP NNP NNP , IN VBG NN NNS ."
Houston 's Astrodome - an engineering marvel when it first opened in 1965 - is used for events like concerts but has not been used for a sporting event in years .,B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NNP IN DT NN NN WRB PRP RB VBD IN CD : VBZ VBN IN NNS IN NNS CC VBZ RB VBN VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NNS .
Officials say it can house refugees at least through the end of December .,O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,NNS VBP PRP MD VB NNS IN JJS IN DT NN IN NNP .
