Russia 's foreign minister says President Vladimir Putin has accepted an invitation to attend the upcoming NATO summit in Bucharest .,B-geo O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-geo O,NNP POS JJ NN VBZ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN TO VB DT JJ NNP NN IN NNP .
Sergei Lavrov said Tuesday that Mr. Putin will take part in the April meeting .,B-per I-per O B-tim O B-per B-org O O O O O B-tim O O,NNP NNP VBD NNP IN NNP NNP MD VB NN IN DT NNP NN .
The alliance last month invited Mr. Putin to join its leaders at the summit for a session of the NATO-Russia Council .,O O O O O B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,DT NN JJ NN VBD NNP NNP TO VB PRP$ NNS IN DT NN IN DT NN IN DT NNP NNP .
"The meetings will take place shortly before Mr. Putin is to step down as Russia 's president in May , after serving the maximum two consecutive terms permitted by the country 's constitution .",O O O O O O O B-per B-org O O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS MD VB NN RB IN NNP NNP VBZ TO VB RP IN NNP POS NN IN NNP , IN VBG DT NN CD JJ NNS VBN IN DT NN POS NN ."
Russia has expressed strong opposition to plans by Ukraine and Georgia to seek NATO membership .,B-geo O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-org O O,NNP VBZ VBN JJ NN TO NNS IN NNP CC NNP TO VB NNP NN .
"Alliance leaders and Mr. Putin created the NATO-Russia Council in 2002 as an organ for consultation , joint decisionmaking and joint action in such areas as crisis management , efforts to deal with terrorism and non-proliferation .",O O O B-per B-org O O B-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNS CC NNP NNP VBD DT NNP NNP IN CD IN DT NN IN NN , JJ NN CC JJ NN IN JJ NNS IN NN NN , NNS TO VB IN NN CC NN ."
