The U.S. motorcycle company Harley-Davidson opened its first authorized Chinese dealership Saturday in Beijing .,O B-geo O O B-per O O O O B-gpe O B-tim O B-geo O,DT NNP NN NN NNP VBD PRP$ JJ JJ JJ NN NNP IN NNP .
Company officials say they expect the motorcycle 's entry into the Chinese market to be a gradual one .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,NN NNS VBP PRP VBP DT NN POS NN IN DT JJ NN TO VB DT JJ CD .
Many Chinese cities have restrictions on where motorcycles can be ridden .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,JJ JJ NNS VBP NNS IN WRB NNS MD VB VBN .
The company says it hopes to address the riding restrictions over time .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ PRP VBZ TO VB DT NN NNS IN NN .
"Harley Davidson officials say that while China 's economy is booming , they also realize their motorcycles may be too expensive in a country where disposable income is limited .",B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNS VBP IN IN NNP POS NN VBZ JJ , PRP RB VBP PRP$ NNS MD VB RB JJ IN DT NN WRB JJ NN VBZ VBN ."
Harley Davidson is based in the midwestern U.S. state of Wisconsin and has been making motorcycles for more than 100 years .,B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NNP NN IN NNP CC VBZ VBN VBG NNS IN JJR IN CD NNS .
They are the only major U.S. motorcycle manufacturer .,O O O O O B-geo O O O,PRP VBP DT RB JJ NNP NN NN .
"They specialize in large , heavyweight bikes , often known as "" hogs . """,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBP IN JJ , JJ NNS , RB VBN IN RQU NNS . LQU"
