Hundreds of Uzbek refugees have left Kyrgyzstan for Romania more than two months after fleeing a deadly government crackdown in their Central Asian nation .,O O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN JJ NNS VBP VBN NNP IN NNP JJR IN CD NNS IN VBG DT JJ NN NN IN PRP$ JJ JJ NN .
"A U.N. Refugee Agency official says 440 refugees boarded a plane early Friday and flew to the Romanian capital , Bucharest .",O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-gpe O O B-org O,"DT NNP NNP NNP NN VBZ CD NNS VBD DT NN JJ NNP CC VBD TO DT JJ NN , NNP ."
Among them were 14 of 29 refugees that were being held for extradition to Uzbekistan for alleged crimes .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,IN PRP VBD CD IN CD NNS WDT VBD VBG VBN IN NN TO NNP IN JJ NNS .
The U.N. agency is trying to secure the release of the other 15 refugees pending court rulings on their extradition .,O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBZ VBG TO VB DT NN IN DT JJ CD NNS VBG NN NNS IN PRP$ NN .
U.N. officials say the refugees on today 's flight to Romania will be placed in a camp until they can be resettled in other countries .,B-org O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBP DT NNS IN NN POS NN TO NNP MD VB VBN IN DT NN IN PRP MD VB VBN IN JJ NNS .
Hundreds of Uzbeks took refuge in Kyrgyzstan after a May 13 uprising in the city of Andijan was violently put down by security forces .,O O B-gpe O O O B-geo O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNS VBD NN IN NNP IN DT NNP CD NN IN DT NN IN NNP VBD RB VBN RP IN NN NNS .
Uzbekistan says all the refugees are criminals who should be repatriated .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ PDT DT NNS VBP NNS WP MD VB VBN .
