"A U.N. conference on climate change has entered its final day , with a deal on long-term efforts to cut carbon emissions still elusive .",O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NN IN NN NN VBZ VBN PRP$ JJ NN , IN DT NN IN JJ NNS TO VB NN NNS RB VBP ."
"Former U.S. President Bill Clinton is scheduled to speak to the meeting in Montreal , Canada , later Friday , highlighting the outsider status of the United States at the conference .",O B-org B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB TO DT NN IN NNP , NNP , RB NNP , VBG DT NN NN IN DT NNP NNPS IN DT NN ."
"During his presidency , Mr. Clinton endorsed the Kyoto Protocol on reducing what are called greenhouse , or heat trapping , gas emissions in the atmosphere .",O O O O B-per I-per O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN PRP$ NN , NNP NNP VBD DT NNP NNP IN VBG WP VBP VBN NN , CC NN NN , NN NNS IN DT NN ."
The Bush administration rejects the protocol as too costly and says it unfairly exempts developing nations such as China and India .,O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,DT NNP NN VBZ DT NN IN RB JJ CC VBZ PRP RB VBZ VBG NNS JJ IN NNP CC NNP .
Mr. Clinton will appear in a private capacity .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O,NNP NNP MD VB IN DT JJ NN .
"Despite the U.S. position , delegates say ministers from more than 90 nations are close to agreeing on a negotiating plan to extend the Kyoto accord beyond 2012 , when it is set to expire .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-tim O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NNP NN , NNS VBP NNS IN JJR IN CD NNS VBP JJ TO VBG IN DT VBG NN TO VB DT NNP NN IN CD , WRB PRP VBZ VBN TO VB ."
