The conquest of Vietnam by France began in 1858 and was completed by 1884 .,O O O B-geo O B-geo O O B-tim O O O O B-tim O,DT NN IN NNP IN NNP VBD IN CD CC VBD VBN IN CD .
It became part of French Indochina in 1887 .,O O O O B-gpe B-geo O B-tim O,PRP VBD NN IN JJ NNP IN CD .
"Vietnam declared independence after World War II , but France continued to rule until its 1954 defeat by Communist forces under Ho Chi MINH .",B-geo O O O O O B-eve O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O,"NNP VBD NN IN NNP NNP NNP , CC NNP VBD TO VB IN PRP$ CD NN IN JJ NNS IN NNP NNP NNP ."
"Under the Geneva Accords of 1954 , Vietnam was divided into the Communist North and anti-Communist South .",O O B-org I-org O B-tim O B-geo O O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O,"IN DT NNP NNP IN CD , NNP VBD VBN IN DT NNP NNP CC JJ NNP ."
"US economic and military aid to South Vietnam grew through the 1960s in an attempt to bolster the government , but US armed forces were withdrawn following a cease-fire agreement in 1973 .",B-geo O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"NNP JJ CC JJ NN TO NNP NNP VBD IN DT NNS IN DT NN TO VB DT NN , CC NNP JJ NNS VBD VBN VBG DT NN NN IN CD ."
"Two years later , North Vietnamese forces overran the South reuniting the country under Communist rule .",B-tim O B-tim O B-org B-gpe O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"CD NNS RB , NNP JJ NNS VBP DT NNP VBG DT NN IN JJ NN ."
"Despite the return of peace , for over a decade the country experienced little economic growth because of conservative leadership policies , the persecution and mass exodus of individuals - many of them successful South Vietnamese merchants - and growing international isolation .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN IN NN , IN IN DT NN DT NN VBD JJ JJ NN IN IN JJ NN NNS , DT NN CC NN NN IN NNS IN NN IN PRP JJ NNP JJ NNS : CC VBG JJ NN ."
"However , since the enactment of Vietnam 's "" doi moi "" ( renovation ) policy in 1986 , Vietnamese authorities have committed to increased economic liberalization and enacted structural reforms needed to modernize the economy and to produce more competitive , export-driven industries .",O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , IN DT NN IN NNP POS RQU FW FW LQU LRB NN RRB NN IN CD , JJ NNS VBP VBN TO VBN JJ NN CC VBN JJ NNS VBN TO VB DT NN CC TO VB RBR JJ , JJ NNS ."
"The Communist leaders , however , maintain control on political expression and have resisted outside calls to improve human rights .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNS , RB , VBP NN IN JJ NN CC VBP VBN JJ NNS TO VB JJ NNS ."
"The country continues to experience small-scale protests from various groups , the vast majority connected to land-use issues , calls for increased political space and the lack of equitable mechanisms for resolving disputes .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ TO VB JJ NNS IN JJ NNS , DT JJ NN VBN TO JJ NNS , NNS IN JJ JJ NN CC DT NN IN JJ NNS IN VBG NNS ."
"Various ethnic minorities , such as the Montagnards of the Central Highlands and the Khmer Krom in the southern delta region , have also held protests .",O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ JJ NNS , JJ IN DT NNS IN DT NNP NNPS CC DT NNP NNP IN DT JJ NN NN , VBP RB VBN NNS ."
