Japan has urged China not to escalate a conflict over natural gas exploration in a disputed area of the East China Sea .,B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O,NNP VBZ VBN NNP RB TO VB DT NN IN JJ NN NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP .
Japan announced Wednesday it will begin reviewing applications for exploring for deep sea natural gas fields in the area .,B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD NNP PRP MD VB VBG NNS IN VBG IN JJ NN JJ NN NNS IN DT NN .
"Beijing , which also claims exploration rights , called the move a provocation .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP , WDT RB VBZ NN NNS , VBD DT NN DT NN ."
"Japanese Prime Minister Junichiro Koizumi said Thursday , China should not overreact to a project that could benefit both countries .",B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP , NNP MD RB VB TO DT NN WDT MD VB DT NNS ."
Tokyo 's relations with China were already at a low over a new Japanese history textbook that critics say glosses over Japan 's wartime occupation of China and other nations .,B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O,NNP POS NNS IN NNP VBD RB IN DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NN NN IN NNS VBP NNS IN NNP POS JJ NN IN NNP CC JJ NNS .
Several Japanese government agencies reported cyber attacks on their web sites Thursday .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,JJ JJ NN NNS VBD NN NNS IN PRP$ NN NNS NNP .
"Earlier this week there were violent protests in China against Japan , and a Chinese consulate in Japan , has also received threats .",O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O,"RBR DT NN EX VBD JJ NNS IN NNP IN NNP , CC DT JJ NN IN NNP , VBZ RB VBN NNS ."
