Thousands of Pakistani lawyers protested again Thursday against President Pervez Musharraf 's suspension of the country 's chief justice .,O O B-gpe O O O B-tim O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN JJ NNS VBD RB NNP IN NNP NNP NNP POS NN IN DT NN POS NN NN .
"Lawyers , opposition workers and rights activists marched through Lahore chanting slogans against General Musharraf .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-org I-org O,"NNS , NN NNS CC NNS NNS VBD IN NNP VBG NNS IN NNP NNP ."
Smaller protests were reported in several other cities .,O O O O O O O O O,JJR NNS VBD VBN IN JJ JJ NNS .
The president suspended Chief Justice Iftikhar Mohammed Chaudhry on March 9 for allegedly abusing his office .,O O O O B-org I-org B-per I-per O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O,DT NN VBD NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP IN NNP CD IN RB VBG PRP$ NN .
Chaudhry 's removal has triggered many protests and sparked outrage among Pakistan 's judiciary and opposition parties .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,NNP POS NN VBZ VBN JJ NNS CC VBD NN IN NNP POS NN CC NN NNS .
"On May 12 , 40 people were killed in street clashes between pro-government activists and opposition workers in the southern city of Karachi .",O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"IN NNP CD , CD NNS VBD VBN IN NN NNS IN JJ NNS CC NN NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
Critics of President Musharraf say he suspended the chief justice as part of efforts to ensure re-election by the current parliament .,O O B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNP NNP VBP PRP VBD DT NN NN IN NN IN NNS TO VB NN IN DT JJ NN .
Mr. Musharraf says he acted in accordance with judicial rules and his opponents have politicized the case .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBD IN NN IN JJ NNS CC PRP$ NNS VBP VBN DT NN .
