U.S. officials have eased immigration rules for some Cubans seeking to leave the island to join family members who are U.S. residents .,B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,NNP NNS VBP VBN NN NNS IN DT NNS VBG TO VB DT NN TO VB NN NNS WP VBP NNP NNS .
The Department of Homeland Security says the new rules announced Friday are intended to increase chances for the reunification of families .,B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP IN NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ NNS VBN NNP VBP VBN TO VB NNS IN DT NN IN NNS .
"Officials say the changes allow U.S. residents to seek expedited visas for family members in Cuba , and will help relieve a backlog in immigration requests .",O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP DT NNS VBP NNP NNS TO VB VBN NNS IN NN NNS IN NNP , CC MD VB VB DT NN IN NN NNS ."
They say 7500 so-called family visas will be available .,O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBP CD JJ NN NNS MD VB JJ .
"Washington issues a total of about 20,000 visas to Cubans each year .",B-geo O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O,NNP VBZ DT NN IN IN CD NNS TO NNS DT NN .
Cuba 's government must grant exit visas for people seeking to leave the island .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NN MD VB NN NNS IN NNS VBG TO VB DT NN .
U.S. officials also said they are seeking to increase the punishments for human smugglers using maritime routes .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS RB VBD PRP VBP VBG TO VB DT NNS IN JJ NNS VBG JJ NNS .
Bush administration officials have repeatedly called on Cubans in recent weeks to avoid making illegal boat crossings to the United States .,B-per O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP NN NNS VBP RB VBN IN NNS IN JJ NNS TO VB VBG JJ NN NNS TO DT NNP NNPS .
