Reports from Rangoon say the military government of Burma quietly sentenced a Buddhist monk to seven years in prison during the visit this week of a United Nations human rights envoy .,O O B-org O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O,NNS IN NNP VBP DT JJ NN IN NNP RB VBD DT NN NN TO CD NNS IN NN IN DT NN DT NN IN DT NNP NNP JJ NNS NN .
A lawyer said Saturday that U Gaw Thita was arrested last August as he returned from a trip to Taiwan .,O O O B-tim O B-org I-org I-org O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NN VBD NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBD VBN JJ NNP IN PRP VBD IN DT NN TO NNP .
He was convicted at Burma 's notorious Insein Prison Wednesday on three charges including unlawful association .,O O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org B-tim O O O O O O O,PRP VBD VBN IN NNP POS JJ NNP NNP NNP IN CD NNS VBG JJ NN .
The lawyer said the monk was also convicted of failing to declare possession of foreign currency and for violation of immigration laws for taking the trip .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD DT NN VBD RB VBN IN VBG TO VB NN IN JJ NN CC IN NN IN NN NNS IN VBG DT NN .
