"U.S. Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice has emphasized the United States ' support for a nuclear deal with India , in a phone call Monday with Foreign Minister Pranab Mukherjee Monday .",B-org O O B-org B-per I-per O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O O B-per I-per I-per B-tim O,"NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NNP NNPS POS NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , IN DT NN NN NNP IN NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
The agreement would allow India to buy nuclear fuel and technology from the United States .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT NN MD VB NNP TO VB JJ NN CC NN IN DT NNP NNPS .
It has been stalled by debate among Indian lawmakers .,O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,PRP VBZ VBN VBN IN NN IN JJ NNS .
India 's communist politicians are threatening to pull out of the ruling coalition if the deal goes through .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS JJ NNS VBP VBG TO VB IN IN DT NN NN IN DT NN VBZ IN .
They argue that the deal will undermine India 's independent foreign policy and nuclear weapons program .,O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBP IN DT NN MD VB NNP POS JJ JJ NN CC JJ NNS NN .
"The U.S. suspended nuclear trade with New Delhi in 1974 , when India conducted a nuclear test without signing a nuclear nonproliferation treaty .",O B-geo O O O O B-org I-org O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP VBD JJ NN IN NNP NNP IN CD , WRB NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN VBG DT JJ NN NN ."
