Bolivia 's Finance Minister has resigned over comments he is said to have made in the United States about alleged financial ties between Bolivia 's opposition and the leaders of Cuba and Venezuela .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,NNP POS NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NNS PRP VBZ VBN TO VB VBN IN DT NNP NNPS IN JJ JJ NNS IN NNP POS NN CC DT NNS IN NNP CC NNP .
"In a communiqué read by Luis Carlos Jemio on Monday , he said his comments were taken out of context by some media .",O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN VBN IN NNP NNP NNP IN NNP , PRP VBD PRP$ NNS VBD VBN IN IN NN IN DT NNS ."
He specifically named the Associated Press .,O O O O B-org I-org O,PRP RB VBD DT NNP NNP .
But he added that VOA reported his comments correctly .,O O O O B-org O O O O O,CC PRP VBD IN NNP VBD PRP$ NNS RB .
"During a conference Friday at the Center for Strategic and International Studies in Washington , Mr. Jemio said he had heard about alleged financial links between Bolivian opposition leader Evo Morales and Presidents Fidel Castro of Cuba and Hugo Chavez of Venezuela - but that they were no more than speculation .",O O O B-tim O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-geo O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O B-per I-per O B-gpe O B-per I-per O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN NNP IN DT NNP IN NNP CC NNP NNP IN NNP , NNP NNP VBD PRP VBD VBN IN JJ JJ NNS IN JJ NN NN NNP NNP CC NNS NNP NNP IN NNP CC NNP NNP IN NNP : CC IN PRP VBD DT JJR IN NN ."
The Associated Press reported him as affirming there are links .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBD PRP IN VBG EX VBP NNS .
Mr. Jemio says he has asked the Associated Press for a retraction .,B-per I-per O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O,NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ VBN DT NNP NNP IN DT NN .
