U.N. Secretary-General Kofi Annan has arrived in the Middle East for talks on advancing the region 's peace process .,B-org O B-per I-per O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN DT NNP NNP IN NNS IN VBG DT NN POS NN NN .
"Mr. Annan met with Israeli Prime Minister Ariel Sharon in Jerusalem Sunday , and plans to travel to the West Bank town of Ramallah on Monday to meet with Palestinian President Mahmud Abbas .",B-per I-per O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-org I-org O B-tim O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O,"NNP NNP VBD IN JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP IN NNP NNP , CC VBZ TO VB TO DT NNP NNP NN IN NNP IN NNP TO VB IN JJ NNP NNP NNP ."
"World leaders have expressed hope for the peace process since last month 's Mideast summit , where Mr. Sharon and Mr. Abbas declared an end to four years of violence .",O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-per I-per O B-per I-per O O O O B-tim O B-tim I-tim O,"NNP NNS VBP VBN NN IN DT NN NN IN JJ NN POS JJ NN , WRB NNP NNP CC NNP NNP VBD DT NN TO CD NNS IN NN ."
The process hit a snag this week when talks on Israel handing over security control in several West Bank cities ended without agreement .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O,DT NN VBD DT NN DT NN WRB NNS IN NNP VBG IN NN NN IN JJ NNP NNP NNS VBD IN NN .
"Meanwhile , the Israeli government says it will dismantle 24 illegal West Bank settler outposts built since Mr. Sharon came to power in March 2001 .",O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"RB , DT JJ NN VBZ PRP MD VB CD JJ NNP NNP NN VBZ VBN IN NNP NNP VBD TO NN IN NNP CD ."
