"Iraqi police say at least 11 people have been killed by gunfire after a roadside bombing near Sadr City , a Shi'ite militia stronghold in Baghdad .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-org O O O B-geo O,"JJ NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBP VBN VBN IN NN IN DT NN VBG IN NNP NNP , DT NNP NN NN IN NNP ."
Local officials say the gunfire erupted Wednesday after roadside bombs exploded near a joint U.S.-Iraqi patrol in the Obeidi neighborhood .,O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,JJ NNS VBP DT NN VBD NNP IN NN NNS VBD IN DT JJ JJ NN IN DT NNP NN .
"The U.S. military , however , says none of its troops were involved .",O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NN , RB , VBZ NN IN PRP$ NNS VBD VBN ."
"Sadr City itself remained calm , a day after some 10,000 Iraqi troops began an operation aimed at bringing government control over the Shi'ite stronghold .",B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O,"NNP NNP PRP VBD JJ , DT NN IN DT CD JJ NNS VBD DT NN VBN IN VBG NN NN IN DT NNP NN ."
"Fighting in Sadr City has killed hundreds of people since late March , when Iraqi Prime Minister Nouri al-Maliki ordered a crackdown on Shi'ite militias .",O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-tim O B-tim O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O B-org O O,"VBG IN NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNS IN NNS IN JJ NNP , WRB JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN NNP NNS ."
