"The World Anti-Doping Agency , WADA , has praised China 's drug testing programs for the Beijing Olympics , but has asked organizers to increase efforts to intercept banned substances .",O B-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP NNP , NNP , VBZ VBN NNP POS NN NN NNS IN DT NNP NNPS , CC VBZ VBN NNS TO VB NNS TO VB VBN NNS ."
"At a meeting in Sydney , Australia , Wednesday , WADA president John Fahey endorsed Beijing 's anti-doping efforts after visiting a state-of-the art laboratory there this month .",O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-tim O B-org O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,"IN DT NN IN NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP NN NNP NNP VBD NNP POS JJ NNS IN VBG DT JJ NN NN RB DT NN ."
"He said testing would be more stringent than ever in Beijing , with numerous "" chaperones "" to ensure athletes submitted genuine blood and urine samples .",O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD NN MD VB RBR JJ IN RB IN NNP , IN JJ RQU NNS RQU TO VB NNS VBN JJ NN CC NN NNS ."
But Fahey also asked Chinese authorities to increase customs and immigration checks to prevent performance-enhancing drugs from reaching the Olympics .,O B-per O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,CC NNP RB VBD JJ NNS TO VB NNS CC NN NNS TO VB JJ NNS IN VBG DT NNPS .
WADA has announced the Beijing labs will be able to implement advanced tests for human growth hormone HGH before and during the Games from August 8-24 .,B-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,NNP VBZ VBN DT NNP NNS MD VB JJ TO VB JJ NNS IN JJ NN NN NNP IN CC IN DT NNPS IN NNP CD .
"Fahey believes advanced testing in China will bring a "" much more effective outcome in dealing with anyone who seeks to cheat . """,B-per O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ JJ NN IN NNP MD VB DT LQU RB RBR JJ NN IN VBG IN DT WP VBZ TO VB . LQU
