"The world 's second-largest food and beverage company says it will reduce the saturated fat , sodium , and sugar in its products to make them more nutritious .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN POS JJ NN CC NN NN VBZ PRP MD VB DT JJ NN , NN , CC NN IN PRP$ NNS TO VB PRP RBR JJ ."
"Pepsi says it will cut up to one-quarter of the unhealthy ingredients by 2020 , and improve labels to give consumers clearer information on what they are eating .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ PRP MD VB RP TO NN IN DT JJ NNS IN CD , CC VB NNS TO VB NNS JJR NN IN WP PRP VBP VBG ."
"Several other major processed food manufacturers – Kraft , ConAgra , and Campbell Soup – have also announced cuts in sodium .",O O O O O O O B-org O B-org O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O,"JJ JJ JJ JJ NN NNS ; NNP , NNP , CC NNP NNP ; VBP RB VBN NNS IN NN ."
Last week Pepsi said it would continue a program to take its high-calorie soft-drinks out of schools and replace them with less-fattening alternatives .,O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN NNP VBD PRP MD VB DT NN TO VB PRP$ JJ NNS IN IN NNS CC VB PRP IN JJ NNS .
The action by various companies comes as First Lady Michelle Obama has been campaigning for healthier foods and more physical activities in schools to fight childhood obesity .,O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN JJ NNS VBZ IN JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN VBG IN JJR NNS CC JJR JJ NNS IN NNS TO VB NN NN .
