Egyptian police have clashed with dozens of protesters criticizing President Hosni Mubarak 's bid to extend his 24-year rule .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN IN NNS IN NNS VBG NNP NNP NNP POS NN TO VB PRP$ JJ NN .
"Protest organizers say plainclothes officers Saturday attacked and arrested protesters , including leaders of the Kefaya opposition group .",O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,"NNP NNS VBP NNS NNS NNP VBD CC VBN NNS , VBG NNS IN DT NNP NN NN ."
Some of them were later released .,O O O O O O O,DT IN PRP VBD RB VBN .
Critics of the government called the protest two days after Mr. Mubarak announced plans to compete for a fifth term in September voting .,O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,NNS IN DT NN VBD DT NN CD NNS IN NNP NNP VBD NNS TO VB IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NN .
"It will be the first time he has faced challengers for the post , and it comes after the government approved electoral reforms .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP MD VB DT JJ NN PRP VBZ VBN NNS IN DT NN , CC PRP VBZ IN DT NN VBD JJ NNS ."
Opposition leaders say Saturday 's violence was similar to clashes between police and protesters during a May referendum .,O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,NN NNS VBP NNP POS NN VBD JJ TO NNS IN NNS CC NNS IN DT NNP NN .
"Last month , U.S. Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice visited Egypt and urged the government not to interfere with peaceful protests .",O O O B-org O O B-org B-per I-per O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN , NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP CC VBD DT NN RB TO VB IN JJ NNS ."
