Russian and Iranian officials have met in Moscow for talks on a compromise deal allowing Iran to conduct uranium enrichment on Russian soil .,B-gpe O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O,JJ CC JJ NNS VBP VBN IN NNP IN NNS IN DT NN NN VBG NNP TO VB NN NN IN JJ NN .
"A Russian official was quoted by the Itar-Tass news agency as saying no breakthrough was made in the talks , which were aimed at resolving a dispute with the West over Iran 's nuclear activities .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN NN IN VBG DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NNS , WDT VBD VBN IN VBG DT NN IN DT NNP IN NNP POS JJ NNS ."
"In a joint statement , officials said discussions would continue at a future date .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN , NNS VBD NNS MD VB IN DT JJ NN ."
Iran has said it agrees to the Russian deal in principle .,B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN PRP VBZ TO DT JJ NN IN NN .
"But Iran 's top negotiator , Ali Larijani , told reporters in Moscow Wednesday that his country has a sovereign right to enrich uranium for its nuclear reactors .",O B-geo O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"CC NNP POS JJ NN , NNP NNP , VBD NNS IN NNP NNP IN PRP$ NN VBZ DT JJ NN TO VB NN IN PRP$ JJ NNS ."
"In Washington , a State Department spokesman Adam Ereli criticized the comments , saying it signaled a move in the wrong direction .",O B-geo O O B-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , DT NNP NNP NN NNP NNP VBD DT NNS , VBG PRP VBD DT NN IN DT JJ NN ."
