"Burma 's military government has begun a crackdown on the country 's illegal car trade , ordering the owners of an estimated 30,000 unregistered vehicles to relinquish their automobiles to police stations .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ NN VBZ VBN DT NN IN DT NN POS JJ NN NN , VBG DT NNS IN DT VBN CD JJ NNS TO VB PRP$ NNS TO NN NNS ."
"A police official , Director-General Khin Yee , says people who do so will avoid legal action and interrogation .",O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN NN , JJ NNP NNP , VBZ NNS WP VBP RB MD VB JJ NN CC NN ."
News reports say the crackdown could be part of Rangoon 's power struggle against former allies of ousted Prime Minister General Khin Nyunt .,O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per I-per O,NNP NNS VBP DT NN MD VB NN IN NNP POS NN NN IN JJ NNS IN JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP .
"He allegedly controlled operations that brought luxury cars from China and Thailand into Burma , where they were sold at a small percentage of their regular cost .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP RB VBD NNS WDT VBD NN NNS IN NNP CC NNP IN NNP , WRB PRP VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN IN PRP$ JJ NN ."
Some owners of illegal cars are reportedly dismantling their vehicles so they can sell spare parts .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS IN JJ NNS VBP RB VBG PRP$ NNS IN PRP MD VB JJ NNS .
