"Riot police in the Nepalese capital , Kathmandu , have used batons and tear gas to disperse thousands of demonstrators protesting King Gyanendra 's direct rule in the Himalayan kingdom .",O O O O B-gpe O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O,"NN NN IN DT JJ NN , NNP , VBP VBN NNS CC JJ NN TO VB NNS IN NNS VBG NNP NNP POS JJ NN IN DT NNP NN ."
"Several political leaders , including former Prime Minister Girija Prasad Koirala , and scores of other activists were detained during Sunday 's rally .",O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,"JJ JJ NNS , VBG JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP , CC NNS IN JJ NNS VBD VBN IN NNP POS NN ."
The protesters shouted pro-democracy slogans as they marched through the city 's center .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBD JJ NNS IN PRP VBD IN DT NN POS NN .
Several demonstrators were injured in clashes with police .,O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBD VBN IN NNS IN NN .
"The rally , organized by seven main political parties , came a day after Maoist rebels announced a three-month unilateral truce in a bid to win their support .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN , VBN IN CD JJ JJ NNS , VBD DT NN IN NNP NNS VBD DT JJ JJ NN IN DT NN TO VB PRP$ NN ."
"The Nepali Congress , the country 's largest political party , has welcomed the Maoist move .",O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP , DT NN POS JJS JJ NN , VBZ VBN DT NNP NN ."
Party officials express hope it will lead to permanent peace .,O O O O O O O O O O O,NN NNS VBP NN PRP MD VB TO JJ NN .
