"Turkey says it is ready to sign a key EU customs agreement , but will also issue a declaration making clear the accord does not imply its official recognition of the Greek Cypriot government .",B-org O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe I-gpe O O,"NNP VBZ PRP VBZ JJ TO VB DT JJ NNP NNS NN , CC MD RB VB DT NN VBG JJ DT NN VBZ RB VB PRP$ JJ NN IN DT JJ JJ NN ."
"Turkish Prime Minister Tayyip Erdogan , in London for talks with British Prime Minister Tony Blair , said Wednesday Ankara would sign the EU protocol soon .",B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O O B-tim I-tim O O O B-org O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP , IN NNP IN NNS IN JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP , VBD NNP NNP MD VB DT NNP NN RB ."
The accord extends Turkey 's custom union with the EU to its 10 new members - including Cyprus .,O O O B-org O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O B-org O,DT NN VBZ NNP POS NN NN IN DT NNP TO PRP$ CD JJ NNS : VBG NNP .
"The agreement has been a key stumbling block for opening Turkey 's membership talks with Brussels , as Ankara only recognizes the Turkish enclave in northern Cyprus .",O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-org O,"DT NN VBZ VBN DT JJ NN NN IN VBG NNP POS NN NNS IN NNP , IN NNP RB VBZ DT JJ NN IN JJ NNP ."
"Mr. Blair , whose country holds the rotating EU presidency , said it was important to restate that the agreement does not in any way legally involve Turkish recognition of Cyprus .",B-per I-per O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-org O,"NNP NNP , WP$ NN VBZ DT VBG NNP NN , VBD PRP VBD JJ TO VB IN DT NN VBZ RB IN DT NN RB VBP JJ NN IN NNP ."
Ankara is due to start entry talks with EU officials in October .,B-geo O O O O O O O B-org O O B-tim O,NNP VBZ JJ TO VB NN NNS IN NNP NNS IN NNP .
