Eyewitnesses and medical officials say an Israeli military strike killed two Palestinians and wounded at least seven people Wednesday in the Gaza Strip .,O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim O O B-geo I-geo O,NNS CC JJ NNS VBP DT JJ JJ NN VBD CD NNS CC VBD IN JJS CD NNS NNP IN DT NNP NNP .
The Islamic Jihad says one of the two killed was a member of the militant group .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ CD IN DT CD VBN VBD DT NN IN DT JJ NN .
At least one child was among those injured .,O O O O O O O O O,IN JJS CD NN VBD IN DT VBN .
The Israeli military said its forces opened fire on a group of suspected militants who approached a border fence in northern Gaza .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT JJ NN VBD PRP$ NNS VBD NN IN DT NN IN JJ NNS WP VBD DT NN NN IN JJ NNP .
The military said the soldiers were responding to reports that a rocket launching cell had been spotted in the area .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD DT NNS VBD VBG TO NNS IN DT NN NN NN VBD VBN VBN IN DT NN .
"In April , Israel warned it would increase the use of military force against militants in Gaza unless Palestinians stopped firing rockets across the border .",O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-gpe O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , NNP VBD PRP MD VB DT NN IN JJ NN IN NNS IN NNP IN NNS VBD VBG NNS IN DT NN ."
Deputy Prime Minister Silvan Shalom announced the warning during a radio interview after Israeli warplanes launched a series of strikes against targets in Hamas-ruled Gaza .,O B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN DT NN NN IN JJ NNS VBD DT NN IN NNS IN NNS IN JJ NNP .
