Thousands of protesting students blocked the center of Rome on Tuesday as part of nationwide demonstrations against proposed budget cuts in the university system .,O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN VBG NNS VBD DT NN IN NNP IN NNP IN NN IN JJ NNS IN JJ NN NNS IN DT NN NN .
"Some 50,000 students were stopped by a wall of police vans and lines of officers in riot gear from reaching the nation 's parliament where lawmakers are voting on a controversial university reform bill .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT CD NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN IN NN NNS CC NNS IN NNS IN NN NN IN VBG DT NN POS NN WRB NNS VBP VBG IN DT JJ NN NN NN .
The Italian Students Union says hundreds of thousands of students around the country were rallying against the bill .,O B-gpe B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNP NNP VBZ NNS IN NNS IN NNS IN DT NN VBD VBG IN DT NN .
"Protestors disrupted traffic in central Rome , as well as Milan , Turin , Naples , Venice , Palermo and Bari .",O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O,"NNS VBD NN IN JJ NNP , RB RB IN NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP CC NNP ."
Brief scuffles erupted between students and riot police in the capital .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN IN NNS CC NN NNS IN DT NN .
The protests are the latest in a wave of demonstrations against austerity measures being introduced by governments across Europe .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNS VBP DT JJS IN DT NN IN NNS IN NN NNS VBG VBN IN NNS IN NNP .
