"European observers said Monday that Sudan 's April election was marred by several problems , but still marked a step forward .",O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBD NNP IN NNP POS NNP NN VBD VBN IN JJ NNS , CC RB VBD DT NN RB ."
"The observer team 's final report on the election said flawed vote counting , lack of transparency in announcing the winner and instances of violence challenged the credibility of the April election .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"DT NN NN POS JJ NN IN DT NN VBD JJ NN NN , NN IN NN IN VBG DT NN CC NNS IN NN VBD DT NN IN DT NNP NN ."
The report said Sudanese officials declared the country 's President Omar Hassan al-Bashir the winner before 50 percent of the votes were counted .,O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD JJ NNS VBD DT NN POS NNP NNP NNP NNP DT NN IN CD NN IN DT NNS VBD VBN .
Mr. Bashir is the only sitting head of state wanted for war crimes by the International Criminal Court .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,NNP NNP VBZ DT RB VBG NN IN NN VBN IN NN NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP .
He denies the charges and rejects the court 's authority .,O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ DT NNS CC VBZ DT NN POS NN .
The report was based on information from 147 observers deployed across the African country in April .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-tim O,DT NN VBD VBN IN NN IN CD NNS VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
