Spanish cyclist Alberto Contador is set to ride into Paris Sunday as the winner of this year 's Tour de France .,B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,JJ NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB IN NNP NNP IN DT NN IN DT NN POS NNP NNP NNP .
Contador extended his overall race lead to 39 seconds after Saturday 's second-to-last stage .,B-per O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O,NNP VBD PRP$ JJ NN NN TO CD NNS IN NNP POS JJ NN .
"The final day of the race is traditionally a ceremonial ride , meaning the leader after 19 stages is virtually assured to win the overall title .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN IN DT NN VBZ RB DT JJ NN , VBG DT NN IN CD NNS VBZ RB VBN TO VB DT JJ NN ."
"Swiss rider Fabian Cancellara won Saturday 's 52-kilometer sprint leg , edging out Tony Martin of Germany by 17 seconds .",B-gpe O B-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O B-per I-per O B-geo O B-tim O O,"JJ NN NNP NNP VBD NNP POS JJ NN NN , VBG RP NNP NNP IN NNP IN CD NNS ."
Contador is set to capture his third Tour de France title in four years .,B-per O O O O O O B-eve I-eve I-eve O O B-tim O O,NNP VBZ VBN TO VB PRP$ JJ NNP NNP NNP NN IN CD NNS .
"Barring any crashes , Luxembourg 's Andy Schleck is poised to finish in second place for the second-straight year .",O O O O B-geo O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"VBG DT NNS , NNP POS NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB IN JJ NN IN DT JJ NN ."
Contador 's winning margin is set to be one of the smallest in the Tour 's history .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O,NNP POS VBG NN VBZ VBN TO VB CD IN DT JJS IN DT NNP POS NN .
