Yemeni officials say clashes between Shi'ite rebels and pro-government tribes in north Yemen have killed at least 34 people in the past three days .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O,JJ NNS VBP NNS IN NNP NNS CC JJ NNS IN JJ NNP VBP VBN IN JJS CD NNS IN DT JJ CD NNS .
"In the Harf Sufyan district , at least 28 people died in fighting between Houthi rebels and the government-allied Aziz tribe .",O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"IN DT NNP NNP NN , IN JJS CD NNS VBD IN VBG IN NNP NNS CC DT JJ NNP NN ."
"In a separate incident late Tuesday in Saada , security officials say Houthi rebels ambushed and killed a tribal chief , his son and four others .",O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN JJ NNP IN NNP , NN NNS VBP NNP NNS VBD CC VBD DT JJ NN , PRP$ NN CC CD NNS ."
The Houthis have denied responsibility for the attack .,O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP VBP VBN NN IN DT NN .
"The Yemeni government struck a truce with the Houthis in February , after a six-year conflict .",O B-gpe O O O O O O B-org O B-tim O O O B-tim O O,"DT JJ NN VBD DT NN IN DT NNP IN NNP , IN DT JJ NN ."
"But instability still threatens Yemen and neighboring Saudi Arabia , which was briefly drawn into the conflict last year when rebels seized Saudi border areas .",O O O O B-gpe O O B-gpe I-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"CC NN RB VBZ NNP CC JJ NNP NNP , WDT VBD RB VBN IN DT NN JJ NN WRB NNS VBD JJ NN NNS ."
"The Houthi rebels complain of socioeconomic and religious discrimination at the hands of the government , but the government denies the accusations .",O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNS VBP IN JJ CC JJ NN IN DT NNS IN DT NN , CC DT NN VBZ DT NNS ."
