"An Iraqi woman screams in tears in front of the security guard as victims of suicide bomb are transported to the emergency hospital in Irbil , Iraq A suicide bomber has killed at least 50 people and wounded 100 others in an attack on police recruits in the northern Iraqi city of Irbil .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O,"DT JJ NN VBZ IN NNS IN NN IN DT NN NN IN NNS IN NN NN VBP VBN TO DT NN NN IN NNP , NNP NNP NN NN VBZ VBN IN JJS CD NNS CC VBD CD NNS IN DT NN IN NN NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP ."
"Pools of blood and body parts stained the street in the normally quiet Kurdish city , as ambulances evacuated the dead and wounded to hospitals .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN NN CC NN NNS VBD DT NN IN DT RB JJ NNP NN , IN NNS VBD DT JJ CC JJ TO NNS ."
Another car bomb attack killed nine Iraqi troops in Baghdad Wednesday .,O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo B-tim O,DT NN NN NN VBD CD JJ NNS IN NNP NNP .
More than 200 people have died in insurgent attacks over the last week .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJR IN CD NNS VBP VBN IN JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN .
"On Tuesday , the new interim government was sworn in .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , DT JJ JJ NN VBD VBN IN ."
