"Iran 's supreme leader , Ayatollah Ali Khamenei , has pledged Iranian support for the Hamas government in the Gaza Strip .",B-geo O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O B-gpe O O O B-org O O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNP POS JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP , VBZ VBN JJ NN IN DT NNP NN IN DT NNP NNP ."
"During his Eid al-Fitr sermons Wednesday , Ayatollah Khamenei called out to the Hamas leader in Gaza , Ismail Haniyeh , saying Iran will not abandon the Palestinians .",O O O O O B-tim O B-org I-org O O O O B-org O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O,"IN PRP$ JJ NN NNS NNP , NNP NNP VBD RP TO DT NNP NN IN NNP , NNP NNP , VBG NNP MD RB VB DT NNS ."
He also said Muslims worldwide are united against Israel .,O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O,PRP RB VBD NNP NN VBP VBN IN NNP .
Ayatollah Khamenei has the final say on Iran 's affairs and has harshly criticized Israel 's actions in the Hamas-ruled Gaza Strip .,B-org I-org O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN NNP POS NNS CC VBZ RB VBN NNP POS NNS IN DT JJ NNP NNP .
"He also has praised Iran 's president , Mahmoud Ahmadinejad , for defying international pressure to stop Iran 's nuclear enrichment program and for rejecting Western ideas .",O O O O B-geo O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-org O O,"PRP RB VBZ VBN NNP POS NN , NNP NNP , IN VBG JJ NN TO VB NNP POS JJ NN NN CC IN VBG JJ NNS ."
Eid al-Fitr marks the end of the Muslim holy month of Ramadan .,B-per I-per O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim I-tim O,NNP NNP VBZ DT NN IN DT NNP JJ NN IN NNP .
