Afghanistan 's election watchdog says it has disqualified 19 winning candidates in the country 's parliamentary elections after allegations of fraud were upheld .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NN NN VBZ PRP VBZ VBN CD VBG NNS IN DT NN POS JJ NNS IN NNS IN NN VBD VBN .
The Electoral Complaints Commission said Sunday two second-place candidates who would have gained by the disqualifications were also ruled not eligible for the same reasons .,B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNPS NNP VBD NNP CD JJ NNS WP MD VB VBN IN DT NNS VBD RB VBN RB JJ IN DT JJ NNS .
An official said the candidates do not have a right to appeal the decision .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD DT NNS VBP RB VB DT NN TO VB DT NN .
"The commission has been investigating some 2,500 complaints that were considered serious after the September 18 elections .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O,DT NN VBZ VBN VBG DT CD NNS WDT VBD VBN JJ IN DT NNP CD NNS .
The vote for the 249-seat parliament is being watched by Afghan President Hamid Karzai 's Western allies for signs that the Afghan leader is committed to reforming his corruption-ridden government .,O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN DT JJ NN VBZ VBG VBN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP POS JJ NNS IN NNS IN DT JJ NN VBZ VBN TO VBG PRP$ JJ NN .
