Officials in Cyprus say the United Nations wants the country to serve as the rear command and staging center for the expanded international force for Lebanon .,O O B-geo O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNS IN NNP VBP DT NNP NNP VBZ DT NN TO VB IN DT JJ NN CC NN NN IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP .
Foreign Minister George Lillikas told reporters Thursday that the U.N. informed Cyprus of its decision several days ago .,O B-per I-per I-per O O B-tim O O B-geo O B-geo O O O B-tim O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNS NNP IN DT NNP VBD NNP IN PRP$ NN JJ NNS RB .
The foreign minister is traveling Thursday to Lebanon for meetings with officials there .,O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBZ VBG NNP TO NNP IN NNS IN NNS RB .
"Cyprus had offered to act as a transit point for the movement of up to 15,000 international peacekeepers .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD VBN TO VB IN DT NN NN IN DT NN IN RB TO CD JJ NNS .
The force is authorized by the ceasefire resolution aimed at ending the war between Israel and Hezbollah .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-org O,DT NN VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NN VBN IN VBG DT NN IN NNP CC NNP .
"As war broke out between Israel and Hezbollah in July , Cyprus was the main destination for foreign nationals evacuated from Lebanon .",O O O O O B-geo O B-org O B-tim O B-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"IN NN VBD RP IN NNP CC NNP IN NNP , NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS VBN IN NNP ."
"Cyprus is located across the Mediterranean from Lebanon , just 150 kilometers away .",B-org O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBN IN DT NNP IN NNP , RB CD NNS RB ."
