North Korea has declared an end to efforts to recover the remains of American soldiers missing in action since the 1950 - 1953 Korean War .,B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim B-eve B-tim O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN TO NNS TO VB DT NNS IN JJ NNS VBG IN NN IN DT CD : CD NNP NNP .
A statement released by Pyongyang Thursday said the action follows a U.S. decision to temporarily suspend the program .,O O O O B-org B-tim O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,DT NN VBN IN NNP NNP VBD DT NN VBZ DT NNP NN TO RB VB DT NN .
The statement says now U.S. remains lost on old North Korean battlefields can never be recovered .,O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo B-gpe O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ RB NNP VBZ VBN IN JJ JJ JJ NNS MD RB VB VBN .
"Pentagon officials said last week they were suspending the recovery mission in the communist state , accusing North Korea of creating an atmosphere dangerous to U.S. workers .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O,"NNP NNS VBD JJ NN PRP VBD VBG DT NN NN IN DT JJ NN , VBG NNP NNP IN VBG DT NN JJ TO NNP NNS ."
"North Korean officials say no member of a U.S. recovery team had ever been at risk , and accused the Bush Administration of politicizing the humanitarian effort .",B-geo B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O,"JJ JJ NNS VBP DT NN IN DT NNP NN NN VBD RB VBN IN NN , CC VBD DT NNP NN IN VBG DT JJ NN ."
"Since the recovery operation began in 1996 , more than 200 sets of remains have been found .",O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN NN VBD IN CD , JJR IN CD NNS IN NNS VBP VBN VBN ."
