NATO 's International Security Assistance Force ( ISAF ) said the incident is under investigation and has not ruled out the possibility of hostile fire .,B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NNP NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP RRB VBD DT NN VBZ IN NN CC VBZ RB VBN IN DT NN IN JJ NN .
There was no immediate word on the nationality of the two service members on board the helicopter .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,EX VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN DT CD NN NNS IN NN DT NN .
