"Michael Jackson has acquired the rights to several hit songs , including material by Eminem .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NNS TO JJ NN NNS , VBG NN IN NNP ."
"The singer , who in 1985 purchased much of the Beatles song catalog , has now bought Famous Music LLC from the U.S. media conglomerate Viacom .",O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-geo O O B-per O,"DT NN , WP IN CD VBD NN IN DT NNP NN NN , VBZ RB VBN NNP NNP NNP IN DT NNP NNS NN NNP ."
"In addition to owning Eminem 's hits "" Without Me "" and "" The Real Slim Shady , "" Michael Jackson now owns the rights to songs by Beck , Bjork , and Shakira .",O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O B-geo O,"IN NN TO VBG NNP POS NNS LQU IN NNP RQU CC LQU DT JJ NNP NNP , LQU NNP NNP RB VBZ DT NNS TO NNS IN NNP , NNP , CC NNP ."
"In a statement , Jackson said "" This is a milestone event for Sony / ATV Music Publishing .",O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,"IN DT NN , NNP VBD LQU DT VBZ DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
"The diverse collection of songs in this catalogue range from timeless classics to contemporary hits , and I am pleased to add the acquisition of Famous Music to Sony / ATV . """,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-org I-org I-org O O,"DT JJ NN IN NNS IN DT NN NN IN JJ NNS TO JJ NNS , CC PRP VBP JJ TO VB DT NN IN NNP NNP TO NNP NNP NNP . RQU"
