Local Pakistani officials and residents say more than 100 people have been killed in three days of fighting in the northwestern tribal region of Waziristan .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ JJ NNS CC NNS VBP JJR IN CD NNS VBP VBN VBN IN CD NNS IN VBG IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP .
"Clashes between Uzbek militants and local tribesmen erupted on Monday near Wana , the main town in South Waziristan , near the border with Afghanistan .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-gpe O,"NNS IN JJ NNS CC JJ NNS VBD IN NNP IN NNP , DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP , IN DT NN IN NNP ."
Most of the dead are said to be Uzbek militants linked to the al-Qaida terrorist network .,O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-org O O O,JJS IN DT NN VBP VBN TO VB JJ NNS VBN TO DT NNP JJ NN .
"Violence continued Wednesday with an exchange of mortar fire between Uzbek fighters and the tribesmen , who support the Pakistani government 's efforts to clear the area of extremists .",O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,"NN VBD NNP IN DT NN IN NN NN IN JJ NNS CC DT NNS , WP VBP DT JJ NN POS NNS TO VB DT NN IN NNS ."
"Elsewhere , unidentified gunmen killed at least five members of the Pakistani security forces Wednesday traveling in a convoy in Pakistan 's Balochistan province , near the Afghan border .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O,"RB , JJ NNS VBN IN JJS CD NNS IN DT JJ NN NNS NNP VBG IN DT NN IN NNP POS NNP NN , IN DT JJ NN ."
It is not clear who was behind the rocket attack .,O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ RB JJ WP VBD IN DT NN NN .
But a military spokesman says it suspects drug smugglers who are active in the region .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC DT JJ NN VBZ PRP VBZ NN NNS WP VBP JJ IN DT NN .
