"French President Jacques Chirac has called for an end to a European ban on arms sales to China , but said he would consider U.S. concerns that the deal not tip the balance of power in the region .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN DT NN TO DT JJ NN IN NNS NNS TO NNP , CC VBD PRP MD VB NNP NNS IN DT NN RB VBZ DT NN IN NN IN DT NN ."
"Mr. Chirac said the ban is "" no longer justified . """,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD DT NN VBZ LQU DT RBR JJ . LQU
"He spoke after President Bush said there is "" deep concern "" in the United States about lifting the embargo .",O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O,PRP VBD IN NNP NNP VBD EX VBZ LQU JJ NN RQU IN DT NNP NNPS IN VBG DT NN .
The United States and the European Union imposed a joint arms embargo against China after the 1989 massacre of pro-democracy demonstrators in Tiananmen Square .,O B-gpe I-gpe O O B-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT NNP NNPS CC DT NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NNS NN IN NNP IN DT CD NN IN JJ NNS IN NNP NNP .
"Last week , the chief of the U.S. Central Intelligence Agency , Porter Goss , said China 's military build-up is tilting the balance of power in the Taiwan Strait and is threatening U.S. forces in the region .",O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-org O O O O O,"JJ NN , DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP , VBD NNP POS JJ NN VBZ VBG DT NN IN NN IN DT NNP NNP CC VBZ VBG NNP NNS IN DT NN ."
