Russia has unveiled a mock-up of a pilotless bomber jet that Russian engineers say will evade enemy radars even better than U.S. Stealth bombers and fighters .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN DT JJ NN NN IN JJ NNS VBP MD VB NN NNS RB JJR IN NNP NNP NNS CC NNS .
Russian television Thursday showed a full-size model of the bat-like jet at an ongoing international air show outside Moscow .,B-gpe O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NN NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ JJ NN NN IN NNP .
"The report said the so-called "" Skat "" aircraft is equipped to carry cruise missiles and can hit targets both at land and at sea .",O O O O O O B-art O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD DT JJ LQU NNP RQU NN VBZ VBN TO VB NN NNS CC MD VB NNS DT IN NN CC IN NN .
"President Vladimir Putin in June vowed to build up Russia 's military capabilities , in response to U.S. plans to deploy a missile defense system in central Europe .",B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP NNP NNP IN NNP VBD TO VB RP NNP POS JJ NNS , IN NN TO NNP NNS TO VB DT NN NN NN IN JJ NNP ."
"Since then , Moscow has resumed the Soviet-era practice of sending long-range bomber flights on regular patrols across the globe .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN RB , NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN VBG JJ NN NNS IN JJ NNS IN DT NN ."
"Mr. Putin has also unveiled a new air defense system near Moscow , and ordered the production of an intercontinental ballistic missile for a new generation of nuclear submarines .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ RB VBN DT JJ NN NN NN IN NNP , CC VBD DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NN IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS ."
