"Following more than three centuries under Portuguese rule , Brazil gained its independence in 1822 , maintaining a monarchical system of government until the abolition of slavery in 1888 and the subsequent proclamation of a republic by the military in 1889 .",O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"VBG JJR IN CD NNS IN JJ NN , NNP VBD PRP$ NN IN CD , VBG DT JJ NN IN NN IN DT NN IN NN IN CD CC DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN DT NN IN CD ."
Brazilian coffee exporters politically dominated the country until populist leader Getulio VARGAS rose to power in 1930 .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-tim O,JJ NN NNS RB VBD DT NN IN JJ NN NNP NNP VBD TO NN IN CD .
"By far the largest and most populous country in South America , Brazil underwent more than half a century of populist and military government until 1985 , when the military regime peacefully ceded power to civilian rulers .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN RB DT JJS CC RBS JJ NN IN NNP NNP , NNP VBD JJR IN PDT DT NN IN JJ CC JJ NN IN CD , WRB DT JJ NN RB VBD NN TO JJ NNS ."
"Brazil continues to pursue industrial and agricultural growth and development of its interior . Exploiting vast natural resources and a large labor pool , it is today South America 's leading economic power and a regional leader , one of the first in the area to begin an economic recovery .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ TO VB JJ CC JJ NN CC NN IN PRP$ NN . VBG JJ JJ NNS CC DT JJ NN NN , PRP VBZ NN NNP NNP POS VBG JJ NN CC DT JJ NN , CD IN DT NN IN DT NN TO VB DT JJ NN ."
Highly unequal income distribution and crime remain pressing problems .,O O O O O O O O O O,RB JJ NN NN CC NN VBP JJ NNS .
