Britain 's highest court has ruled that the government can not hold foreign terror suspects indefinitely without trial .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS JJS NN VBZ VBN IN DT NN MD RB VB JJ NN NNS RB IN NN .
"The court was deciding the cases of nine Muslim men jailed without charge for up to three years under the controversial Anti-Terrorism , Crime and Security Act .",O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"DT NN VBD VBG DT NNS IN CD NNP NNS VBD IN NN IN RB TO CD NNS IN DT JJ NNP , NNP CC NNP NNP ."
"The ruling is a major blow for the government of Prime Minister Tony Blair , which had argued that the detention without trial of some terror suspects is necessary in the wake of the September 11 , 2001 , attacks on the United States .",O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"DT NN VBZ DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP , WDT VBD VBN IN DT NN IN NN IN DT NN NNS VBZ JJ IN DT NN IN DT NNP CD , CD , NNS IN DT NNP NNPS ."
"The head of the nine-judge panel , Thomas Bingham , said after the ruling that "" the measures are unjustifiably discriminatory against foreign nationals as they require the detentions of some , but not all , those who present the same risk . """,O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN DT JJ NN , NNP NNP , VBD IN DT NN IN LQU DT NNS VBP RB JJ IN JJ NNS IN PRP VBP DT NNS IN DT , CC RB DT , DT WP VBP DT JJ NN . LQU"
