"The World Health Organization says yet another person in Indonesia has died from bird flu , bringing the nation 's death toll to 55 .",O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ RB DT NN IN NNP VBZ VBN IN NN NN , VBG DT NN POS NN NN TO CD ."
"The agency said in a statement Monday that a 27-year old woman died from the virus in Central Java province Friday , five days after she developed symptoms of the disease .",O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD IN DT NN NNP IN DT JJ JJ NN VBD IN DT NN IN NNP NNP NN NNP , CD NNS IN PRP VBD NNS IN DT NN ."
The W.H.O. says it is still investigating how she was exposed to bird flu .,O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP VBZ PRP VBZ RB VBG WRB PRP VBD VBN TO VB NN .
"And on Saturday , an 11-year-old boy died from the virus in a Jakarta hospital .",O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"CC IN NNP , DT JJ NN VBD IN DT NN IN DT NNP NN ."
