The United States is calling on Bangladesh to help improve the living conditions of Muslim Rohingya refugees from Burma .,O B-geo I-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O,DT NNP NNPS VBZ VBG IN NNP TO VB VB DT NN NNS IN NNP NNP NNS IN NNP .
"Assistant Secretary for Population , Refugee and Migration Affairs , Ellen Sauerbrey made the appeal during talks in Dhaka Wednesday with Bangladesh 's Food and Disaster Management Minister , Chowdhury Kamal Ibne Yusuf .",O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O,"NNP NNP IN NNP , NNP CC NNP NNP , NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN NNS IN NNP NNP IN NNP POS NNP CC NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
Mr. Yusuf is quoted by Reuters news agency as saying he would like the United States and the United Nations to try to relocate the refugees to a third country .,B-per I-per O O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NNP NN NN IN VBG PRP MD VB DT NNP NNPS CC DT NNP NNPS TO VB TO VB DT NNS TO DT JJ NN .
He said Bangladesh is not in a position to accommodate the refugees for an indefinite period of time .,O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD NNP VBZ RB IN DT NN TO VB DT NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NN .
"More than 250,000 Burmese minority Rohingyas fled across the border to Bangladesh in the early 1990s .",O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O,JJR IN CD JJ NN NNS VBD IN DT NN TO NNP IN DT JJ NNS .
"Dhaka has repatriated all but 21,000 , who live in two camps in squalid conditions .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBN DT CC CD , WP VBP IN CD NNS IN JJ NNS ."
"Bangladesh has refused to grant the Rohingyas refugee status , saying they are illegal immigrants and must return to Burma .",B-org O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP VBZ VBN TO VB DT NNP NN NN , VBG PRP VBP JJ NNS CC MD VB TO NNP ."
