A commander of Colombia 's second-largest leftist rebel group has voiced optimism that new efforts to reach peace with the government will be more fruitful than past failed attempts .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN NNP POS JJ JJ NN NN VBZ VBN NN IN JJ NNS TO VB NN IN DT NN MD VB RBR JJ IN JJ JJ NNS .
Antonio Garcia of the National Liberation Army made the remark Wednesday as the two sides prepare for talks on ending the ELN 's decades-old war against the government .,B-per I-per O O B-org I-org I-org O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,NNP NNP IN DT NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN NNP IN DT CD NNS VBP IN NNS IN VBG DT NNP POS JJ NN IN DT NN .
He acknowledged many obstacles exist but that efforts would be made to overcome them .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD JJ NNS VBP CC IN NNS MD VB VBN TO VB PRP .
"Facilitators from Norway , Spain and Switzerland are monitoring the talks , which begin this week in Cuba .",O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNS IN NNP , NNP CC NNP VBP VBG DT NNS , WDT VBP DT NN IN NNP ."
"Colombia 's high commissioner for peace , Luis Carlos Restrepo , is heading his government 's delegation .",B-geo O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ NN IN NN , NNP NNP NNP , VBZ VBG PRP$ NN POS NN ."
The talks are expected to last about 10 days and will be the current Colombian administration 's first formal negotiations with insurgents .,O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP VBN TO VB IN CD NNS CC MD VB DT JJ JJ NN POS JJ JJ NNS IN NNS .
The last talks hosted by Cuba broke down in 2002 .,O O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O,DT JJ NNS VBN IN NNP VBD RP IN CD .
