"Bomb explosions have hit two cities and a town in Nepal , just hours after communist rebels announced an end to their unilateral cease-fire .",O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NN NNS VBP VBN CD NNS CC DT NN IN NNP , RB NNS IN JJ NNS VBD DT NN TO PRP$ JJ NN ."
There were no immediate reports of any casualties .,O O O O O O O O O,EX VBD DT JJ NNS IN DT NNS .
"One explosion damaged a government building in Bhairahawa city , southwest of Kathmandu , and another hit a city council office in nearby Butwal .",O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"CD NN VBD DT NN NN IN NNP NN , NN IN NNP , CC DT VBD DT NN NN NN IN JJ NNP ."
"The third bomb exploded near a police station in Pokhara , a resort town west of Kathmandu .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT JJ NN VBD IN DT NN NN IN NNP , DT NN NN NN IN NNP ."
"Earlier Monday , the rebels said they have been forced to abandon the four-month truce , because the government was continuing its attacks .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,"RBR NNP , DT NNS VBD PRP VBP VBN VBN TO VB DT JJ NN , IN DT NN VBD VBG PRP$ NNS ."
"Nepal 's political parties , who formed a loose alliance with the rebels to press King Gyanendra to return the country to democratic rule , had asked the rebels not to resume violence .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ NNS , WP VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NNS TO VB NNP NNP TO VB DT NN TO JJ NN , VBD VBN DT NNS RB TO VB NN ."
U.N. Secretary-General Kofi Annan made a similar appeal last week .,B-org I-org B-per I-per O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN JJ NN .
Nepal 's royal government dismissed the rebel cease-fire as a ploy to buy time to regroup .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS JJ NN VBD DT NN NN IN DT NN TO VB NN TO VB .
