A U.N. official says Rwanda has decided to leave its peacekeeping troops in Sudan 's volatile Darfur region .,O B-org O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O,DT NNP NN VBZ NNP VBZ VBN TO VB PRP$ VBG NNS IN NNP POS JJ NNP NN .
"Rwanda had threatened to pull out its troops in protest to a leaked U.N. draft report , linking Rwandan soldiers to genocide in the neighboring Democratic Republic of Congo in the 1990s .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O O B-tim O,"NNP VBD VBN TO VB RP PRP$ NNS IN NN TO DT JJ NNP NN NN , VBG JJ NNS TO VB IN DT JJ NNP NNP IN NNP IN DT NNS ."
"U.N. peacekeeping chief Alain Le Roy said Friday , Rwandan President Paul Kagame confirmed during a visit to the U.N. this week his country 's troops will stay in Darfur .",B-org O O B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP NN NN NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP , JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD IN DT NN TO DT NNP DT NN PRP$ NN POS NNS MD VB IN NNP ."
U.N. Secretary-General Ban Ki-moon went to Rwanda recently to work out a comprise with President Kagame allowing Rwanda to contribute comments to the final U.N. Human Rights report due out October 1 .,B-org B-per I-per I-per O O B-org O O O O O O O B-per I-per O B-per O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O B-tim I-tim O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD TO NNP RB TO VB RP DT NN IN NNP NNP VBG NNP TO VB NNS TO DT JJ NNP NNP NNP NN JJ IN NNP CD .
