The governor of the U.S. state of Arizona has declared a state of emergency along the Mexican border in response to illegal drug and immigration activity .,O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN DT NNP NN IN NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN NN IN DT JJ NN IN NN TO JJ NN CC NN NN .
"On Monday , Governor Janet Napolitano earmarked $ 1.5 million in state funding for four counties that border Mexico .",O B-tim O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"IN NNP , NNP NNP NNP VBD $ CD CD IN NN NN IN CD NNS IN NN NNP ."
"The governor says the federal government has failed to secure the Arizona-Mexico border , a situation she says is threatening the health and safety of Arizona residents .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"DT NN VBZ DT JJ NN VBZ VBN TO VB DT JJ NN , DT NN PRP VBZ VBZ VBG DT NN CC NN IN NNP NNS ."
Governor Bill Richardson in the neighboring U.S. state of New Mexico declared a similiar state of emergency last week .,O B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP IN DT JJ NNP NN IN NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN NN JJ NN .
State leaders from both states have been urging President Bush for more resources to improve border security .,O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O,NN NNS IN DT NNS VBP VBN VBG NNP NNP IN JJR NNS TO VB NN NN .
