"The new U.S. ambassador to the United Nations , John Bolton , has presented his credentials to U.N. Secretary-General Kofi Annan .",O O B-geo O O O B-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-org I-org B-per I-per O,"DT JJ NNP NN TO DT NNP NNP , NNP NNP , VBZ VBN PRP$ NNS TO NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
Mr. Annan said he expects to work closely with the new diplomat on improving U.S. - U.N. relations and reforming the world body .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD PRP VBZ TO VB RB IN DT JJ NN IN VBG NNP IN NNP NNS CC VBG DT NN NN .
"Mr. Bolton was in New York to begin work Tuesday , one day after President Bush bypassed the Senate to appoint Mr. Bolton to the U.N. post .",B-per I-per O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-tim O O O O B-per I-per O O B-org O O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O,"NNP NNP VBD IN NNP NNP TO VB NN NNP , CD NN IN NNP NNP VBD DT NNP TO VB NNP NNP TO DT NNP NN ."
The president used his constitutional power to make the temporary appointment after Congress went on recess .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O,DT NN VBD PRP$ JJ NN TO VB DT JJ NN IN NNP VBD IN NN .
Democrats have reacted angrily to the move .,O O O O O O O O,NNPS VBP VBN RB TO DT NN .
"Over the past five months , they have twice delayed a vote on Mr. Bolton 's nomination , amid allegations that he abused subordinates and twisted intelligence .",O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ CD NNS , PRP VBP RB VBN DT NN IN NNP NNP POS NN , IN NNS IN PRP VBD NNS CC JJ NN ."
But President Bush says he thinks Mr. Bolton will take a strong leadership role at the U.N.,O B-per I-per O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-org,CC NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ NNP NNP MD VB DT JJ NN NN IN DT NNP
