Ecuador 's parliament has voted to dismiss the country 's entire 31-member Supreme Court following massive protests against recent judicial reforms .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NN VBZ VBN TO VB DT NN POS JJ JJ NNP NNP VBG JJ NNS IN JJ JJ NNS .
Lawmakers voted unanimously during a special session late Sunday to dismiss the judges and begin work on choosing their replacements .,O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBD RB IN DT JJ NN JJ NNP TO VB DT NNS CC VB NN IN VBG PRP$ NNS .
The vote came four months after the ruling coalition pushed through reforms that included dismissing the previous high court when President Lucio Guteirrez accused it of being biased against him .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD CD NNS IN DT NN NN VBD IN NNS WDT VBD VBG DT JJ JJ NN WRB NNP NNP NNP VBD PRP IN VBG VBN IN PRP .
"That move sparked massive , peaceful protests in the capital , Quito .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NN VBD JJ , JJ NNS IN DT NN , NNP ."
"In an effort to quell the protests , Mr. Guteirrez issued a brief state of emergency last Friday .",O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-tim O,"IN DT NN TO VB DT NNS , NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN NN JJ NNP ."
"Thousands of Ecuadorians took to the streets in recent days , banging pots and pans and demanding the president 's resignation , accusing him of acting like a dictator .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN NNS VBD TO DT NNS IN JJ NNS , VBG NNS CC NNS CC VBG DT NN POS NN , VBG PRP IN VBG IN DT NN ."
Mr. Guteirrez rejects calls to step down .,B-per I-per O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ NNS TO VB RB .
