Venezuelan President Hugo Chavez says his view that South American nations should work together to solve their problems does not put him at odds with the United States .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP$ NN IN JJ JJ NNS MD VB RB TO VB PRP$ NNS VBZ RB VB PRP IN NNS IN DT NNP NNPS .
"Mr. Chavez spoke to VOA Thursday on the sidelines of the Mercosur meeting in Montevideo , Uruguay .",B-per I-per O O B-org B-tim O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O B-geo O,"NNP NNP VBD TO NNP NNP IN DT NNS IN DT NNP NN IN NNP , NNP ."
The outspoken critic of President Bush said his focus on South America helps bring Venezuela closer to solving its most serious problems .,O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP VBD PRP$ NN IN NNP NNP VBZ VB NNP RBR TO VBG PRP$ RBS JJ NNS .
"Mr. Chavez also promised that Venezuela will remain in the Andean Community trade pact , even though the country is becoming a full member of the much larger Mercosur trade bloc .",B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,"NNP NNP RB VBD IN NNP MD VB IN DT NNP NNP NN NN , RB IN DT NN VBZ VBG DT JJ NN IN DT JJ JJR NN NN NN ."
He said he will try to unite the two groups .,O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD PRP MD VB TO VB DT CD NNS .
