International reaction has been mixed to President Bush 's inaugural speech and his sweeping pledge to spread freedom and end tyranny in the world .,O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NN VBZ VBN VBN TO NNP NNP POS JJ NN CC PRP$ JJ NN TO VB NN CC NN NN IN DT NN .
"Several Asian allies welcomed Mr. Bush 's second term , while North Korea condemned the United States as a "" wrecker of democracy . """,O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O,"JJ JJ NNS VBD NNP NNP POS JJ NN , IN NNP NNP VBD DT NNP NNPS IN DT RQU NN IN NN . LQU"
"Pakistani President General Pervez Musharraf promised continued support for the U.S.-led war on terror , and the Japanese government also expressed confidence in Mr. Bush 's experience .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-per I-per O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD JJ NN IN DT JJ NN IN NN , CC DT JJ NN RB VBD NN IN NNP NNP POS NN ."
European Union officials welcomed signals that Mr. Bush may be willing to strengthen traditional ties strained by the Iraq war .,B-org I-org O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,NNP NNP NNS VBD NNS IN NNP NNP MD VB JJ TO VB JJ NNS VBN IN DT NNP NN .
"But a large number of newspaper commentators were skeptical of how the president intends to carry out his ambitious goals , pointing to ongoing problems in Iraq .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"CC DT JJ NN IN NN NNS VBD JJ IN WRB DT NN VBZ TO VB RP PRP$ JJ NNS , VBG TO JJ NNS IN NNP ."
"Mr. Bush 's promises to spread freedom abroad were also met with broad skepticism in the Arab press , with many editorials calling on the president to first do more to help the Palestinian people .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"NNP NNP POS NNS TO VB NN RB VBD RB VBN IN JJ NN IN DT JJ NN , IN JJ NNS VBG IN DT NN TO RB VB JJR TO VB DT JJ NNS ."
