Prominent Egyptian opposition leader Ayman Nour has registered to run in his country 's first multi-candidate presidential elections .,O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,NNP JJ NN NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB IN PRP$ NN POS JJ JJ JJ NNS .
"The leader of the Al-Ghad Party registered early Friday , the first day presidential hopefuls could present their candidacy papers for the September 7 election .",O O O O B-org I-org O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,"DT NN IN DT NNP NNP VBD JJ NNP , DT JJ NN JJ NNS MD VB PRP$ NN NNS IN DT NNP CD NN ."
"On Thursday , President Hosni Mubarak announced his intention to stand for a sixth five-year term .",O B-tim O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , NNP NNP NNP VBD PRP$ NN TO VB IN DT JJ JJ NN ."
The state-run news agency reports that his candidacy papers were also presented to the Presidential Elections Committee today .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org B-tim O,DT JJ NN NN NNS IN PRP$ NN NNS VBD RB VBN TO DT NNP NNPS NNP NN .
"Ayman Nour , shouts from inside his court cell as he is greeted by supporters Mr. Nour is currently on trial for presenting fraudulent signatures in order to win the license for his party .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP , VBZ IN IN PRP$ NN NN IN PRP VBZ VBN IN NNS NNP NNP VBZ RB IN NN IN VBG JJ NNS IN NN TO VB DT NN IN PRP$ NN ."
He and his supporters say the charges are politically motivated and intended to eliminate him as a rival to Mr. Mubarak 's ruling party .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O,PRP CC PRP$ NNS VBP DT NNS VBP RB JJ CC JJ TO VB PRP IN DT NN TO NNP NNP POS VBG NN .
"He is out of jail on bail , and the next session of his trial is scheduled for after the voting .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBZ IN IN NN IN NN , CC DT JJ NN IN PRP$ NN VBZ VBN IN IN DT NN ."
