"Kurdish and Iranian opposition reports from northern Iran say thousands of Kurds have rallied this week in the Iranian city Mahabad , to protest the killing of a Kurdish activist by Iranian para-militaries .",O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-per O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"NNP CC JJ NN NNS IN JJ NNP VBP NNS IN NNS VBP VBN DT NN IN DT JJ NN NNP , TO VB DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS ."
The reports are displayed on Kurdish web sites and in the opposition Iran Focus .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT NNS VBP VBN IN JJ NN NNS CC IN DT NN NNP NNP .
They say the protests erupted after para-militaries shot and wounded activist Shivane Qadri on Sunday .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-tim O,PRP VBP DT NNS VBD IN NNS VBD CC VBD JJ NNP NNP IN NNP .
The attackers then dragged the dying Kurd through a nearby neighborhood from the back of a truck .,O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS RB VBD DT JJ NNP IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN DT NN .
Four sources tell VOA 's Kurdish service the protests merged with anti-Iranian sentiment that spread on Wednesday when Kurds marked the 16th anniversary of of the assassination of exiled Kurdish leader Abdul Rahman Qassemlou in Vienna .,O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O B-per I-per I-per O B-geo O,CD NNS VBP NNP POS JJ NN DT NNS VBN IN JJ NN WDT VBD IN NNP WRB NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN IN DT NN IN JJ JJ NN NNP NNP NNP IN NNP .
"The sources said 60 to 70 Kurdish protesters have been arrested in Mahabad this week , and say demonstrations were continuing Thursday evening .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"DT NNS VBD CD TO CD JJ NNS VBP VBN VBN IN NNP DT NN , CC VB NNS VBD VBG NNP NN ."
