The European Parliament has called for United Nations economic sanctions against Burma for what it says is the military government 's total disregard for the welfare of the Burmese people .,O B-org I-org O O O B-org I-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NNP NNPS JJ NNS IN NNP IN WP PRP VBZ VBZ DT JJ NN POS JJ NN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NNS .
The European lawmakers Thursday overwhelmingly passed a resolution calling on the Security Council to address the Burmese situation as a matter of urgency .,O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNS NNP RB VBD DT NN VBG IN DT NNP NNP TO VB DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN NN .
They also want Secretary General Kofi Annan to mediate a transition to democracy in Burma .,O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O,PRP RB VBP NNP NNP NNP NNP TO VB DT NN TO NN IN NNP .
The lawmakers demanded immediate freedom from house arrest for opposition leader Aung San Suu Kyi and condemned what they said was the Burmese military 's brutal campaign against ethnic groups fighting for autonomy .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBD JJ NN IN NN NN IN NN NN NNP NNP NNP NNP CC VBD WP PRP VBD VBD DT JJ NN POS JJ NN IN JJ NNS VBG IN NN .
"The parliament Thursday also called on Philippine President Gloria Arroyo to pardon Spanish citizen Francisco Larranaga , sentenced to death in July for rape and murder .",O B-org B-tim O O O B-org B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-tim O O O O O,"DT NN NNP RB VBD IN JJ NNP NNP NNP TO VB JJ NN NNP NNP , VBD TO NN IN NNP IN NN CC NN ."
The parliament calls his trial unfair under international legal standards .,O B-org O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ PRP$ NN JJ IN JJ JJ NNS .
