Afghan President Hamid Karzai and the head of U.S. and NATO troops in Afghanistan have made another public show of unity before expected military action against insurgents .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-geo O B-org O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP CC DT NN IN NNP CC NNP NNS IN NNP VBP VBN DT JJ NN IN NN IN VBN JJ NN IN NNS .
"Mr. Karzai and General Stanley McChrystal met with hundreds of tribal elders in northern Kunduz province , a region that has seen a surge in Taliban activity over the past year .",B-per I-per O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O B-tim O O,"NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP VBD IN NNS IN JJ NNS IN JJ NNP NN , DT NN WDT VBZ VBN DT NN IN NNP NN IN DT JJ NN ."
Rockets landed about 10 kilometers from the venue but failed to interrupt the meeting .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBD IN CD NNS IN DT NN CC VBD TO VB DT NN .
Sunday 's gathering was the third time in recent weeks the two men have presented the counter-insurgency strategy to groups of elders to emphasize the Afghan government 's role in military efforts .,B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,NNP POS NN VBD DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS DT CD NNS VBP VBN DT NN NN TO NNS IN NNS TO VB DT JJ NN POS NN IN JJ NNS .
"The United States is deploying an additional 30,000 troops this year to battle the Taliban insurgency .",O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O,DT NNP NNPS VBZ VBG DT JJ CD NNS DT NN TO VB DT NNP NN .
Unity between the Afghan government and its international backers is seen as essential for the push against the Taliban .,O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,NN IN DT JJ NN CC PRP$ JJ NNS VBZ VBN IN JJ IN DT NN IN DT NNP .
