"The Siboney were the first to inhabit the islands of Antigua and Barbuda in 2400 B.C. , but Arawak Indians populated the islands when COLUMBUS landed on his second voyage in 1493 .",O B-org O O O O O O O O B-geo B-org B-geo O B-tim I-tim O O B-org B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"DT NNP VBD DT JJ TO VB DT NNS IN NNP CC NNP IN CD NNP , CC NNP NNS VBD DT NNS WRB NNS VBD IN PRP$ JJ NN IN CD ."
Early settlements by the Spanish and French were succeeded by the English who formed a colony in 1667 .,O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,JJ NNS IN DT NNS CC NNS VBD VBN IN DT NNS WP VBD DT NN IN CD .
"Slavery , established to run the sugar plantations on Antigua , was abolished in 1834 .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim O,"NNP , VBN TO VB DT NN NNS IN NNP , VBD VBN IN CD ."
The islands became an independent state within the British Commonwealth of Nations in 1981 .,O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-org I-org I-org O B-tim O,DT NNS VBD DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NNP IN NNPS IN CD .
