Israel 's cabinet has approved the release of five Palestinian prisoners as the final step of a prisoner exchange with Lebanon 's Hezbollah militia .,B-org O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-org O O,NNP POS NN VBZ VBN DT NN IN CD JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN NN IN NNP POS NNP NN .
Israeli officials say none of the prisoners were involved in deadly attacks against Israel .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNS VBP NN IN DT NNS VBD VBN IN JJ NNS IN NNP .
The two soldiers were captured by Hezbollah in a raid that triggered the 2006 Lebanon war .,O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-tim B-eve O O,DT CD NNS VBD VBN IN NNP IN DT NN WDT VBD DT CD NNP NN .
