"The cyber attack occurred just hours after Mr. Obama finished delivering his State of the Union address in Washington Hackers infiltrated the Web sites of dozens of U.S. lawmakers , using the pages to curse U.S. President Barack Obama .",O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo B-per I-per I-per O,"DT NN NN VBD RB NNS IN NNP NNP VBD VBG PRP$ NN IN DT NNP NN IN NNP NNPS VBD DT NNP NNS IN NNS IN NNP NNS , VBG DT NNS TO VB NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
"Congressional officials say the Internet attack took place late Wednesday or early Thursday , just hours after Mr. Obama finished delivering his State of the Union address in Washington .",O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-tim O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O,"JJ NNS VBP DT NNP NN VBD NN JJ NNP CC JJ NNP , RB NNS IN NNP NNP VBD VBG PRP$ NN IN DT NNP NN IN NNP ."
"The attack affected 49 Web sites , targeting lawmakers from both the Democratic and Republican parties , as well as the Web site for a key congressional committee , the House of Representatives Oversight and Government Reform Committee .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,"DT NN VBD CD NNP NNS , VBG NNS IN DT DT JJ CC JJ NNS , RB RB IN DT NNP NN IN DT JJ JJ NN , DT NNP IN NNPS NNP CC NNP NNP NNP ."
"A congressional spokesman says a private company is responsible for providing security for the Internet sites impacted in the attack , but was updating the security software ( programming ) when the attack occurred .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBZ DT JJ NN VBZ JJ IN VBG NN IN DT NNP NNS VBN IN DT NN , CC VBD VBG DT NN NN LRB NN RRB WRB DT NN VBD ."
