A senior U.S. official has dismissed Serbian efforts to portray its referendum on a new constitution as an opportunity to restore sovereignty over Kosovo .,O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT JJ NNP NN VBZ VBN JJ NNS TO VB PRP$ NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN TO VB NN IN NNP .
U.S. Kosovo envoy Frank Wisner told reporters in Pristina that what happens in Kosovo is an international matter and one to be decided by the people of the Serbian province .,B-geo I-geo O B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,NNP NNP NN NNP NNP VBD NNS IN NNP IN WP VBZ IN NNP VBZ DT JJ NN CC CD TO VB VBN IN DT NNS IN DT JJ NN .
"He said it is not a matter of Serbian sovereignty , which changed when the United Nations Security Council placed the area under U.N. administration in 1999 .",O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O,"PRP VBD PRP VBZ RB DT NN IN JJ NN , WDT VBD WRB DT NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN NNP NN IN CD ."
The new constitution declares Kosovo an inalienable part of Serbia .,O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O,DT JJ NN VBZ NNP DT JJ NN IN NNP .
Authorities in Belgrade have been rallying voters to back the document in a referendum Saturday and Sunday as the best way to halt the province 's independence .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNP VBP VBN VBG NNS TO VB DT NN IN DT NN NNP CC NNP IN DT JJS NN TO VB DT NN POS NN .
Kosovo 's majority ethnic Albanians seek full independence .,B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O,NNP POS NN JJ NNS VBP JJ NN .
Serbia insists it will never surrender control of the province .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ PRP MD RB VB NN IN DT NN .
Little progress is reported in U.N.-brokered talks on the area 's future .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN VBZ VBN IN JJ NNS IN DT NN POS NN .
