The United Nations says unsafe sex and intravenous drug use have led to an increase in HIV / AIDS cases in Latin America this year .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ JJ NN CC JJ NN NN VBP VBN TO DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNS IN NNP NNP DT NN .
"The agency released its annual AIDS report Monday , saying the region had 200,000 new infections this year .",O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD PRP$ JJ NNP NN NNP , VBG DT NN VBD CD JJ NNS DT NN ."
"The report says the South American countries of Argentina , Brazil and Colombia have the biggest epidemics in the region , primarily due to their large populations .",O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ DT NNP JJ NNS IN NNP , NNP CC NNP VBP DT JJS NNS IN DT NN , RB JJ TO PRP$ JJ NNS ."
"But the highest prevalence of HIV was found in the smaller Central American countries of Belize , Guatemala and Honduras , with about one percent of adults infected .",O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"CC DT JJS NN IN NNP VBD VBN IN DT JJR JJ JJ NNS IN NNP , NNP CC NNP , IN IN CD NN IN NNS VBN ."
"In the Caribbean , the AIDS epidemic claimed an estimated 24,000 lives in 2005 , making it the leading cause of deaths among adults aged 15 to 44 years old .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NNP , DT NNP NN VBD DT JJ CD NNS IN CD , VBG PRP DT VBG NN IN NNS IN NNS VBN CD CC CD NNS JJ ."
