Russia says some of the documents submitted in the United Nations oil-for-food investigation are forged .,B-geo O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O,NNP VBZ DT IN DT NNS VBN IN DT NNP NNP NN NN VBP VBN .
"Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov says Russia must study the Volcker Report carefully , because he says some of its documents bear false signatures of Russian officials .",O O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNP MD VB DT NNP NNP RB , IN PRP VBZ DT IN PRP$ NNS VBP JJ NNS IN JJ NNS ."
"Investigators of the oil-for-food program said 2,200 companies from 66 countries made illegal payments to Saddam Hussein 's government .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O,NNS IN DT NN NN VBD CD NNS IN CD NNS VBD JJ NNS TO NNP NNP POS NN .
The commission report Thursday said nearly half of the companies in the oil-for-food program made illegal payments totaling $ 1.8 billion .,O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN NN NNP VBD RB NN IN DT NNS IN DT NN NN VBN JJ NNS VBG $ CD CD .
"It named such companies as Daimler-Chrysler and subsidiaries of Siemens , as well as politicians in France , Britain , Italy and elsewhere .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O,"PRP VBD JJ NNS IN NNP CC NNS IN NNP , RB RB IN NNS IN NNP , NNP , NNP CC RB ."
"Under the plan , which ran from 1996 to 2003 , Iraq was allowed to sell oil in order to buy humanitarian goods during the period of U.N. sanctions .",O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"IN DT NN , WDT VBD IN CD TO CD , NNP VBD VBN TO VB NN IN NN TO VB JJ NNS IN DT NN IN NNP NNS ."
"Former U.S. central bank chief Paul Volcker , who led the investigation , said better U.N. management could have lessened the corruption .",O B-geo O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP JJ NN NN NNP NNP , WP VBD DT NN , VBD JJR NNP NN MD VB VBN DT NN ."
