Britain says two of its soldiers serving with NATO 's mission in Afghanistan have been killed in southern Helmand province .,B-geo O O O O O O O B-org O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O,NNP VBZ CD IN PRP$ NNS VBG IN NNP POS NN IN NNP VBP VBN VBN IN JJ NNP NN .
The British Defense Ministry says the two soldiers were on a routine army patrol in Afghanistan 's opium-producing heartland Wednesday when their vehicle was hit by an explosion .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT CD NNS VBD IN DT JJ NN NN IN NNP POS JJ NN NNP WRB PRP$ NN VBD VBN IN DT NN .
"Earlier in Helmand , two police officers died after a bomb exploded under their vehicle .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RBR IN NNP , CD NNS NNS VBD IN DT NN VBD IN PRP$ NN ."
"Also Wednesday , the U.S. military in Afghanistan says about 24 insurgents were killed in battles with Afghan and coalition forces in southern Kandahar province .",O B-tim O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O O,"RB NNP , DT NNP NN IN NNP VBZ IN CD NNS VBD VBN IN NNS IN JJ CC NN NNS IN JJ NNP NN ."
The U.S. says insurgents clashed with joint Afghan and coalition troop patrols in two separate areas of Kandahar late Tuesday .,O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O,DT NNP VBZ NNS VBN IN JJ JJ CC NN NN NNS IN CD JJ NNS IN NNP JJ NNP .
It adds the military carried out air strikes against enemy positions .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ DT NN VBD RP NN NNS IN NN NNS .
"The military says coalition and Afghan forces also battled with Taleban insurgents in neighboring Ghazni province early Wednesday , killing several militants .",O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-org O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O O O O,"DT JJ VBZ NN CC JJ NNS RB VBD IN NNP NNS IN JJ NNP NN JJ NNP , VBG JJ NNS ."
