The Palestinian Authority says it was unable to pay its workers this month because it did not receive tax revenues from Israel .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT JJ NNP VBZ PRP VBD JJ TO VB PRP$ NNS DT NN IN PRP VBD RB VB NN NNS IN NNP .
Palestinian officials said Sunday that Israel informed them it is delaying the transfer of tax money for technical reasons .,B-gpe O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBD NNP IN NNP VBD PRP PRP VBZ VBG DT NN IN NN NN IN JJ NNS .
The reason for the delay was not clear .,O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN DT NN VBD RB JJ .
"Under an Israeli-Palestinian agreement , Israeli authorities collect taxes on behalf of the Palestinian government in the West Bank .",O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org O,"IN DT JJ NN , JJ NNS VBP NNS IN NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP ."
"The Palestinian Authority relies on the tax money to pay the salaries of more than 150,000 civil servants in the West Bank and the Gaza Strip .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-org I-org O,DT JJ NNP VBZ IN DT NN NN TO VB DT NNS IN JJR IN CD JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNP CC DT NNP NNP .
"In another development , Palestinian shepherds say a group of masked Jewish settlers physically assaulted them Sunday near the West Bank city of Hebron .",O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O,"IN DT NN , JJ NNS VBP DT NN IN VBN JJ NNS RB VBD PRP NNP IN DT NNP NNP NN IN NNP ."
"Four Palestinians were injured in the incident , including a woman who was taken to an Israeli hospital in Beersheba in serious condition .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O,"CD NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN , VBG DT NN WP VBD VBN TO DT JJ NN IN NNP IN JJ NN ."
