Venezuela 's government says it will take over all or parts of three privately owned ranches as part of its anti-poverty efforts .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NN VBZ PRP MD VB RP DT CC NNS IN CD RB VBN NNS IN NN IN PRP$ JJ NNS .
"One of those ranches is the nearly 13,000-hectare El~Charcote cattle ranch , which is owned by the British-based Vestey Group .",O O O O O O O O B-art O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,"CD IN DT NNS VBZ DT RB JJ NNP NNS NN , WDT VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NNP NNP ."
Officials say the government will also take over several hectares of land devoted to an animal reserve .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP DT NN MD RB VB RP JJ NNS IN NN VBN TO DT NN NN .
President Hugo Chavez pushed through a law passed in 2001 that allows the government to seize any land that is judged to be idle .,B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP VBD IN DT NN VBN IN CD WDT VBZ DT NN TO VB DT NN WDT VBZ VBN TO VB JJ .
The law is part of Mr. Chavez 's plan to redistribute thousands of hectares of land to Venezuela 's poor .,O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,DT NN VBZ NN IN NNP NNP POS NN TO VB NNS IN NNS IN NN TO NNP POS NN .
