Taiwan has announced plans to allow the exchange of Chinese currency on two of its offshore islands .,B-geo O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN NNS TO VB DT NN IN JJ NN IN CD IN PRP$ JJ NNS .
"Taiwan Premier Frank Hsieh made the announcement Wednesday , in Taipei .",B-geo B-per I-per I-per O O O B-tim O O B-geo O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN NNP , IN NNP ."
"He said people on the islands of Kinmen and Matsu , just off the coast of China 's Fujian Province , will , for the first time , be allowed to exchange the yuan and the New Taiwan dollar beginning October 3 .",O O O O O O O B-geo B-org B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-tim I-tim O,"PRP VBD NNS IN DT NNS IN NNP CC NNP , RB IN DT NN IN NNP POS NNP NNP , MD , IN DT JJ NN , VB VBN TO VB DT NN CC DT NNP NNP NN JJ NNP CD ."
Exchange of the two currencies on the main island of Taiwan is still banned .,B-org O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O,NNP IN DT CD NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NNP VBZ RB VBN .
"Taiwan has restricted transportation links , as well as commercial and financial contacts with China since the island separated at the end of a civil war in 1949 .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"NNP VBZ VBN NN NNS , RB RB IN JJ CC JJ NNS IN NNP IN DT NN VBD IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN CD ."
