A leading Cuban human rights group says the number of political prisoners has jumped 10 percent in the past six months in the communist country .,O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O,DT VBG JJ JJ NNS NN VBZ DT NN IN JJ NNS VBZ VBN CD NN IN DT JJ CD NNS IN DT NN NN .
"The Cuban Commission for Human Rights and National Reconciliation , based in Havana , reports the number of documented prisoners now stands at 333 .",B-org B-gpe B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNP IN NNP NNPS CC NNP NNP , VBN IN NNP , VBZ DT NN IN JJ NNS RB VBZ IN CD ."
The group says it has no way of knowing how many other people may also be detained .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ PRP VBZ DT NN IN VBG WRB JJ JJ NNS MD RB VB VBN .
"The Cuban government says it does not hold any prisoners of conscience , only common criminals .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBZ PRP VBZ RB VB DT NNS IN NN , RB JJ NNS ."
But the commission says the government continues to hold 60 of 75 dissidents arrested during a roundup of pro-democracy leaders in 2003 .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,CC DT NN VBZ DT NN VBZ TO VB CD IN CD NNS VBN IN DT NN IN JJ NNS IN CD .
