South Korean defense officials say North Korea is deploying massive numbers of troops and arms near the capital of Pyongyang .,O B-gpe O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ JJ NN NNS VBP NNP NNP VBZ VBG JJ NNS IN NNS CC NNS IN DT NN IN NNP .
"South Korea 's defense ministry said in a report to Parliament Tuesday that the large numbers of soldiers , armored vehicles and artillery have been stationed near the Stalinist state 's capital since mid-July .",B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-org B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim O,"NNP NNP POS NN NN VBD IN DT NN TO NNP NNP IN DT JJ NNS IN NNS , JJ NNS CC NN VBP VBN VBN IN DT NNP NN POS NN IN NNP ."
The report said the deployment appears to be related to a meeting of key communist party delegates next month and the party 's 65th anniversary on October 10 .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-tim I-tim O,DT NN VBD DT NN VBZ TO VB VBN TO DT NN IN JJ JJ NN VBZ JJ NN CC DT NN POS JJ NN IN NNP CD .
North Korea-watchers say the massing of military assets could be for a parade or to provide security for the events .,B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP DT NN IN JJ NNS MD VB IN DT NN CC TO VB NN IN DT NNS .
"Some analysts say North Korean leader Kim Jong Il will probably designate his youngest son Kim Jong Un as his successor at the September meeting , only the third such gathering since the communist state was founded in 1948 .",O O O B-geo B-gpe O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"DT NNS VBP JJ JJ NN NNP NNP NNP MD RB VB PRP$ JJS NN NNP NNP NNP IN PRP$ NN IN DT NNP NN , RB DT JJ JJ NN IN DT JJ NN VBD VBN IN CD ."
