German Chancellor Gerhard Schroeder and main opposition leader Angela Merkel have finished a second round of talks on forming a governing coalition without results - 10 days after an inconclusive general election .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP CC JJ NN NN NNP NNP VBP VBN DT JJ NN IN NNS IN VBG DT NN NN IN NNS IN CD NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN .
"The chairman of Mr. Schroeder 's Social Democratic Party , Franz Muentefering , said the two sides will meet again next week .",O O O B-per I-per O B-org I-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN NNP NNP POS NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP , VBD DT CD NNS MD VB RB JJ NN ."
"Mr. Schroeder says he should remain chancellor in a so-called "" Grand Coalition "" with the Christian Democrats so he can continue his free-market reforms .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ PRP MD VB NN IN DT JJ LQU NNP NNP RQU IN DT NNP NNPS IN PRP MD VB PRP$ NN NNS .
"Ms. Merkel and her supporters oppose the idea , noting they won slightly more votes than the Social Democrats in the September 18 vote .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,"NNP NNP CC PRP$ NNS VBP DT NN , VBG PRP VBD RB JJR NNS IN DT NNP NNPS IN DT NNP CD NN ."
"Also , a government spokesman says Mr. Schroeder will represent Germany at an informal European Union summit in late October , days after the new German parliament is scheduled to meet and elect a new chancellor .",O O O O O O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O B-org I-org O O O B-tim O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , DT NN NN VBZ NNP NNP MD VB NNP IN DT JJ NNP NNP NN IN JJ NNP , NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN VBZ VBN TO VB CC VB DT JJ NN ."
