"Representatives of an alliance of Pakistani madrassas , or Islamic Seminaries , who met in Islamabad on Monday , have decided not to register .",O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O,"NNS IN DT NN IN JJ NNS , CC NNP NNPS , WP VBD IN NNP IN NNP , VBP VBN RB TO VB ."
"Under a new order decreed by President Pervez Musharraf last month , all madrassas are required to register by the end of this year or close down .",O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN VBN IN NNP NNP NNP JJ NN , DT NNS VBP VBN TO VB IN DT NN IN DT NN CC VB RP ."
An alliance spokesman says the new law is discriminatory because it does not require other religious seminaries to register .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN NN VBZ DT JJ NN VBZ JJ IN PRP VBZ RB VB JJ JJ NNS TO VB .
"The madrassas also argue that donors will stop giving them money if they release their names , as required by the new law .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS RB VBP IN NNS MD VB VBG PRP NN IN PRP VBP PRP$ NNS , IN VBN IN DT JJ NN ."
Authorities say they suspect some of the madrassas have been breeding grounds for Islamist militants .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP PRP VBP DT IN DT NNS VBP VBN VBG NNS IN NNP NNS .
President Musharraf decreed the new law after revelations that at least one of the four bombers in the July seventh attacks on London had visited a Pakistani madrassa just before the attack .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN NNS IN IN JJS CD IN DT CD NNS IN DT NNP JJ NNS IN NNP VBD VBN DT JJ NN RB IN DT NN .
