"Iran 's top nuclear negotiator Ali Larijani has criticized a plan to enrich uranium in Russia , saying Iran should have control over its nuclear activities .",B-geo O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ JJ NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN TO VB NN IN NNP , VBG NNP MD VB NN IN PRP$ JJ NNS ."
Mr. Larijani told state-run television Sunday that officials are studying the Russian proposal aimed at resolving a dispute over Iran 's nuclear program .,B-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,NNP NNP VBD JJ NN NNP IN NNS VBP VBG DT JJ NN VBN IN VBG DT NN IN NNP POS JJ NN .
"But he said any plan should not block Iran from enriching uranium at home , saying it 's not logical for Iran to rely on another nation for nuclear fuel .",O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"CC PRP VBD DT NN MD RB VB NNP IN VBG NN IN NN , VBG PRP VBZ RB JJ IN NNP TO VB IN DT NN IN JJ NN ."
"Earlier , Iranian state media reported that the country has developed equipment to separate uranium from its ore - a key step in the nuclear fuel cycle .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , JJ NN NNS VBD IN DT NN VBZ VBN NN TO JJ NN IN PRP$ NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN NN ."
U.S. and European officials have expressed concern that Iran may use enriched uranium to build nuclear weapons .,B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,NNP CC JJ NNS VBP VBN NN IN NNP MD VB VBN NN TO VB JJ NNS .
Iran insists its nuclear program is peaceful .,B-geo O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ PRP$ JJ NN VBZ JJ .
