"African Union authorities say robbers have killed a U.N. military officer near al-Fasher , the capital of north Darfur state , in western Sudan .",B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNP NNP NNS VBP NNS VBP VBN DT NNP JJ NN IN NNP , DT NN IN JJ NNP NN , IN JJ NNP ."
"An AU spokesman , Noureddine Menzi , says Saturday robbers broke into a house , shot the officer and took property .",O B-org O O B-per I-per O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NN , NNP NNP , VBZ NNP NNS VBD IN DT NN , VBD DT NN CC VBD NN ."
The officer died after he was taken to a hospital .,O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD IN PRP VBD VBN TO DT NN .
"The spokesman says the officer , an Egyptian lieutenant colonel , was part of the U.N. effort to bolster peacekeeping efforts in western Sudan .",O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"DT NN VBZ DT NN , DT JJ NN NN , VBD NN IN DT NNP NN TO VB VBG NNS IN JJ NNP ."
"The U.N. and African Union are assembling a force of more than 20,000 peacekeepers .",O B-org O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP CC NNP NNP VBP VBG DT NN IN JJR IN CD NNS .
"The joint force is part of a plan to take over peacekeeping duties in Darfur from the current 7,000 AU peacekeepers .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-org O O,DT JJ NN VBZ NN IN DT NN TO VB RP VBG NNS IN NNP IN DT JJ CD NNP NNS .
