"Venezuelan President Hugo Chavez is set to attend the Summit of the Americas , but will also speak Friday at the opposition Summit of the People .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB DT NN IN DT NNPS , CC MD RB VB NNP IN DT NN NN IN DT NNS ."
"Tens of thousands of people are expected to participate in the opposition rally , which has scheduled a march Friday to protest President Bush 's presence in Argentina .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org B-tim O O B-per I-per O O O B-geo O,"NNS IN NNS IN NNS VBP VBN TO VB IN DT NN NN , WDT VBZ VBN DT NN NNP TO VB NNP NNP POS NN IN NNP ."
Some activists say they are participating because they oppose the Iraq war and President Bush 's proposed Free Trade Area of the Americas .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-org O,DT NNS VBP PRP VBP VBG IN PRP VBP DT NNP NN CC NNP NNP POS VBN NNP NNP NNP IN DT NNPS .
Venezuelan ally Cuba is sending a delegation to the opposition summit .,B-gpe O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN NNP VBZ VBG DT NN TO DT NN NN .
Cuba was not allowed to participate in the Summit of the Americas because it is a communist country .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,NNP VBD RB VBN TO VB IN DT NN IN DT NNPS IN PRP VBZ DT JJ NN .
Argentine soccer hero Diego Maradona has also announced he will participate in the protests .,B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN NN NNP NNP VBZ RB VBN PRP MD VB IN DT NNS .
"As many as 8,000 security officers have been deployed around the summit site of Mar del Plata in case violence occurs .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O,RB JJ IN CD NN NNS VBP VBN VBN IN DT NN NN IN NNP NNP NNP IN NN NN VBZ .
