Security officials in Mali say suspected Tuareg rebels have kidnapped at least 15 government soldiers .,O O O B-geo O O B-org O O O O O O O O O,NN NNS IN NNP VBP JJ NNP NNS VBP VBN IN JJS CD NN NNS .
"The officials say the soldiers were taken hostage Sunday in a remote town , Tedjerete , in the country 's northeast .",O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"DT NNS VBP DT NNS VBD VBN NN NNP IN DT JJ NN , NNP , IN DT NN POS NN ."
They say the kidnappers initially grabbed about 23 soldiers before letting several go and fleeing with the rest toward neighboring Niger .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,PRP VBP DT NNS RB VBD IN CD NNS IN VBG JJ NN CC NN IN DT NN IN VBG NNP .
"Tuareg rebels in northern Niger launched an uprising in February , saying Niger 's government has violated a 1995 peace accord .",B-org O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O O O,"NNP NNS IN JJ NNP VBD DT NN IN NNP , VBG NNP POS NN VBZ VBN DT CD NN NN ."
Fighters from the nomadic Tuareg group also rebelled against Mali 's government in the early 1990s .,O O O O B-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O,NNS IN DT JJ NNP NN RB VBD IN NNP POS NN IN DT JJ NNS .
The kidnapped soldiers had been assigned to protect technicians who were working to prevent a locust infestation .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT VBN NNS VBD VBN VBN TO VB NNS WP VBD VBG TO VB DT NN NN .
