"If so , you may be sleep deprived .",O O O O O O O O O,"IN RB , PRP MD VB NN VBN ."
Sleep experts say sleep deprivation is a common problem among many people who put in long hours on the job or take work home with them .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP NN NN VBZ DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS WP VBP RP JJ NNS IN DT NN CC VB NN NN IN PRP .
VOA 's Melinda Smith has results of a recent poll conducted by the National Sleep Foundation .,B-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,NNP POS NNP NNP VBZ NNS IN DT JJ NN VBN IN DT NNP NNP NNP .
