Pakistan security officials say they believe the militant killed in a clash with soldiers in a tribal area bordering Afghanistan on Thursday was a wanted al-Qaida terrorist .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-tim O O O B-org O O,NNP NN NNS VBP PRP VBP DT NN VBN IN DT NN IN NNS IN DT JJ NN VBG NNP IN NNP VBD DT VBN NNP NN .
"Officials say the man is believed to be Abu Marwan al-Suri , a Saudi Arabian national .",O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O,"NNS VBP DT NN VBZ VBN TO VB NNP NNP NNP , DT JJ JJ NN ."
"They say he was killed at a checkpoint near Khar , the main town in the Bajaur tribal district , when he opened fire on security personnel , killing one of them .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBP PRP VBD VBN IN DT NN IN NNP , DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NN NN , WRB PRP VBD NN IN NN NNS , VBG CD IN PRP ."
Officials say the gunman 's body will undergo further testing to confirm his identity .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP DT NN POS NN MD VB JJ NN TO VB PRP$ NN .
"The man is believed to have been one of several senior al-Qaida members targeted in a U.S. bombing attack in January , in the town of Damadola , that killed at least 18 civilians and several al-Qaida operatives .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-org O O,"DT NN VBZ VBN TO VB VBN CD IN JJ JJ NNP NNS VBN IN DT NNP NN NN IN NNP , IN DT NN IN NNP , WDT VBD IN JJS CD NNS CC JJ NNP NNS ."
Pakistan 's tribal areas along the Afghan border have been the scene of scores of military operations against remnants of the Taleban in the past two years .,B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-tim I-tim O O,NNP POS JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN VBP VBN DT NN IN NNS IN JJ NNS IN NNS IN DT NNP IN DT JJ CD NNS .
