President Bush is calling on the new Democratic-controlled Congress to pass a comprehensive immigration reform bill .,B-per I-per O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBG IN DT JJ JJ NNP TO VB DT JJ NN NN NN .
"During his annual State of the Union address on Tuesday , Mr. Bush said the United States needs an immigration system that extends "" hope and opportunity "" to millions of people seeking a better life .",O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O B-per I-per O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN PRP$ JJ NN IN DT NNP NN IN NNP , NNP NNP VBD DT NNP NNP VBZ DT NN NN WDT VBZ RQU NN CC NN LQU TO NNS IN NNS VBG DT JJR NN ."
"He called for the creation of a temporary guest worker program , and bolstering security along the porous U.S.-Mexican border .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN NN NN , CC VBG NN IN DT JJ JJ NN ."
The president backed a plan approved by a Republican-led U.S. Senate last year that would have provided eventual citizenship to the nation 's 11 million illegal immigrants .,O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD DT NN VBN IN DT JJ NNP NNP JJ NN WDT MD VB VBN JJ NN TO DT NN POS CD CD JJ NNS .
"But that plan was derailed in the Republican-controlled House , which favored a bill focusing on tighter border security , including a long fence along the Mexican border to prevent undocumented immigrants from entering the U.S.",O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-org,"CC DT NN VBD VBN IN DT JJ NNP , WDT VBD DT NN VBG IN JJR NN NN , VBG DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN TO VB JJ NNS IN VBG DT NNP"
