China has condemned Japan 's decision to begin awarding gas drilling rights in a disputed part of the East China Sea .,B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O,NNP VBZ VBN NNP POS NN TO VB VBG NN NN NNS IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP .
"Chinese foreign ministry spokesman Qin Gang called the action a provocation , and said China has the right to react to the move .",B-gpe O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"JJ JJ NN NN NNP NNP VBD DT NN DT NN , CC VBD NNP VBZ DT NN TO VB TO DT NN ."
Tokyo 's move comes at a time when relations with China are at a low over a new Japanese history textbook critics say glosses over Japan 's wartime occupation of China and other nations .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O,NNP POS NN VBZ IN DT NN WRB NNS IN NNP VBP IN DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NN NN NNS VBP NNS IN NNP POS JJ NN IN NNP CC JJ NNS .
"On Saturday and Sunday , protesters damaged windows in the Japanese embassy in Beijing , and two Japanese students were attacked in a Shanghai restaurant .",O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O O,"IN NNP CC NNP , NNS VBN NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , CC CD JJ NNS VBD VBN IN DT NNP NN ."
"Meanwhile , the Chinese consulate in Osaka , Japan , has received threats against Chinese citizens in Japan .",O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O,"RB , DT JJ NN IN NNP , NNP , VBZ VBN NNS IN JJ NNS IN NNP ."
