Officials in Vietnam have confirmed an eighth outbreak of bird flu among poultry in the country 's southern Mekong Delta region .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O,NNS IN NNP VBP VBN DT JJ NN IN NN NN IN NN IN DT NN POS JJ NNP NNP NN .
"The Department of Animal Health said Thursday , that 30 ducklings in the city of Can Tho died from the deadly H5N1 strain of the virus .",B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP IN NNP NNP VBD NNP , IN CD NNS IN DT NN IN NNP NNP VBD IN DT JJ NNP NN IN DT NN ."
"Vietnam has had no human cases of bird flu since late 2005 , but the virus re-emerged on poultry farms in the Mekong Delta last month .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O,"NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NNS IN NN NN IN JJ CD , CC DT NN VBD IN NN NNS IN DT NNP NNP JJ NN ."
The disease has killed or forced the slaughter of tens of thousands of birds .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBN CC VBN DT NN IN NNS IN NNS IN NNS .
"The H5N1 strain has killed more than 150 people worldwide , mainly in Asia , since 2003 .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim I-tim O,"DT NNP NN VBZ VBN JJR IN CD NNS JJ , RB IN NNP , IN CD ."
Experts fear the virus could mutate into a form easily passed between people .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP DT NN MD VB IN DT NN RB VBN IN NNS .
"At 42 deaths , Vietnam is second only to Indonesia in the number of human bird flu fatalities .",O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"IN CD NNS , NNP VBZ JJ RB TO NNP IN DT NN IN JJ NN NN NNS ."
