"British military contractor BAE Systems says it will buy its U.S.-based rival , United Defense Industries , for nearly $ 4 billion in cash .",B-gpe O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O,"JJ JJ NN NNP NNP VBZ PRP MD VB PRP$ JJ NN , NNP NNP NNPS , IN RB $ CD CD IN NN ."
"The British firm 's American subsidiary , BAE Systems North America , also will assume more than $ 200 million of debt from United Defense Industries , raising the total price of the acquisition to nearly $ 4.2 billion .",O B-gpe O O B-gpe O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN POS JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP NNP , RB MD VB JJR IN $ CD CD IN NN IN NNP NNP NNPS , VBG DT JJ NN IN DT NN TO RB $ CD CD ."
Corporate officials in London say they expect the combined company will benefit from the U.S. military 's war on terrorism and ongoing military operations in Afghanistan and Iraq .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,JJ NNS IN NNP VBP PRP VBP DT VBN NN MD VB IN DT NNP NN POS NN IN NN CC JJ JJ NNS IN NNP CC NNP .
"United Defense Industries designs and manufactures armored vehicles , artillery systems , naval guns and missile launchers for the United States and other nations .",B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe I-gpe O O O O,"NNP NNP NNPS VBZ CC VBZ JJ NNS , NN NNS , JJ NNS CC NN NNS IN DT NNP NNPS CC JJ NNS ."
Its sales last year brought in over $ 2 billion .,O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP$ NNS JJ NN VBD IN IN $ CD CD .
"BAE , one of Europe 's biggest defense contractors , also owns a stake in aircraft maker Airbus .",B-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,"NNP , CD IN NNP POS JJS NN NNS , RB VBZ DT NN IN NN NN NNP ."
