"Russian President Vladimir Putin is calling for a speed up in plans for reinforcing his country 's southern border , following an attack on a police vehicle in northwest Chechnya that killed at least 14 people .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBG IN DT NN RP IN NNS IN VBG PRP$ NN POS JJ NN , VBG DT NN IN DT NN NN IN JJ NNP WDT VBD IN JJS CD NNS ."
The Russian leader Tuesday said plans for strengthening the frontiers should be carried out as soon as possible .,O B-gpe O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN NNP VBD NNS IN VBG DT NNS MD VB VBN RP RB RB IN JJ .
Mr. Putin originally called for the buildup in the Caucasus region while visiting Dagestan last Friday .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O B-tim O,NNP NNP RB VBD IN DT NN IN DT NNP NN IN VBG NNP JJ NNP .
Officials in Chechnya say gunmen opened fire on a police vehicle in the northwestern village of Znamenskoye .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNS IN NNP VBP NNS VBD NN IN DT NN NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
"When reinforcements arrived , the attackers blew up the vehicle , killing 11 policemen and several civilians .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"WRB NNS VBD , DT NNS VBD RP DT NN , VBG CD NNS CC JJ NNS ."
Chechnya has been the center of a brutal conflict between government and separatist forces for much of the past decade .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN NN CC JJ NNS IN NN IN DT JJ NN .
