Iraq is opening up some of its most prized oil and gas fields to international developers in its second round of licensing since the U.S.-led invasion in 2003 .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP VBZ VBG RP DT IN PRP$ RBS JJ NN CC NN NNS TO JJ NNS IN PRP$ JJ NN IN NN IN DT JJ NN IN CD .
Oil Minister Hussain al-Shahristani announced Wednesday that the 11 fields could increase production by 2.5 million barrels per day .,O B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP IN DT CD NNS MD VB NN IN CD CD NNS IN NN .
Two of the fields - the Majnoon and West Qurna - are believed to hold huge reserves of untapped oil .,O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O,CD IN DT NNS IN DT NNP CC NNP NNP : VBP VBN TO VB JJ NNS IN JJ NN .
Iraq announced its first bidding round for licensing six months ago .,B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,NNP VBD PRP$ JJ NN NN IN NN CD NNS RB .
"The country has the world 's third largest oil reserves , but sabotage and theft have seriously hampered output in recent years .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"DT NN VBZ DT NN POS JJ JJS NN NNS , CC NN CC NN VBP RB VBN NN IN JJ NNS ."
"Oil officials say improved security is helping this industry , which is crucial to the nation 's economy .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NN NNS VBP VBN NN VBZ VBG DT NN , WDT VBZ JJ TO DT NN POS NN ."
