A U.S. court has sentenced Haiti 's former national police commander to 15 years in jail for laundering money and protecting Colombian cocaine smuggling through the Caribbean nation .,O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O O,DT NNP NN VBZ VBN NNP POS JJ JJ NN NN TO CD NNS IN NN IN NN NN CC VBG JJ NN VBG IN DT NNP NN .
"The Miami judge on Wednesday ordered Rudy Therassan to forfeit nearly $ 2 million , including two houses in Florida , allegedly purchased with money from drug activities .",O B-geo O O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NN IN NNP VBD NNP NNP TO VB RB $ CD CD , VBG CD NNS IN NNP , RB VBN IN NN IN NN NNS ."
"Haiti 's former national police director , Jean Nesly Lucien , also was sentenced to five years in jail for money laundering .",B-geo O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ JJ NN NN , NNP NNP NNP , RB VBD VBN TO CD NNS IN NN IN NN NN ."
"Last April , Therassan pleaded guilty to some charges against him , and agreed to testify against other alleged members of a Haitian drug ring .",O B-tim O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O,"JJ NNP , NNP VBD JJ TO DT NNS IN PRP , CC VBD TO VB IN JJ JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN NN ."
Prosecutors say Therassan and other Haitian police officers gave protection to illegal drug shipments arriving from Colombia .,O O B-per O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNS VBP NNP CC JJ JJ NN NNS VBD NN TO JJ NN NNS VBG IN NNP .
A U.S. trial against alleged Haitian drug kingpin Serge Edouard is due to open Monday .,O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O B-tim O,DT NNP NN IN JJ JJ NN NN NNP NNP VBZ JJ TO JJ NNP .
