U.S. Defense Secretary Donald Rumsfeld says the Pentagon may send more troops to Iraq to guard against insurgent violence during January 's elections .,B-org I-org O B-per I-per O O B-org O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-tim O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT NNP MD VB JJR NNS TO NNP TO VB IN JJ NN IN NNP POS NNS .
Mr. Rumsfeld is meeting Saturday with counterparts from 18 countries aboard a U.S. aircraft carrier in the Persian Gulf .,B-per I-per O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP NNP VBZ VBG NNP IN NNS IN CD NNS IN DT NNP NN NN IN DT NNP NNP .
He expressed hope other nations will bear some of the responsibility for ensuring a smooth vote .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD NN JJ NNS MD VB DT IN DT NN IN VBG DT JJ NN .
"Referring to Saturday 's election in Afghanistan , he said there are 1,000 additional American troops stationed in that country as well as forces sent by NATO .",O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,"VBG TO NNP POS NN IN NNP , PRP VBD EX VBP CD JJ JJ NNS VBN IN DT NN RB RB IN NNS VBN IN NNP ."
"In Iraq , Mr. Rumsfeld said there are about 100,000 Iraqi soldiers fighting alongside some 135,000 U.S. troops .",O B-geo O B-per I-per O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O O,"IN NNP , NNP NNP VBD EX VBP IN CD JJ NNS VBG IN DT CD NNP NNS ."
"He said that by January , there should be 40,000 more qualified Iraqi soldiers .",O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"PRP VBD IN IN NNP , EX MD VB CD JJR JJ JJ NNS ."
Mr. Rumsfeld said it will be up to U.S. commanders to decide if more troops are needed .,B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD PRP MD VB RB TO NNP NNS TO VB IN JJR NNS VBP VBN .
The secretary will meet with his NATO counterparts in Romania Wednesday to review similar issues .,O O O O O O B-org O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O,DT NN MD VB IN PRP$ NNP NNS IN NNP NNP TO VB JJ NNS .
