A human rights group says Chinese authorities have extended the labor camp sentence of a Shanghai woman detained for protesting the country 's one-child policy .,O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNS NN VBZ JJ NNS VBP VBN DT NN NN NN IN DT NNP NN VBD IN VBG DT NN POS JJ NN .
"Human Rights in China says Mao Hengfeng , who was serving an 18-month sentence , recently had three months added to her term .",B-org I-org O B-geo O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP IN NNP VBZ NNP NNP , WP VBD VBG DT JJ NN , RB VBD CD NNS VBD TO PRP$ NN ."
"The rights group says Ms. Mao has been fighting for basic human rights for 15 years , and has been forcibly committed to psychiatric institutions several times .",O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS NN VBZ NNP NNP VBZ VBN VBG IN JJ JJ NNS IN CD NNS , CC VBZ VBN RB VBN TO JJ NNS JJ NNS ."
The group says she has been repeatedly subjected to severe beatings during her current detention .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ PRP VBZ VBN RB VBN TO JJ NNS IN PRP$ JJ NN .
"China 's one-child policy , introduced a generation ago , has been widely criticized for leading to forced abortions and other human rights violations .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ NN , VBD DT NN RB , VBZ VBN RB VBN IN VBG TO JJ NNS CC JJ JJ NNS NNS ."
