Ukrainian lawmakers have rejected demands for a total recount of last month 's parliamentary elections .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN NNS IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NN POS JJ NNS .
A group of parties that failed to reach the three percent barrier for representation in parliament had sought the recount .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN NNS WDT VBD TO VB DT CD NN NN IN NN IN NN VBD VBN DT NN .
"But the four top vote-getting parties rejected the request Tuesday , saying they would support court ordered recounts .",O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,"CC DT CD JJ JJ NNS VBD DT NN NNP , VBG PRP MD VB NN VBD NNS ."
"The vote came as hundreds of recount supporters demonstrated outside parliament waving the flags of minor parties , which now must turn to the courts in hopes of gaining parliamentary seats .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD IN NNS IN JJ NNS VBD JJ NN VBG DT NNS IN JJ NNS , WDT RB MD VB TO DT NNS IN NNS IN VBG JJ NNS ."
"The pro-Russian Party of Regions , led by former Prime Minister Viktor Yanukovych , won the most seats in the vote , followed by supporters of former Prime Minister Yulia Tymoshenko and then deputies backing President Viktor Yushchenko .",O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O B-per I-per I-per O,"DT JJ NN IN NNS , VBN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP , VBD DT JJS NNS IN DT NN , VBN IN NNS IN JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP CC RB NNS VBG NNP NNP NNP ."
International observers praised the election as essentially free and fair .,O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBD DT NN IN RB JJ CC JJ .
