It can also determine when the cancer cells become resistant to drug treatments .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP MD RB VB WRB DT NN NNS VBP JJ TO NN NNS .
A clinical trial using the device was published in the New England Journal of Medicine .,O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,DT JJ NN VBG DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NNP NNP NNP IN NNP .
VOA 's Deborah Block has more .,B-org O B-geo I-geo O O O,NNP POS NNP NNP VBZ RBR .
