"Cuban singer Ibrahim Ferrer , one of the leading voices with the Buena Vista Social Club of vintage Cuban performers , has died at age 78 .",B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim O,"JJ NN NNP NNP , CD IN DT VBG NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP IN JJ JJ NNS , VBZ VBN IN NN CD ."
"The cause of death was not known , but it follows Ferrer 's recent return to Cuba from a trip to Europe .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O,"DT NN IN NN VBD RB VBN , CC PRP VBZ NNP POS JJ NN TO NNP IN DT NN TO NNP ."
"Born in the Cuban city of Santiago in 1927 , Ferrer began singing professionally in 1941 .",O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O B-tim O B-per O O O O B-tim O,"VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP IN CD , NNP VBD VBG RB IN CD ."
"By the late 1950s , he was an established singer who performed with well-known Cuban bands .",O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"IN DT JJ NNS , PRP VBD DT JJ NN WP VBD IN JJ JJ NNS ."
Ferrer was a master singer of the son and bolero music styles .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD DT NN NN IN DT NN CC NN NN NNS .
"By the 1990s , Ferrer had left the musical scene and was shining shoes for money when U.S. musician Ry Cooder recruited him to participate in the Buena Vista Social Club album , a hugely popular recording that won a Grammy .",O O B-tim O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-org O,"IN DT NNS , NNP VBD VBN DT JJ NN CC VBD VBG NNS IN NN WRB NNP NN NNP NNP VBD PRP TO VB IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP NN , DT RB JJ NN WDT VBD DT NNP ."
The group 's fame grew with a film of the same name by German director Wim Wenders .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-per I-per O,DT NN POS NN VBD IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NN NNP NNP .
