"Unknown attackers chopped off two fingers from the right hand of a journalist who writes for one of China 's most outspoken and progressive newspapers , as apparent retaliation for his articles detailing organized crime activities in the southern part of the country .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBD RP CD NNS IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN WP VBZ IN CD IN NNP POS RBS JJ CC JJ NNS , IN JJ NN IN PRP$ NNS VBG JJ NN NNS IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN ."
"Thirty-year-old Wen Chong , a reporter for the Guangdong-based Nanfang Dushi Bao ( Southern Metropolitan News ) , was attacked inside his home late Thursday .",O B-per I-per O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"JJ NNP NNP , DT NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP NNP NNP RRB , VBD VBN IN PRP$ NN RB NNP ."
"Officials say his index and middle fingers were cut off to prevent him from holding a pen properly , perhaps as an intentional warning from his assailants .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP PRP$ NN CC JJ NNS VBD VBN RP TO VB PRP IN VBG DT NN RB , RB IN DT JJ NN IN PRP$ NNS ."
Journalism advocacy groups say attacks and government pressure on journalists who report about crime and corruption in China have become increasingly more common .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,NNP NN NNS VBP NNS CC NN NN IN NNS WP VBP IN NN CC NN IN NNP VBP VBN RB RBR JJ .
The former chief editor of the Nanfang Dushi Bao was terminated and imprisoned for five months after controversial articles detailed the SARS virus and the beating of a migrant worker two years ago .,O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-tim O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,DT JJ NN NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP VBD VBN CC VBN IN CD NNS IN JJ NNS VBN DT NNS NN CC DT NN IN DT NN NN CD NNS RB .
