Syrian economic growth remained in the 4-5 % range in 2008 - 10 even though the global economic crisis affected oil prices and the economies of Syria 's key export partners and sources of investment .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,JJ JJ NN VBD IN DT CD NN NN IN CD : CD RB IN DT JJ JJ NN VBD NN NNS CC DT NNS IN NNP POS JJ NN NNS CC NNS IN NN .
"Damascus has implemented modest economic reforms in the past few years , including cutting lending interest rates , opening private banks , consolidating all of the multiple exchange rates , raising prices on some subsidized items , most notably gasoline and cement , and establishing the Damascus Stock Exchange - which began operations in 2009 .",B-org O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-tim O,"NNP VBZ VBN JJ JJ NNS IN DT JJ JJ NNS , IN VBG NN NN NNS , VBG JJ NNS , VBG DT IN DT JJ NN NNS , VBG NNS IN DT JJ NNS , JJS RB NN CC NN , CC VBG DT NNP NNP NNP : WDT VBD NNS IN CD ."
"In addition , President ASAD signed legislative decrees to encourage corporate ownership reform , and to allow the Central Bank to issue Treasury bills and bonds for government debt .",O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-org O O O O O O O,"IN NN , NNP NNP VBD JJ NNS TO VB JJ NN NN , CC TO VB DT NNP NNP TO VB NNP NNS CC NNS IN NN NN ."
"Nevertheless , the economy remains highly controlled by the government .",O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , DT NN VBZ RB VBN IN DT NN ."
"Long-run economic constraints include declining oil production , high unemployment , rising budget deficits , and increasing pressure on water supplies caused by heavy use in agriculture , rapid population growth , industrial expansion , and water pollution .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ JJ NNS VBP VBG NN NN , JJ NN , VBG NN NNS , CC VBG NN IN NN NNS VBN IN JJ NN IN NN , JJ NN NN , JJ NN , CC NN NN ."
