"Visiting Afghan President Hamid Karzai and his Pakistani counterpart , Pervez Musharraf , have agreed that more cooperation is needed to curb cross-border terrorism .",O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"VBG JJ NNP NNP NNP CC PRP$ JJ NN , NNP NNP , VBP VBN IN JJR NN VBZ VBN TO VB JJ NN ."
Pakistani officials say the two leaders also agreed that extremism and terrorism must be addressed in the long-term .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP DT CD NNS RB VBD IN NN CC NN MD VB VBN IN DT JJ .
"They say Mr. Karzai and General Musharraf also discussed activities of the Taleban and recent events on the Pakistani side of the border , as well as regional and international issues of mutual interest .",O O B-per B-org O B-org I-org O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP RB VBD NNS IN DT NNP CC JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN , RB RB IN JJ CC JJ NNS IN JJ NN ."
The officials did not elaborate .,O O O O O O,DT NNS VBD RB VB .
"In a goodwill gesture at the start of Mr. Karzai 's three-day visit , Pakistan released 562 Afghans held in detention in the southern city of Karachi for visa violations .",O O O O O O O O B-per B-org O B-tim O O B-per O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"IN DT NN NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP POS JJ NN , NNP VBD CD NNS VBN IN NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP IN NN NNS ."
Mr. Karzai is scheduled to meet with Prime Minister Shaukat Aziz on Thursday and return to Kabul the following day .,B-per B-org O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB IN NNP NNP NNP NNP IN NNP CC NN TO NNP DT VBG NN .
