The United States has imposed a ban on arms sales to Venezuela because of what U.S. officials say is a lack of support for counter-terrorism efforts .,O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNPS VBZ VBN DT NN IN NNS NNS TO NNP IN IN WP NNP NNS VBP VBZ DT NN IN NN IN NN NNS .
A U.S. State Department spokeswoman Monday accused Caracas of failing to stop Colombia 's leftist guerrillas from using Venezuelan soil .,O B-org I-org I-org O B-tim O B-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT NNP NNP NNP NN NNP VBD NNP IN VBG TO VB NNP POS JJ NNS IN VBG JJ NN .
Venezuela has repeatedly denied allowing access to Colombian fighters .,B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O,NNP VBZ RB VBN VBG NN TO JJ NNS .
The U.S. ban is likely to further strain relations between Washington and Caracas .,O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-org O,DT NNP NN VBZ JJ TO JJ NN NNS IN NNP CC NNP .
Venezuelan President Hugo Chavez has frequently condemned the U.S.-led war in Iraq and criticized Washington for planning a military strike in Iran .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ RB VBN DT JJ NN IN NNP CC VBD NNP IN VBG DT JJ NN IN NNP .
"Speaking in London today , the Venezuelan leader called on the international community , especially Europe , to prevent military action in Iran because of its nuclear program .",O O B-geo B-tim O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"VBG IN NNP NN , DT JJ NN VBD IN DT JJ NN , RB NNP , TO VB JJ NN IN NNP IN IN PRP$ JJ NN ."
