"A Kremlin spokesman says that Russian President Vladimir Putin will not travel to Riga , Latvia to meet with the French and Latvian presidents .",O B-org O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O B-gpe O O,"DT NNP NN VBZ IN JJ NNP NNP NNP MD RB VB TO NNP , NNP TO VB IN DT JJ CC JJ NNS ."
Dmitry Peskov told reporters in Moscow Tuesday that efforts to accommodate the schedules of the three leaders proved unsuccessful .,B-per I-per O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD NNS IN NNP NNP IN NNS TO VB DT NNS IN DT CD NNS VBD JJ .
A French presidential spokesman said earlier that Mr. Putin might travel to Latvia on Wednesday following the NATO summit .,O B-gpe O O O O O B-per I-per O O O B-geo O B-tim O O B-org O O,DT JJ JJ NN VBD RBR IN NNP NNP MD VB TO NNP IN NNP VBG DT NNP NN .
"He planned to help mark the 74th birthday of French President Jacques Chirac , and also meet with Latvian President Vaira Vike-Freiberga .",O O O O O O B-tim O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O,"PRP VBD TO VB VB DT JJ NN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP , CC RB VB IN JJ NNP NNP NNP ."
The trip would have been Mr. Putin 's first to the Baltic country as president .,O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,DT NN MD VB VBN NNP NNP POS JJ TO DT JJ NN IN NN .
"Latvia and the other two Baltic countries , Estonia and Lithuania , gained independence in 1991 after almost 50 years of Soviet rule .",B-geo O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O B-tim O B-tim I-tim O O O O O,"NNP CC DT JJ CD JJ NNS , NNP CC NNP , VBD NN IN CD IN RB CD NNS IN JJ NN ."
Relations between Russia and Latvia have been strained .,O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O,NNP IN NNP CC NNP VBP VBN VBN .
