Afghan and coalition forces said they have killed one suspected militant and detained four others during operations in southern and eastern Afghanistan .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ CC NN NNS VBD PRP VBP VBN CD JJ NN CC VBD CD NNS IN NNS IN JJ CC JJ NNP .
In a joint statement released Thursday the forces said they targeted bomb-making ( improvised explosive device ) networks in Kandahar and Khost provinces .,O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O,IN DT JJ NN VBN NNP DT NNS VBD PRP VBD NN LRB JJ JJ NN RRB NNS IN NNP CC NNP NNS .
"The joint forces , acting on information from local citizens , targeted a compound Thursday in Maywand district in Kandahar , killing one militant , detaining two others and confiscating bomb-making materials .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNS , VBG IN NN IN JJ NNS , VBD DT NN NNP IN NNP NN IN NNP , VBG CD NN , VBG CD NNS CC VBG JJ NNS ."
"In Khost , Afghan special forces and coalition soldiers detained two suspected members of the Haqqani network without firing a shot .",O B-geo O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"IN NNP , JJ JJ NNS CC NN NNS VBD CD JJ NNS IN DT NNP NN IN VBG DT NN ."
The United States alleges the network has ties to al-Qaida and Pakistani intelligence agents .,O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-org O B-gpe O O O,DT NNP NNPS VBZ DT NN VBZ NNS TO NNP CC JJ NN NNS .
