Officials in Colombia say Marxist rebels killed the mayor of the small central town of Genova Wednesday .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O,NNS IN NNP VBP JJ NNS VBD DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP NNP .
Police say Mayor Jose Castro was shot by members of the Revolutionary Armed Forces of Colombia ( FARC ) rebel group .,O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O,NNS VBP NNP NNP NNP VBD VBN IN NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNS IN NNP LRB NNP RRB NN NN .
The FARC rebels have declared Colombian mayors to be military targets and killed at least three in the past year .,O B-org O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim O O,DT NNP NNS VBP VBN JJ NNS TO VB JJ NNS CC VBN IN JJS CD IN DT JJ NN .
The rebel group has been waging war against the Colombian government for at least 40 years and funds itself largely through the drug trade and kidnapping .,O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN NN VBZ VBN VBG NN IN DT JJ NN IN IN JJS CD NNS CC VBZ PRP RB IN DT NN NN CC NN .
