"President Bush has called on Syria to "" stop exporting violence and start importing democracy "" .",B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NNP TO RQU VB VBG NN CC NN VBG NN LQU .
The president spoke Friday at a Veterans Day ceremony at a military base in Pennsylvania .,O O O B-tim O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NN VBD NNP IN DT NNP NNP NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
He said Syria should cooperate fully with a United Nations investigation into the shooting death of former Lebanese Prime Minister Rafik Hariri .,O O B-geo O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O,PRP VBD NNP MD VB RB IN DT NNP NNP NN IN DT NN NN IN JJ JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP .
"He also criticized Syrian president Bashar al-Assad for delivering what Mr. Bush called "" a strident speech "" that lashed out at both the Lebanese government and the U.N. probe of Mr. Hariri 's death .",O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo O O B-per I-per O O O,PRP RB VBD JJ NN NNP NNP IN VBG WP NNP NNP VBD LQU DT JJ NN RQU WDT VBD RP IN DT DT JJ NN CC DT NNP NN IN NNP NNP POS NN .
"Mr. Bush also called on Syria to stop , in his words , "" trying to intimidate and destabilize "" Lebanon .",B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP NNP RB VBD IN NNP TO VB , IN PRP$ NNS , LQU VBG TO VB CC VB RQU NNP ."
"Mr. Bush also criticized the Syrian government for arresting opposition activist Kamal Labwani for , in the president 's words , serving as an advocate for democratic reform .",B-per I-per O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP RB VBD DT JJ NN IN VBG NN NN NNP NNP IN , IN DT NN POS NNS , VBG IN DT NN IN JJ NN ."
