Insurgents in the western Iraqi city of Ramadi launched a brief assault Thursday against a U.S. base and Iraqi government buildings .,O O O O B-gpe O O B-org O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O,NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP VBD DT JJ NN NNP IN DT NNP NN CC JJ NN NNS .
Residents first reported the incident .,O O O O O O,NNS RB VBD DT NN .
"They said scores of masked gunmen , believed to be al-Qaida in Iraq terrorists , launched mortar rounds and rockets in the streets , as local tribal leaders and U.S. military officials met .",O O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"PRP VBD NNS IN VBN NNS , VBN TO VB NNP IN NNP NNS , VBD NN NNS CC NNS IN DT NNS , IN JJ JJ NNS CC NNP JJ NNS VBD ."
"U.S. military spokesman , Major General Rick Lynch downplayed the incident , saying there was only one rocket-propelled grenade attack against a joint Iraqi coalition checkpoint , and that it caused no casualties .",B-geo O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN , VBG EX VBD RB CD JJ NN NN IN DT JJ JJ NN NN , CC IN PRP VBD DT NNS ."
"U.S. and Iraqi troops have been in Ramadi since Sunday , conducting anti-insurgent operations ahead of parliamentary elections scheduled for December 15 .",B-geo O B-gpe O O O O B-org B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"NNP CC JJ NNS VBP VBN IN NNP IN NNP , VBG JJ NNS RB IN JJ NNS VBN IN NNP CD ."
But officials caution that they expect a spike in violence as insurgents grow more desperate in the lead-up to the vote .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC NNS VBP IN PRP VBP DT NN IN NN IN NNS VBP RBR JJ IN DT NN TO DT NN .
