"Niger has made an "" anguished appeal "" for emergency food aid to help some three million people facing famine after years of drought and a locust infestation .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN DT LQU JJ NN RQU IN NN NN NN TO VB DT CD CD NNS VBG NN IN NNS IN NN CC DT JJ NN .
"The appeal from Prime Minister Hama Amadou comes about a week after the United Nations asked for more than 16 million dollars to help what it calls Niger 's "" silent crisis . """,O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ IN DT NN IN DT NNP NNP VBD IN JJR IN CD CD NNS TO VB WP PRP VBZ NNP POS LQU JJ NN . LQU
"U.N. estimates say 800,000 children under the age of five suffer from hunger in the northwest African country , including 150,000 who are severely malnourished .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNS VBP CD NNS IN DT NN IN CD VBP IN NN IN DT JJ JJ NN , VBG CD WP VBP RB VBN ."
A majority of the country 's 11 million people survive on subsistence farming .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN DT NN POS CD CD NNS VBP IN NN NN .
Years of drought and a recent locust invasion has decimated crops .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NN CC DT JJ NN NN VBZ VBN NNS .
"In addition , Niger 's government has levied large taxes on staple goods .",O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NN , NNP POS NN VBZ VBN JJ NNS IN NN NNS ."
Civil society groups have called for protests against those taxes next Thursday .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,JJ NN NNS VBP VBN IN NNS IN DT NNS JJ NNP .
