"Afghan officials say more than 28 civilians , including women and children , were killed Thursday in air strikes by international troops in Afghanistan 's southern Helmand province .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O,"JJ NNS VBP JJR IN CD NNS , VBG NNS CC NNS , VBD VBN NNP IN NN NNS IN JJ NNS IN NNP POS JJ NNP NN ."
Gereshk district chief Abdul Manaf Khan says the air strikes were called in after hours of fierce fighting in the village of Kumbarak late Thursday .,O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O,NNP NN NN NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT NN NNS VBD VBN IN IN NNS IN JJ NN IN DT NN IN NNP JJ NNP .
Khan says most of the victims were killed while fleeing the air strikes .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ JJS IN DT NNS VBD VBN IN VBG DT NN NNS .
"He originally identified the foreign troops as NATO forces , but NATO says it is not aware of any such incident .",O O O O O O O B-org O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP RB VBD DT JJ NNS IN NNP NNS , CC NNP VBZ PRP VBZ RB JJ IN DT JJ NN ."
A statement from the coalition said there were no military deaths .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN DT NN VBD EX VBD DT JJ NNS .
