Polls have closed in Zimbabwe where parliamentary elections were conducted smoothly and without the kind of violence that has marred previous elections .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP VBN IN NNP WRB JJ NNS VBD VBN RB CC IN DT NN IN NN WDT VBZ VBN JJ NNS .
"Turnout was reported to be high , with long lines at polling stations across the country .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NN VBD VBN TO VB JJ , IN JJ NNS IN VBG NNS IN DT NN ."
"After casting his ballot , President Robert Mugabe said he was confident his ruling ZANU-PF party would win an overwhelming victory .",O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN VBG PRP$ NN , NNP NNP NNP VBD PRP VBD JJ PRP$ NN NNP NN MD VB DT JJ NN ."
Morgan Tsvangirai the leader of the Movement for Democratic Change casts his vote Opposition leader Morgan Tsvangirai said he believed Zimbabweans want change .,B-per I-per O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-per I-per O O O B-gpe O O O,NNP NNP DT NN IN DT NN IN JJ NNP VBZ PRP$ NN NN NN NNP NNP VBD PRP VBD NNS VBP NN .
"He called the election fundamentally unfair , accusing the ruling party of using repressive policies to guarantee victory .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD DT NN RB JJ , VBG DT VBG NN IN VBG JJ NNS TO VB NN ."
Vote counting is expected to begin immediately .,O O O O O O O O,JJ NN VBZ VBN TO VB RB .
120 parliamentary seats are at stake in the election .,O O O O O O O O O O,CD JJ NNS VBP IN NN IN DT NN .
"In another development , a police spokesman says two British journalists were arrested in the town of Norton while interviewing voters .",O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"IN DT NN , DT NN NN VBZ CD JJ NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN IN NNP IN VBG NNS ."
They are accused of covering the election without proper accreditation as required by Zimbabwe law .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,PRP VBP VBN IN VBG DT NN IN JJ NN IN VBN IN NNP NN .
