World number-one men 's tennis player Rafael Nadal of Spain is missing this week 's Paris Masters tournament with a shoulder injury but he says it wo n't prevent him from playing at the ATP World Tour finals later this month in London .,O O O O O O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-tim O O O B-geo O,NNP JJ NNS POS NN NN NNP NNP IN NNP VBZ VBG DT NN POS NNP NNP NN IN DT NN NN CC PRP VBZ PRP MD RB VB PRP IN VBG IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNS RB DT NN IN NNP .
Nadal told a news conference Monday in Paris that he has a small case of tendinitis in his left shoulder and that he withdrew from the last Masters tournament of the season to avoid risking a serious injury before the season-ending finals .,B-per O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD DT NN NN NNP IN NNP IN PRP VBZ DT JJ NN IN NNS IN PRP$ NN NN CC IN PRP VBD IN DT JJ NNP NN IN DT NN TO VB VBG DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NNS .
"The top-ranked Spaniard said he will need one week of full training to be ready for the ATP Finals , which run November 21 - 28 .",O O B-gpe O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,"DT JJ NN VBD PRP MD VB CD NN IN JJ NN TO VB JJ IN DT NNP NNP , WDT VBP NNP CD IN CD ."
"After winning the French Open , Wimbledon and the U.S. Open this season , Nadal is guaranteed to finish the year at number-one .",O O O B-gpe B-org O B-org O O B-org I-org O B-tim O B-per O O O O O O O O O,"IN VBG DT JJ NN , NNP CC DT NNP NNP DT NN , NNP VBZ VBN TO VB DT NN IN NN ."
He has played in 33 of the past 35 Masters 1000 tournaments .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ VBN IN CD IN DT JJ CD NNS CD NNS .
