"China 's Central Bank is issuing a special 10 yuan note to commemorate the Beijing Olympics , swapping the image of communist leader Mao Zedong for a picture of the city 's iconic national stadium .",B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NNP NNP VBZ VBG DT JJ CD JJ NN TO VB DT NNP NNPS , VBG DT NN IN JJ NN NNP NNP IN DT NN IN DT NN POS JJ JJ NN ."
"The People 's Bank of China says it plans to issue six million of the notes , worth about $ 1.45 each , during the games .",O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP POS NNP IN NNP VBZ PRP VBZ TO VB CD CD IN DT NNS , JJ IN $ CD DT , IN DT NNS ."
Beijing 's Bird 's Nest stadium is an interlocking mesh of steel that looks much like a roost for birds .,B-geo B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NNP POS NNP NN VBZ DT VBG NN IN NN WDT VBZ RB IN DT NN IN NNS .
"A picture of the stadium will be on one side of the note , along with the dancing man emblem of the 2008 Olympic Games .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN DT NN MD VB IN CD NN IN DT NN , IN IN DT VBG NN NN IN DT CD NNP NNPS ."
On the other side will be an image of an ancient Greek statue of a discus thrower .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,IN DT JJ NN MD VB DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NN IN DT NN NN .
"Both sides of the bill will also feature the Temple of Heaven as a backdrop , one of China 's best known landmarks .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,"DT NNS IN DT NN MD RB VB DT NNP IN NNP IN DT NN , CD IN NNP POS JJS VBN NNS ."
