Cuban President Fidel Castro has marked the 52nd anniversary of his attack on a military garrison that started the Cuban revolution .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN PRP$ NN IN DT JJ NN WDT VBD DT JJ NN .
"President Castro addressed supporters at a Havana theater Tuesday - the anniversary of his failed July 26 , 1953 assault on the Moncada barracks in Santiago .",B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O B-tim I-tim O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O B-geo O O B-geo O,"NNP NNP VBD NNS IN DT NNP NN NNP IN DT NN IN PRP$ VBN NNP CD , CD NN IN DT NNP NNS IN NNP ."
"In previous years , mass outdoor rallies have been held to mark the assault that culminated in his taking power on January 1 , 1959 .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,"IN JJ NNS , NN NN NNS VBP VBN VBN TO VB DT NN WDT VBD IN PRP$ VBG NN IN NNP CD , CD ."
"During his speech , Mr. Castro said the economy grew at seven percent in the first half of the year .",O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O,"IN PRP$ NN , NNP NNP VBD DT NN VBD IN CD NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN ."
He also lashed out at dissidents during his speech .,O O O O O O O O O O,PRP RB VBD RP IN NNS IN PRP$ NN .
"Last week , Cuban authorities rounded up at least 33 dissidents in an apparent effort to stop them from attending a rally to call for the release of political prisoners in Cuba .",O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"JJ NN , JJ NNS VBD RP IN JJS CD NNS IN DT JJ NN TO VB PRP IN VBG DT NN TO VB IN DT NN IN JJ NNS IN NNP ."
At least nine still remain in custody .,O O O O O O O O,IN JJS CD RB VBP IN NN .
