Malaysian authorities have arrested a fugitive Iraqi terrorism suspect as he tried to enter the Asian country using a false passport .,B-gpe O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN DT JJ JJ NN NN IN PRP VBD TO VB DT JJ NN VBG DT JJ NN .
Malaysian news media report that immigration police arrested Mohammed Al-Daini at Kuala Lumpur airport last Saturday .,B-gpe O O O O O O O B-per I-per O B-geo I-geo O O B-tim O,JJ NN NNS VBP IN NN NN VBN NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NN JJ NNP .
Immigration officials say he tried to enter the country using someone else 's passport .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NN NNS VBP PRP VBD TO VB DT NN VBG DT RB POS NN .
Al-Daini is a former member of Iraq 's parliament .,B-per O O O O O B-geo O O O,NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN NNP POS NN .
"Iraq 's Shi'ite-led government has accused him of ordering a series of attacks and insurgent plots , including a 2007 bombing that killed two other Iraqi lawmakers .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-gpe O O,"NNP POS JJ NN VBZ VBN PRP IN VBG DT NN IN NNS CC JJ NNS , VBG DT CD NN WDT VBD CD JJ JJ NNS ."
"Al-Daini has been on the run since parliament lifted his immunity in late February , paving the way for his arrest .",B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBN IN DT NN IN NN VBD PRP$ NN IN JJ NNP , VBG DT NN IN PRP$ NN ."
Bernama news agency says Malaysian immigration officials plan to deport al-Daini once they obtain new travel documents for him from the Iraqi embassy .,B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,NNP NN NN VBZ JJ NN NNS VBP TO VB JJ RB PRP VBP JJ NN NNS IN PRP IN DT JJ NN .
