"For centuries China stood as a leading civilization , outpacing the rest of the world in the arts and sciences , but in the 19th and early 20th centuries , the country was beset by civil unrest , major famines , military defeats , and foreign occupation .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNS NNP VBD IN DT VBG NN , VBG DT NN IN DT NN IN DT NNS CC NNS , CC IN DT JJ CC JJ JJ NNS , DT NN VBD VBN IN JJ NN , JJ NNS , JJ NNS , CC JJ NN ."
"After World War II , the Communists under MAO Zedong established an autocratic socialist system that , while ensuring China 's sovereignty , imposed strict controls over everyday life and cost the lives of tens of millions of people .",O O O B-eve O O B-org O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP NNP NNP , DT NNPS IN NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN NN WDT , IN VBG NNP POS NN , VBD JJ NNS IN JJ NN CC VBD DT NNS IN NNS IN NNS IN NNS ."
"After 1978 , MAO 's successor DENG Xiaoping and other leaders focused on market-oriented economic development and by 2000 output had quadrupled .",O B-tim O B-org O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O,"IN CD , NNP POS NN NNP NNP CC JJ NNS VBD IN JJ JJ NN CC IN CD NN VBD VBN ."
"For much of the population , living standards have improved dramatically and the room for personal choice has expanded , yet political controls remain tight .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NN IN DT NN , VBG NNS VBP VBN RB CC DT NN IN JJ NN VBZ VBN , RB JJ NNS VBP JJ ."
China since the early 1990s has increased its global outreach and participation in international organizations .,B-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP IN DT JJ NNS VBZ VBN PRP$ JJ NN CC NN IN JJ NNS .
