President Bush has acknowledged plans for a comprehensive free-trade zone in the Western Hemisphere have stalled .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN IN DT JJ NNP VBP VBN .
"Mr. Bush told journalists from Argentina , Panama and Brazil Tuesday he still sees the need for the free-trade zone , but the priority now is broader global trade talks on agriculture .",B-per I-per O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD NNS IN NNP , NNP CC NNP NNP PRP RB VBZ DT NN IN DT JJ NN , CC DT NN RB VBZ JJR JJ NN NNS IN NN ."
"The president leaves Washington Thursday for a five-day visit to Latin America , starting in Argentina at the Summit of the Americas .",O O O B-geo B-tim O O B-tim O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-geo O O B-eve I-eve I-eve I-eve O,"DT NN VBZ NNP NNP IN DT JJ NN TO NNP NNP , VBG IN NNP IN DT NNP IN DT NNPS ."
The proposal for a Free Trade Area for the Americas has been bogged down because of disagreements between the United States and Brazil .,O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-org O,DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP IN DT NNP VBZ VBN VBN RB IN IN NNS IN DT NNP NNPS CC NNP .
"In the global talks , the U.S. , Brazil , India and the European Union are trying to reach a compromise on farm subsidies before a World Trade Organization summit in Hong Kong next month .",O O O O O O B-geo O B-org O B-org O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-geo I-geo O O O,"IN DT JJ NNS , DT NNP , NNP , NNP CC DT NNP NNP VBP VBG TO VB DT NN IN NN NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP NN IN NNP NNP JJ NN ."
