Democrats in the Republican-controlled U.S. Senate have announced they will launch investigative hearings into what they view as problems in the Bush administration .,O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,NNS IN DT JJ NNP NNP VBP VBN PRP MD VB JJ NNS IN WP PRP VBP IN NNS IN DT NNP NN .
Senate Democrats say the hearings are necessary because Senate Republicans have abdicated their responsibility for oversight of the administration 's policies and use of taxpayer money .,B-org O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNPS VBP DT NNS VBP JJ IN NNP NNPS VBP VBN PRP$ NN IN NN IN DT NN POS NNS CC NN IN NN NN .
Democratic Senator Byron Dorgan of North Dakota said the first hearing will be in January .,B-org B-per B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O B-tim O,JJ NNP NNP NNP IN NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN MD VB IN NNP .
He said a possible target of the hearings is alleged contract abuses in Iraq .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,PRP VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NNS VBZ VBN NN NNS IN NNP .
Other topics could include pre-war intelligence on Iraq and the Abu Ghraib prison scandal .,O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org O O O,JJ NNS MD VB JJ NN IN NNP CC DT NNP NNP NN NN .
"The Democratic-organized hearings will not have subpoena powers , but Senator Dorgan said he believes there will be "" plenty of whistleblowers "" ready to speak out against the administration .",O O O O O O O O O O B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNS MD RB VB NN NNS , CC NNP NNP VBD PRP VBZ EX MD VB LQU NN IN NNS LQU JJ TO VB RP IN DT NN ."
"When the new Congress convenes in January , Republicans will have an expanded majority of 55 senators , leaving Democrats with less influence .",O O O B-org O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"WRB DT JJ NNP VBZ IN NNP , NNPS MD VB DT VBN NN IN CD NNS , VBG NNPS IN JJR NN ."
