Japan and the Southeast Asian countries on the Mekong River issued a joint statement Friday calling for free and fair elections in Burma .,B-geo O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP CC DT JJ JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN NNP VBG IN JJ CC JJ NNS IN NNP .
"The Mekong summit , which met on the sidelines of the ASEAN summit in Vietnam 's capital Hanoi , also called for the Korean Peninsula to become a nuclear-free zone .",O B-org O O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-geo O O B-per O O O O O B-gpe B-org O O O O O O,"DT NNP NN , WDT VBD IN DT NNS IN DT NNP NN IN NNP POS NN NNP , RB VBD IN DT JJ NN TO VB DT JJ NN ."
"The group , including Cambodia , Laos , Thailand , Burma and Vietnam , issued an action plan calling for Japanese economic aid and technical help to develop transportation and energy resources in the Mekong River region , while protecting its environment .",O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O,"DT NN , VBG NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP CC NNP , VBD DT NN NN VBG IN JJ JJ NN CC JJ NN TO VB NN CC NN NNS IN DT NNP NNP NN , IN VBG PRP$ NN ."
"United Nations Secretary-General Ban Ki-moon told reporters in Hanoi Friday that it is not too late for a credible , democratic transition in Burma , which is planning to hold controversial elections on November 7 .",B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O B-per B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNS IN NNP NNP IN PRP VBZ RB RB JJ IN DT JJ , JJ NN IN NNP , WDT VBZ VBG TO VB JJ NNS IN NNP CD ."
