Israeli Prime Minister Ariel Sharon says Israel will not keep all Jewish settlements in the West Bank in any final peace deal with the Palestinians .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNP MD RB VB DT JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNP IN DT JJ NN NN IN DT NNS .
But Mr. Sharon ruled out another unilateral pullback like last week 's in the Gaza Strip .,O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,CC NNP NNP VBD RP DT JJ NN IN JJ NN POS IN DT NNP NNP .
He says any future settlement evacuations will be the result of negotiations with the Palestinians under the international road map peace plan .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ DT JJ NN NNS MD VB DT NN IN NNS IN DT NNS IN DT JJ NN NN NN NN .
He also told Israeli television that all main West Bank settlements will remain under Israeli control .,O O O B-gpe O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-gpe O O,PRP RB VBD JJ NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP NNS MD VB IN JJ NN .
Palestinian Authority President Mahmoud Abbas said it is essential that Israel stop expanding West Bank settlements in order for both sides to return to peace talks .,B-org I-org B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD PRP VBZ JJ IN NNP VB VBG NNP NNP NNS IN NN IN DT NNS TO VB IN NN NNS .
