A former financial adviser to South African Deputy President Jacob Zuma has been found guilty of fraud and corruption .,O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ JJ NN TO NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN VBN JJ IN NN CC NN .
The high court in Durban Thursday found Schabir Shaik guilty on three counts .,O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-org I-org O O O O O,DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP JJ IN CD NNS .
"He was accused of paying Mr. Zuma $ 200,000 in bribes to help further Shaik 's business interests .",O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-org O O O O,PRP VBD VBN IN VBG NNP NNP $ CD IN NNS TO VB JJ NNP POS NN NNS .
He was also charged with brokering a bribe between Mr. Zuma and a French arms firm so the company would be shielded from an investigation .,O O O O O O O O O B-per B-org O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD RB VBN IN VBG DT NN IN NNP NNP CC DT JJ NNS NN IN DT NN MD VB VBN IN DT NN .
Shaik told reporters Thursday that he is innocent .,B-org O O B-tim O O O O O,NNP VBD NNS NNP IN PRP VBZ JJ .
"Mr. Zuma , who is seen as a favorite to succeed President Thabo Mbeki , was not charged in the case .",B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP , WP VBZ VBN IN DT NN TO VB NNP NNP NNP , VBD RB VBN IN DT NN ."
It is not clear if South African prosecutors will now charge him .,O O O O O B-geo B-gpe O O O O O O,PRP VBZ RB JJ IN JJ JJ NNS MD RB VB PRP .
"Following Thursday 's ruling , opposition groups immediately called for Mr. Zuma 's resignation .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-per B-org O O O,"VBG NNP POS NN , NN NNS RB VBD IN NNP NNP POS NN ."
