Political rivals in Madagascar have agreed to reconvene in two weeks to continue their talks aimed at creating a unity government .,O O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS IN NNP VBP VBN TO VB IN CD NNS TO VB PRP$ NNS VBN IN VBG DT NN NN .
Interim leader Andry Rajoelina and his three predecessors failed to reach an agreement Saturday after three days of talks .,O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O,NNP NN NNP NNP CC PRP$ CD NNS VBD TO VB DT NN NNP IN CD NNS IN NNS .
The negotiations are being facilitated by French and South African mediators in Pretoria .,O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-gpe O O B-geo O,DT NNS VBP VBG VBN IN JJ CC JJ JJ NNS IN NNP .
One of the major points of disagreement is a timetable for holding new elections .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CD IN DT JJ NNS IN NN VBZ DT NN IN VBG JJ NNS .
The country has been in a political crisis since March of 2009 when Mr. Rajoelina seized power from former president Marc Ravalomanana .,O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O B-per B-org O O O O O B-per I-per O,DT NN VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP IN CD WRB NNP NNP VBD NN IN JJ NN NNP NNP .
The interim government is not recognized by the African Union .,O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT JJ NN VBZ RB VBN IN DT NNP NNP .
The group imposed sanctions on Mr. Rajoelina and his political allies in March for their refusal to honor agreements that had been mandated by the AU .,O O O O O B-per B-org O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,DT NN VBD NNS IN NNP NNP CC PRP$ JJ NNS IN NNP IN PRP$ NN TO VB NNS WDT VBD VBN VBN IN DT NNP .
