Pakistani officials say heavy rains and snowfalls have killed at least 31 people across Pakistan over the past week and ended a drought in some parts of the country .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP JJ NNS CC NNS VBP VBN IN JJS CD NNS IN NNP IN DT JJ NN CC VBD DT NN IN DT NNS IN DT NN .
"Most of the victims were killed in avalanches , flash floods and collapsing roofs .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJS IN DT NNS VBD VBN IN NNS , NN NNS CC VBG NNS ."
"The French News Agency , AFP , reports that six people have been killed in three separate avalanches in Indian Kashmir .",O B-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-geo O,"DT NNP NNP NNP , NNP , VBZ IN CD NNS VBP VBN VBN IN CD JJ NNS IN JJ NNP ."
"Also heavy snowfall has trapped some 3,000 motorists on the main Jammu-Srinagar highway .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,RB JJ NN VBZ VBN DT CD NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN .
"In neighboring Afghanistan , snowfall has been so heavy that an operation to recover the bodies of 104 people killed in a plane crash one week ago still has not begun .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O,"IN VBG NNP , NN VBZ VBN RB JJ IN DT NN TO VB DT NNS IN CD NNS VBN IN DT NN NN CD NN IN RB VBZ RB VBN ."
Bad weather so far has allowed only a brief inspection of the crash site .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN RB RB VBZ VBN RB DT JJ NN IN DT NN NN .
