Iraqi troops are sealing off Baghdad to search for insurgents in their biggest such operation since the fall of Saddam Hussein .,B-gpe O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,JJ NNS VBP VBG RP NNP TO VB IN NNS IN PRP$ JJS JJ NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP .
"Iraqi officials say Operation Lighting involves 40,000 Iraqi troops .",B-gpe O O B-org I-org O O B-gpe O O,JJ NNS VBP NNP NNP VBZ CD JJ NNS .
They began setting up the first of several hundred checkpoints in and around Baghdad Sunday .,O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O B-geo B-tim O,PRP VBD VBG RP DT NN IN JJ CD NNS IN CC IN NNP NNP .
Al-Qaida in Iraq says it is launching an offensive to counter the operation .,B-org O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP IN NNP VBZ PRP VBZ VBG DT NN TO VB DT NN .
The group also claimed responsibility for Monday 's double suicide bombing in Hillah that killed 27 people .,O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,DT NN RB VBD NN IN NNP POS JJ NN VBG IN NNP WDT VBD CD NNS .
"Also Monday , the U.S. military released the head of Iraq 's top Sunni political party after mistakenly arresting him hours earlier .",O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB NNP , DT NNP NN VBD DT NN IN NNP POS JJ NNP JJ NN IN RB VBG PRP NNS RBR ."
And the U.S. military says an Iraqi aircraft with four Americans and one Iraqi on board crashed in eastern Iraq .,O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo I-geo O,CC DT NNP NN VBZ DT JJ NN IN CD NNS CC CD JJ IN NN VBD IN JJ NNP .
The statement says the crash is under investigation and gave no indication whether there are casualties .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ DT NN VBZ IN NN CC VBD DT NN IN EX VBP NNS .
