"Afghan officials say a series of bomb and suicide attacks Sunday killed at least 18 people , including 11 construction workers .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP DT NN IN NN CC NN NNS NNP VBD IN JJS CD NNS , VBG CD NN NNS ."
"Eight workers died when their vehicle hit a roadside bomb in eastern Nangarhar province , while three more construction workers were killed in a similar incident in southeastern Zabul province .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"CD NNS VBD WRB PRP$ NN VBD DT NN NN IN JJ NNP NN , IN CD JJR NN NNS VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NNP NN ."
"In southern Helmand province , a double suicide bombing claimed by the Taliban killed four security personnel and three civilians .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O,"IN JJ NNP NN , DT JJ NN VBG VBN IN DT NNP VBD CD NN NNS CC CD NNS ."
"Local officials say the first bomber blew himself up near a police checkpoint in the town of Gereshk , while the second bomber struck as Afghan security forces arrived at the scene .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP DT JJ NN VBD PRP RP IN DT NN NN IN DT NN IN NNP , IN DT JJ NN VBD IN JJ NN NNS VBD IN DT NN ."
"Also Sunday , the U.S. military said Afghan and coalition forces killed one militant and detained seven others in eastern Paktika province .",O B-tim O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"RB NNP , DT NNP NN VBD JJ CC NN NNS VBD CD NN CC VBD CD NNS IN JJ NNP NN ."
"In a separate operation in northeastern Nangarhar province , Afghan and coalition forces say they captured five suspected militants , including a Taliban commander .",O O O O O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O,"IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NNP NN , JJ CC NN NNS VBP PRP VBD CD JJ NNS , VBG DT NNP NN ."
