Officials in Afghanistan say suspected Taleban rebels have killed a candidate in the country 's upcoming legislative election .,O O B-geo O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNP VBP JJ NNP NNS VBP VBN DT NN IN DT NN POS JJ JJ NN .
Authorities say National Assembly candidate Abdul Hadi was shot dead late Thursday in front of his house in southern Helmand province .,O O B-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O O,NNS VBP NNP NNP NN NNP NNP VBD VBN RB JJ NNP IN NN IN PRP$ NN IN JJ NNP NN .
At least six candidates and several poll workers have been murdered ahead of Sunday 's ballot .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,IN JJS CD NNS CC JJ NN NNS VBP VBN VBN RB IN NNP POS NN .
"The Taleban , who have denounced the polls , have claimed responsibility for several of the killings .",O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP , WP VBP VBN DT NNS , VBP VBN NN IN NN IN DT NNS ."
"In Kabul , senior U.N. envoy to Afghanistan Filippo Grandi said murders and intimidation continue to be a serious obstacle to free and fair elections , but stressed the attacks have not derailed the electoral process .",O B-geo O O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , JJ NNP NN TO NNP NNP NNP VBD NNS CC NN VBP TO VB DT JJ NN TO JJ CC JJ NNS , CC VBD DT NNS VBP RB VBN DT JJ NN ."
"Campaigning officially ended Thursday , with electoral officials racing to educate more than 12 million Afghans on the voting process prior to the balloting .",O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O,"VBG RB VBN NNP , IN JJ NNS VBG TO VB JJR IN CD CD NNS IN DT NN NN RB TO DT NN ."
