Equatorial Guinea gained independence in 1968 after 190 years of Spanish rule .,B-org I-org O O O B-tim O B-tim O O B-gpe O O,NNP NNP VBD NN IN CD IN CD NNS IN JJ NN .
"This tiny country , composed of a mainland portion plus five inhabited islands , is one of the smallest on the African continent .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"DT JJ NN , VBN IN DT JJ NN CC CD JJ NNS , VBZ CD IN DT JJS IN DT JJ NN ."
President Teodoro OBIANG NGUEMA MBASOGO has ruled the country since 1979 when he seized power in a coup .,B-per I-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN CD WRB PRP VBD NN IN DT NN .
"Although nominally a constitutional democracy since 1991 , the 1996 , 2002 , and 2009 presidential elections - as well as the 1999 , 2004 , and 2008 legislative elections - were widely seen as flawed .",O O O O O O B-tim O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN RB DT JJ NN IN CD , DT CD , CD , CC CD JJ NNS : RB RB IN DT CD , CD , CC CD JJ NNS : VBD RB VBN IN JJ ."
The president exerts almost total control over the political system and has discouraged political opposition .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ RB JJ NN IN DT JJ NN CC VBZ VBN JJ NN .
"Equatorial Guinea has experienced rapid economic growth due to the discovery of large offshore oil reserves , and in the last decade has become Sub-Saharan Africa 's third largest oil exporter .",B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBN JJ JJ NN JJ TO DT NN IN JJ JJ NN NNS , CC IN DT JJ NN VBZ VBN JJ NNP POS JJ JJS NN NN ."
"Despite the country 's economic windfall from oil production resulting in a massive increase in government revenue in recent years , improvements in the population 's living standards have been slow to develop .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN POS JJ NN IN NN NN VBG IN DT JJ NN IN NN NN IN JJ NNS , NNS IN DT NN POS NN NNS VBP VBN JJ TO VB ."
