A U.S. Appeals Court has turned down a government request to change the status of American terror suspect Jose Padilla until the Supreme Court hears his case .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O B-org I-org O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN RP DT NN NN TO VB DT NN IN JJ NN NN NNP NNP IN DT NNP NNP VBZ PRP$ NN .
The Bush administration had sought to have Mr. Padilla transferred from military to civilian custody .,O B-per O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBD VBN TO VB NNP NNP VBD IN JJ TO JJ NN .
The court said the request could be seen as an attempt by the government to avoid a Supreme Court ruling on the case .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O,DT NN VBD DT NN MD VB VBN IN DT NN IN DT NN TO VB DT NNP NNP NN IN DT NN .
His lawyers question the administration 's authority to detain him under such conditions .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP$ NNS VBP DT NN POS NN TO VB PRP IN JJ NNS .
The judge who wrote the ruling Wednesday argued that the case was of sufficient national importance to warrant the Supreme Court 's consideration .,O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O,DT NN WP VBD DT NN NNP VBD IN DT NN VBD IN JJ JJ NN TO VB DT NNP NNP POS NN .
Human rights groups and Bush administration critics have denounced imprisoning terror suspects without the promise of a trial .,O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS NNS CC NNP NN NNS VBP VBN VBG NN NNS IN DT NN IN DT NN .
