Palestinian officials say jailed uprising leader Marwan Barghouti has dropped plans to run for president .,B-gpe O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP JJ NN NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNS TO VB IN NN .
Officials from the main Fatah faction Friday said Palestinian cabinet minister Kadoura Fares had visited Barghouti in his Israeli prison to dissuade him from running in the January 9 poll .,O O O O B-geo O B-tim O B-gpe O B-per B-org I-org O O B-per O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O,NNS IN DT JJ NNP NN NNP VBD JJ NN NN NNP NNP VBD VBN NNP IN PRP$ JJ NN TO VB PRP IN VBG IN DT NNP CD NN .
The officials say Mr. Fares ' message was that Barghouti 's participation in the race could threaten the unity of Fatah and the success of the vote to elect a successor to the late Yasser Arafat .,O O O B-per B-org O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,DT NNS VBP NNP NNP POS NN VBD IN NNP POS NN IN DT NN MD VB DT NN IN NNP CC DT NN IN DT NN TO VB DT NN TO DT JJ NNP NNP .
Fatah has chosen former Prime Minister Mahmoud Abbas as its presidential candidate .,B-geo O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP IN PRP$ JJ NN .
Barghouti had previously said he would not run if Fatah nominated Mr. Abbas .,B-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-per I-per O,NNP VBD RB VBN PRP MD RB VB IN NNP VBD NNP NNP .
Barghouti is a popular Palestinian politician .,B-per O O O B-gpe O O,NNP VBZ DT JJ JJ NN .
