"Iraqi police say a suicide car bomber has killed at least five people in Baghdad , the latest violence in a week of grim attacks in the Iraqi capital .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"JJ NNS VBP DT NN NN NN VBZ VBN IN JJS CD NNS IN NNP , DT JJS NN IN DT NN IN JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN ."
Officials say the attacker drove an explosives-packed car into a security checkpoint in Baghdad 's mostly Sunni neighborhood of Ghazaliya Friday .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo B-tim O,NNS VBP DT NN VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NN NN IN NNP POS RB JJ NN IN NNP NNP .
About 20 people were wounded .,O O O O O O,IN CD NNS VBD VBN .
"Attacks targeting Shi'ite pilgrims in Baghdad killed more than 60 other people this week , which marked the anniversary of Shi'ite Imam Moussa al-Kadhim 's death .",O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O,"NNS VBG NNP NNS IN NNP VBD JJR IN CD JJ NNS DT NN , WDT VBD DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP POS NN ."
Overall violence in Iraq is yet to match the peak reached in 2006 and 2007 .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,JJ NN IN NNP VBZ RB TO VB DT NN VBN IN CD CC CD .
