Indonesian police say masked gunmen shot and wounded a Christian couple in the latest violence to hit the restive province of Central Sulawesi .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,JJ NNS VBP VBN NNS VBD CC VBD DT JJ NN IN DT JJS NN TO VB DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP .
Police said Sunday a university lecturer and his wife were shot late Saturday on their way home from a church service in the provincial capital Palu .,O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per O,NNP VBD NNP DT NN NN CC PRP$ NN VBD VBN JJ NNP IN PRP$ NN NN IN DT NN NN IN DT JJ NN NNP .
The shooting was the latest in a series of violent incidents to hit Central Sulawesi .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,DT NN VBD DT JJS IN DT NN IN JJ NNS TO VB NNP NNP .
"Late last month , unidentified assailants beheaded three Christian teenage girls in Poso , about 100 kilometers east of Palu .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-per O,"RB JJ NN , JJ NNS VBD CD NNP NN NNS IN NNP , IN CD NNS NN IN NNP ."
"Two other girls , a Muslim and a Christian , were seriously wounded by gun-wielding assailants in the same city earlier this month .",O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"CD JJ NNS , DT NN CC DT NNP , VBD RB VBN IN VBG NNS IN DT JJ NN RBR DT NN ."
"Conflict between Muslims and Christians has left more than 1,000 people dead in the province since 2000 .",O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,NN IN NNPS CC NNPS VBZ VBN JJR IN CD NNS JJ IN DT NN IN CD .
