A British news report says that the Iraqi judge who sentenced former President Saddam Hussein to death has applied for asylum in London .,O B-gpe O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT JJ NN NN VBZ IN DT JJ NN WP VBD JJ NNP NNP NNP TO NN VBZ VBN IN NN IN NNP .
"The Times newspaper said Saturday that Raouf Abdel Rahman is living in Britain , because he fears for his life in Iraq .",O O O O B-tim O B-org I-org I-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NNP NN VBD NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBG IN NNP , IN PRP VBZ IN PRP$ NN IN NNP ."
The report says Abdel Rahman arrived in Britain with his family two weeks prior to Saddam 's December 30 execution .,O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,DT NN VBZ NNP NNP VBD IN NNP IN PRP$ NN CD NNS RB TO NNP POS NNP CD NN .
Judiciary officials in Baghdad say Rahman requested a vacation and that he said he was returning home .,B-org O O B-geo O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS IN NNP VBP NNP VBD DT NN CC IN PRP VBD PRP VBD VBG NN .
"Judge Abdel Rahman , an Iraqi Kurd , presided over the court that sentenced the former Iraqi dictator and some of his top aides to death in November of last year .",O B-per I-per O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O,"NNP NNP NNP , DT JJ NNP , VBD IN DT NN WDT VBD DT JJ JJ NN CC DT IN PRP$ JJ NNS TO NN IN NNP IN JJ NN ."
"Militants in Iraq have often targeted relatives of prominent public figures , including judges .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN NNP VBP RB VBN NNS IN JJ JJ NNS , VBG NNS ."
Arabic Al-Jazeera television reported earlier this month that Abdel Rahman was seeking asylum in London .,O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP NN VBD RBR DT NN IN NNP NNP VBD VBG NN IN NNP .
