President Bush says that the most destabilizing thing that can happen in the Middle East and in the world is for Iran to develop a nuclear weapon .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ IN DT RBS JJ NN WDT MD VB IN DT NNP NNP CC IN DT NN VBZ IN NNP TO VB DT JJ NN .
"During a joint news conference Wednesday in Kabul with Afghan President Hamid Karzai , Mr. Bush repeated Washington 's position that Iran should not be allowed to develop nuclear arms .",O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN NN NNP IN NNP IN JJ NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP VBD NNP POS NN IN NNP MD RB VB VBN TO VB JJ NNS ."
"In Japan Wednesday , Iranian Foreign Minister Manouchehr Mottaki said his country has accepted in principle a Russian proposal to enrich uranium for Iran 's nuclear energy needs .",O B-geo B-tim O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,"IN NNP NNP , JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD PRP$ NN VBZ VBN IN NN DT JJ NN TO VB NN IN NNP POS JJ NN NNS ."
But he said the period of time and the place for uranium enrichment must still be negotiated .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC PRP VBD DT NN IN NN CC DT NN IN NN NN MD RB VB VBN .
A high level Iranian delegation is in Moscow Wednesday for more negotiations on the nuclear issue .,O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN JJ NN VBZ IN NNP NNP IN JJR NNS IN DT JJ NN .
Mottaki also said that Iran has nothing to hide about its nuclear activities .,B-per O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,NNP RB VBD IN NNP VBZ DT TO VB IN PRP$ JJ NNS .
