U.S. government officials say the Obama administration is considering creating a special unit of professional interrogators to handle high-value terror suspects .,B-geo O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NN NNS VBP DT NNP NN VBZ VBG VBG DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS TO VB JJ NN NNS .
"Officials told two major U.S. newspapers The Wall Street Journal and The Washington Post about the creation of the unit on the condition of anonymity , saying the government task force on interrogation methods has not yet reported to the president .",O O O O B-geo O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBD CD JJ NNP NNS DT NNP NNP NNP CC DT NNP NNP IN DT NN IN DT NN IN DT NN IN NN , VBG DT NN NN NN IN NN NNS VBZ RB RB VBN TO DT NN ."
"Officials say the unit 's primary purpose would be intelligence gathering , rather than building criminal cases for prosecution .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP DT NN POS JJ NN MD VB NN NN , RB IN VBG JJ NNS IN NN ."
The team would also devise new interrogation methods .,O O O O O O O O O,DT NN MD RB VB JJ NN NNS .
"Officials say the task force has not yet determined what agency should run the new unit , but it will not be the Central Intelligence Agency .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,"NNS VBP DT NN NN VBZ RB RB VBN WP NN MD VB DT JJ NN , CC PRP MD RB VB DT NNP NNP NNP ."
The CIA headed up interrogations under the Bush administration .,O B-org O O O O O B-geo O O,DT NNP VBD RP NNS IN DT NNP NN .
"The small , specialized unit would be composed of personnel from the federal government 's intelligence , military , and law agencies .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ , JJ NN MD VB VBN IN NNS IN DT JJ NN POS NN , JJ , CC NN NNS ."
