Members of the four-nation Andean Community trade alliance have gathered in Ecuador for a summit aimed at salvaging their regional commerce bloc .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN DT NN NNP NNP NN NN VBP VBN IN NNP IN DT NN VBN IN VBG PRP$ JJ NN NN .
"The presidents of Bolivia , Ecuador , Colombia and Peru are attending the summit in Quito , Ecuador 's capital .",O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O,"DT NNS IN NNP , NNP , NNP CC NNP VBP VBG DT NN IN NNP , NNP POS NN ."
"During the summit , the presidents plan to discuss pursuing a free trade pact with the European Union .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"IN DT NN , DT NNS VBP TO VB VBG DT JJ NN NN IN DT NNP NNP ."
They also are seeking an extension of trade preferences granted by Washington in 1991 .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O,PRP RB VBP VBG DT NN IN NN NNS VBN IN NNP IN CD .
The preferences are due to expire at the end of this year .,O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O,DT NNS VBP JJ TO VB IN DT NN IN DT NN .
"Venezuela withdrew from the Andean Community last month , saying the bloc is "" fatally wounded "" because Peru and Colombia signed free trade deals with the United States .",B-per O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNP VBD IN DT NNP NNP JJ NN , VBG DT NN VBZ RQU RB VBN RQU IN NNP CC NNP VBD JJ NN NNS IN DT NNP NNPS ."
