The World Bank has approved a series of loans aimed at economic development and poverty reduction in Latin American .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN NNS VBN IN JJ NN CC NN NN IN NNP NNP .
"In a series of statements issued Tuesday in Washington , the bank announced loan programs to Argentina , Peru and Brazil .",O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O,"IN DT NN IN NNS VBN NNP IN NNP , DT NN VBD NN NNS TO NNP , NNP CC NNP ."
The bank approved a $ 200 million loan to Argentina designed to improve infrastructure in the Province of Buenos Aires .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,DT NN VBD DT $ CD CD NN TO NNP VBN TO VB NN IN DT NNP IN NNP NNPS .
"The improvements include road , water , sewerage and drainage construction .",O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS VBP NN , NN , NN CC NN NN ."
Another $ 200 million loan was approved for Peru to improve social programs for the poor and enhance the nation 's economic competitiveness .,O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT $ CD CD NN VBD VBN IN NNP TO VB JJ NNS IN DT NN CC VB DT NN POS JJ NN .
And a $ 4.8 million loan was awarded to Brazil 's northern Amapa state .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O,CC DT $ CD CD NN VBD VBN TO NNP POS JJ NNP NN .
The loan will subsidize a program designed to reduce rural and urban poverty through environmentally sustainable projects around the Amazon river .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,DT NN MD VB DT NN VBN TO VB JJ CC JJ NN IN RB JJ NNS IN DT NNP NN .
