Japanese Prime Minister Junichiro Koizumi has paid another visit to a Tokyo war shrine seen by critics as a symbol of Japan 's past militarism .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN TO DT NNP NN NN VBN IN NNS IN DT NN IN NNP POS JJ NN .
"Monday 's visit was Mr. Koizumi 's fifth to the war shrine since he became prime minister in April , 2001 .",B-tim O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-per O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,"NNP POS NN VBD NNP NNP POS NN TO DT NN NN IN PRP VBD JJ NN IN NNP , CD ."
"The shrine in central Tokyo honors 2.5 million Japanese war dead , including convicted war criminals executed by the Allies after World War Two .",O O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN JJ NNP NNS CD CD JJ NN NN , VBG VBN NN NNS VBN IN DT NNS IN NNP NNP CD ."
Mr. Koizumi was driven to the shrine where he bowed in silence without entering and made a donation before leaving .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD VBN TO DT NN WRB PRP VBD IN NN IN VBG CC VBD DT NN IN VBG .
"China , South Korea and other victims of Japanese aggression have protested the visits saying they pay homage to Japan 's wartime past .",B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"NNP , NNP NNP CC JJ NNS IN JJ NN VBP VBN DT NNS VBG PRP VBP NN TO NNP POS NN NN ."
"Mr. Koizumi has said that during his visits to the shrine , he prays for peace and prosperity in Japan .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN IN PRP$ NNS TO DT NN , PRP VBZ IN NN CC NN IN NNP ."
