"China is updating its government-sanctioned school music curriculum , for the first time adding some current pop hits to the old communist standards .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBG PRP$ JJ NN NN NN , IN DT JJ NN VBG DT JJ NNS VBZ TO DT JJ NN NNS ."
"The Shanghai Daily newspaper says this year 's list of 100 approved songs for music classes includes several current pop hits , including two from Taiwanese performers .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"DT NNP NNP NN VBZ DT NN POS NN IN CD VBN NNS IN NN NNS VBZ JJ JJ NN NNS , VBG CD IN JJ NNS ."
"Songs from hip-hop singer Jay Chou ( ' Snail ' ) and singer-actor Andy Lau ( ' Hero ' ) will join old standards such as "" Chairman Mao is with Us Forever "" and other patriotic ballads .",O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O B-org I-org O O O O O O,NNS IN JJ NN NNP NNP LRB LQU NNP RQU RRB CC JJ NNP NNP LRB LQU NNP RQU RRB MD VB JJ NNS JJ IN LQU NNP NNP VBZ IN NNP NNP RQU CC JJ JJ NNS .
The newspaper says that students apparently were bored with the old anthems .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ IN NNS RB VBD VBN IN DT JJ NNS .
"One student quoted by the newspaper said the children are always asked to sing what he called "" monotonous revolutionary songs . """,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CD NN VBN IN DT NN VBD DT NNS VBP RB VBN TO VB WP PRP VBD LQU JJ JJ NNS . RQU
But he said finally they can sing something of their own .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC PRP VBD RB PRP MD VB DT IN PRP$ NN .
