Dutch oil giant Shell says it has resumed normal production at a Nigerian oilfield that was shut down last month after militants took four oil workers hostage .,B-gpe O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN NN NNP VBZ PRP VBZ VBN JJ NN IN DT JJ NN WDT VBD VBN RB JJ NN IN NNS VBD CD NN NNS NN .
"Shell officials say the offshore EA oilfield is back to producing about 115,000 barrels of crude per day .",B-per O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBP DT JJ NNP NN VBZ RB TO VBG IN CD NNS IN NN IN NN .
The hostages were captured from a boat working the field on January 11 .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN VBG DT NN IN NNP CD .
They were freed Monday after spending 19 days in captivity .,O O O B-tim O O B-tim O B-tim I-tim O,PRP VBD VBN NNP IN VBG CD NNS IN NN .
Militants seeking greater local control over oil wealth in southern Nigeria have threatened more attacks on oil workers and facilities in the region .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBG JJR JJ NN IN NN NN IN JJ NNP VBP VBN JJR NNS IN NN NNS CC NNS IN DT NN .
"A string of recent attacks , some of which were deadly , has contributed to a rise in world oil prices .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN JJ NNS , DT IN WDT VBD JJ , VBZ VBN TO DT NN IN NN NN NNS ."
