Seeded players had mixed results Tuesday at the Legg Mason Tennis Classic in Washington .,O O O O O B-tim O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-geo O,VBN NNS VBD VBN NNS NNP IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP IN NNP .
"Tim Henman of Britain , the tournament 's 14th seed , needed three sets to oust American Phillip King , 6-7 , 6-3 , 7-5 , in a second round match .",B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP IN NNP , DT NN POS JJ NN , VBD CD NNS TO VB JJ NNP NNP , CD , CD , CD , IN DT JJ NN NN ."
But the hardcourt event is over for ninth-seeded Paradorn Srichaphan .,O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,CC DT NN NN VBZ IN IN JJ NNP NNP .
"Kenneth Carlsen of Denmark upended his Thai opponent , 4-6 , 7-6 , 6-3 .",B-per I-per O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP IN NNP VBD PRP$ JJ NN , CD , CD , CD ."
"In first round action , American Vince Spadea advanced when Roko Karanusic of Croatia retired while trailing , 7-5 , 1-0 .",O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per O O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"IN JJ NN NN , JJ NNP NNP VBD WRB NNP NNP IN NNP VBD IN VBG , CD , CD ."
"Russian Teimuraz Gabashvili defeated Jean-Christophe Faurel of France , 6-3 , 6-3 .",B-gpe B-per I-per O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP IN NNP , CD , CD ."
"Ramon Delgado of Paraguay beat Australian Peter Luczak , 6-4 , 6-4 .",B-per I-per O B-geo O B-gpe B-per I-per O O O O O,"NNP NNP IN NNP VBD JJ NNP NNP , CD , CD ."
"Edgardo Massa of Argentina ousted Somdev Dev Varman of India , 6-4 , 6-0 .",B-per I-per O B-geo O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O,"NNP NNP IN NNP VBD NNP NNP NNP IN NNP , CD , CD ."
"Tomas Zib of the Czech Republic toppled Jean-Rene Lisnard of France , 7-5 , 6-4 .",B-per I-per O O B-gpe B-geo O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O,"NNP NNP IN DT JJ NNP VBD NNP NNP IN NNP , CD , CD ."
