Israel says Prime Minister Ariel Sharon will turn over his duties to his deputy before undergoing a heart procedure at a Jerusalem hospital on Thursday .,B-geo O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O,NNP VBZ NNP NNP NNP NNP MD VB RP PRP$ NNS TO PRP$ NN IN VBG DT NN NN IN DT NNP NN IN NNP .
"Deputy Ehud Olmert is expected to assume the prime minister 's duties for about three hours , while doctors at Hadassah University Hospital administer general anesthesia to plug a tiny hole in Mr. Sharon 's heart .",O B-per I-per O O O O O B-per O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O,"NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB DT JJ NN POS NNS IN IN CD NNS , IN NNS IN NNP NNP NNP NN JJ NN TO VB DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP POS NN ."
The hole was discovered after the 77-year-old leader suffered a mild stroke December 18 .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT NN VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN VBD DT JJ NN NNP CD .
"Cardiologists say Mr. Sharon did not suffer permanent damage from the stroke , and they say Thursday 's procedure should prevent similar strokes in the future .",O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP NNP NNP VBD RB VB JJ NN IN DT NN , CC PRP VBP NNP POS NN MD VB JJ NNS IN DT NN ."
