The pro-democracy winners of Burma 's 1990 parliamentary elections have asked the United Nations to recognize their representatives at the General Assembly in place of the representatives of the current military regime .,O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNS IN NNP POS CD JJ NNS VBP VBN DT NNP NNPS TO VB PRP$ NNS IN DT NNP NNP IN NN IN DT NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN .
"In a letter Tuesday , the winning candidates challenged the legitimacy of the military government , which never recognized election results that saw a landslide victory for the National League for Democracy led by Aung San Suu Kyi .",O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O,"IN DT NN NNP , DT VBG NNS VBD DT NN IN DT JJ NN , WDT RB VBD NN NNS WDT VBD DT NN NN IN DT NNP NNP IN NN VBN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
The pro-democracy leaders called on all U.N. member states to support their cause .,O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNS VBD IN DT NNP NN NNS TO VB PRP$ NN .
The military has ruled Burma since 1962 and has been widely criticized for suppressing basic freedoms .,O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBN NNP IN CD CC VBZ VBN RB VBN IN VBG JJ NNS .
Pro-democracy leader and Nobel peace laureate Aung San Suu Kyi was detained in July 1989 and has spent 13 of the past 19 years under house arrest .,O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O B-tim I-tim O O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim I-tim O O O O O,NNP NN CC NNP NN NN NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD VBN IN NNP CD CC VBZ VBN CD IN DT JJ CD NNS IN NN NN .
