Zimbabwe says it is appealing a court decision to acquit opposition leader Morgan Tsvangirai of charges of plotting to kill President Robert Mugabe .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O,NNP VBZ PRP VBZ VBG DT NN NN TO VB NN NN NNP NNP IN NNS IN VBG TO VB NNP NNP NNP .
Acting Attorney-General Bharat Patel said the government has filed papers asking the Supreme Court to review the verdict in the treason trial against Mr. Tsvangirai .,O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-per B-geo O,VBG JJ NNP NNP VBD DT NN VBZ VBN NNS VBG DT NNP NNP TO VB DT NN IN DT NN NN IN NNP NNP .
"In October , Zimbabwe 's High Court rejected the case , saying prosecutors had failed to enter evidence showing Mr. Tsvangirai was involved in the alleged plot .",O B-tim O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per B-geo O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , NNP POS NNP NNP VBD DT NN , VBG NNS VBD VBN TO VB NN VBG NNP NNP VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN ."
"The opposition leader has denied the charges , saying the trial was an attempt by the government to silence its critics .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN NN VBZ VBN DT NNS , VBG DT NN VBD DT NN IN DT NN TO VB PRP$ NNS ."
Mr. Tsvangirai also faces treason charges in a separate trial linked to opposition protests last year .,B-per B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP RB VBZ NN NNS IN DT JJ NN VBN TO NN NNS JJ NN .
