A Turkish official says a key protocol with the European Union should be finalized after talks Wednesday between top British and Turkish officials .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O B-tim O O B-gpe O B-gpe O O,DT JJ NN VBZ DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP MD VB VBN IN NNS NNP IN JJ JJ CC JJ NNS .
"Foreign Ministry spokesman Namik Tan did not say when the customs accord will be signed , but EU and Turkish diplomats are quoted as saying it would be in the next days .",B-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NN NNP NNP VBD RB VB WRB DT NNS NN MD VB VBN , CC NNP CC JJ NNS VBP VBN IN VBG PRP MD VB IN DT JJ NNS ."
"Turkish Prime Minister Recep Tayyip Erdogan meets with his British counterpart , Tony Blair , Wednesday in London .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per I-per O O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O B-tim O B-geo O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ IN PRP$ JJ NN , NNP NNP , NNP IN NNP ."
Britain holds the rotating EU presidency .,B-geo O O O B-org O O,NNP VBZ DT VBG NNP NN .
"The accord would extend a Turkish-EU customs union accord to Cyprus , but the Turkish Foreign Ministry spokesman said Ankara would include a declaration saying it does not recognize the Greek Cypriot government .",O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe B-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe I-gpe O O,"DT NN MD VB DT JJ NNS NN NN TO NNP , CC DT JJ NNP NNP NN VBD NNP MD VB DT NN VBG PRP VBZ RB VB DT JJ JJ NN ."
Turkey only recognizes the Turkish enclave in northern Cyprus .,B-org O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo O,NNP RB VBZ DT JJ NN IN JJ NNP .
Turkey and the European Union are expected to begin accession talks in October .,B-org O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP CC DT NNP NNP VBP VBN TO VB NN NNS IN NNP .
