The Iraqi Cabinet has approved an agreement with the country 's autonomous Kurdish government to resume oil exports from Kurdish areas .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN DT NN POS JJ JJ NN TO VB NN NNS IN JJ NNS .
Iraq 's central government had objected to the oil exports because authorities in the Kurdish region signed deals with Western oil companies independently .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O,NNP POS JJ NN VBD VBN TO DT NN NNS IN NNS IN DT JJ NN VBD NNS IN JJ NN NNS RB .
Those companies began oil exports last year but stopped a few months later when Baghdad refused to pay them .,O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O,DT NNS VBD NN NNS JJ NN CC VBD DT JJ NNS RB WRB NNP VBD TO VB PRP .
"Under the deal approved Tuesday , the Iraqi government will pay the costs of Western oil companies operating in the self-ruled Kurdish region in northern Iraq .",O O O O B-tim O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"IN DT NN VBN NNP , DT JJ NN MD VB DT NNS IN JJ NN NNS VBG IN DT JJ JJ NN IN JJ NNP ."
Iraqi government spokesman Ali al-Dabbagh says Baghdad has agreed to guarantee the expenses of oil companies in the Kurdish region after auditing them .,B-gpe O O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN NN NNP NNP VBZ NNP VBZ VBN TO VB DT NNS IN NN NNS IN DT JJ NN IN VBG PRP .
It was not immediately clear who will pay the oil companies ' profits or when the oil exports will resume .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD RB RB JJ WP MD VB DT NN NNS POS NNS CC WRB DT NN NNS MD VB .
