China and Russia top the latest U.S. list of countries that are havens for the illegal copying and distribution of the intellectual property of U.S. businesses .,B-geo O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,NNP CC NNP VBP DT JJS NNP NN IN NNS WDT VBP NNS IN DT JJ NN CC NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNS .
"The Office of the U.S. Trade Representative released an annual report Friday that noted China 's efforts to curb the piracy of intellectual property , but said enforcement continues to lag far behind the promises made by top Chinese officials .",O B-org O O B-geo O O O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"DT NNP IN DT NNP NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN NNP IN VBD NNP POS NNS TO VB DT NN IN JJ NN , CC VBD NN VBZ TO VB RB IN DT NNS VBN IN JJ JJ NNS ."
The report also called Russia a serious pirating concern .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O,DT NN RB VBD NNP DT JJ NN NN .
"While Moscow has shut down some CD and DVD factories , particularly on government-owned land , the report said high levels of infringement remain .",O B-geo O O O O B-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP VBZ VBN RP DT NN CC NNP NNS , RB IN JJ NN , DT NN VBD JJ NNS IN NN VBP ."
"In addition to China and Russia , the 11 other countries topping the trade commission list were Argentina , Belize , Brazil , Egypt , India , Indonesia , Israel , Lebanon , Turkey , Ukraine and Venezuela .",O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O,"IN NN TO NNP CC NNP , DT CD JJ NNS VBG DT NN NN NN VBD NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP CC NNP ."
