"The bestselling book Midnight in the Garden of Good and Evil is based on a true story of murder in the southern city of Savannah , Georgia .",O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,"DT VBG NN NN IN DT NNP IN NNP CC NNP VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , NNP ."
"Hollywood turned it into a movie - making the crime 's location , a historic building known as Mercer House , a major tourist attraction .",B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O,"NNP VBD PRP IN DT NN IN VBG DT NN POS NN , DT JJ NN VBN IN NNP NNP , DT JJ NN NN ."
