Hard-line Hindus are warning couples not to take foreign celebrations of Valentine 's day too seriously because it corrupts traditional values .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBG NNS RB TO VB JJ NNS IN NNP POS NN RB RB IN PRP VBZ JJ NNS .
"Various Hindu nationalist groups warned people to stay indoors Tuesday , saying they would confront young couples showing affection in public and variously threatened to beat them , show their pictures to parents or force them to get married .",O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NN NNS VBD NNS TO VB NNS NNP , VBG PRP MD VB JJ NNS VBG NN IN JJ CC RB VBD TO VB PRP , VBP PRP$ NNS TO NNS CC VB PRP TO VB VBN ."
"In the past , Hindu nationalists have accosted young couples and vandalized shops selling Valentine 's Day cards and gifts .",O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O,"IN DT NN , NNP NNS VBP VBN JJ NNS CC VBN NNS VBG NNP POS NNP NNS CC NNS ."
Police say Muslim groups also have objected to the growing popularity of Valentine 's Day .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O,NNS VBP NN NNS RB VBP VBN TO DT VBG NN IN NNP POS NNP .
"Last week , more than 20 black-veiled Muslim women stormed gift and stationery shops in Indian Kashmir , burning Valentine 's Day cards to protest what they called the imposition of Western values on Muslim youth .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O,"JJ NN , JJR IN CD JJ NN NNS VBD NN CC NN NNS IN NNP NNP , VBG NNP POS NN NNS TO VB WP PRP VBD DT NN IN JJ NNS IN NNP NN ."
