Iraqi officials say eight people were killed when armed robbers raided a marketplace in a Shi'ite neighborhood of Baghdad .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNS VBP CD NNS VBD VBN WRB JJ NNS VBD DT NN IN DT NNP NN IN NNP .
Police say mortar shells or rockets exploded in the popular market in the Shula district before gunmen stormed the market 's gold and jewelry shops .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP NN NNS CC NNS VBD IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NN IN NNS VBD DT NN POS NN CC NN NNS .
The gunmen escaped with the merchants ' wares .,O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBD IN DT NNS POS NNS .
Eight people were killed and at least 14 wounded in the assault that accompanied the heist .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CD NNS VBD VBN CC IN JJS CD VBN IN DT NN WDT VBD DT NN .
"Sectarian violence has declined in Iraq , but crime and lawlessness continue to plague the country .",O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN VBZ VBN IN NNP , CC NN CC NN VBP TO VB DT NN ."
Wednesday 's assault comes one day after a suicide bomber killed eight people at a cafe in a predominantly Sunni town of Buhriz north of Baghdad .,B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O,NNP POS NN VBZ CD NN IN DT NN NN VBD CD NNS IN DT NN IN DT RB JJ NN IN NNP NN IN NNP .
"The casualties included Leith Mishaan , the leader of a Sunni militia that had turned against al-Qaida .",O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,"DT NNS VBD NNP NNP , DT NN IN DT NNP NN WDT VBD VBN IN NNP ."
