"Iran 's foreign minister says he remains hopeful that talks with the European Union on Tehran 's nuclear program will lead to what he calls a "" very fruitful agreement . """,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS JJ NN VBZ PRP VBZ JJ IN NNS IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP POS JJ NN MD VB TO WP PRP VBZ DT LQU RB JJ NN . LQU
"Iranian Foreign Minister Kamal Kharrazi made his remarks Tuesday after conferring with Hungarian officials in the capital , Budapest .",B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD PRP$ NNS NNP IN VBG IN JJ NNS IN DT NN , NNP ."
"EU officials have been trying to persuade Iran to give up its uranium enrichment program in exchange for economic incentives , and help in obtaining a light-water reactor , which can only be used for energy production .",B-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNS VBP VBN VBG TO VB NNP TO VB RP PRP$ NN NN NN IN NN IN JJ NNS , CC NN IN VBG DT NN NN , WDT MD RB VB VBN IN NN NN ."
The United States accuses Iran of secretly working to develop nuclear weapons .,O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNPS VBZ NNP IN RB VBG TO VB JJ NNS .
"Tehran strongly denies the allegation , insisting its nuclear program is only for making electricity .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP RB VBZ DT NN , VBG PRP$ JJ NN VBZ RB IN VBG NN ."
"On Sunday , an Iranian foreign ministry spokesman Hamid Reza Asefi said Iran will not , under any circumstances , halt its plans to build a heavy-water reactor .",O B-tim O O B-gpe O O O B-per I-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , DT JJ JJ NN NN NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP MD RB , IN DT NNS , VB PRP$ NNS TO VB DT NN NN ."
