The president of Malawi has pardoned a gay couple sentenced to 14 years in prison .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN VBN TO CD NNS IN NN .
President Bingu wa Mutharika said Saturday that he was ordering the release of the men on humanitarian grounds .,B-per I-per I-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP IN PRP VBD VBG DT NN IN DT NNS IN JJ NNS .
He made the announcement after meeting with United Nations Secretary-General Ban Ki-moon .,O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,PRP VBD DT NN IN NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP .
"Last week , a court sentenced Steven Monjeza , 26 , and Tiwonge Chimbalanga , 20 , to 14 years of hard labor for sodomy and indecency .",O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN , DT NN VBN NNP NNP , CD , CC NNP NNP , CD , TO CD NNS IN JJ NN IN NN CC NN ."
The couple was arrested in December after holding a symbolic engagement ceremony .,O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD VBN IN NNP IN VBG DT JJ NN NN .
"U.S. officials said the United States was "" appalled "" by the sentence .",B-geo O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBD DT NNP NNPS VBD RQU VBN LQU IN DT NN .
A White House spokesman said the case marred Malawi 's human rights record .,O B-org I-org O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NN VBD DT NN VBD NNP POS JJ NNS NN .
Homosexuality is illegal in Malawi and many other African countries .,O O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O,NN VBZ JJ IN NNP CC JJ JJ JJ NNS .
The laws have triggered outrage and concern among Western nations and human rights groups .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP VBN NN CC NN IN JJ NNS CC JJ NNS NNS .
