Pakistani security forces say at least 25 militants and three soldiers have died in the latest round of fighting in a northwestern tribal region near Afghanistan .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NN NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS CC CD NNS VBP VBN IN DT JJS NN IN VBG IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP .
Military officials said Saturday the militants were killed in battles that broke out Friday in the Bajaur region in the Loi Sam and Rashakai areas .,O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O,NN NNS VBD NNP DT NNS VBD VBN IN NNS WDT VBD RP NNP IN DT NNP NN IN DT NNP NNP CC NNP NNS .
They say at least two of the soldiers killed were officers .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBP IN JJS CD IN DT NNS VBN VBD NNS .
Bajaur is a key battleground in Pakistan 's effort to drive out militants believed to be responsible for deadly attacks inside Pakistan and on neighboring Afghanistan .,B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O,NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN NNP POS NN TO VB RP NNS VBN TO VB JJ IN JJ NNS IN NNP CC IN VBG NNP .
"The military says it has killed at least 1,000 Taliban and al-Qaida militants in the past month .",O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-org O O O B-tim O O,DT JJ VBZ PRP VBZ VBN IN JJS CD NNP CC NNP NNS IN DT JJ NN .
More than 60 soldiers have died in the operation .,O O O O O O O O B-tim O,JJR IN CD NNS VBP VBN IN DT NN .
"Pakistan is recovering from a massive suicide car bombing that killed 53 people in the capital , Islamabad , last week .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBG IN DT JJ NN NN NN WDT VBD CD NNS IN DT NN , NNP , JJ NN ."
The explosion gutted a luxury ( Marriott ) hotel and seriously shook the people 's confidence in their security .,O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD DT NN LRB NNP RRB NN CC RB VBD DT NNS POS NN IN PRP$ NN .
