Colombia 's government says it is prepared to withdraw military forces from around a small mountain town to negotiate with the country 's largest Marxist rebel group about a possible deal to free dozens of hostages .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NN VBZ PRP VBZ VBN TO VB JJ NNS IN IN DT JJ NN NN TO VB IN DT NN POS JJS JJ NN NN IN DT JJ NN TO JJ NNS IN NNS .
"President Alvaro Uribe said Tuesday his government accepted the proposal by a commission comprising France , Spain and Switzerland .",B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O,"NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP PRP$ NN VBD DT NN IN DT NN VBG NNP , NNP CC NNP ."
"But there was no immediate word on whether the rebels , known as the FARC , has accepted .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O,"CC EX VBD DT JJ NN IN IN DT NNS , VBN IN DT NNP , VBZ VBN ."
"The plan calls for the government to pull troops from a 180-kilometer radius surrounding El~Retiro ( in the southern province of Valle del Cauca ) and for the area to be free of FARC rebels , except for guerrilla negotiators .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ IN DT NN TO VB NNS IN DT JJ NN VBG NNP LRB IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP NNP RRB CC IN DT NN TO VB JJ IN NNP NNS , IN IN NN NNS ."
It calls for the area to be demilitarized seven days before and after talks .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ IN DT NN TO VB VBN CD NNS IN CC IN NNS .
"The FARC wants to exchange dozens of hostages - who include politicians , military personnel and three Americans - for imprisoned guerrillas .",O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,"DT NNP VBZ TO VB NNS IN NNS : WP VBP NNS , JJ NNS CC CD NNS : IN JJ NNS ."
