OPEC has decided it wo n't increase its crude oil output despite record high oil prices .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN PRP MD RB VB PRP$ JJ NN NN IN JJ JJ NN NNS .
Saudi Oil Minister Ali Al-Naimi said the reason for high prices is not from a shortage of supply and that the market determines the oil price .,O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN JJ NNS VBZ RB IN DT NN IN NN CC IN DT NN VBZ DT NN NN .
Rising tensions between the U.S. and Iran are also influencing the high prices .,O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O,VBG NNS IN DT NNP CC NNP VBP RB VBG DT JJ NNS .
"OPEC president Edmund Daukoru , who is also Nigeria 's oil minister , said the market remains volatile with prices being driven more by geopolitical uncertainties and speculation than by supply-demand fundamentals .",B-geo O B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NN NNP NNP , WP VBZ RB NNP POS NN NN , VBD DT NN VBZ JJ IN NNS VBG VBN RBR IN JJ NNS CC NN IN IN JJ NNS ."
U.S. Energy Secretary Samuel Bodman said high oil prices are causing great pain to the United States and global economies .,B-geo O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD JJ NN NNS VBP VBG JJ NN TO DT NNP NNPS CC JJ NNS .
He called for more security at energy facilities around the world to avoid any potentially catastrophic supply disruptions .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD IN JJR NN IN NN NNS IN DT NN TO VB DT RB JJ NN NNS .
The three-day forum officially opened Sunday .,O B-tim O O O B-tim O,DT JJ NN RB VBD NNP .
It brings together ministers and representatives from 58 countries in order to foster dialogue between producer nations and consumers .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ RB NNS CC NNS IN CD NNS IN NN TO VB NN IN NN NNS CC NNS .
