Syrian officials say the government is considering a formal U.N. request to question six Syrian officers in connection with the killing of former Lebanese Prime Minister Rafik Hariri .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O,JJ NNS VBP DT NN VBZ VBG DT JJ NNP NN TO VB CD JJ NNS IN NN IN DT NN IN JJ JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP .
"Officials say the request from chief U.N. investigator , German Prosecutor Detlev Mehlis , was handed over to the Syrian Foreign Ministry Sunday .",O O O O O O B-geo O O B-gpe B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-gpe B-org I-org B-tim O,"NNS VBP DT NN IN JJ NNP NN , JJ NNP NNP NNP , VBD VBN IN TO DT JJ NNP NNP NNP ."
"The officials did not identify the six wanted for questioning , or say if the United Nations wanted to conduct the questioning in Syria or outside .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O,"DT NNS VBD RB VB DT CD VBN IN VBG , CC VB IN DT NNP NNPS VBD TO VB DT VBG IN NNP CC JJ ."
