A group calling itself al-Qaida in Iraq has ridiculed this week 's terrorism conference in Spain marking the first anniversary of the bombing of Madrid trains that killed nearly 200 people and wounded more than 1000 .,O O O O B-org O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NN VBG PRP NNP IN NNP VBZ VBN DT NN POS NN NN IN NNP VBG DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNS WDT VBD RB CD NNS CC VBD JJR IN CD .
A message posted on a web site used by Islamists describes the international officials and experts who met in Madrid as ' infidels ' who will never be victorious .,O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBN IN DT NN NN VBN IN NNS VBZ DT JJ NNS CC NNS WP VBD IN NNP IN LQU NNS RQU WP MD RB VB JJ .
"At the conference , which concluded Friday , U.N. Secretary-General Kofi Annan said the world must move quickly to prevent terrorists from getting access to nuclear weapons .",O O O O O O B-tim O B-org B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN , WDT VBD NNP , NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN MD VB RB TO VB NNS IN VBG NN TO JJ NNS ."
"Spain observed five minutes of silence Friday to remember the March 11 , 2004 coordinated bombings of four Madrid trains , which killed 191 people .",B-gpe O O O O O B-tim O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD CD NNS IN NN NNP TO VB DT NNP CD , CD VBD NNS IN CD NNP NNS , WDT VBD CD NNS ."
