Burma 's military government says talks aimed at completing a draft constitution will resume in October .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP POS JJ NN VBZ NNS VBN IN VBG DT NN NN MD VB IN NNP .
The chairman of the National Convention ( Lieutenant General Thein Sein ) announced Saturday that the next meeting of the constitutional convention will take place the second week of October .,O O O O B-eve I-eve O O B-per I-per I-per O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-tim I-tim O,DT NN IN DT NNP NNP LRB NNP NNP NNP NNP RRB VBD NNP IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN MD VB NN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
Officials said after earlier talks that the draft was about 75-percent complete .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBD IN RB NNS IN DT NN VBD IN JJ JJ .
Burma 's military leadership crushed a pro-democracy movement in 1988 and has refused to recognize an election victory by the opposition National League for Democracy .,B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,NNP POS JJ NN VBN DT JJ NN IN CD CC VBZ VBN TO VB DT NN NN IN DT NN NNP NNP IN NNP .
"That group refuses to take part in the constitutional talks , because its leader , Aung San Suu Kyi , is barred from participating .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo B-per I-per O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ TO VB NN IN DT JJ NNS , IN PRP$ NN , NNP NNP NNP NNP , VBZ VBN IN VBG ."
Aung San Suu Kyi has been under house arrest or imprisoned for much of the last 20 years .,B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NN NN CC VBN IN NN IN DT JJ CD NNS .
