A key figure in South Africa 's mediation efforts in Ivory Coast says elections set for next month in the war-divided nation are unlikely .,O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP POS NN NNS IN NNP NNP VBZ NNS VBN IN JJ NN IN DT JJ NN VBP JJ .
South African Defense Minister Mosiuoa Lekota said Thursday it is possible to postpone the October 30 elections until November .,B-geo O O B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O B-tim O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP PRP VBZ JJ TO VB DT NNP CD NNS IN NNP .
But he added there is no reason elections can not be held by the end of the year .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O,CC PRP VBD EX VBZ DT NN NNS MD RB VB VBN IN DT NN IN DT NN .
United Nations Secretary-General Kofi Annan has said it will be impossible to hold the October elections .,B-org I-org I-org B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP MD VB JJ TO VB DT NNP NNS .
He said Ivorian leaders have not cooperated and have not taken the necessary steps ahead of the polls .,O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD JJ NNS VBP RB VBN CC VBP RB VBN DT JJ NNS RB IN DT NNS .
Efforts to hold the elections have been plagued by problems .,O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS TO VB DT NNS VBP VBN VBN IN NNS .
"Ivory Coast rebels have rejected the polls , claiming conditions are not in place for a free vote .",B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNS VBP VBN DT NNS , VBG NNS VBP RB IN NN IN DT JJ NN ."
