U.S. legislators and North Korean activists have recounted stories of injustice they said China has inflicted on refugees .,B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,NNP NNS CC JJ JJ NNS VBP VBN NNS IN NN PRP VBD NNP VBZ VBN IN NNS .
"At a news conference in Washington , the group called on world leaders to boycott the 2008 Olympics opening ceremonies .",O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O,"IN DT NN NN IN NNP , DT NN VBD IN NN NNS TO VB DT CD NNPS VBG NNS ."
"They accused China of a "" record of shame "" in its treatment of North Korean defectors who tried to flee repression .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,PRP VBD NNP IN DT RQU NN IN NN RQU IN PRP$ NN IN JJ JJ NNS WP VBD TO VB NN .
VOA 's Carolyn Presutti has our story from the perspective of a defector .,B-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NNP NNP VBZ PRP$ NN IN DT NN IN DT NN .
