"During the search , a gun battle erupted and several suspected militants died .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN , DT NN NN VBD CC JJ JJ NNS VBD ."
"Helmand province , one of the world 's top opium growing regions , has been badly affected by a renewed Taliban insurgency .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O,"NNP NN , CD IN DT NN POS JJ NN VBG NNS , VBZ VBN RB VBN IN DT VBN NNP NN ."
"Also Tuesday , the Afghan government defended its decision to expel two top European diplomats , saying they will not be allowed to return .",O B-tim O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB NNP , DT JJ NN VBD PRP$ NN TO VB CD JJ JJ NNS , VBG PRP MD RB VB VBN TO VB ."
"The pair were forced to leave Afghanistan last week , after being accused of threatening the nation 's security for holding unauthorized talks with Taliban rebels .",O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O,"DT NN VBD VBN TO VB NNP JJ NN , IN VBG VBN IN VBG DT NN POS NN IN VBG JJ NNS IN NNP NNS ."
