Witnesses in Somalia say the brother of the country 's deputy prime minister has been shot dead by government forces .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNP VBP DT NN IN DT NN POS JJ JJ NN VBZ VBN VBN JJ IN NN NNS .
"The witnesses say the brother , Abukar Abdisalam , was talking on a mobile phone outside his home in the capital , Mogadishu , when government troops became suspicious , chased him and shot him .",O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS VBP DT NN , NNP NNP , VBD VBG IN DT JJ NN IN PRP$ NN IN DT NN , NNP , WRB NN NNS VBD JJ , VBD PRP CC VBD PRP ."
"Abdisalam is a brother of Ahmed Abdisalam Adan , who is also the country 's information minister .",B-per O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP , WP VBZ RB DT NN POS NN NN ."
The motive for the shooting is unclear .,O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN DT NN VBZ JJ .
