Israel says it has halted fuel deliveries to the Gaza Strip after a mortar shell fired by Palestinian militants hit the territory 's main fuel distribution center .,B-geo O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ PRP VBZ VBN NN NNS TO DT NNP NNP IN DT NN NN VBN IN JJ NNS VBD DT NN POS JJ NN NN NN .
"Israeli and Palestinian officials say the attack Wednesday prompted Israel to close the border and suspend the transfer of all types of fuel , including supplies for the coastal strip 's main power plant .",B-gpe O B-gpe O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ CC JJ NNS VBP DT NN NNP VBD NNP TO VB DT NN CC VB DT NN IN DT NNS IN NN , VBG NNS IN DT JJ NN POS JJ NN NN ."
Palestinian medics say the mortar shell wounded a Palestinian employee at the Nahal Oz fuel terminal in Gaza .,B-gpe O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org O O O B-geo O,JJ NNS VBP DT NN NN VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP NN NN IN NNP .
Militants loyal to Hamas have been firing rockets into Israel since the radical group took over the Gaza Strip last June .,O O O B-org O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-tim O,NNS JJ TO NNP VBP VBN VBG NNS IN NNP IN DT JJ NN VBD RP DT NNP NNP JJ NNP .
"Israel has imposed a strict blockade on Gaza , reducing fuel and supplies to residents in the impoverished territory .",B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN NNP , VBG NN CC NNS TO NNS IN DT JJ NN ."
