"Trucks with the remains of 465 Bosnian massacre victims have rolled through Sarajevo on the way to ceremonies near Srebrenica Wednesday , the 12th anniversary of the killings .",O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O B-tim O,"NNS IN DT NNS IN CD JJ NN NNS VBP VBN IN NNP IN DT NN TO NNS IN NNP NNP , DT JJ NN IN DT NNS ."
"The victims , newly identified through DNA analysis , will be buried at the Potocari memorial alongside 2,400 victims already interred there .",O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS , RB VBN IN NNP NN , MD VB VBN IN DT NNP JJ NN CD NNS RB VBD RB ."
"About 1,000 police officers are being sent to keep order at Wednesday 's ceremonies , which up to 30,000 people are expected to attend .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN CD NN NNS VBP VBG VBN TO VB NN IN NNP POS NNS , WDT RB TO CD NNS VBP VBN TO VB ."
"They are expected to include chief United Nations war crimes prosecutor Carla del Ponte , who is currently visiting the Balkans .",O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O,"PRP VBP VBN TO VB JJ NNP NNP NN NNS NN NNP NNP NNP , WP VBZ RB VBG DT NNPS ."
The massacre is considered the worst in Europe since World War II .,O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-eve O,DT NN VBZ VBN DT JJS IN NNP IN NNP NNP NNP .
