The U.S. House of Representatives has approved a $ 3.4 trillion budget outline without a single vote of support from Republicans .,O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP IN NNP VBZ VBN DT $ CD CD NN NN IN DT JJ NN IN NN IN NNPS .
The House passed the resolution Wednesday by a vote of 233 to 193 .,O B-org O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NNP VBD DT NN NNP IN DT NN IN CD TO CD .
"The measure now moves on to the Democratic-controlled Senate , where it is expected to pass .",O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O,"DT NN RB VBZ IN TO DT JJ NNP , WRB PRP VBZ VBN TO VB ."
The non-binding budget resolution is the lawmakers ' response to President Barack Obama 's $ 3.6 trillion budget proposal released in February .,O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT JJ NN NN VBZ DT NNS POS NN TO NNP NNP NNP POS $ CD CD NN NN VBN IN NNP .
Lawmakers will use this resolution as an outline for actual spending legislation later this year .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,NNS MD VB DT NN IN DT NN IN JJ NN NN RB DT NN .
Opposition Republican lawmakers in both chambers accused Democrats of approving a budget that they say will hurt the economy in the long-run and saddle future generations with too much debt .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNS IN DT NNS VBD NNS IN VBG DT NN IN PRP VBP MD VB DT NN IN DT JJ CC JJ JJ NNS IN RB JJ NN .
"The budget outline will help Mr. Obama pursue his ambitious agenda , including promoting energy independence , clean energy , a more competitive education system and health care reform .",O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN NN MD VB NNP NNP VB PRP$ JJ NN , VBG VBG NN NN , JJ NN , DT RBR JJ NN NN CC NN NN NN ."
