Double-amputee sprinter Oscar Pistorius resumes his bid to qualify for the Olympics on Friday at a Golden Gala meet in Rome .,O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O,NN NN NNP NNP VBZ PRP$ NN TO VB IN DT NNS IN NNP IN DT NNP NNP VB IN NNP .
The South African needs to meet an Olympic qualifying time of 45.55 in the 400 meter event .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ TO VB DT NNP VBG NN IN CD IN DT CD NN NN .
"Should he fall short in Rome , he will have one more chance next Wednesday in Lucerne , Switzerland .",O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O B-geo O,"MD PRP VB JJ IN NNP , PRP MD VB CD JJR NN IN NNP IN NNP , NNP ."
"Last week in Milan , Pistorius clocked 47.78 seconds in his first able-bodied race in nearly a year .",O O B-tim I-tim O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN IN NNP , NNP VBD CD NNS IN PRP$ JJ JJ NN IN RB DT NN ."
"Pistorius resumed training only seven weeks ago when the Court of Arbitration for Sport , CAS , ruled that he was eligible to run in Beijing .",B-per O O O B-tim O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP VBD NN RB CD NNS RB WRB DT NNP IN NNP IN NNP , NNP , VBD IN PRP VBD JJ TO VB IN NNP ."
The CAS overturned a decision by the International Association of Athletics Federations that Pistorius ' carbon fiber prosthetic racing blades gave him an unfair advantage against able-bodied runners .,O B-org O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP VBD DT NN IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP NNS IN NNP POS NN NN JJ NN NNS VBD PRP DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS .
