The World Health Organization says Egypt has confirmed its first human bird flu death .,O B-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNP VBZ VBN PRP$ JJ JJ NN NN NN .
The Egyptian health ministry says a 30-year-old woman near Cairo died last Friday after coming in contact with diseased poultry .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN NN VBZ DT JJ NN IN NNP VBD JJ NNP IN VBG IN NN IN JJ NN .
"If confirmed by the WHO , she would be the 99th human death from bird flu since 2003 .",O O O O B-org O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"IN VBN IN DT NNP , PRP MD VB DT JJ JJ NN IN NN NN IN CD ."
Most of the deaths have come in Asia .,O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJS IN DT NNS VBP VBN IN NNP .
"Monday , the Bush administration warned that the United States is likely to see its first case in wild birds this year .",B-tim O O B-geo O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP , DT NNP NN VBD IN DT NNP NNPS VBZ JJ TO VB PRP$ JJ NN IN JJ NNS DT NN ."
"Officials with the U.S. Interior and Agriculture Departments say they plan to collect samples from as many as 100,000 live and dead wild birds to monitor the virus .",O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN DT NNP NNP CC NNP NNS VBP PRP VBP TO VB NNS IN RB JJ IN CD JJ CC JJ JJ NNS TO VB DT NN .
Officials say they will focus on migration routes through Alaska and Pacific Ocean islands .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O,NNS VBP PRP MD VB IN NN NNS IN NNP CC NNP NNP NNS .
