Yemen has blamed al-Qaida for the bombing of an oil pipeline Saturday in the eastern part of the country .,B-gpe O O B-org O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN NNP IN DT NN IN DT NN NN NNP IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN .
The Yemeni defense ministry said Monday the militants who blew up the pipeline in Maarib Province included Yemenis and at least two Saudis .,O B-gpe O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-gpe O O O O B-gpe O,DT JJ NN NN VBD NNP DT NNS WP VBD RP DT NN IN NNP NNP VBD NNS CC IN JJS CD NNS .
The bombing followed raids targeting al-Qaida sympathizers .,O O O O O B-org O O,DT NN VBD NNS VBG NNP NNS .
Yemen intensified its campaign against al-Qaida after the group 's local branch -- al-Qaida in the Arabian Peninsula -- claimed responsibility for the failed bombing of a US-bound airliner on Christmas Day .,B-gpe O O O O B-org O O O O O O O B-org O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,NNP VBD PRP$ NN IN NNP IN DT NN POS JJ NN : NNP IN DT NNP NNP : VBD NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP .
"On Saturday , Yemeni officials said suspected al-Qaida members killed a senior army officer and at least one other person in Maarib .",O B-tim O B-gpe O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"IN NNP , JJ NNS VBD JJ NNP NNS VBD DT JJ NN NN CC IN JJS CD JJ NN IN NNP ."
