Australian Prime Minister John Howard says his government will send an extra 150 soldiers to Afghanistan to protect an Australian reconstruction team that will arrive in the country next month .,B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP$ NN MD VB DT JJ CD NNS TO NNP TO VB DT JJ NN NN WDT MD VB IN DT NN JJ NN .
Mr. Howard told parliament Wednesday the additional troops are necessary because of escalating violence in southern and central Afghanistan .,B-per I-per O B-org B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP VBD NN NNP DT JJ NNS VBP JJ IN IN VBG NN IN JJ CC JJ NNP .
"The reinforcements will protect a team of 240 Australian reconstruction workers , due to join a Dutch-led humanitarian project in the southern Afghan province of Uruzgan .",O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O,"DT NNS MD VB DT NN IN CD JJ NN NNS , JJ TO VB DT JJ JJ NN IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP ."
The Australian military will also send more armored vehicles to Afghanistan as part of the extra troop deployment .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN MD RB VB RBR JJ NNS TO NNP IN NN IN DT JJ NN NN .
"Australia already has more than 300 troops in Afghanistan , including 190 special forces and two Chinook helicopters .",B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP RB VBZ JJR IN CD NNS IN NNP , VBG CD JJ NNS CC CD NNP NNS ."
"Spokesman for Australia 's opposition Labor Party , Kevin Rudd , expressed deep concern about the safety of Australian forces in Afghanistan , saying the country remains a center of terrorist activity .",O O B-geo O O B-tim I-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP IN NNP POS NN NNP NNP , NNP NNP , VBD JJ NN IN DT NN IN JJ NNS IN NNP , VBG DT NN VBZ DT NN IN JJ NN ."
Canberra announced plans to send the reconstruction team to Afghanistan in May .,B-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O,NNP VBD NNS TO VB DT NN NN TO NNP IN NNP .
