Syria says security forces have killed a Muslim extremist and arrested dozens of others trying to illegally cross into neighboring Lebanon .,B-geo O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP VBZ NN NNS VBP VBN DT NNP NN CC VBN NNS IN NNS VBG TO RB VB IN JJ NNP .
Syria 's official news agency ( SANA ) says the clash erupted after the militant opened fire on a Syrian border patrol .,B-geo O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O,NNP POS JJ NN NN LRB NNP RRB VBZ DT NN VBD IN DT NN VBD NN IN DT JJ NN NN .
Two soldiers were killed in the clash .,O O O O O O O O,CD NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN .
"The report did not say when or where the incident occurred , and only identified the dead militant by the initials MZ .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD RB VB WRB CC WRB DT NN VBD , CC RB VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NNS NNP ."
The news agency says 34 extremists of various nationalities were arrested following the clash .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN NN VBZ CD NNS IN JJ NNS VBD VBN VBG DT NN .
"Security forces reportedly later found passports , identity cards and other forged documents in an isolated house near the border allegedly used by the group .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NN NNS RB RB VBD NNS , NN NNS CC JJ VBN NNS IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN RB VBN IN DT NN ."
Syria has been under intense pressure to crack down on suspected militants who the United States and Iraq say are using Syrian territory to infiltrate Iraq to fight coalition forces .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN IN JJ NN TO VB RP IN JJ NNS WP DT NNP NNPS CC NNP VBP VBP VBG JJ NN TO VB NNP TO VB NN NNS .
