Protesters in the Israeli town of Nazareth have taken to the streets for a second day to protest an incident in which a Jewish man and his family detonated firecrackers in a Christian shrine .,O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NNP VBP VBN TO DT NNS IN DT JJ NN TO VB DT NN IN WDT DT JJ NN CC PRP$ NN VBD NNS IN DT JJ NN .
"Hundreds of people peacefully marched through the town Saturday , accusing Israeli authorities of not doing enough to protect holy sites of all faiths .",O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN NNS RB VBD IN DT NN NNP , VBG JJ NNS IN RB VBG RB TO VB JJ NNS IN DT NNS ."
Friday 's incident triggered panic in the Basilica of the Annunciation and rioting by local residents outside the church .,B-tim O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NN VBD NN IN DT NNP IN DT NN CC NN IN JJ NNS IN DT NN .
"Authorities say at least 12 people were injured in the melee , before order was restored .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN , IN NN VBD VBN ."
"Israeli police said the man has a history of mental illness , and had previously threatened to attack other churches in Israel .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"JJ NN VBD DT NN VBZ DT NN IN JJ NN , CC VBD RB VBN TO VB JJ NNS IN NNP ."
"The Basilica is built at the site of the Annunciation , where Christians believe the archangel Gabriel told the Virgin Mary she had been chosen by God to bear His son , Jesus .",O B-geo O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-per O O B-org I-org O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-per O,"DT NNP VBZ VBN IN DT NN IN DT NN , WRB NNS VBP DT NN NNP VBD DT NN NNP PRP VBD VBN VBN IN NNP TO VB PRP$ NN , NNP ."
