Tens of thousands of supporters of an anti-U.S. Shi'ite cleric have rallied in Baghdad to protest the U.S. military presence six years after American forces captured the Iraqi capital .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O,NNS IN NNS IN NNS IN DT JJ NNP NNS VBP VBN IN NNP TO VB DT NNP JJ NN CD NNS IN JJ NNS VBD DT JJ NN .
"Backers of cleric Moqtada al-Sadr gathered Thursday at Firdous Square , where Saddam Hussein 's statue was toppled on April 9 , 2003 .",O O O B-per I-per O B-tim O B-org I-org O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,"NNS IN NN NNP NNP VBD NNP IN NNP NNP , WRB NNP NNP POS NN VBD VBN IN NNP CD , CD ."
"An aide to al-Sadr relayed a message from the cleric , believed to be in Iran , describing the U.S. presence in Iraq as a "" crime against all Iraqis . """,O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"DT NN TO NNP VBD DT NN IN DT NN , VBN TO VB IN NNP , VBG DT NNP NN IN NNP IN DT LQU NN IN DT NNS . LQU"
"The protest was in marked contrast to the jubilation on the square six years ago , when Iraqis cheered as U.S. Marines pulled Saddam 's statue down .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo I-geo O B-per O O O O,"DT NN VBD IN JJ NN TO DT NN IN DT JJ CD NNS RB , WRB NNS VBD IN NNP NNPS VBD NNP POS NN RB ."
The U.S. military is scheduled to withdraw from Iraq in 2011 .,O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O,DT NNP NN VBZ VBN TO VB IN NNP IN CD .
