"Meantime , China 's total foreign trade , both exports and imports , fell 13.9 percent in 2009 Chinese officials say the country 's exports surged in December to edge out Germany as the world 's biggest exporter .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"RB , NNP POS JJ JJ NN , DT NNS CC NNS , VBD CD NN IN CD JJ NNS VBP DT NN POS NNS VBD IN NNP TO VB RP NNP IN DT NN POS JJS NN ."
The official Xinhua news agency reported Sunday that figures from the General Administration for Customs showed that exports jumped 17.7 percent in December from a year earlier .,O O B-org O O O B-tim O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O,DT JJ NNP NN NN VBD NNP IN NNS IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP VBD IN NNS VBD CD NN IN NNP IN DT NN RBR .
"Huang Guohua , a statistics official with the customs administration , said the December exports rebound was an important turning point for China 's export sector .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"NNP NNP , DT NNS NN IN DT NNS NN , VBD DT NNP NNS NN VBD DT JJ NN NN IN NNP POS NN NN ."
Huang added that the jump was an indication that exporters have emerged from their downslide .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD IN DT NN VBD DT NN IN NNS VBP VBN IN PRP$ NN .
"However , although China overtook Germany in exports , China 's total foreign trade -- both exports and imports -- fell 13.9 percent in 2009 .",O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"RB , IN NNP VBD NNP IN NNS , NNP POS JJ JJ NN IN DT NNS CC NNS : VBD CD NN IN CD ."
