Chinese officials say police have shot and killed two Muslim Uighurs and injured another in renewed violence in northwestern Xinjiang province .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,JJ NNS VBP NNS VBP VBN CC VBN CD NNP NNPS CC VBD DT IN VBN NN IN JJ NNP NN .
The state-run Xinhua news agency says police opened fire Monday to stop the three from attacking another Uighur with clubs and knives .,O O B-org O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNP NN NN VBZ NNS VBD NN NNP TO VB DT CD IN VBG DT NN IN NNS CC NNS .
Xinhua says the police first fired warning shots .,B-org O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ DT NN RB VBD NN NNS .
The reports have not been independently confirmed .,O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP RB VBN RB VBN .
"The shooting happened in the provincial capital , Urumqi , a little more than a week after bloody clashes broke out there between Uighurs and members of China 's ethnic Han majority .",O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O B-geo O O B-per O O,"DT NN VBD IN DT JJ NN , NNP , DT RB JJR IN DT NN IN JJ NNS VBD IN RB IN NNS CC NNS IN NNP POS JJ NNP NN ."
"The violence left 184 people dead and 1,680 people wounded .",O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD CD NNS JJ CC CD NNS VBN .
"China 's Uighurs complain of religious and cultural persecution , and say an influx of Han in the area is taking away their economic opportunities .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NNS VBP IN JJ CC JJ NN , CC VB DT NN IN NNP IN DT NN VBZ VBG RP PRP$ JJ NNS ."
The Uighurs ' Muslim religion and Turkic language link them more to their Central Asian neighbors than to China 's ethnic Han majority .,O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-per O O,DT NNS POS NN NN CC JJ NN NN PRP RBR TO PRP$ JJ JJ NNS IN TO NNP POS JJ NNP NN .
