The U.S. Justice Department says authorities have arrested 485 people in a major crackdown on mortgage fraud .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNS VBP VBN CD NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NN NN .
"Attorney General Eric Holder said Thursday the suspects in "" Operation Stolen Dreams "" were responsible for $ 2.3 billion in losses .",O B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP DT NNS IN RQU NNP NNP NNP RQU VBD JJ IN $ CD CD IN NNS .
He noted one scheme that targeted the Haitian-American community .,O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD CD NN WDT VBD DT JJ NN .
"He said the defendants would claim to offer immigration and housing assistance , and then use the victims ' personal information to obtain mortgage loans .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD DT NNS MD VB TO VB NN CC NN NN , CC RB VB DT NNS POS JJ NN TO VB NN NNS ."
Holder said these schemes ruin people 's lives and are dangerous to the economy .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD DT NNS VBP NNS POS NNS CC VBP JJ TO DT NN .
The operation was organized after huge losses from home loans in the United States triggered a broader economic crisis .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O,DT NN VBD VBN IN JJ NNS IN NN NNS IN DT NNP NNPS VBD DT JJR JJ NN .
