"Hurricane Beta has made landfall in northeast Nicaragua , pounding the country 's Caribbean coast with strong winds and heavy rain .",O B-eve O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"NN NNP VBZ VBN NN IN NN NNP , VBG DT NN POS JJ NN IN JJ NNS CC JJ NN ."
The U.S. National Hurricane Center says Beta hit land Sunday as a category two storm with sustained winds near 175 kilometers per hour .,O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ NN VBD NN NNP IN DT NN CD NN IN JJ NNS IN CD NNS IN NN .
Forecasters expect Beta to steadily weaken as it moves inland but say it could dump up to 40 centimeters of rain on parts of Nicaragua and eastern Honduras .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O,NNS VBP NN TO RB VB IN PRP VBZ JJ CC VBP PRP MD VB RP TO CD NNS IN NN IN NNS IN NNP CC JJ NNP .
Nicaraguan authorities have moved tens of thousands of people into temporary shelters .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN NNS IN NNS IN NNS IN JJ NNS .
"Honduras has declared a state of emergency , and has begun evacuating more than 100,00 people from areas prone to flooding and mudslides .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN NN , CC VBZ VBN VBG JJR IN CD NNS IN NNS JJ TO NN CC NNS ."
