"The United States has proposed a 10,000 strong U.N. peacekeeping force for southern Sudan to help enforce a January cease-fire agreement that ended two decades of civil war .",O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNPS VBZ VBN DT CD JJ NNP NN NN IN JJ NNP TO VB VB DT NNP NN NN WDT VBD CD NNS IN JJ NN .
The draft Security Council resolution circulated Monday also imposes sanctions on those responsible for the violence in Sudan 's western Darfur region .,O O B-org I-org O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O,DT NN NNP NNP NN VBD NNP RB VBZ NNS IN DT JJ IN DT NN IN NNP POS JJ NNP NN .
It would widen an arms embargo to include the government and also demand Khartoum stop offensive military flights over Darfur .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O,PRP MD VB DT NNS NN TO VB DT NN CC RB VB NNP VB JJ JJ NNS IN NNP .
"The draft avoids the contentious issue of where to try those accused of war crimes committed in Darfur , simply calling for those suspected of atrocities to be brought to justice .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ DT JJ NN IN WRB TO VB DT VBN IN NN NNS VBN IN NNP , RB VBG IN DT VBN IN NNS TO VB VBN TO NN ."
Most Security Council members want to use the existing International Criminal Court in The Hague .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-org I-org O,JJS NNP NNP NNS VBP TO VB DT VBG NNP NNP NNP IN DT NNP .
Washington opposes the court and wants to use an existing tribunal in Tanzania instead .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,NNP VBZ DT NN CC VBZ TO VB DT JJ NN IN NNP RB .
