People in many countries are honoring military veterans Friday .,O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNS IN JJ NNS VBP VBG JJ NNS NNP .
"In the United States , where the holiday is known as Veterans Day , a solemn ceremony was held at Arlington National Cemetery , just outside Washington .",O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O B-geo O,"IN DT NNP NNPS , WRB DT NN VBZ VBN IN NNP NNP , DT NN NN VBD VBN IN NNP NNP NNP , RB IN NNP ."
"A bugler played the traditional "" Taps "" tattoo , while Vice President Dick Cheney laid a wreath at the Tomb of the Unknowns , containing the remains of unidentified service members killed in wartime .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD DT JJ LQU NNP LQU NN , IN NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN DT NNP IN DT NNS , VBG DT NNS IN JJ NN NNS VBN IN NN ."
"President Bush honored veterans at another event in Wilkes-Barre , Pennsylvania , where he defended current military campaigns .",B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD NNS IN DT NN IN NNP , NNP , WRB PRP VBD JJ JJ NNS ."
"The eleventh hour of the eleventh day of the eleventh month is also observed in many British Commonwealth countries , in honor of the moment the armistice ending the First World War was signed in 1918 .",O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O B-tim O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O B-tim O,"DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN VBZ RB VBN IN JJ JJ NN NNS , IN NN IN DT NN DT NN VBG DT NNP NNP NNP VBD VBN IN CD ."
"Remembrance or Armistice Day , was renamed in the United States in 1954 when the observance was broadened to include all men and women who have served in the U.S. armed forces .",B-eve O B-eve I-eve O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,"NNP CC NNP NNP , VBD VBN IN DT NNP NNPS IN CD WRB DT NN VBD VBN TO VB DT NNS CC NNS WP VBP VBN IN DT NNP JJ NNS ."
