"Australia 's abundant and diverse natural resources attract high levels of foreign investment and include extensive reserves of coal , iron ore , copper , gold , natural gas , uranium , and renewable energy sources .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ CC JJ JJ NNS VBP JJ NNS IN JJ NN CC VBP JJ NNS IN NN , NN NN , NN , NN , JJ NN , NN , CC JJ NN NNS ."
"A series of major investments , such as the US $ 40 billion Gorgon Liquid Natural Gas project , will significantly expand the resources sector .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN JJ NNS , JJ IN DT NNP $ CD CD NNP NNP NNP NNP NN , MD RB VB DT NNS NN ."
"Australia also has a large services sector and is a significant exporter of natural resources , energy , and food .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP RB VBZ DT JJ NNS NN CC VBZ DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS , NN , CC NN ."
"Key tenets of Australia 's trade policy include support for open trade and the successful culmination of the Doha Round of multilateral trade negotiations , particularly for agriculture and services .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"NN NNS IN NNP POS NN NN VBP NN IN JJ NN CC DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP IN JJ NN NNS , RB IN NN CC NNS ."
The Australian economy grew for 17 consecutive years before the global financial crisis .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBD IN CD JJ NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN .
"Subsequently , the Rudd government introduced a fiscal stimulus package worth over US $ 50 billion to offset the effect of the slowing world economy , while the Reserve Bank of Australia cut interest rates to historic lows .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O,"RB , DT NNP NN VBD DT JJ NN NN NN IN NNP $ CD CD TO VB DT NN IN DT VBG NN NN , IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP VBD NN NNS TO JJ NNS ."
"These policies - and continued demand for commodities , especially from China - helped the Australian economy rebound after just one quarter of negative growth .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS : CC VBN NN IN NNS , RB IN NNP : VBD DT JJ NN VBD IN RB CD NN IN JJ NN ."
The economy grew by 1.2 % during 2009 - the best performance in the OECD - and by 3.3 % in 2010 .,O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NN VBD IN CD NN IN CD IN DT JJS NN IN DT NNP : CC IN CD NN IN CD .
"Unemployment , originally expected to reach 8-10 % , peaked at 5.7 % in late 2009 and fell to 5.1 % in 2010 .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-tim O,"NN , RB VBN TO VB CD NN , VBD IN CD NN IN JJ CD CC VBD TO CD NN IN CD ."
"As a result of an improved economy , the budget deficit is expected to peak below 4.2 % of GDP and the government could return to budget surpluses as early as 2015 .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN , DT NN NN VBZ VBN TO VB IN CD NN IN NN CC DT NN MD VB TO NN NNS RB RB IN CD ."
"Australia was one of the first advanced economies to raise interest rates , with seven rate hikes between October 2009 and November 2010 .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,"NNP VBD CD IN DT JJ JJ NNS TO VB NN NNS , IN CD NN NNS IN NNP CD CC NNP CD ."
"The GILLARD government is focused on raising Australia 's economic productivity to ensure the sustainability of growth , and continues to manage the symbiotic , but sometimes tense , economic relationship with China .",O B-per O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NNP NN VBZ VBN IN VBG NNP POS JJ NN TO VB DT NN IN NN , CC VBZ TO VB DT JJ , CC RB JJ , JJ NN IN NNP ."
"Australia is engaged in the Trans-Pacific Partnership talks and ongoing free trade agreement negotiations with China , Japan , and Korea .",B-org O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O B-geo O,"NNP VBZ VBN IN DT NNP NNP NNS CC JJ JJ NN NN NNS IN NNP , NNP , CC NNP ."
