Pakistani military officials say a suicide bomber has killed five soldiers and wounded at least five others near the Afghan border .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,JJ JJ NNS VBP DT NN NN VBZ VBN CD NNS CC VBN IN JJS CD NNS IN DT JJ NN .
The bomber detonated his explosives Thursday in South Waziristan 's main town of Wana .,O O O O O B-tim O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-geo O,DT NN VBD PRP$ NNS NNP IN NNP NNP POS JJ NN IN NNP .
"It is unclear which group planned the attack , although al-Qaida and Taliban militants are active in the tribal region .",O O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-org O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBZ JJ WDT NN VBD DT NN , IN NNP CC NNP NNS VBP JJ IN DT JJ NN ."
