Chinese state media say at least 14 people were killed as Typhoon Sepat and a tornado hit China 's eastern and southern coasts .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,JJ NN NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN IN NNP NNP CC DT NN VBD NNP POS JJ CC JJ NNS .
"The Xinhua News Agency says torrential rains from the typhoon triggered a landslide in Fujian province Sunday , killing two people .",O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ JJ NNS IN DT NN VBD DT NN IN JJ NN NNP , VBG CD NNS ."
One person is missing .,O O O O O,CD NN VBZ VBG .
Rains also caused the collapse of the Daruo train station in Minging .,O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O,NNS RB VBD DT NN IN DT NNP NN NN IN VBG .
Six carriages of a cargo train derailed .,O O O O O O O O,CD NNS IN DT NN NN VBD .
The agency says a farmer was killed when his house collapsed Sunday in Zhejian province 's Wencheng county .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O B-per I-per O,DT NN VBZ DT NN VBD VBN WRB PRP$ NN VBD NNP IN NNP NN POS NNP NN .
"Before its landfall Saturday , the typhoon spawned a tornado that killed 11 people and destroyed 156 houses in the city of Wenzhou in Zhejian .",O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,"IN PRP$ NN NNP , DT NN VBD DT NN WDT VBD CD NNS CC VBD CD NNS IN DT NN IN NNP IN NNP ."
"Chinese authorities evacuated more than 900,000 people from Zhejian , Fujian and Guangdong provinces after the typhoon cut power to thousands of homes in Taiwan and the Philippines Saturday .",B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org B-tim O,"JJ NNS VBD JJR IN CD NNS IN NNP , NNP CC NNP NNS IN DT NN VBD NN TO NNS IN NNS IN NNP CC DT NNPS NNP ."
