A British parliamentary report says the war in Iraq is making it more difficult to tackle terrorism .,O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ JJ NN VBZ DT NN IN NNP VBZ VBG PRP RBR JJ TO VB NN .
The Foreign Affairs Select Committee says the fighting in Iraq is providing extremists a crucial training ground .,B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT NN IN NNP VBZ VBG NNS DT JJ NN NN .
"It says despite successes in targeting al-Qaida 's leadership in Iraq , the danger of international terrorism and al-Qaida is growing .",O O O O O O B-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-org O O O,"PRP VBZ IN NNS IN VBG NNP POS NN IN NNP , DT NN IN JJ NN CC NNP VBZ VBG ."
"The report also talks about what it says is the deteriorating security situation in Afghanistan , where two more British soldiers were reported killed Sunday .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-tim O,"DT NN RB VBZ IN WP PRP VBZ VBZ DT JJ NN NN IN NNP , WRB CD JJR JJ NNS VBD VBN VBN NNP ."
The lawmakers warned against military action in Iran over that country 's refusal to end its nuclear program .,O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBD IN JJ NN IN NNP IN DT NN POS NN TO VB PRP$ JJ NN .
The report says attacking Iran would likely unleash extremely serious consequences .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBG NNP MD RB VB RB JJ NNS .
