Chinese authorities say a fire at a nightclub in southern China has killed 43 people and injured at least 88 others .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP DT NN IN DT NN IN JJ NNP VBZ VBN CD NNS CC VBN IN JJS CD NNS .
The official Xinhua news agency says the blaze erupted in a club in the southern city of Shenzhen in province late Saturday .,O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O,DT JJ NNP NN NN VBZ DT NN VBD IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP IN NN JJ NNP .
Xinhua said the fire was triggered by fireworks ignited during a performance .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD DT NN VBD VBN IN NNS VBN IN DT NN .
"The report said that as of Sunday morning , 59 of the injured had been hospitalized and six others were under medial observation .",O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD IN IN IN NNP NN , CD IN DT NN VBD VBN VBN CC CD NNS VBD IN JJ NN ."
The agency said police had detained 12 people in connection with the blaze .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD NN VBD VBN CD NNS IN NN IN DT NN .
"Xinhua said an investigation team of officials from the country 's work safety watchdog , the Ministry of public Security , and the provincial and local governments , has been set up .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD DT NN NN IN NNS IN DT NN POS NN NN NN , DT NNP IN JJ NN , CC DT JJ CC JJ NNS , VBZ VBN VBN RP ."
