The Chinese have a strong affinity for their mountains .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP DT JJ NN IN PRP$ NNS .
"As China modernizes and the middle class grows , the country has found a new way to capitalize on its reverence for snow-capped peaks .",O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP VBZ CC DT JJ NN VBZ , DT NN VBZ VBN DT JJ NN TO VB IN PRP$ NN IN JJ NNS ."
Sam Beattie reports from the Tibetan Plateau .,B-per I-per O O O B-gpe O O,NNP NNP VBZ IN DT JJ NNP .
