A military judge has ordered a British soldier cleared of one charge of simulating a kick at an Iraqi prisoner .,O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT JJ NN VBZ VBN DT JJ NN VBN IN CD NN IN VBG DT NN IN DT JJ NN .
"In the court-martial trial of three British soldiers Wednesday at a British base in Germany , the judge directed the panel of military officers to find Lance Corporal Mark Cooley not guilty on the charge of conduct prejudicial to good order and military discipline .",O O O O O O B-gpe O B-tim O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN IN CD JJ NNS NNP IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , DT NN VBD DT NN IN JJ NNS TO VB NNP NNP NNP NNP RB JJ IN DT NN IN NN JJ TO JJ NN CC JJ NN ."
He said the legal reasons for his decision could not be reported at the present time .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT JJ NNS IN PRP$ NN MD RB VB VBN IN DT JJ NN .
Cooley still faces two other mistreatment charges .,B-per O O O O O O O,NNP RB VBZ CD JJ NN NNS .
The three British soldiers originally faced a total of nine charges of mistreating and sexually humiliating Iraqis .,O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O,DT CD JJ NNS RB VBD DT NN IN CD NNS IN NN CC RB JJ NNS .
"The men have denied the charges , although one has pleaded guilty to one count of assault .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS VBP VBN DT NNS , IN CD VBZ VBN JJ TO CD NN IN NN ."
