The families of two U.S. soldiers who were captured in Iraq say the soldiers ' remains have been found more than a year after they disappeared .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS IN CD NNP NNS WP VBD VBN IN NNP VBP DT NNS POS NNS VBP VBN VBN RBR IN DT NN IN PRP VBD .
The families of Private Byron Fouty and Sergeant Alex Jimenez said Friday that the U.S. Army notified them of the soldiers ' deaths this week .,O O O O B-per I-per O B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS IN JJ NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP IN DT NNP NNP VBD PRP IN DT NNS POS NNS DT NN .
They say the men were identified by their dental records .,O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBP DT NNS VBD VBN IN PRP$ JJ NNS .
The soldiers were captured in May of 2007 when their unit was ambushed near Baghdad .,O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNS VBD VBN IN NNP IN CD WRB PRP$ NN VBD VBN IN NNP .
The body of a third soldier kidnapped in the same attack was recovered earlier this year from the Euphrates River .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT NN IN DT JJ NN VBN IN DT JJ NN VBD VBN RBR DT NN IN DT NNP NNP .
Four other U.S. soldiers and an Iraqi were killed in the ambush .,O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,CD JJ NNP NNS CC DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NN .
