An Afghan police official says border police have shot and killed seven civilians after mistaking them for insurgents .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN NN VBZ NN NNS VBP VBN CC VBN CD NNS IN VBG PRP IN NNS .
"Abdul Raziq , head of the border police , told reporters the incident occurred in Kandahar 's Shubarak district in southern Afghanistan near the border with Pakistan .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-geo O,"NNP NNP , NN IN DT NN NN , VBD NNS DT NN VBD IN NNP POS NNP NN IN JJ NNP IN DT NN IN NNP ."
The civilians were gathering wood when they were spotted by a six-member border police patrol .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBD VBG NN WRB PRP VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN NN NN .
"Raziq said the officers involved have been detained for questioning , and the incident is under investigation .",B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD DT NNS VBN VBP VBN VBN IN VBG , CC DT NN VBZ IN NN ."
Afghan troops and NATO forces have been fighting a fierce insurgency in Afghanistan .,B-gpe O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNS CC NNP NNS VBP VBN VBG DT JJ NN IN NNP .
Last year was the deadliest for Afghan civilians and international troops in Afghanistan since the U.S.-led invasion in late 2001 toppled the Taliban,O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-tim O O B-org,JJ NN VBD DT JJS IN JJ NNS CC JJ NNS IN NNP IN DT JJ NN IN JJ CD VBD DT NNP
