The United States has imposed financial sanctions on an Iranian-based foundation for allegedly providing support to Islamic terrorist organizations .,O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNPS VBZ VBN JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN IN RB VBG NN TO JJ JJ NNS .
The U.S. Treasury Department Tuesday accused the Martyrs Foundation of working directly with Lebanon 's Shi'ite militant group Hezbollah .,O B-org I-org I-org B-tim O O B-org I-org O O O O B-geo O O O O B-org O,DT NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NNP NNP IN VBG RB IN NNP POS NNP JJ NN NNP .
The U.S. said the Martyrs Foundation has channeled financial support to Hezbollah and the Palestinian militant groups Hamas and Palestinian Islamic Jihad .,O B-geo O O B-org I-org O O O O O B-org O O B-gpe O O B-org O B-gpe O O O,DT NNP VBD DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN JJ NN TO NNP CC DT JJ JJ NNS NNP CC JJ NNP NNP .
The department is freezing all the foundation 's bank accounts or assets in the U.S. and forbidding Americans from doing business with the group .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBG PDT DT NN POS NN NNS CC NNS IN DT NNP CC VBG NNS IN VBG NN IN DT NN .
"The action also covers the foundation 's U.S. branch , Goodwill Charitable Organization .",O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org I-org O,"DT NN RB VBZ DT NN POS NNP NN , NNP NNP NNP ."
The U.S. Treasury Department acted according to an executive order aimed at financially isolating terrorists and their support networks .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBD VBG TO DT NN NN VBN IN RB VBG NNS CC PRP$ NN NNS .
The department Tuesday also targeted a Beirut finance firm Al-Qard al-Hassan accused of being a cover for Hezbollah 's financial dealings and two Lebanese individuals .,O O B-tim O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT NN NNP RB VBD DT NNP NN NN NNP NNP VBN IN VBG DT NN IN NNP POS JJ NNS CC CD JJ NNS .
