A U.S. businessman and a former occupation official in Iraq have been charged in a scheme in which coalition authorities were bribed in exchange for reconstruction contracts .,O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN CC DT JJ NN NN IN NNP VBP VBN VBN IN DT NN IN WDT NN NNS VBD VBN IN NN IN NN NNS .
"U.S. authorities Thursday announced that Robert Stein , who worked with the Coalition Provisional Authority , is one of the officials who received kickbacks from American businessman Philip Bloom .",B-geo O B-tim O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-per I-per O,"NNP NNS NNP VBD IN NNP NNP , WP VBD IN DT NNP NNP NNP , VBZ CD IN DT NNS WP VBD NNS IN JJ NN NNP NNP ."
"Mr. Bloom , who authorities say controlled three companies , was charged late Wednesday in Washington federal court with paying hundreds of thousands of dollars in bribes and kickbacks to U.S. occupation officials in Iraq and their spouses .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O,"NNP NNP , WP NNS VBP VBN CD NNS , VBD VBN JJ NNP IN NNP JJ NN IN VBG NNS IN NNS IN NNS IN NNS CC NNS TO NNP NN NNS IN NNP CC PRP$ NNS ."
A government affidavit says the contracts secured by Mr. Bloom were awarded in early 2004 and were worth about $ 3.5 million .,O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O,DT NN NN VBZ DT NNS VBN IN NNP NNP VBD VBN IN JJ CD CC VBD JJ IN $ CD CD .
"There have been allegations of corruption in the coalition government , which ran Iraq from just after the March 2003 invasion until June 2004 .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim I-tim O O B-tim I-tim O,"EX VBP VBN NNS IN NN IN DT NN NN , WDT VBD NNP IN RB IN DT NNP CD NN IN NNP CD ."
