"Afghan officials say a suicide bomber has killed three people in the capital of Kabul , while fighting intensified with Taliban militants in the southwestern part of the country .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP DT NN NN VBZ VBN CD NNS IN DT NN IN NNP , IN VBG VBN IN NNP NNS IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN ."
Police in Kabul say the bomber exploded his car near a coalition military convoy as it traveled down a busy street .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNP VBP DT NN VBD PRP$ NN IN DT NN JJ NN IN PRP VBD RP DT JJ NN .
"The blast killed three bystanders , including a child .",O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD CD NNS , VBG DT NN ."
"A coalition spokesman , U.S. Lieutenant Colonel Dave Johnson , says none of the soldiers were hurt .",O O O O B-org I-org I-org B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN NN , NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP , VBZ NN IN DT NNS VBD VBN ."
"In southwestern Farah province , police officials say Afghan and NATO forces inflicted heavy casualties in clashes with Taliban militants .",O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O B-org O O O O O O O B-org O O,"IN JJ NNP NN , NN NNS VBP JJ CC NNP NNS VBD JJ NNS IN NNS IN NNP NNS ."
They say Afghan troops surrounded the Taliban as they gathered in the Bala Buluk district .,O O B-gpe O O O B-org O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O,PRP VBP JJ NNS VBN DT NNP IN PRP VBD IN DT NNP NNP NN .
NATO forces then called in an airstrike .,B-org O O O O O O O,NNP NNS RB VBD IN DT NN .
Afghan officials say 30 Taliban militants were killed .,B-gpe O O O B-org O O O O,JJ NNS VBP CD NNP NNS VBD VBN .
Two Afghan soldiers and a policeman also died in the clash .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,CD JJ NNS CC DT NN RB VBD IN DT NN .
