"U.S. and German authorities have initialed an agreement under which Berlin and Washington will share fingerprints , personal data and DNA samples of people suspected of terrorist activities .",B-geo O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP CC JJ NNS VBP VBN DT NN IN WDT NNP CC NNP MD VB NNS , JJ NNS CC NN NNS IN NNS VBN IN JJ NNS ."
German Interior Minister Wolfgang Schaeuble and U.S. Homeland Security Secretary Michael Chertoff initialed the deal Tuesday in Berlin .,B-gpe O B-per I-per I-per O B-org I-org I-org B-per I-per I-per O O O B-tim O B-geo O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN NNP IN NNP .
German and U.S. lawmakers still must approve the agreement .,B-gpe O B-geo O O O O O O O,JJ CC NNP NNS RB MD VB DT NN .
"If endorsed , the deal is to take effect by the end of the year .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O,"IN VBN , DT NN VBZ TO VB NN IN DT NN IN DT NN ."
The agreement comes six months after German authorities uncovered what they described as a plot to bomb U.S. personnel and military bases in that country .,O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ CD NNS IN JJ NNS VBD WP PRP VBD IN DT NN TO VB NNP NNS CC JJ NNS IN DT NN .
German prosecutors said three suspects attended training camps in Pakistan and were stockpiling chemicals to manufacture car bombs .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBD CD NNS VBD NN NNS IN NNP CC VBD VBG NNS TO VB NN NNS .
