The former head of Russian oil giant Yukos says the government takeover of the company 's main asset has inflicted severe damage on the Russian economy .,O O O O B-gpe O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT JJ NN IN JJ NN NN NNP VBZ DT NN NN IN DT NN POS JJ NN VBZ VBN JJ NN IN DT JJ NN .
"In a letter published Tuesday , Mikhail Khodorkovsky said Moscow 's approval for state-owned Rosneft to purchase Yukos ' largest subsidiary , Yuganskneftegaz , was the most destructive economic event since Russian President Vladimir Putin took office .",O O O O B-tim O B-org B-per O B-geo O O O O B-org O O B-org O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O,"IN DT NN VBN NNP , NNP NNP VBD NNP POS NN IN JJ NNP TO VB NNP POS JJS NN , NNP , VBD DT RBS JJ JJ NN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD NN ."
"The former oil tycoon , imprisoned on alleged tax fraud , said Russian authorities want to lock him away because they are afraid he will seek revenge .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN NN , VBN IN JJ NN NN , VBD JJ NNS VBP TO VB PRP RB IN PRP VBP JJ PRP MD VB NN ."
"He denied any such intention , and said he would like to play a role in helping Russia prosper .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"PRP VBD DT JJ NN , CC VBD PRP MD VB TO VB DT NN IN VBG NNP NN ."
"Meanwhile in Moscow today , Mr. Putin 's economic advisor Andrei Illarionov said this month 's government-forced sale of Yukos ' main asset was "" the fraud of the year . """,O O B-geo B-tim O B-per B-org O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB IN NNP NN , NNP NNP POS JJ NN NNP NNP VBD DT NN POS JJ NN IN NNP POS JJ NN VBD LQU DT NN IN DT NN . LQU"
