An American member of the al-Qaida terrorist network has warned President Bush to end U.S. involvement in all Muslim countries or face attacks worse than the September 11 ( 2001 ) assault .,O B-gpe O O O B-org O O O O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim O O O,DT JJ NN IN DT NNP JJ NN VBZ VBN NNP NNP TO VB NNP NN IN DT NNP NNS CC NN NNS JJR IN DT NNP CD LRB CD RRB NN .
"In a video posted on the Internet Tuesday , Adam Gadahn demanded that Mr. Bush remove all U.S. military and spies from Islamic countries , free all Muslims from U.S. prisons and end support for Israel .",O O O O O O O B-tim O B-per I-per O O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O,"IN DT NN VBN IN DT NNP NNP , NNP NNP VBD IN NNP NNP VB DT NNP JJ CC NNS IN JJ NNS , JJ DT NNS IN NNP NNS CC NN NN IN NNP ."
"Gadahn , who also goes by the name Azzam al-Amriki , warned that if the demands are not met , Americans will experience things "" which will make you forget all about the horrors of September 11 , Afghanistan and Iraq . """,B-per O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-geo O B-geo O O,"NNP , WP RB VBZ IN DT NN NNP NNP , VBD IN IN DT NNS VBP RB VBN , NNS MD VB NNS LQU WDT MD VB PRP VB DT IN DT NNS IN NNP CD , NNP CC NNP . LQU"
"Gadahn , who is a convert to Islam , has been indicted in the United States for treason and aiding al-Qaida .",B-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-org O,"NNP , WP VBZ DT NN IN NNP , VBZ VBN VBN IN DT NNP NNPS IN NN CC VBG NNP ."
He has appeared on some of the terrorist group 's past videos .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ VBN IN DT IN DT NN NN POS JJ NNS .
