China has confirmed that a high-ranking North Korean diplomat visited Beijing earlier this week to discuss the stalled six-party talks on Pyongyang 's nuclear program .,B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN IN DT JJ JJ JJ NN VBD NNP RBR DT NN TO VB DT VBN JJ NNS IN NNP POS JJ NN .
"A spokesman for China 's Foreign Ministry says Kang Sok Ju , North Korea 's first vice foreign minister , arrived in Beijing last Saturday for talks with Chinese officials , including Vice Foreign Minister Dai Bingguo .",O O O B-geo O B-org I-org O B-per I-per I-per O B-geo I-geo O O B-per O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O B-gpe O O O B-per O B-per I-per I-per O,"DT NN IN NNP POS NNP NNP VBZ NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP POS JJ NN JJ NN , VBD IN NNP JJ NNP IN NNS IN JJ NNS , VBG NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
The talks ended Tuesday .,O O O B-tim O,DT NNS VBD NNP .
The spokesman did not say if North Korea has agreed to return to the negotiations .,O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD RB VB IN NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB TO DT NNS .
"Meanwhile , the head of North Korea 's legislature , Choe Thae Bok , told a conference in Manila on Tuesday that his country produced nuclear weapons because it needs to protect itself from an invasion by the United States .",O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"RB , DT NN IN NNP NNP POS NN , NNP NNP NNP , VBD DT NN IN NNP IN NNP IN PRP$ NN VBD JJ NNS IN PRP VBZ TO VB PRP IN DT NN IN DT NNP NNPS ."
Washington has repeatedly said it has no plans for such an attack .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ RB VBN PRP VBZ DT NNS IN JJ DT NN .
