Iraq 's ruling Shi'ite alliance has chosen incumbent Prime Minister Ibrahim al-Jaafari to head the new government .,B-geo O O O O O O O B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O,NNP POS NN NNP NN VBZ VBN JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP TO VB DT JJ NN .
"He received 64 votes in the caucus of Shi'ite legislators , beating his rival , Vice President Abel Abdul-Mahdi by one vote .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O,"PRP VBD CD NNS IN DT NN IN NNP NNS , VBG PRP$ NN , NNP NNP NNP NNP IN CD NN ."
The Shi'ite alliance won a majority in Iraq 's December legislative election .,O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O,DT NNP NN VBD DT NN IN NNP POS NNP JJ NN .
"Naming the prime minister is a key step in forming a new Iraqi government , the nation 's first post-Saddam Hussein parliament with a four-year mandate .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"VBG DT JJ NN VBZ DT JJ NN IN VBG DT JJ JJ NN , DT NN POS JJ JJ NNP NN IN DT JJ NN ."
"Separately , Iraqi police say at least 12 people were wounded today when two roadside bombs exploded in quick succession near a restaurant in central Baghdad .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"RB , JJ NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN NN WRB CD NN NNS VBD IN JJ NN IN DT NN IN JJ NNP ."
"Also , the U.S. military says insurgents fired a mortar round Sunday into the heavily fortified Green Zone , home to the U.S. Embassy and Iraqi government .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-org I-org I-org B-gpe O O,"RB , DT NNP NN VBZ NNS VBD DT NN NN NNP IN DT RB VBN NNP NNP , NN TO DT NNP NNP CC JJ NN ."
There were no reports of casualties .,O O O O O O O,EX VBD DT NNS IN NNS .
