Police in Sudan say they have arrested a number of suspects in connection with the murder of a Khartoum newspaper editor .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O,NNS IN NNP VBP PRP VBP VBN DT NN IN NNS IN NN IN DT NN IN DT NNP NN NN .
"Sudan 's official news agency cites a top police official , Major General Mohamed Najib al-Tayeb , as saying authorities continue their investigation into the murder of Taha Mohamed Ahmed .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O,"NNP POS JJ NN NN VBZ DT JJ NN NN , NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP , IN VBG NNS VBP PRP$ NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP ."
"Ahmed was found decapitated in southern Khartoum Wednesday , less than a day after he was kidnapped from his home .",B-per O O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD VBN VBN IN JJ NNP NNP , JJR IN DT NN IN PRP VBD VBN IN PRP$ NN ."
Ahmed was editor of the newspaper al-Wifaq .,B-per O O O O O B-org O,NNP VBD NN IN DT NN NNP .
"Last year , Islamic radicals called for him to be killed after he published articles that questioned the roots of the Prophet Muhammad .",O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"JJ NN , NNP NNS VBD IN PRP TO VB VBN IN PRP VBD NNS WDT VBD DT NNS IN DT NNP NNP ."
"The editor of the Khartoum Monitor newspaper , Alfred Taban , has said he fears Ahmed 's murder indicates the presence of extremist groups in Sudan .",O O O O B-org I-org O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NN , NNP NNP , VBZ VBN PRP VBZ NNP POS NN VBZ DT NN IN NN NNS IN NNP ."
