Israeli Defense Minister Ehud Barak is in Egypt to discuss a dispute over cross-border weapons smuggling for Palestinian militants in the Gaza Strip .,B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo I-geo O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ IN NNP TO VB DT NN IN JJ NNS VBG IN JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNP .
Israel says Cairo has failed to stop the smuggling of weapons through tunnels under Egypt 's border with Gaza .,B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O,NNP VBZ NNP VBZ VBN TO VB DT NN IN NNS IN NNS IN NNP POS NN IN NNP .
Israeli authorities say they have handed videotapes to U.S. officials that allegedly show Egyptian border guards helping the weapons smugglers .,B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP PRP VBP VBN NNS TO NNP NNS WDT RB VBP JJ NN NNS VBG DT NNS NNS .
"Egypt rejects the criticism , and has accused Israel of pressing the United States to withhold military aid from Egypt over the issue .",B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"NNP VBZ DT NN , CC VBZ VBN NNP IN VBG DT NNP NNPS TO VB JJ NN IN NNP IN DT NN ."
"Speaking to reporters in Jerusalem Wednesday , two U.S. lawmakers said the United States could make aid to Egypt conditional on Cairo doing more to halt arms smuggling .",O O O O B-geo B-tim O O B-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"VBG TO NNS IN NNP NNP , CD NNP NNS VBD DT NNP NNPS MD VB NN TO VB JJ IN NNP VBG JJR TO VB NNS VBG ."
Republican Senator Arlen Spector and Democratic Congressman Partrick Kennedy are members of appropriations committees that control U.S. foreign aid spending .,B-org B-per B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP NNP VBP NNS IN NNS NNS WDT VBP NNP JJ NN NN .
