The resolution was adopted Tuesday in Strasbourg by delegates from the Council 's 46 member states .,O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O B-org O O O O O,DT NN VBD VBN NNP IN NNP IN NNS IN DT NNP POS CD NN NNS .
It said the United States has betrayed its own highest principles in the way it has prosecuted the war on terror .,O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT NNP NNPS VBZ VBN PRP$ JJ JJS NNS IN DT NN PRP VBZ VBN DT NN IN NN .
U.S. authorities are holding about 500 terrorism suspects at Guantanamo .,B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNS VBP VBG IN CD NN NNS IN NNP .
"Last year , a report by the International Committee of the Red Cross said the U.S. military has intentionally used psychological and sometimes physical coercion on prisoners .",O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN , DT NN IN DT NNP NNP IN DT NNP NNP VBD DT NNP NN VBZ RB VBN JJ CC RB JJ NN IN NNS ."
"The report said the U.S. treatment of detainees is "" tantamount to torture . """,O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD DT NNP NN IN NNS VBZ RQU JJ TO VB . LQU
"U.S. officials rejected the accusations , saying the prisoners are treated humanely .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNS VBD DT NNS , VBG DT NNS VBP VBN RB ."
