"Formed from the merger of the British colony of the Gold Coast and the Togoland trust territory , Ghana in 1957 became the first sub-Saharan country in colonial Africa to gain its independence .",O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,"VBN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP CC DT NNP NN NN , NNP IN CD VBD DT JJ JJ NN IN JJ NNP TO VB PRP$ NN ."
Ghana endured a long series of coups before Lt. Jerry RAWLINGS took power in 1981 and banned political parties .,B-geo O O O O O O O B-per B-org I-org O O O B-tim O O O O O,NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN NNS IN NNP NNP NNP VBD NN IN CD CC VBD JJ NNS .
"After approving a new constitution and restoring multiparty politics in 1992 , RAWLINGS won presidential elections in 1992 and 1996 , but was constitutionally prevented from running for a third term in 2000 .",O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-org O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"IN VBG DT JJ NN CC VBG JJ NNS IN CD , NNP VBD JJ NNS IN CD CC CD , CC VBD RB VBN IN VBG IN DT JJ NN IN CD ."
John KUFUOR succeeded him and was reelected in 2004 .,B-per I-per O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP NNP VBD PRP CC VBD VBN IN CD .
John Atta MILLS took over as head of state in early 2009 .,B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP NNP NNP VBD RP IN NN IN NN IN JJ CD .
