A British magistrate has ordered four suspects linked to activities at suspected terrorism training camps in Britain held in custody for another two weeks .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim I-tim O O,DT JJ NN VBZ VBN CD NNS VBN TO NNS IN JJ NN NN NNS IN NNP VBN IN NN IN DT CD NNS .
The suspects were among 12 people arrested last week in major raids across south London .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT NNS VBD IN CD NNS VBN JJ NN IN JJ NNS IN JJ NNP .
Police say Yassin Mutegombwa underwent terror training earlier this year at several training camps in the countryside around the British capital .,O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,NNS VBP NNP NNP VBD NN NN RBR DT NN IN JJ NN NNS IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN .
"His brother , Hassan , was charged with fundraising for terrorist activities .",O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O,"PRP$ NN , NNP , VBD VBN IN VBG IN JJ NNS ."
Two other men were charged with possessing information that could be useful to someone preparing to commit acts of terrorism .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CD JJ NNS VBD VBN IN VBG NN WDT MD VB JJ TO DT VBG TO VB NNS IN NN .
Police are still questioning eight other suspects .,O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP RB VBG CD JJ NNS .
They have not been formally charged .,O O O O O O O,PRP VBP RB VBN RB VBN .
