The United Nations says at least 30 civilians were massacred in eastern Congo in an apparent reprisal attack for the killing of three dissident soldiers .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN IN JJ NNP IN DT JJ NN NN IN DT NN IN CD JJ NNS .
"A team of U.N. investigators says renegade Congolese forces attacked Buramba village in mid-December , targeting civilians it believed supported pro-government fighters .",O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN NNP NNS VBZ NN JJ NNS VBN NNP NN IN NNP , VBG NNS PRP VBD VBN JJ NNS ."
The investigators say among the dead are women and children .,O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP IN DT NN VBP NNS CC NNS .
It found some burned corpses and others killed in the hills surrounding Buramba .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,PRP VBD DT VBN NNS CC NNS VBN IN DT NNS VBG NNP .
It says the town was looted and completely deserted .,O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ DT NN VBD VBN CC RB VBN .
"Buramba is in Congo 's restive North Kivu province where fighting broke out last month between former Rwandan-backed rebels , who are supposed to be part of Congo 's new army , and regular army forces .",B-geo O O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ IN NNP POS JJ JJ NNP NN WRB VBG VBN IN JJ NN IN JJ JJ NNS , WP VBP VBN TO VB NN IN NNP POS JJ NN , CC JJ NN NNS ."
The United Nations says the massacre was in revenge for the killing of three dissident soldiers who were trying to steal rice by pro-government Mai Mai fighters militiamen .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ DT NN VBD IN NN IN DT NN IN CD JJ NNS WP VBD VBG TO VB NN IN JJ NNP NNP NNS NNS .
