Thousands of Islamic hard-liners protested in northwestern Pakistan Friday against the U.S. missile strike that targeted al-Qaida leaders in a northern village bordering Afghanistan .,O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O O B-geo O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-gpe O,NNS IN NNP NNS VBD IN JJ NNP NNP IN DT NNP NN NN WDT VBD NNP NNS IN DT JJ NN VBG NNP .
The protesters chanted anti-American slogans and pledged to wage jihad against the United States .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT NNS VBD JJ NNS CC VBD TO VB NN IN DT NNP NNPS .
Nationwide demonstrations erupted after missiles reported to be targeting Osama bin Laden 's deputy Ayman al-Zawahiri hit a village in the remote Bajur tribal region on January 13 .,O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim I-tim O,JJ NNS VBD IN NNS VBN TO VB VBG NNP NNP NNP POS NN NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN DT JJ NNP JJ NN IN NNP CD .
"Media reports say the strike killed at least three top al-Qaida leaders , including a top chemical weapons expert .",O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O,"NN NNS VBP DT NN VBD IN JJS CD JJ NNP NNS , VBG DT JJ NN NNS NN ."
"Meanwhile , just 90 kilometers from the site of the attack , police detained more than 10 people believed to have links with outlawed extremist groups .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , RB CD NNS IN DT NN IN DT NN , NNS VBD JJR IN CD NNS VBN TO VB NNS IN JJ NN NNS ."
Pakistani media reports say several foreign nationals were said to be among the detainees .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS NNS VBP JJ JJ NNS VBD VBN TO VB IN DT NNS .
