"A leading Iranian cleric says his nation will continue to hate America even under a Barack Obama presidency , unless Washington changes what he called its "" arrogant "" nature .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-org B-per O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"DT VBG JJ NN VBZ PRP$ NN MD VB TO VB NNP RB IN DT NNP NNP NN , IN NNP VBZ WP PRP VBD PRP$ LQU JJ LQU NN ."
"During Friday prayers in Tehran , Ayatollah Ahmad Khatami said Mr. Obama would suffer the same destiny as U.S. President George Bush , whom he described as hated by the world .",O B-tim O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo I-geo O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP NNS IN NNP , NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP MD VB DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP , WP PRP VBD IN VBN IN DT NN ."
"The ayatollah , an ally of supreme leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei , said Mr. Obama 's slogan of change was imposed by world conditions and the resistance of the Iranian people .",O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"DT NN , DT NN IN JJ NN NNP NNP NNP , VBD NNP NNP POS NN IN NN VBD VBN IN NN NNS CC DT NN IN DT JJ NNS ."
"Iran has sent mixed messages on Mr. Obama 's election victory , with some hardliners expressing caution .",B-geo O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBN JJ NNS IN NNP NNP POS NN NN , IN DT NNS VBG NN ."
"But President Mahmoud Ahmedinejad sent a letter of congratulations to the president-elect , the first time a leader of revolutionary Iran has offered such a message .",O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"CC NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN NNS TO DT NN , DT JJ NN DT NN IN JJ NNP VBZ VBN PDT DT NN ."
"Ayatollah Khamenei , who has final say on state matters , has yet to publicly comment on Mr. Obama 's election victory .",B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O,"NNP NNP , WP VBZ JJ NN IN NN NNS , VBZ RB TO RB VB IN NNP NNP POS NN NN ."
