The United States has urged Israel to consider the ramifications of imposing travel restrictions on the West Bank .,O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,DT NNP NNPS VBZ VBN NNP TO VB DT NNS IN VBG NN NNS IN DT NNP NNP .
"A State Department spokesman , Sean McCormick , said Monday Washington supports Israel 's right to defend itself .",O B-org I-org O O B-per I-per O O B-tim B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP NN , NNP NNP , VBD NNP NNP VBZ NNP POS NN TO VB PRP ."
"He said , however , Israel should consider the long-term goals of peace and security for both the Israeli and Palestinian people .",O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-gpe O O,"PRP VBD , RB , NNP MD VB DT JJ NNS IN NN CC NN IN DT DT JJ CC JJ NNS ."
His comments follow Israel 's decision to suspend security contacts with the Palestinian Authority after Palestinian militant attacks killed three Jewish settlers in the West Bank .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,PRP$ NNS VBP NNP POS NN TO VB NN NNS IN DT JJ NNP IN JJ JJ NNS VBD CD JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNP .
Israeli forces also re-imposed some recently-lifted restrictions on Palestinian movement and set up roadblocks at the entrances to Bethlehem and Hebron .,B-gpe O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,JJ NNS RB VBD DT JJ NNS IN JJ NN CC VBD RP NNS IN DT NNS TO NNP CC NNP .
"Top Palestinian negotiator Saeb Erekat called Sunday 's attacks by the al-Aqsa Martyrs Brigades "" unfortunate , "" and designed to sabotage peace talks with Israel .",O B-gpe O B-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"JJ JJ NN NNP NNP VBD NNP POS NNS IN DT JJ NNPS NNPS LQU JJ , LQU CC VBN TO VB NN NNS IN NNP ."
He also said Israeli travel restrictions will not move the peace process forward .,O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,PRP RB VBD JJ NN NNS MD RB VB DT NN NN RB .
