A group of Republican members of the U.S. Congress plans to unveil proposed spending cuts on Wednesday to pay for Hurricane Katrina relief and recovery efforts .,O O O B-org O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN NNP NNS IN DT NNP NNP VBZ TO VB JJ NN NNS IN NNP TO VB IN NNP NNP NN CC NN NNS .
"Members of the group have said they want to cut projects from a recently-passed transportation bill , and delay the start of the government 's prescription-drug coverage plan .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN DT NN VBP VBN PRP VBP TO VB NNS IN DT JJ NN NN , CC VB DT NN IN DT NN POS JJ NN NN ."
The New York Times says the group of congress members may also suggest shutting down the U.S. space agency 's plan to send astronauts back to the Moon .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT NN IN NN NNS MD RB VB VBG IN DT NNP NN NN POS NN TO VB NNS RB TO DT NN .
"Congress has already approved more than 62-billion dollars in hurricane relief , with tens of billions more expected as New Orleans and other hurricane-ravaged areas begin to rebuild .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ RB VBN JJR IN JJ NNS IN NN NN , IN NNS IN NNS RBR VBN IN NNP NNP CC JJ JJ NNS VBP TO VB ."
House Majority Leader Tom DeLay has come out against any change to the transportation bill .,B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN RP IN DT NN TO DT NN NN .
But the group of House Republicans says the cuts are needed to avoid increasing the debt burden on future generations .,O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC DT NN IN NNP NNPS VBZ DT NNS VBP VBN TO VB VBG DT NN NN IN JJ NNS .
