The United Nations says restrictions imposed by Eritrea have limited the U.N. 's ability to watch the tense Eritrea-Ethiopia border .,O B-org I-org O O O O B-geo O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ NNS VBN IN NNP VBP VBN DT NNP POS NN TO VB DT NN NN NN .
"A new report from Secretary-General Kofi Annan , released late Friday , says U.N. observers are able to monitor just 40 percent of the territory in their mandated area .",O O O O O B-per I-per O O O B-tim O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN IN JJ NNP NNP , VBN JJ NNP , VBZ NNP NNS VBP JJ TO VB RB CD NN IN DT NN IN PRP$ VBN NN ."
"It says the observers ' ability to give timely warning of any military action along the border has been "" seriously reduced . """,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ DT NNS POS NN TO VB JJ NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN VBZ VBN LQU RB VBN . LQU
Eritrea has kept restrictions on U.N. helicopter flights and ground patrols despite a Security Council demand that the restrictions be lifted .,B-geo O O O O B-org O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN NNS IN NNP NN NNS CC NN NNS IN DT NNP NNP NN IN DT NNS VB VBN .
Eritrean leaders say the U.N. is doing too little to make Ethiopia accept a borderline drawn up by an independent panel .,B-gpe O O O B-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP DT NNP VBZ VBG RB JJ TO VB NNP VB DT NN VBN RP IN DT JJ NN .
"The countries fought a two-year border war ending in 2000 that killed 70,000 people .",O O O O B-tim O O O O B-tim O O O O O,DT NNS VBD DT JJ NN NN VBG IN CD WDT VBD CD NNS .
