"A new U.S. Census Bureau report says Hispanics accounted for almost half of the population growth in the U.S. last year , and most of those new residents were born in the United States instead of Latin America .",O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo I-geo I-geo O,"DT JJ NNP NNP NNP NN VBZ NNS VBD IN RB NN IN DT NN NN IN DT NNP JJ NN , CC JJS IN DT JJ NNS VBD VBN IN DT NNP NNPS IN IN NNP NNP ."
"The report suggests the Hispanic population boom would continue for at least a generation , even if immigration stopped .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ DT JJ NN NN MD VB IN IN JJS DT NN , RB IN NN VBD ."
"Meanwhile , the portion of the population descended from Europeans is both shrinking and getting older .",O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,"RB , DT NN IN DT NN VBD IN NNS VBZ DT NN CC VBG JJR ."
Analysts say the shift in age and ethnic make up could cause increased social strains .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP DT NN IN NN CC JJ VB RP MD VB VBN JJ NNS .
The United States is currently embroiled in a debate about regulating illegal immigration .,O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNPS VBZ RB VBN IN DT NN IN VBG JJ NN .
Hundreds of thousands of demonstrators have rallied across the country in recent weeks to demand more rights for illegal immigrants and to generally emphasize the importance of immigrants to the nation 's economy and culture .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNS IN NNS VBP VBN IN DT NN IN JJ NNS TO VB JJR NNS IN JJ NNS CC TO RB VB DT NN IN NNS TO DT NN POS NN CC NN .
