El Salvador has sent a fourth contingent of soldiers to Iraq .,B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN NNS TO NNP .
Officials say the troops will make a stop in Kuwait .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNS VBP DT NNS MD VB DT NN IN NNP .
The Salvadorans will replace 380 troops who have been in Iraq since last August .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O B-tim O,DT NNS MD VB CD NNS WP VBP VBN IN NNP IN JJ NNP .
El Salvador is the only Latin American country with troops in Iraq .,B-org I-org O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP VBZ DT RB JJ JJ NN IN NNS IN NNP .
"Last April , one Salvadoran soldier was killed and 12 others wounded during a clash with insurgents .",O B-tim O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP , CD JJ NN VBD VBN CC CD NNS VBN IN DT NN IN NNS ."
