"China has urged rival Taiwan to recognize its "" one-China "" policy as a condition for resuming talks frozen since 1999 .",B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,NNP VBZ VBN JJ NNP TO VB PRP$ RQU NNP RQU NN IN DT NN IN VBG NNS VBN IN CD .
Official media cited a spokesman for Beijing 's Taiwan Affairs Office Sunday as blaming tensions across the Taiwan Strait on authorities in Taipei who do not recognize the one-China principle .,O O O O O O B-geo O B-org I-org I-org B-tim O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBD DT NN IN NNP POS NNP NNP NNP NNP IN VBG NNS IN DT NNP NNP IN NNS IN NNP WP VBP RB VB DT NNP NN .
"China said it was responding to a joint declaration by Taiwan President Chen Shui-bian and the island 's opposition leader , James Soong .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-org B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-per I-per O,"NNP VBD PRP VBD VBG TO DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP CC DT NN POS NN NN , NNP NNP ."
Their statement on Thursday vowed that no possibilities would be ruled out in future ties between China and Taiwan .,O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,PRP$ NN IN NNP VBD IN DT NNS MD VB VBN RP IN JJ NNS IN NNP CC NNP .
"Mr. Chen also promised not to declare independence , change the country 's official name or promote a referendum on independence that would alter the status quo .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP RB VBD RB TO VB NN , VB DT NN POS JJ NN CC VB DT NN IN NN WDT MD VB DT NN NN ."
China sees Taiwan as part of its territory and has threatened to invade if it declares independence .,B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ NNP IN NN IN PRP$ NN CC VBZ VBN TO VB IN PRP VBZ NN .
