A prominent U.S. senator has demanded a probe into allegations that the federal agency charged with guarding drug safety is attempting to discredit an agency whistleblower .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNP NN VBZ VBN DT NN IN NNS IN DT JJ NN VBN IN VBG NN NN VBZ VBG TO VB DT NN NN .
"Senate Finance Chairman Charles Grassley , a Republican wrote the Health and Human Services Department Wednesday to request an investigation of defaming phone calls about Food and Drug Administration , FDA , safety officer David Graham .",B-org I-org O B-per I-per O O B-org O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O B-per I-per O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP , DT NNP VBD DT NNP CC NNP NNP NNP NNP TO VB DT NN IN VBG NN NNS IN NNP CC NNP NNP , NNP , NN NN NNP NNP ."
"The phone calls were received by the Government Accountability Project , a public interest group that defends whistleblowers .",O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN NNS VBD VBN IN DT NNP NNP NNP , DT JJ NN NN WDT VBZ NNS ."
"Dr. Graham alleges the calls are a response to his congressional testimony last week during which he said the FDA has abandoned its watchdog role for a cozy relationship with the pharmaceutical industry , a charge the agency denies .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ DT NNS VBP DT NN TO PRP$ JJ NN JJ NN IN WDT PRP VBD DT NNP VBZ VBN PRP$ NN NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN , DT NN DT NN VBZ ."
He told Congress the FDA has left consumers virtually defenseless against unsafe prescription drugs .,O O B-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD NNP DT NNP VBZ VBN NNS RB JJ IN JJ NN NNS .
"He also said five drugs on the market , besides the recently withdrawn pain medication Vioxx , need further review .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O,"PRP RB VBD CD NNS IN DT NN , IN DT RB VBN NN NN NNP , VBP JJ NN ."
