German Chancellor Gerhard Schroeder is traveling to China and Japan this week to discuss business ties and the European Union 's arms embargo against China .,B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-geo O,JJ NN NNP NNP VBZ VBG TO NNP CC NNP DT NN TO VB NN NNS CC DT NNP NNP POS NNS NN IN NNP .
"Mr. Schroeder , who is making his sixth visit to China , is to meet Monday in Beijing with Prime Minister Wen Jiabao .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim O B-geo O B-per O B-per I-per O,"NNP NNP , WP VBZ VBG PRP$ JJ NN TO NNP , VBZ TO VB NNP IN NNP IN NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
He will see President Hu Jintao on Tuesday .,O O O B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O,PRP MD VB NNP NNP NNP IN NNP .
"The German chancellor opposes the European Union 's continuing ban on weapons sales to China , imposed after Beijing 's bloody crackdown 15 years ago on pro-democracy demonstrators in Tiananmen Square .",O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"DT JJ NN VBZ DT NNP NNP POS VBG NN IN NNS NNS TO NNP , VBN IN NNP POS JJ NN CD NNS RB IN JJ NNS IN NNP NNP ."
"The arms embargo has strained contacts between China and the European Union , which otherwise have good trade and diplomatic relations .",O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS NN VBZ VBN NNS IN NNP CC DT NNP NNP , WDT RB VBP JJ NN CC JJ NNS ."
Mr. Schroeder will travel to Tokyo on Wednesday for two days of talks with with Japanese officials .,B-per I-per O O O B-geo O B-tim O B-tim O O O O O B-gpe O O,NNP NNP MD VB TO NNP IN NNP IN CD NNS IN NNS IN IN JJ NNS .
