Venezuelan President Hugo Chavez says authorities have confiscated some 2.5 metric tons of cocaine and arrested 11 suspected drug smugglers in a raid on a hidden airstrip in a remote eastern region .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNS VBP VBN DT CD JJ NNS IN NN CC VBN CD JJ NN NNS IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ JJ NN .
Mr. Chavez said the drugs were found in a private plane that had been registered in the United States .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP NNP VBD DT NNS VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN WDT VBD VBN VBN IN DT NNP NNPS .
Venezuela has been criticized recently by Washington for failing to fight drug trafficking effectively .,B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN VBN RB IN NNP IN VBG TO VB NN NN RB .
Venezuela serves as a corridor for illegal drugs moving from Colombia to the United State or Europe .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O,NNP VBZ IN DT NN IN JJ NNS VBG IN NNP TO DT NNP NNP CC NNP .
