Bulgaria 's parliament has approved a plan to withdraw all Bulgarian troops from Iraq by the end of the year .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O B-tim I-tim O O O,NNP POS NN VBZ VBN DT NN TO VB DT JJ NNS IN NNP IN DT NN IN DT NN .
The decision in Sofia Thursday finalizes a March proposal by the government of Prime Minister Simeon Saxe-Coburg-Gotha to withdraw the 450-soldiers by December .,O O O B-geo B-tim O O B-tim O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-tim O,DT NN IN NNP NNP VBZ DT NNP NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP TO VB DT NNS IN NNP .
"It also comes one month before voters , many opposed to the troop deployment , elect a new parliament .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP RB VBZ CD NN IN NNS , JJ JJ TO DT NN NN , VB DT JJ NN ."
"Opposition Socialists , who have been ahead in opinion polls , oppose Bulgaria 's continued involvement in Iraq .",B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O,"NNP NNPS , WP VBP VBN RB IN NN NNS , VBP NNP POS JJ NN IN NNP ."
"Nine Bulgarian soldiers have been killed in the war-torn country , including one by U.S. troops in a friendly fire incident .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"CD JJ NNS VBP VBN VBN IN DT JJ NN , VBG CD IN NNP NNS IN DT JJ NN NN ."
