"China 's 10th National Games have ended in Nanjing , with nearly 10,000 athletes competing in 32 sports at the quadrennial event .",B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ NNP NNPS VBP VBN IN NNP , IN RB CD NNS VBG IN CD NNS IN DT JJ NN ."
"International Olympic Committee president Jacques Rogge praised China 's organization of the Games Sunday , saying he was confident it would translate into a successful 2008 Summer Olympics in Beijing .",O O B-org O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O B-geo O,"NNP NNP NNP NN NNP NNP VBD NNP POS NN IN DT NNPS NNP , VBG PRP VBD JJ PRP MD VB IN DT JJ CD NNP NNPS IN NNP ."
"While numerous Olympic medalists were crowned champion , a new generation of young athletes also made its mark .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN JJ NNP NNS VBD JJ NN , DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS RB VBD PRP$ NN ."
China is hoping to top the medal table at the Beijing Olympics after coming third in Athens and trailing the United States by just three in the gold medal tally .,B-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBG TO VB DT NN NN IN DT NNP NNPS IN VBG JJ IN NNP CC VBG DT NNP NNPS IN RB CD IN DT NN NN RB .
"But the National Games were also tainted by the positive dope test of star distance runner Sun Yingjie , a reminder of Chinese drugs scandals of the past .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,"CC DT NNP NNPS VBD RB VBN IN DT JJ NN NN IN NN NN NN NNP NNP , DT NN IN JJ NNS NNS IN DT NN ."
