A South African group has presented one of its highest honors - the Mahatma Gandhi prize - to a representative of Burmese democracy leader Aung San Suu Kyi .,O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O,DT JJ JJ NN VBZ VBN CD IN PRP$ JJS NNS IN DT NNP NNP NN : TO DT NN IN JJ NN NN NNP NNP NNP NNP .
The prize is awarded by the Gandhi Development Trust in honor of India 's political and spiritual leader during that country 's movement for independence from Britain .,O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NN VBZ VBN IN DT NNP NNP NNP IN NN IN NNP POS JJ CC JJ NN IN DT NN POS NN IN NN IN NNP .
The award was presented Monday to Sein Win - the prime minister of the self-proclaimed government-in-exile - at a ceremony in the South African city of Durban .,O O O O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O,DT NN VBD VBN NNP IN NNP NNP IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ JJ : IN DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP .
"The award , created in 2003 , was given last year to anti-apartheid leader Nelson Mandela .",O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O,"DT NN , VBN IN CD , VBD VBN JJ NN TO JJ NN NNP NNP ."
Aung San Suu Kyi is in prison in Rangoon facing a trial on charges of violating the terms of her house arrest .,B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ IN NN IN NNP VBG DT NN IN NNS IN VBG DT NNS IN PRP$ NN NN .
