The government of the Central African Republic has signed a peace accord with two of the country 's main rebel groups .,O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN NN IN CD IN DT NN POS JJ NN NNS .
The agreement was signed Saturday in the West African nation of Gabon .,O O O O B-tim O B-geo I-geo B-gpe O O B-geo O,DT NN VBD VBN NNP IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP .
The deal calls for the demobilization of all rebel fighters as well as their reintegration into civilian life .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ IN DT NN IN DT NN NNS RB RB IN PRP$ NN IN JJ NN .
It was signed by the members of the C.A.R. government and rebels from the Popular Army for the Restoration of Democracy ( APRD ) and the Union of Democratic Forces Coalition .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,PRP VBD VBN IN DT NNS IN DT NNP NN CC NNS IN DT NNP NNP IN DT NN IN NN LRB NNP RRB CC DT NNP IN JJ NNS NN .
The ceremony was also attended by C.A.R. President Francois Bozize and his Gabonese counterpart Omar Bongo Ondimba .,O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-per I-per I-per O,DT NN VBD RB VBN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP CC PRP$ JJ NN NNP NNP NNP .
The Central African Republic has suffered through decades of coups and rebellions since gaining independence in 1960 .,O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NNS IN NNS CC NNS IN VBG NN IN CD .
"The United Nations says unrest in the country has forced more than 300,000 people to flee their homes .",O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ NN IN DT NN VBZ VBN JJR IN CD NNS TO VB PRP$ NNS .
