Britain 's defense ministry has given the long-awaited go-ahead for a nearly $ 8 billion deal to build two aircraft carriers that will be the Royal Navy 's largest warships .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O,NNP POS NN NN VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN DT RB $ CD CD NN TO VB CD NN NNS WDT MD VB DT NNP NNP POS JJS NNS .
"Authorities say the contract for the 65,000-ton carriers , the HMS Queen Elizabeth and the HMS Prince of Wales , will safeguard about 10,000 jobs in Britain 's shipbuilding sector .",O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"NNS VBP DT NN IN DT JJ NNS , DT NNP NNP NNP CC DT NNP NNP IN NNP , MD VB IN CD NNS IN NNP POS NN NN ."
Blueprints show the 280-meter-long ships carrying up to 40 aircraft .,O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP DT JJ NNS VBG RP TO CD NN .
They are expected to be launched by 2016 .,O O O O O O O B-tim O,PRP VBP VBN TO VB VBN IN CD .
"Defense Minister Des Brown said Tuesday the ships will provide British forces with "" modern , world-class capabilities . """,O B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP DT NNS MD VB JJ NNS IN LQU JJ , JJ NNS . LQU"
"Britain 's largest defense firm , BAE Systems , will join the VT Group as part of a consortium that will build the new carriers in shipyards in Scotland and England .",B-geo O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,"NNP POS JJS NN NN , NNP NNPS , MD VB DT NNP NNP IN NN IN DT NN WDT MD VB DT JJ NNS IN NNS IN NNP CC NNP ."
Authorities say contracts are likely to be signed next month .,O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP NNS VBP JJ TO VB VBN JJ NN .
