The European Union has warned Serbia that it may freeze negotiations on closer ties if Belgrade does not cooperate fully in capturing fugitive war crimes suspect Ratko Mladic .,O B-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNP IN PRP MD VB NNS IN JJR NNS IN NNP VBZ RB VB RB IN VBG JJ NN NNS VBP NNP NNP .
EU enlargement chief Olli Rehn issued the threat Thursday as he prepared to publish a highly anticipated report next week on Serbia 's progress towards EU standards .,B-org O O B-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-org O O,NNP NN NN NNP NNP VBD DT NN NNP IN PRP VBD TO VB DT RB JJ NN JJ NN IN NNP POS NN IN NNP NNS .
Rehn told a committee of the European Parliament that Serbia 's cooperation includes Mladic 's arrest and transfer .,B-per O O O O O B-org I-org O B-geo O O O B-org O O O O O,NNP VBD DT NN IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP POS NN VBZ NNP POS NN CC NN .
The U.N. War Crimes Tribunal has indicted the former top Bosnian Serb military commander for attacks on civilians during the conflict of the 1990s in Bosnia-Herzegovina .,O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-gpe I-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O,DT NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ JJ JJ JJ JJ NN IN NNS IN NNS IN DT NN IN DT NNS IN NNP .
Many Serbs regard the handover of Mladic to the tribunal as necessary to boost Serbia 's hopes of eventual EU membership .,O B-gpe O O O O B-org O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-org O O,JJ NNS VBP DT NN IN NNP TO DT NN IN JJ TO VB NNP POS NNS IN JJ NNP NN .
But others view Mladic as a hero .,O O O B-org O O O O,CC NNS VBP NNP IN DT NN .
