"Spain 's High Court has convicted a suspected al-Qaida cell leader of conspiracy in the plotting of the September 11 , 2001 attacks on the United States in Europe 's biggest terror trial .",B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O,"NNP POS NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NNP NN NN IN NN IN DT NN IN DT NNP CD , CD NNS IN DT NNP NNPS IN NNP POS JJS NN NN ."
The court sentenced Imad Eddin Barakat Yarkas to 27 years in prison .,O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-tim O O O O,DT NN VBD NNP NNP NNP NNP TO CD NNS IN NN .
"Prosecutors say he arranged a meeting in Spain of key planners of the attacks in July , 2001 .",O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,"NNS VBP PRP VBD DT NN IN NNP IN JJ NNS IN DT NNS IN NNP , CD ."
Two other suspects were acquitted of charges related to the attacks .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,CD JJ NNS VBD VBN IN NNS VBN TO DT NNS .
The court also sentenced al-Jazeera correspondent Tayssir Alouni to seven years in prison for carrying money to al-Qaida members in Afghanistan .,O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-geo O,DT NN RB VBD JJ NN NNP NNP TO CD NNS IN NN IN VBG NN TO NNP NNS IN NNP .
Al-Jazeera denounced the verdict .,B-geo O O O O,NNP VBD DT NN .
"Media rights group Reporters Without Borders says the conviction was linked to Alouni 's job , because prosecutors repeatedly referred to his 2001 interview with al-Qaida leader Osama bin Laden in Afghanistan .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-org O B-per I-per I-per O B-geo O,"NN NNS NN VBZ IN NNS VBZ DT NN VBD VBN TO NNP POS NN , IN NNS RB VBD TO PRP$ CD NN IN NNP NN NNP NNP NNP IN NNP ."
Sixteen other suspects were convicted of charges of collaborating with or belonging to a terrorist group .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CD JJ NNS VBD VBN IN NNS IN VBG IN CC VBG TO DT JJ NN .
