Iranian officials are denying a Canadian newspaper report that the parliament in Tehran is considering a bill that would require non-Muslims to wear colored labels .,B-gpe O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBG DT JJ NN NN IN DT NN IN NNP VBZ VBG DT NN WDT MD VB JJ TO VB JJ NNS .
"The officials say there is no law under consideration that requires colored identification labels for Jews , Christians and Zoroastrians .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,"DT NNS VBP EX VBZ DT NN IN NN WDT VBZ VBN NN NNS IN NNPS , NNPS CC NNPS ."
"On Friday , the National Post newspaper in Canada said the Iranian parliament passed a law Monday that would force non-Muslims to wear colored identification labels .",O B-tim O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , DT NNP NNP NN IN NNP VBD DT JJ NN VBD DT NN NNP WDT MD VB JJ TO VB VBN NN NNS ."
"The Associated Press says it received a copy of the proposed legislation , and that it encourages the wearing of Islamic clothing , but not special attire for religious minorities .",B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBD DT NN IN DT VBN NN , CC IN PRP VBZ DT VBG IN JJ NN , CC RB JJ NN IN JJ NNS ."
"The U.S. State Department and the prime ministers of Canada and Australia expressed concern about the report , and said if true , the measure is abhorrent .",B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP NNP CC DT JJ NNS IN NNP CC NNP VBD NN IN DT NN , CC VBD IN JJ , DT NN VBZ JJ ."
