Experts from an international group opposed to the spread of nuclear arms have met with Pakistani officials to discuss non-proliferation efforts .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,NNS IN DT JJ NN VBN TO DT NN IN JJ NNS VBP VBN IN JJ NNS TO VB JJ NNS .
Monday 's meeting was the first between the Nuclear Suppliers Group and representatives of Pakistan 's Foreign Ministry .,B-tim O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,NNP POS NN VBD DT JJ IN DT NNP NNP NNP CC NNS IN NNP POS NNP NNP .
The talks focused on Pakistan 's desire to join the organization .,O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBD IN NNP POS NN TO VB DT NN .
Pakistani officials learned what criteria the Asian country would need to meet for membership in the group .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBD WP NNS DT JJ NN MD VB TO VB IN NN IN DT NN .
Pakistan contacted the 44-member organization earlier this year asking the group to join in coordinating the country 's non-proliferation efforts .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD DT JJ NN RBR DT NN VBG DT NN TO VB IN VBG DT NN POS JJ NNS .
The Nuclear Suppliers Group was formed in 1974 .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O B-tim O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBD VBN IN CD .
Its members monitor sensitive equipment from industrialized countries that could be used for illicit weapons .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP$ NNS VBP JJ NN IN JJ NNS WDT MD VB VBN IN JJ NNS .
The group also coordinates the implementation of guidelines that would govern nuclear and nuclear-related exports .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN RB VBZ DT NN IN NNS WDT MD VB JJ CC JJ NNS .
Pakistan became a nuclear power in 1998 .,B-org O O O O O B-tim O,NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN CD .
