"The foreign ministers of France , Italy and Spain are in Lebanon Saturday to urge rival factions to agree on the election of a new president as a step toward breaking a lengthy political deadlock .",O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNS IN NNP , NNP CC NNP VBP IN NNP NNP TO VB JJ NNS TO VB IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN VBG DT JJ JJ NN ."
"The one-day visits by Bernard Kouchner of France , Massimo D'Alema of Italy and Miguel Angel Moratinos of Spain come three days before Lebanon 's parliament is to make another attempt to select a new president .",O B-tim O O B-per I-per O B-geo O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O B-per I-per I-per O B-geo O B-tim O B-tim B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNS IN NNP NNP IN NNP , NNP NNP IN NNP CC NNP NNP NNP IN NNP VBD CD NNS IN NNP POS NN VBZ TO VB DT NN TO VB DT JJ NN ."
The ministers are to meet in with top pro-government and opposition political leaders .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP TO VB IN IN JJ NN CC NN JJ NNS .
"A first parliamentary session in September was postponed due to disagreement between the ruling anti-Syrian majority and Hezbollah-led pro-Syrian opposition , and it is feared Tuesday 's session will also end in failure .",O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP VBD VBN JJ TO NN IN DT NN JJ NN CC JJ JJ NN , CC PRP VBZ VBN NNP POS NN MD RB VB IN NN ."
"If the deadlock continues , some fear the country could end up with two rival governments .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN VBZ , DT VBP DT NN MD VB RP IN CD JJ NNS ."
