A top Chinese swimmer has been banned for life for doping only six weeks before the start of the Beijing Olympics .,O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT JJ JJ NN VBZ VBN VBN IN NN IN VBG RB CD NNS IN DT NN IN DT NNP NNPS .
"The Chinese Swimming Association said Friday , it imposed a lifetime ban against star backstroker Ouyang Kunpeng after he failed an out-of-competition drug test on May 1 .",O B-gpe B-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"DT JJ NNP NNP VBD NNP , PRP VBD DT NN NN IN NN NN NNP NNP IN PRP VBD DT JJ NN NN IN NNP CD ."
"Ouyang 's coach , Feng Shangbao , also received a life-time ban .",B-per O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NN , NNP NNP , RB VBD DT JJ NN ."
The association says it is cracking down on doping violations .,O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ PRP VBZ VBG RP IN VBG NNS .
Ouyang competed in the 2004 Athens Olympics and won three silver medals at the 2006 Asian Games .,B-per O O O B-tim B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,NNP VBD IN DT CD NNPS NNPS CC VBD CD NN NNS IN DT CD NNP NNPS .
The 25-year-old was considered perhaps Olympic host China 's best chance of winning a backstroke medal this August .,O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT JJ VBD VBN RB JJ NN NNP POS JJS NN IN VBG DT JJ NN DT NNP .
Ouyang is the biggest-name Chinese swimmer to fail a doping test for several years .,B-per O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-tim O O,NNP VBZ DT JJ JJ NN TO VB DT NN NN IN JJ NNS .
Chinese swimmers were involved in a series of doping scandals in the 1990s .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,JJ NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN IN NN NNS IN DT NNS .
