A South African film that sets a famous opera in a South African township has won the top prize at the Berlin International Film Festival .,O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,DT JJ JJ NN WDT VBZ DT JJ NN IN DT JJ JJ NN VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP .
The Xhosa-language U-Carmen eKhayelitsha took home the Golden Bear award .,O O O O O O O B-art I-art O O,DT JJ NNP NNP VBD NN DT NNP NNP NN .
"The film portrays Georges Bizet 's classic opera , Carmen , amid the struggles of life in a poor South African township .",O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"DT NN VBZ NNP NNP POS JJ NN , NNP , IN DT NNS IN NN IN DT JJ JJ JJ NN ."
"A Chinese film , The Kong Que , or Peacock , won the second place Silver Bear award .",O B-gpe O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-per O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN , DT NNP NNP , CC NNP , VBD DT JJ NN NNP NNP NN ."
"Marc Rothemund was given the Silver Bear for Best Director for Sophie Scholl - Die Letzten Tage , or Sophie Scholl - The Final Days .",B-per I-per O O O B-art I-art B-org I-org I-org O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD VBN DT NNP NNP IN NNP NNP IN NNP NNP : NNP NNP NNP , CC NNP NNP : DT JJ NNS ."
"Actress Julia Jentsch was honored with a Silver Bear for Best Actress for portraying Sophie Scholl , the real-life war-time resistance fighter who was killed by the Nazis .",O B-per I-per O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,"NN NNP NNP VBD VBN IN DT NN NNP IN NNP NNP IN VBG NNP NNP , DT JJ JJ NN NN WP VBD VBN IN DT NNPS ."
The Silver Bear for Best Actor went to Lou Taylor Pucci for his role as an insecure teenager in the U.S. film Thumbsucker .,O B-art I-art B-org B-art I-art O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,DT NNP NNP IN NNP NNP VBD TO NNP NNP NNP IN PRP$ NN IN DT NN NN IN DT NNP NN NN .
