"Kyrgyzstan 's ousted President Askar Akayev says he is prepared to formally resign , but only under certain conditions .",B-geo O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS VBN NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ VBN TO RB VB , CC RB IN JJ NNS ."
He did not specify .,O O O O O,PRP VBD RB VB .
"In an interview on Russian television , Mr. Akayev asked for what he called "" relevant legal protections "" for himself .",O O O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN IN JJ NN , NNP NNP VBD IN WP PRP VBD LQU JJ JJ NNS RQU IN PRP ."
"During his 15 years of rule , he was accused of corruption and nepotism .",O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN PRP$ CD NNS IN NN , PRP VBD VBN IN NN CC NN ."
"On Tuesday , he gave several interviews to Russian radio and television channels at his new residence outside Moscow .",O B-tim O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"IN NNP , PRP VBD JJ NNS TO JJ NN CC NN NNS IN PRP$ JJ NN IN NNP ."
"Mr. Akayev fled last Thursday when thousands of opposition activists stormed the seat of government and the presidential quarters in Bishkek , alleging that recent parliamentary elections were rigged .",B-per I-per O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD JJ NNP WRB NNS IN NN NNS VBD DT NN IN NN CC DT JJ NNS IN NNP , VBG IN JJ JJ NNS VBD VBN ."
"The new interim president , Kurmanbek Bakiyev , has pledged to fight corruption and help victims of the looting that followed last week 's uprising .",O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN NN , NNP NNP , VBZ VBN TO VB NN CC VB NNS IN DT NN WDT VBD JJ NN POS NN ."
Mr. Bakiyev told a gathering of government workers Tuesday that the battle against corruption and nepotism in government is his main goal .,B-per B-geo O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN NN NNS NNP IN DT NN IN NN CC NN IN NN VBZ PRP$ JJ NN .
