"FIFA president Sepp Blatter has denied allegations that football 's world governing body is corrupt and says England was a "" bad loser "" for complaining after Russia was chosen last week to host the 2018 World Cup .",B-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,NNP NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNS IN NN POS NN NN NN VBZ JJ CC VBZ NNP VBD DT LQU JJ NN LQU IN VBG IN NNP VBD VBN JJ NN TO VB DT CD NNP NNP .
"Blatter said Wednesday FIFA is "" financially clean and clear , "" but acknowledged it needs to improve its image .",B-per O B-tim B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD NNP NNP VBZ LQU RB JJ CC JJ , LQU CC VBD PRP VBZ TO VB PRP$ NN ."
He promised to form a task force to look into compliance issues .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD TO VB DT NN NN TO VB IN NN NNS .
England bid officials accused FIFA executive committee members of not delivering votes they had promised .,B-geo O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NN NNS VBD NNP JJ NN NNS IN RB VBG NNS PRP VBD VBN .
England 's 2018 bid chief Andy Anson claimed Blatter influenced committee members against England 's bid by reminding them of British media reports that resulted in two members being banned .,B-geo O B-tim O O B-per I-per O B-per O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS CD NN NN NNP NNP VBD NNP VBD NN NNS IN NNP POS NN IN VBG PRP IN JJ NNS NNS WDT VBD IN CD NNS VBG VBN .
"Blatter also said England 's reaction was an example of the arrogance of the western world , and that is unhappy when "" others get a chance for a change . """,B-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP RB VBD NNP POS NN VBD DT NN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN , CC DT VBZ JJ WRB LQU NNS VBP DT NN IN DT NN . LQU"
