Israeli officials have confirmed that the United Nations is investigating the alleged sale of Israeli arms to Ivory Coast - a possible violation of a U.N. arms embargo against the West African country .,B-gpe O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-gpe O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN IN DT NNP NNP VBZ VBG DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS TO NNP NNP IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNS NN IN DT JJ JJ NN .
Israeli Foreign Ministry spokesman Mark Regev Thursday said that Israel is cooperating fully with the U.N. probe .,B-gpe B-org I-org O B-per I-per B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O B-org O O,JJ NNP NNP NN NNP NNP NNP VBD IN NNP VBZ VBG RB IN DT NNP NN .
Israeli officials say a U.N. team was in Israel this week to look into possible violations of the arms embargo against Ivory Coast .,B-gpe O O O B-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,JJ NNS VBP DT NNP NN VBD IN NNP DT NN TO VB IN JJ NNS IN DT NNS NN IN NNP NNP .
Israeli officials have denied any wrongdoing .,B-gpe O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN DT NN .
The U.N. Security Council unanimously imposed the embargo last November to try and stop a renewal of fighting in the country .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP RB VBD DT NN JJ NNP TO VB CC VB DT NN IN VBG IN DT NN .
The French-drafted resolution prohibits arms sales to both Ivory Coast 's government and rebels in the north .,O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBZ NNS NNS TO DT NNP NNP POS NN CC NNS IN DT NN .
It also allows U.N. and French peacekeepers to inspect cargo shipments into the country .,O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O,PRP RB VBZ NNP CC NNP NNS TO VB NN NNS IN DT NN .
