"The Serbian parliament has overwhelmingly approved a new constitution that declares Kosovo part of the country , despite ongoing United Nations-mediated talks on the status of the province .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBZ RB VBN DT JJ NN WDT VBZ NNP NN IN DT NN , IN JJ NNP NNP NNS IN DT NN IN DT NN ."
The parliament also voted Saturday to put the draft constitution to a referendum on October 28 and 29 .,O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim O,DT NN RB VBD NNP TO VB DT NN NN TO DT NN IN NNP CD CC CD .
"Prime Minister Vojislav Kostunica said the draft affirms that "" Kosovo is an integral part of Serbia . """,O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-geo O O,JJ NN NNP NNP VBD DT NN VBZ IN LQU NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN NNP . RQU
Serbia 's troubled Kosovo province has been under United Nations administration since 1999 when NATO bombing halted Belgrade 's crackdown on ethnic Albanian separatists .,B-geo O O B-geo O O O O B-org I-org O B-tim I-tim O B-org O O B-gpe O O O O B-gpe O O,NNP POS JJ NNP NN VBZ VBN IN NNP NNP NN IN CD WRB NNP NN VBD NNP POS NN IN JJ JJ NNS .
"The ethnic Albanians insist on independence , but the Serb minority and Belgrade both want Serbia to retain some control over the area .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-gpe O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNS VBP IN NN , CC DT JJ NN CC NNP DT VBP NNP TO VB DT NN IN DT NN ."
The constitution replaces the one drafted by former leader Slobodan Milosevic in 1990 .,O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O B-tim O,DT NN VBZ DT CD VBN IN JJ NN NNP NNP IN CD .
"It treats Serbia as an independent state , following the breakup of the former Yugoslavia .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"PRP VBZ NNP IN DT JJ NN , VBG DT NN IN DT JJ NNP ."
