About 100 protesters on the Indonesian island of Bali held a protest Monday calling for the swift execution of three men convicted of the 2002 Bali bombing .,O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O,IN CD NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NNP VBD DT NN NNP NN IN DT JJ NN IN CD NNS VBN IN DT CD NNP NN .
"The three central figures in the 2002 attack have been sentenced to death , but convicts often wait years on Indonesia 's death row .",O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"DT CD JJ NNS IN DT CD NN VBP VBN VBN TO NN , CC NNS RB VBP NNS IN NNP POS NN NN ."
"The protesters , many wearing traditional Balinese clothing , gathered outside the High Court in Bali 's provincial capital , Denpasar .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-geo O O O O B-geo O,"DT NNS , JJ VBG JJ JJ NN , VBD IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP POS JJ NN , NNP ."
Wednesday is the third anniversary of the blasts that killed 202 people in Kuta .,B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN DT NNS WDT VBD CD NNS IN NNP .
Anger over terrorist acts in Bali is especially strong in the run-up to the anniversary because of the recent Kuta and Jimbaran bombings that killed 20 people and the three bombers October 1 .,O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,NNP IN JJ NNS IN NNP VBZ RB JJ IN DT NN TO DT NN IN IN DT JJ NNP CC NNP NNS WDT VBD CD NNS CC DT CD NNS NNP CD .
