"The Fédération Internationale de Football Association , the governing body of world football , or soccer , has agreed to increase its spending on tsunami relief by $ 2.8 million .",O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP , DT NN NN IN NN NN , CC NN , VBZ VBN TO VB PRP$ NN IN NN NN IN $ CD CD ."
"Sri Lanka will get $ 1.5 million , the most money of any countries receiving a portion of the new payment .",B-per B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP MD VB $ CD CD , DT RBS NN IN DT NNS VBG DT NN IN DT JJ NN ."
That sum will be distributed to 13 projects across the country .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN MD VB VBN TO CD NNS IN DT NN .
"Thailand will get about $ 449,000 , which will be used to build the Tsunami Memorial Football Center .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,"NNP MD VB RB $ CD , WDT MD VB VBN TO VB DT NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
"Maldives will get $ 441 , 500 to fix that country 's football association 's headquarters and national training center .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNPS MD VB $ CD , CD TO VB DT NN POS NN NN POS NN CC JJ NN NN ."
"The money will come from a tsunami relief fund operated jointly by FIFA and the Asian Football Confederation , created in response to last December 's catastrophe .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-tim O O O,"DT NN MD VB IN DT NN NN NN VBN RB IN NNP CC DT NNP NNP NNP , VBN IN NN TO JJ NNP POS NN ."
