The U.S. military says Afghan and coalition forces have destroyed what they called a Taleban headquarters and killed 25 militants in southern Afghanistan .,O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNP NN VBZ JJ CC NN NNS VBP VBN WP PRP VBD DT NNP NN CC VBD CD NNS IN JJ NNP .
"The military says soldiers raided two Taleban compounds near Kandahar city late Saturday , following intelligence reports that the rebels were trying to re-establish control in the area .",O O O O O O B-org O O B-geo O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ VBZ NNS VBD CD NNP NNS IN NNP NN JJ NNP , VBG NN NNS IN DT NNS VBD VBG TO VB NN IN DT NN ."
The military says the troops called in air strikes after insurgents opened fire and one man blew himself up in a suicide attack .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ VBZ DT NNS VBN IN NN NNS IN NNS VBD NN CC CD NN VBD PRP RP IN DT NN NN .
It says there were no casualties among Afghan and coalition soldiers .,O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O,PRP VBZ EX VBD DT NNS IN JJ CC NN NNS .
"In other violence , Afghan police say a bomb attached to a bicycle exploded in the northern city of Mazar-e-Sharif late Saturday .",O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O,"IN JJ NN , JJ NNS VBP DT NN VBN TO DT NN VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP JJ NNP ."
Nine people were wounded in the attack .,O O O O O O O O,CD NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN .
