"Iran says it has developed a new , 900-kilogram guided "" smart "" bomb that it says can be fired from its aging fleet of U.S.-built F-4 and F-5 fighter jets .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ PRP VBZ VBN DT JJ , JJ JJ LQU JJ RQU NN IN PRP VBZ MD VB VBN IN PRP$ VBG NN IN JJ NN CC NN NN NNS ."
The state-run Islamic Republic News Agency ( IRNA ) made an announcement about the weapon on Wednesday and state-run television reported it Thursday .,O O B-geo I-geo B-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-tim O,DT JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP RRB VBD DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP CC JJ NN VBD PRP NNP .
"The Iranian news agency says the bomb , called Qased or Messenger , is "" one of the most powerful , modern and intelligent bombs "" in the world .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN NN VBZ DT NN , VBN JJ CC NNP , VBZ LQU CD IN DT RBS JJ , JJ CC JJ NNS LQU IN DT NN ."
"The news agency says the bomb will be unveiled during Iran 's "" Government Week , "" which begins Friday .",O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"DT NN NN VBZ DT NN MD VB VBN IN NNP POS LQU NN NN , RQU WDT VBZ NNP ."
