The head of the U.S. foreign aid agency has warned that the cost of rebuilding from Hurricane Katrina may reduce available funds for international assistance .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN DT NNP JJ NN NN VBZ VBN IN DT NN IN VBG IN NNP NNP MD VB JJ NNS IN JJ NN .
"Administrator of the U.S. Agency for International Development , Andrew Natsios , said he discussed the issue with foreign diplomats Thursday on the sidelines of the U.N. General Assembly meeting .",O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O,"NNP IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP NNP , NNP NNP , VBD PRP VBD DT NN IN JJ NNS NNP IN DT NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP NN ."
"He told reporters that Washington is trying to lower the expectations of some governments , which have been calling for aid increases .",O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD NNS IN NNP VBZ VBG TO VB DT NNS IN DT NNS , WDT VBP VBN VBG IN NN NNS ."
But Mr. Natsios said Washington will maintain its commitment to helping failed states that U.S. officials fear could become havens for international terrorists .,O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,CC NNP NNP VBD NNP MD VB PRP$ NN TO VBG VBN NNS IN NNP NNS VBP MD VB NNS IN JJ NNS .
"Congress has already approved $ 62 billion for hurricane recovery efforts , and may be asked to authorize more next month .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,"NNP VBZ RB VBN $ CD CD IN NN NN NNS , CC MD VB VBN TO VB RBR JJ NN ."
