Russian state-controlled gas firm Gazprom has filed an appeal in U.S. district court seeking to overturn a judge 's order blocking the auction of Yukos ' main oil producing subsidiary .,B-gpe O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O,JJ JJ NN NN NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN NNP NN NN VBG TO VB DT NN POS NN VBG DT NN IN NNP POS JJ NN VBG NN .
"Yukos , which has financial holdings in the United States , filed for bankruptcy in Texas this week and won a 10-day restraining order against the sale from a court in Houston .",B-org O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP , WDT VBZ JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNPS , VBD IN NN IN NNP DT NN CC VBD DT JJ NN NN IN DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP ."
Russia said earlier it would proceed with the auction Sunday disregarding the U.S. court 's order .,B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O,NNP VBD JJR PRP MD VB IN DT NN NNP VBG DT NNP NN POS NN .
"Russian officials say the sale of Yuganskneftgaz is in accord with Russian law , and U.S. courts have no jurisdiction .",B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP DT NN IN NNP VBZ IN NN IN JJ NN , CC NNP NNS VBP DT NN ."
"However , Gazprom is facing trouble in securing financing from U.S. and European banks which reportedly put on hold a $ 10 billion loan awaiting the U.S. court 's final decision .",O O B-org O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,"RB , NNP VBZ VBG NN IN VBG NN IN NNP CC JJ NNS WDT RB VBD IN NN DT $ CD CD NN VBG DT NNP NN POS JJ NN ."
Russian authorities ordered the sale to help cover Yukos ' tax bill of more than $ 27 billion .,B-gpe O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O B-tim O O,JJ NNS VBD DT NN TO VB VB NNP POS NN NN IN JJR IN $ CD CD .
