Pakistani police officials say gunmen kidnapped a Polish engineer in northern Pakistan Sunday and killed three Pakistanis during the abduction .,B-gpe O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo B-tim O O O B-gpe O O O O,JJ NN NNS VBP NNS VBD DT JJ NN IN JJ NNP NNP CC VBD CD NNS IN DT NN .
Authorities say the kidnapping took place in the Attock district of the Punjab province .,O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-org O O,NNS VBP DT NN VBD NN IN DT NNP NN IN DT NNP NN .
"Officials say the kidnapped Pole worked for Geofizyka Krakow , an oil company .",O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O,"NNS VBP DT VBN NN VBD IN NNP NNP , DT NN NN ."
It was not immediately clear if the kidnappers planned to seek a ransom or make political demands in return for his release .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD RB RB JJ IN DT NNS VBN TO VB DT NN CC VB JJ NNS IN NN IN PRP$ NN .
