Somali President Sheikh Sharif Sheikh Ahmed joined his troops on the front lines Wednesday night as they fought Islamist militants in the capital .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD PRP$ NNS IN DT NN NNS NNP NN IN PRP VBD NNP NNS IN DT NN .
"Witnesses and officials say the president , dressed in military fatigues , was stationed with Somali government forces and African Union peacekeepers .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo I-geo O O,"NNS CC NNS VBP DT NN , VBN IN JJ NNS , VBD VBN IN JJ NN NNS CC NNP NNP NNS ."
One presidential aide said Mr. Sharif was armed with an AK-47 rifle .,O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O,CD JJ NN VBD NNP NNP VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN .
At least seven people were killed in Mogadishu late Wednesday as government forces traded shell and gunfire with al-Shabab insurgents .,O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN IN NNP JJ NNP IN NN NNS VBD NN CC NN IN JJ NNS .
"Mr. Sharif was unhurt in the fighting , but a journalist told VOA 's Somali Service that a mortar shell landed about a third of a kilometer away from the president .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org B-gpe B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD JJ IN DT NN , CC DT NN VBD NNP POS JJ NNP IN DT NN NN VBD IN DT NN IN DT NN RB IN DT NN ."
"Mr. Sharif , a moderate Islamist , was elected by parliament 18 months ago to lead Somalia 's fragile transitional government .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O B-geo O O O O O,"NNP NNP , DT JJ NN , VBD VBN IN NN CD NNS RB TO VB NNP POS JJ JJ NN ."
The government controls only small parts of the capital after a three-and-a-half-year Islamist insurgency .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,DT NN VBZ RB JJ NNS IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN NN .
