"Authorities in Afghanistan say Taleban fighters ambushed a police patrol in the southern province of Kandahar late Friday , killing four police officers and wounding three .",O O B-geo O B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN NNP VBP NNP NNS VBD DT NN NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP JJ NNP , VBG CD NN NNS CC VBG CD ."
Police said the ambush occurred in the Panjwayi district .,O O O O O O O B-geo O O,NNS VBD DT NN VBD IN DT NNP NN .
There was no information about Taleban casualties .,O O O O O B-org O O,EX VBD DT NN IN NNP NNS .
"The police chief of southern Helmand province said Friday that NATO war planes bombarded a militant hideout during clashes in the Sangin district Thursday , killing 10 Taleban fighters .",O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O B-org O O,"DT NN NN IN JJ NNP NN VBD NNP IN NNP NN NNS VBD DT JJ NN IN NNS IN DT NNP NN NNP , VBG CD NNP NNS ."
"Some reports say a Taleban commander was killed , while other reports say he was wounded in the clashes with NATO and Afghan forces .",O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-gpe O O,"DT NNS VBP DT NNP NN VBD VBN , IN JJ NNS VBP PRP VBD VBN IN DT NNS IN NNP CC JJ NNS ."
"NATO did not confirm the number of Taleban casualties , but said no NATO troops were killed in the fighting .",B-org O O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD RB VB DT NN IN NNP NNS , CC VBD DT NNP NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN ."
Militant attacks are frequent in restive Kandahar and Helmand provinces .,O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O,JJ NNS VBP JJ IN JJ NNP CC NNP NNS .
