A children 's rights groups in Malawi has called on the government to delay plans for American pop star Madonna to adopt a one-year-old boy .,O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-per O O O O O O,DT NNS POS NNS NNS IN NNP VBZ VBN IN DT NN TO VB NNS IN JJ NN NN NNP TO VB DT JJ NN .
"The group Eye of the Child expressed concern Friday about the adoption process , saying it should not be like buying property .",O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN NN IN DT NN VBD NN NNP IN DT NN NN , VBG PRP MD RB VB IN VBG NN ."
"The group warned it may seek to block a court order this week granting interim approval for the adoption by Madonna and her husband , Guy Ritchie .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O B-per I-per O,"DT NN VBD PRP MD VB TO VB DT NN NN DT NN VBG JJ NN IN DT NN IN NNP CC PRP$ NN , NNP NNP ."
"Under Malawi law , the couple 's adoption will be reviewed for 18 months before the judge gives his final decision .",O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-tim O O O O O O O,"IN NNP NN , DT NN POS NN MD VB VBN IN CD NNS IN DT NN VBZ PRP$ JJ NN ."
"Madonna and her husband left the southern African nation Friday , ending a nine-day trip .",B-per O O O O O O B-gpe O B-tim O O O B-tim O O,"NNP CC PRP$ NN VBD DT JJ JJ NN NNP , VBG DT JJ NN ."
"But the one-year-old boy , David Banda , remained in the country because of ongoing legal procedures .",O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,"CC DT JJ NN , NNP NNP , VBD IN DT NN IN IN JJ JJ NNS ."
"Madonna arrived in Malawi last week , in part to inspect an orphan care center she is funding near Lilongwe .",B-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP VBD IN NNP JJ NN , IN NN TO VB DT JJ NN NN PRP VBZ VBG IN NNP ."
