The Hong Kong Department of Health reports Tuesday that the 31-year-old patient is being treated at a hospital in Shenzhen near Hong Kong .,O B-geo I-geo B-org I-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O,DT NNP NNP NNP IN NNP VBZ NNP IN DT JJ NN VBZ VBG VBN IN DT NN IN NNP IN NNP NNP .
They say he developed fever and pneumonia June 3 .,O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,PRP VBP PRP VBD NN CC NN NNP CD .
The health officials say the man reportedly had visited a local market in Shenzhen where live chickens were sold .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,DT NN NNS VBP DT NN RB VBD VBN DT JJ NN IN NNP WRB JJ NNS VBD VBN .
Officials in Hong Kong are urging the public to take health precautions and to watch for bird flu symtoms .,O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNP NNP VBP VBG DT NN TO VB NN NNS CC TO VB IN NN NN NNS .
There is a good deal of travel between the city and Guangdong province .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,EX VBZ DT JJ NN IN NN IN DT NN CC NNP NN .
Most of the victims have been in Asia .,O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJS IN DT NNS VBP VBN IN NNP .
