Afghan officials say a roadside bomb in southeastern Afghanistan has killed seven Afghan soldiers .,B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O,JJ NNS VBP DT NN NN IN JJ NNP VBZ VBN CD JJ NNS .
"Authorities say the bomb struck an Afghan army vehicle Wednesday in Paktika province , which borders Pakistan .",O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O B-geo O,"NNS VBP DT NN VBD DT JJ NN NN NNP IN NNP NN , WDT VBZ NNP ."
"Elsewhere , Afghan officials say militants ambushed a police vehicle late Tuesday in the country 's western Herat province , killing at least three police officers and wounding two others .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , JJ NNS VBP NNS VBD DT NN NN JJ NNP IN DT NN POS JJ NNP NN , VBG IN JJS CD NNS NNS CC VBG CD NNS ."
"Also on Tuesday , Afghan officials say Afghan and NATO forces clashed with Taleban insurgents in southern Zabul province .",O O B-tim O B-gpe O O B-gpe O B-org O O O B-org O O O B-geo O O,"RB IN NNP , JJ NNS VBP JJ CC NNP NNS VBD IN NNP NNS IN JJ NNP NN ."
Eleven militants were killed .,O O O O O,CD NNS VBD VBN .
"NATO and U.S.-led coalition troops have been fighting Taleban insurgents , whose attacks have increased dramatically over the past year .",B-org O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"NNP CC JJ NN NNS VBP VBN VBG NNP NNS , WP$ NNS VBP VBN RB IN DT JJ NN ."
