The U.S. military says it is investigating allegations that American soldiers in Afghanistan burned the bodies of two dead Taleban fighters and then used the act to taunt other Islamic militants .,O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBZ PRP VBZ VBG NNS IN JJ NNS IN NNP VBD DT NNS IN CD JJ NNP NNS CC RB VBD DT NN TO VB JJ JJ NNS .
"An Australian television network broadcast a video late Wednesday that purportedly showed U.S. soldiers burning the bodies on October 1 , outside a southern village near the former Taleban stronghold of Kandahar .",O B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-geo O,"DT JJ NN NN VBD DT NN JJ NNP IN RB VBD NNP NNS VBG DT NNS IN NNP CD , IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NNP NN IN NNP ."
"In the video , two soldiers from what was reported to be a U.S. Army psychological operations unit later read messages calling the Taleban "" cowardly dogs "" for allowing their fighters to be laid down facing West and burned .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,"IN DT NN , CD NNS IN WP VBD VBN TO VB DT NNP NNP JJ NNS NN RB VBD NNS VBG DT NNP RQU RB VBZ LQU IN VBG PRP$ NNS TO VB VBN RP VBG NNP CC VBN ."
The Muslim faith prohibits cremation .,O O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBZ NN .
"The messages were reportedly broadcast to the village , which was believed to be harboring Taleban fighters .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O,"DT NNS VBD RB VBN TO DT NN , WDT VBD VBN TO VB VBG NNP NNS ."
"The U.S. Central Command said desecration , abuse or inappropriate treatment of enemy combatants violate U.S. policies as well as the Geneva Convention .",O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-org I-org O,"DT NNP NNP NNP VBD NN , NN CC JJ NN IN NN NNS VBP NNP NNS RB RB IN DT NNP NNP ."
