Pakistani police say a bomb blast in the northwestern city of Peshawar killed a provincial lawmaker and wounded at least six other people .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP DT NN NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP VBD DT JJ NN CC VBD IN JJS CD JJ NNS .
Police said it appeared that the bomb was hidden in a motorcycle and then remotely detonated when secular party lawmaker Alamzeb Khan passed by in his vehicle .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O,NNP VBD PRP VBD IN DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NN CC RB RB VBN WRB JJ NN NN NNP NNP VBN IN IN PRP$ NN .
"The attack came shortly after President Barack Obama 's special envoy to Pakistan and Afghanistan , Richard Holbrooke , arrived in Peshawar .",O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-per I-per O O O B-geo O,"DT NN VBD RB IN NNP NNP NNP POS JJ NN TO NNP CC NNP , NNP NNP , VBD IN NNP ."
Holbrooke is on his first visit to the region to meet with senior Pakistani leaders on new ways of fighting extremism and uprooting terrorist bases .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ IN PRP$ JJ NN TO DT NN TO VB IN JJ JJ NNS IN JJ NNS IN VBG NN CC VBG JJ NNS .
Holbrooke is scheduled to meet with military leaders and representatives of Pakistan 's civil society and business sectors before he travels later this week to India and Afghanistan .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim B-geo O B-geo O,NNP VBZ VBN TO VB IN JJ NNS CC NNS IN NNP POS JJ NN CC NN NNS IN PRP VBZ RB DT NN TO NNP CC NNP .
