U.S. Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice says free trade is the key to reducing poverty and inequality in Latin America .,B-org O O B-org B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBZ JJ NN VBZ DT NN TO VBG NN CC NN IN NNP NNP .
"Speaking Wednesday in Washington , Rice repeated that the United States wants a free trade zone stretching from Canada to the tip of South America .",O B-tim O B-geo O B-per O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"VBG NNP IN NNP , NNP VBD IN DT NNP NNPS VBZ DT JJ NN NN VBG IN NNP TO DT NN IN NNP NNP ."
She spoke at the annual meeting of the Council of the Americas .,O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-org O,PRP VBD IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP IN DT NNPS .
"Rice said that for democracies to be effective , they must invest in their people , provide security and encourage economic growth and development .",B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD IN IN NNS TO VB JJ , PRP MD VB IN PRP$ NNS , VBP NN CC VB JJ NN CC NN ."
She said the United States wants to work with all Latin American governments that share those democratic ideals .,O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT NNP NNPS VBZ TO VB IN DT JJ JJ NNS WDT VBP DT JJ NNS .
She also said the U.S. has worked tirelessly for debt relief to the poorest countries .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP RB VBD DT NNP VBZ VBN RB IN NN NN TO DT JJS NNS .
"The president of Uruguay , Tabare Vazquez , told the forum that economic growth must benefit all the citizens of a country , and that countries can not think of development without freedom , peace and democracy .",O O O B-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN NNP , NNP NNP , VBD DT NN IN JJ NN MD VB PDT DT NNS IN DT NN , CC IN NNS MD RB VB IN NN IN NN , NN CC NN ."
