"News agencies in Iran say Tehran welcomes "" constructive "" talks with world powers on its nuclear program .",O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS IN NNP VBP NNP VBZ LQU JJ RQU NNS IN NN NNS IN PRP$ JJ NN .
"The statement by Iranian officials Wednesday is in response to a recent invitation from six major world powers , including the U.S. , to discuss the nuclear dispute .",O O O B-gpe O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN JJ NNS NNP VBZ IN NN TO DT JJ NN IN CD JJ NN NNS , VBG DT NNP , TO VB DT JJ NN ."
"The head of the International Atomic Energy Agency , IAEA , had said earlier this week that Iran should "" reciprocate "" recent overtures by the Obama administration aimed at ending an international standoff over Tehran 's nuclear drive .",O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O B-tim B-geo O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP , NNP , VBD VBN RBR DT NN IN NNP MD LQU VB RQU JJ NNS IN DT NNP NN VBN IN VBG DT JJ NN IN NNP POS JJ NN ."
"The IAEA is the United Nations ' global nuclear watchdog and has wrestled with Tehran over its efforts to enrich uranium , which can be used as an ingredient in atomic weapons .",O B-org O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP VBZ DT NNP NNPS POS JJ JJ NN CC VBZ VBN IN NNP IN PRP$ NNS TO VB NN , WDT MD VB VBN IN DT NN IN JJ NNS ."
The U.S. and its Western allies believe Iran 's nuclear program may have a military component .,O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP CC PRP$ JJ NNS VBP NNP POS JJ NN MD VB DT JJ NN .
"Iran says its atomic activities are for peaceful , civilian use .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ PRP$ JJ NNS VBP IN JJ , JJ NN ."
