"The two senior members of the U.S. Senate Armed Services Committee say they witnessed what they call a "" great deal of apprehension "" by the Iraqi government to shed sectarian divisions .",O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,DT CD JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBP PRP VBD WP PRP VBP DT LQU JJ NN IN NN LQU IN DT JJ NN TO VB JJ NNS .
Democrat Carl Levin and Republican John Warner have just returned to Washington from a two-day visit to Iraq .,B-per I-per I-per O B-org B-per B-org O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O B-geo O,NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP VBP RB VBN TO NNP IN DT JJ NN TO NNP .
They say the surge of U.S. forces has made parts of Baghdad and its immediate vicinity more secure and given Iraqi politicians more opportunities to compromise .,O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,PRP VBP DT NN IN NNP NNS VBZ VBN NNS IN NNP CC PRP$ JJ NN RBR JJ CC VBN JJ NNS JJR NNS TO VB .
But the senators say they are not optimistic about the chances for compromise .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC DT NNS VBP PRP VBP RB JJ IN DT NNS IN NN .
They say they believe the politicians are afraid to end sectarian biases and unify .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBP PRP VBP DT NNS VBP JJ TO VB JJ NNS CC NN .
Senators Levin and Warner said they told Iraqi leaders that the American people and Congress are running out of patience with the political process and that the need to compromise is urgent .,B-per I-per O B-org O O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP CC NNP VBD PRP VBD JJ NNS IN DT JJ NNS CC NNP VBP VBG IN IN NN IN DT JJ NN CC IN DT NN TO VB VBZ JJ .
