"The Democratic U.S. congressman who represents President Bush 's district in Texas has called on the president to sign a $ 64.7 billion bill to fund veterans ' affairs , including health care .",O O B-geo O O O B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNP NN WP VBZ NNP NNP POS NN IN NNP VBZ VBN IN DT NN TO VB DT $ CD CD NN TO VB NNS POS NNS , VBG NN NN ."
"The White House has threatened to veto the bill , which increases spending for veterans by six billion dollars .",O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,"DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB DT NN , WDT VBZ NN IN NNS IN CD CD NNS ."
Representative Chet Edwards says in the Democrats ' radio address Saturday that the Bush administration and Republican congressional budgets seem to put higher priority on tax cuts for the wealthy than health care benefits for veterans .,O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP VBZ IN DT NNPS POS NN NN NNP IN DT NNP NN CC JJ JJ NNS VBP TO VB JJR NN IN NN NNS IN DT NN IN NN NN NNS IN NNS .
Edwards says President Bush backed down from his veto threat when it became clear that Congress could override his veto .,B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O,NNP VBZ NNP NNP VBD RB IN PRP$ NN NN WRB PRP VBD JJ IN NNP MD VB PRP$ NN .
Edwards adds the spending bill honors U.S. troops by providing better health care .,B-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ DT NN NN NNS NNP NNS IN VBG JJR NN NN .
President Bush formed a bipartisan commission to investigate the quality of health care for veterans after deplorable conditions were discovered at a Washington military hospital earlier this year .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN TO VB DT NN IN NN NN IN NNS IN JJ NNS VBD VBN IN DT NNP JJ NN RBR DT NN .
