"Kyrgyzstan 's new leadership is meeting with the head of the Organization for Security and Cooperation in Europe , OSCE , as well as senior officials from Ukraine and Georgia - the two former Soviet states where popular revolts toppled autocratic regimes .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ NN VBZ VBG IN DT NN IN DT NNP IN NNP CC NNP IN NNP , NNP , RB RB IN JJ NNS IN NNP CC NNP IN DT CD JJ JJ NNS WRB JJ NNS VBD JJ NNS ."
"OSCE Chairman Dimitrij Rupel and interim Kyrgyz President Kurmanbek Bakiyev met Thursday , to discuss preparations for a June presidential election .",B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O B-tim O O O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP CC JJ JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP , TO VB NNS IN DT NNP JJ NN ."
The Georgian and Ukrainian foreign ministers are due to meet other interim Kyrgyz officials later in the day .,O B-gpe O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-tim O,DT JJ CC JJ JJ NNS VBP JJ TO VB JJ JJ JJ NNS RB IN DT NN .
"Wednesday , Mr. Bakiyev warned ousted President Askar Akayev against returning to the country , saying it could provoke a new wave of violence as passions sparked by last week 's political crisis have not yet died down .",B-tim O B-per I-per O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP , NNP NNP VBD JJ NNP NNP NNP IN VBG TO DT NN , VBG PRP MD VB DT JJ NN IN NN IN NNS VBN IN JJ NN POS JJ NN VBP RB RB VBN RP ."
Mr. Akayev has expressed willingness to return to Bishkek to offer his resignation .,B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN NN TO VB TO VB TO VB PRP$ NN .
Mr. Akayev fled to Moscow last week after thousands of opposition demonstrators stormed the presidential palace .,B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD TO NNP JJ NN IN NNS IN NN NNS VBD DT JJ NN .
