Two British lawmakers have asked a French oil company to stop doing business in Burma .,O B-gpe O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo O,CD JJ NNS VBP VBN DT JJ NN NN TO VB VBG NN IN NNP .
"The members of parliament , Vera Baird and John Bercow , met with officials from France 's Total Oil Company earlier this week .",O O O O O B-per I-per O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O B-org I-org I-org O O O O,"DT NNS IN NN , NNP NNP CC NNP NNP , VBD IN NNS IN NNP POS NNP NNP NNP RBR DT NN ."
Ms. Baird says Total 's business in Burma is propping up the dictatorship .,B-per I-per O B-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ NNP POS NN IN NNP VBZ VBG RP DT NN .
The French oil giant has not commented on the meeting but Mizzima News quotes a spokeswoman for Mr. Bercow as saying the oil company representatives were not receptive to the lawmakers ' request .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN NN VBZ RB VBN IN DT NN CC NNP NNP VBZ DT NN IN NNP NNP IN VBG DT NN NN NNS VBD RB JJ IN DT NNS POS NN .
"International rights activists have for years pressured corporations not to do business in Burma , so as to avoid supporting the country 's military junta .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS NNS VBP IN NNS VBN NNS RB TO VB NN IN NNP , RB IN TO VB VBG DT NN POS JJ NN ."
