Rebels in the Democratic Republic of Congo have called for a ceasefire ahead of expected peace talks with the government .,O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN DT JJ NNP IN NNP VBP VBN IN DT NN RB IN VBN NN NNS IN DT NN .
Renegade General Laurent Nkunda Wednesday said a ceasefire between his rebels and the DRC army would help facilitate the upcoming peace conference .,B-org I-org I-org I-org B-tim O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN PRP$ NNS CC DT NNP NN MD VB VB DT JJ NN NN .
"The Congolese government had been expected to convene a meeting Thursday with all armed groups on peace , security and development in the eastern regional capital of Goma .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT JJ NN VBD VBN VBN TO VB DT NN NNP IN DT JJ NNS IN NN , NN CC NN IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP ."
But officials Wednesday postponed the talks until January 6 .,O O B-tim O O O O B-tim I-tim O,CC NNS NNP VBD DT NNS IN NNP CD .
"The national army , renegade troops led by Nkunda , and various armed militias have been fighting in the eastern provinces of North and South Kivu since August .",O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo B-tim I-tim O,"DT JJ NN , NN NNS VBN IN NNP , CC JJ JJ NNS VBP VBN VBG IN DT JJ NNS IN NNP CC NNP NNP IN NNP ."
"The fighting has displaced around 800,000 civilians .",O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBN IN CD NNS .
"During this month alone , tens of thousands of people have been forced to flee fighting in or near their villages .",B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN RB , NNS IN NNS IN NNS VBP VBN VBN TO VB VBG IN CC IN PRP$ NNS ."
"Displacement camps in the region are now overflowing , and many aid agencies have had to suspend delivery of aid because of the security risks .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NN NNS IN DT NN VBP RB VBG , CC JJ NN NNS VBP VBN TO VB NN IN NN IN IN DT NN NNS ."
