"In 1816 , the United Provinces of the Rio Plata declared their independence from Spain .",O B-tim O O B-org I-org O O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-geo O,"IN CD , DT NNP NNPS IN DT NNP NNP VBD PRP$ NN IN NNP ."
"After Bolivia , Paraguay , and Uruguay went their separate ways , the area that remained became Argentina .",O B-geo O B-geo O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"IN NNP , NNP , CC NNP VBD PRP$ JJ NNS , DT NN WDT VBD VBD NNP ."
"The country 's population and culture were heavily shaped by immigrants from throughout Europe , but most particularly Italy and Spain , which provided the largest percentage of newcomers from 1860 to 1930 .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,"DT NN POS NN CC NN VBD RB VBN IN NNS IN IN NNP , CC JJS RB NNP CC NNP , WDT VBD DT JJS NN IN NNS IN CD TO CD ."
"Up until about the mid-20th century , much of Argentina 's history was dominated by periods of internal political conflict between Federalists and Unitarians and between civilian and military factions .",O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN IN IN DT JJ NN , NN IN NNP POS NN VBD VBN IN NNS IN JJ JJ NN IN NNS CC NNS CC IN JJ CC JJ NNS ."
"After World War II , an era of Peronist populism and direct and indirect military interference in subsequent governments was followed by a military junta that took power in 1976 .",O O O B-eve O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"IN NNP NNP NNP , DT NN IN NNP NN CC JJ CC JJ JJ NN IN JJ NNS VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN WDT VBD NN IN CD ."
"Democracy returned in 1983 after a failed bid to seize the Falkland ( Malvinas ) Islands by force , and has persisted despite numerous challenges , the most formidable of which was a severe economic crisis in 2001 - 02 that led to violent public protests and the successive resignations of several presidents .",O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD IN CD IN DT VBN NN TO VB DT NNP LRB NNP RRB NNP IN NN , CC VBZ VBN IN JJ NNS , DT JJS NN IN WDT VBD DT JJ JJ NN IN CD : CD WDT VBD TO JJ JJ NNS CC DT JJ NNS IN JJ NNS ."
