Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu is due to deliver a major policy speech Sunday that is expected to outline his vision for advancing the Middle East peace process .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ JJ TO VB DT JJ NN NN NNP WDT VBZ VBN TO VB PRP$ NN IN VBG DT NNP NNP NN NN .
The Reuters news agency quotes Mr. Netanyahu 's spokesman ( Mark Regev ) as saying the prime minister intends to share a clear view on moving forward on a peace plan with the Palestinians .,O B-org O O O B-per I-per O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O,DT NNP NN NN VBZ NNP NNP POS NN LRB NNP NNP RRB IN VBG DT JJ NN VBZ TO VB DT JJ NN IN VBG RB IN DT NN NN IN DT NNS .
Mr. Netanyahu has refused to accept U.S. demands that Israel halt all Jewish settlement construction in the West Bank .,B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB NNP NNS IN NNP VB DT JJ NN NN IN DT NNP NNP .
He says building in existing settlements will continue to accommodate what he calls the natural growth of resident families .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ NN IN VBG NNS MD VB TO VB WP PRP VBZ DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS .
The Israeli prime minister also has not endorsed the creation of a Palestinian state .,O B-gpe B-per O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT JJ JJ NN RB VBZ RB VBN DT NN IN DT JJ NN .
U.S. President Barack Obama has called for a separate Palestinian state alongside Israel .,B-geo B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP .
