Mexican soldiers have captured one of the country 's most-wanted drug lords .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN CD IN DT NN POS JJ NN NNS .
"Officials say Hector Huerta Rios was arrested Tuesday in the state of Nuevo Leon , which borders Texas in the southwestern United States .",O O B-per I-per I-per O O B-tim O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-org O O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNS VBP NNP NNP NNP VBD VBN NNP IN DT NN IN NNP NNP , WDT VBZ NNP IN DT JJ NNP NNPS ."
They say he was one of dozens of drug suspects on a most-wanted list published by the Mexican government on Monday .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-tim O,PRP VBP PRP VBD CD IN NNS IN NN NNS IN DT JJ NN VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
Authorities have described Huerta Rios as a member of the powerful Beltran Leyva cartel and that he was sought on a murder charge .,O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP VBN NNP NNP IN DT NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP NN CC IN PRP VBD VBN IN DT NN NN .
"Known as "" La Burra , "" or "" the donkey , "" he is the third person arrested in less than a week as the government of President Felipe Calderon cracks down on drug cartels .",O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O,"VBN IN LQU NNP NNP , RQU CC LQU DT NN , RQU PRP VBZ DT JJ NN VBN IN JJR IN DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP VBZ RB IN NN NNS ."
"Word of the arrest Wednesday came shortly before U.S. Secretary of State Hillary Clinton arrived in Mexico City for talks with President Calderon on the drug issue , trade and other regional matters .",O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O B-org B-per I-per O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,"NN IN DT NN NNP VBD RB IN NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBD IN NNP NNP IN NNS IN NNP NNP IN DT NN NN , NN CC JJ JJ NNS ."
