The World Health Organization says Africa needs around $ 2 billion to fight malaria each year -- 10 times the money that has been pledged by international donors .,O B-org I-org I-org O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNP VBZ IN $ CD CD TO VB NN DT NN IN CD NNS DT NN WDT VBZ VBN VBN IN JJ NNS .
The WHO says using that amount of money to prevent and treat malaria in Africa would ultimately save nations around $ 10 billion per year in health costs .,O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP VBZ VBG DT NN IN NN TO VB CC VB NN IN NNP MD RB VB NNS IN $ CD CD IN NN IN NN NNS .
"But in 2002 , the latest year figures are available , the agency says the international community spent only $ 200 million to fight malaria around the globe .",O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"CC IN CD , DT JJS NN NNS VBP JJ , DT NN VBZ DT JJ NN VBD RB $ CD CD TO VB NN IN DT NN ."
It estimates the mosquito-born disease kills more than one million people each year worldwide .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ DT JJ NN VBZ JJR IN CD CD NNS DT NN NN .
More than 90 percent of those deaths occur in sub-Saharan Africa .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJR IN CD NN IN DT NNS VBP IN JJ NNP .
