Israeli Prime Minister Ariel Sharon and Palestinian President Mahmoud Abbas are to meet as early as Tuesday for the first summit since Israel 's withdrawal from the Gaza Strip .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo I-geo O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP CC JJ NNP NNP NNP VBP TO VB RB RB IN NNP IN DT JJ NN IN NNP POS NN IN DT NNP NNP .
Israeli officials say representatives from both governments will meet Friday to set the date and other details of the meeting .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP NNS IN DT NNS MD VB NNP TO VB DT NN CC JJ NNS IN DT NN .
"Earlier , Jordan said King Abdullah had helped arrange the meeting in an effort to advance the Middle East peace process .",O O B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O,"RB , NNP VBD NNP NNP VBD VBN VB DT NN IN DT NN TO VB DT NNP NNP NN NN ."
It was not clear if King Abdullah would attend .,O O O O O B-per I-per O O O,PRP VBD RB JJ IN NNP NNP MD VB .
"A summit between the Israeli and Palestinian leaders was called off earlier this month , amid violence in the Gaza Strip .",O O O O B-gpe O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"DT NN IN DT JJ CC JJ NNS VBD VBN RP RBR DT NN , IN NN IN DT NNP NNP ."
"Meanwhile , Egypt has begun construction on a new crossing along the borders of Egypt , Gaza and Israel .",O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O,"RB , NNP VBZ VBN NN IN DT JJ VBG IN DT NNS IN NNP , NNP CC NNP ."
"Last month , a key crossing at Rafah was closed as part of the Israeli withdrawal .",O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"JJ NN , DT NN VBG IN NNP VBD VBN IN NN IN DT JJ NN ."
