Two more witnesses have testified before the special tribunal in Iraq trying former dictator Saddam Hussein and seven of his lieutenants for the murders of more than 140 Shi'ite Muslims 23 years ago .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,CD JJR NNS VBP VBD IN DT JJ NN IN NNP VBG JJ NN NNP NNP CC CD IN PRP$ NNS IN DT NNS IN JJR IN CD NNP NNPS CD NNS RB .
"The televised session began several hours late Wednesday after Saddam refused to attend , complaining of mistreatment .",O O O O O O O B-tim O B-per O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBD JJ NNS JJ NNP IN NNP VBD TO VB , VBG IN NN ."
"One of the witnesses , whose identity was concealed behind a curtain , told the court how he was arrested and kept with little food and water for several days .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"CD IN DT NNS , WP$ NN VBD VBN IN DT NN , VBD DT NN WRB PRP VBD VBN CC VBN IN JJ NN CC NN IN JJ NNS ."
Saddam and his co-defendants are accused of ordering the crackdown on Dujail residents after a failed assassination attempt on his life when he visited the town in 1982 .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP CC PRP$ NNS VBP VBN IN VBG DT NN IN NNP NNS IN DT JJ NN NN IN PRP$ NN WRB PRP VBD DT NN IN CD .
"Following the testimony Wednesday , presiding Judge Rizgar Mohammed Amin adjourned the session for two weeks , until December 21 , so that the country can focus on next Thursday 's parliamentary elections .",O O O B-tim O O B-org I-org B-per I-per O O O O B-tim O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O,"VBG DT NN NNP , VBG NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN CD NNS , IN NNP CD , RB IN DT NN MD VB IN JJ NNP POS JJ NNS ."
"If found guilty , Saddam could face the death penalty .",O O O O B-per O O O O O O,"IN VBN JJ , NNP MD VB DT NN NN ."
