Kurdish officials say Iran has closed its border with Iraq 's northern Kurdish region as a protest to the arrest of an Iranian by the U.S. military .,O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O,JJ NNS VBP NNP VBZ VBN PRP$ NN IN NNP POS JJ NNP NN IN DT NN TO DT NN IN DT NN IN DT NNP NN .
"The closure of the border Monday , came after the detention of Mahmudi Farhadi , a civilian official , who was arrested Thursday at a hotel in Sulaimaniyah .",O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-geo O,"DT NN IN DT NN NNP , VBD IN DT NN IN NNP NNP , DT JJ NN , WP VBD VBN NNP IN DT NN IN NNP ."
"The U.S. military says Farhadi is a member of the Islamic Revolutionary Guards Quds Force , a covert action arm of the Iranian government accused of aiding lethal attacks against the Iraq government and coalition forces .",O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,"DT NNP NN VBZ NNP VBZ DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNPS NNP NNP , DT JJ NN NN IN DT JJ NN VBN IN VBG JJ NNS IN DT NNP NN CC NN NNS ."
Iraqi and Iranian leaders say he was in the country on official business and with the full knowledge of the government .,B-gpe O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ CC JJ NNS VBP PRP VBD IN DT NN IN JJ NN CC IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN .
U.S. military officials say Farhadi has been involved in transporting explosives into Iraq .,B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP JJ NNS VBP NNP VBZ VBN VBN IN VBG NNS IN NNP .
The military says intelligence reports also indicate he was involved in the infiltration and training of foreign terrorists in Iraq .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT JJ VBZ NN NNS RB VBP PRP VBD VBN IN DT NN CC NN IN JJ NNS IN NNP .
