The United Nations war crimes tribunal has upheld the 25-year prison sentence for former Bosnian Croat politician Dario Kordic .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe I-gpe O B-per I-per O,DT NNP NNPS NN NNS JJ VBZ VBN DT JJ NN NN IN JJ JJ JJ NN NNP NNP .
Appeals judges in The Hague Friday confirmed a lower panel 's ruling that Kordic committed crimes against humanity when he ordered the notorious 1993 massacre in the Muslim village of Ahmici in central Bosnia-Herzegovina .,O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O B-geo O,NNP NNS IN DT NNP NNP VBD DT JJR NN POS NN IN NNP VBD NNS IN NN WRB PRP VBD DT JJ CD NN IN DT NNP NN IN NNP IN JJ NNP .
"Bosnian Croat troops massacred more than 100 civilians , including women and children .",B-gpe I-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ JJ NNS VBD JJR IN CD NNS , VBG NNS CC NNS ."
"In another ruling , the justices reduced to six years the 15-year term of former Bosnian Croat military commander Mario Cerkez , finding him not guilty in the Ahmici operation .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe I-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"IN DT NN , DT NNS VBD TO CD NNS DT JJ NN IN JJ JJ JJ JJ NN NNP NNP , VBG PRP RB JJ IN DT NNP NN ."
"Cerkez already has served seven years in prison , and was released by the court earlier this month .",B-per O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP RB VBZ VBN CD NNS IN NN , CC VBD VBN IN DT NN RBR DT NN ."
