Russian President Vladimir Putin has assured China that the relationship between their countries will remain strong even after he steps down as leader next year .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNP IN DT NN IN PRP$ NNS MD VB JJ RB IN PRP VBZ RP IN NN IN NN .
"Mr. Putin and his Chinese counterpart , Hu Jintao met on the sidelines of the APEC summit in Sydney Saturday .",B-per I-per O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-org O O B-geo B-tim O,"NNP NNP CC PRP$ JJ NN , NNP NNP VBD IN DT NNS IN DT NNP NN IN NNP NNP ."
"The Russian leader said that he and Mr. Hu have achieved the highest level of Russian-Chinese relations , and he said there is no doubt that the strong relations will continue in the coming years .",O B-gpe O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBD IN PRP CC NNP NNP VBP VBN DT JJS NN IN JJ NNS , CC PRP VBD EX VBZ DT NN IN DT JJ NNS MD VB IN DT JJ NNS ."
Russia will hold presidential elections in March of next year .,B-geo O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O,NNP MD VB JJ NNS IN NNP IN JJ NN .
Mr. Putin is not eligible to run for reelection after serving two terms .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ RB JJ TO VB IN NN IN VBG CD NNS .
