"Jordan 's King Abdullah has accused Israel of , in his words , "" playing with fire "" for its policies in East Jerusalem and other occupied territories .",B-gpe O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O,"NNP POS NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNP IN , IN PRP$ NNS , LQU VBG IN NN LQU IN PRP$ NNS IN NNP NNP CC JJ JJ NNS ."
"Speaking to foreign ambassadors Thursday , the king said for Mideast peace negotiations to be successful , Israel must stop all "" unilateral measures in occupied territories "" - particularly the controversial expansion of Jewish settlement construction in the West Bank and East Jerusalem .",O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-geo I-geo O,"VBG TO JJ NNS NNP , DT NN VBD IN JJ NN NNS TO VB JJ , NNP MD VB DT LQU JJ NNS IN JJ NNS LQU : RB DT JJ NN IN JJ NN NN IN DT NNP NNP CC NNP NNP ."
The issue of settler expansion is a key stumbling block because Palestinians want East Jerusalem as the capital of a future state .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN JJ NN VBZ DT JJ NN NN IN NNS VBP NNP NNP IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN .
"Although some city officials this week indicated an unofficial freeze on construction in East Jerusalem , Israel 's government has publicly insisted it will not halt expansion .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN NNS DT NN VBD DT JJ NN IN NN IN NNP NNP , NNP POS NN VBZ RB VBN PRP MD RB VB NN ."
"Palestinian President Mahmoud Abbas said Monday that he is ready to start indirect talks with Israel , possibly as early as next week .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP IN PRP VBZ JJ TO VB JJ NNS IN NNP , RB RB JJ IN JJ NN ."
