At least 25 insurgents were killed in a battle with U.S. troops in the northern Iraqi city of Mosul Wednesday .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo B-tim O,IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN IN NNP NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP NNP .
Fifteen American soldiers were wounded in the fighting and one later died at a military hospital .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CD JJ NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN CC CD RB VBD IN DT JJ NN .
U.S. forces then called in warplanes which fired missiles at insurgents .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS RB VBD IN NNS WDT VBD NNS IN NNS .
"In other developments , the Iraqi government announced Thursday , the arrest of Fadil Hussain Ahmed al-Kurdi a senior member of the al-Qaida linked militant group led by Abu Musab al-Zarqawi .",O O O O O B-gpe O O B-tim O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O,"IN JJ NNS , DT JJ NN VBD NNP , DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP DT JJ NN IN DT NNP VBN NN NN VBN IN NNP NNP NNP ."
"The arrest of another suspected senior militant commander , Abu Marwan in Mosul , was announced Wednesday .",O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O B-tim O,"DT NN IN DT JJ JJ JJ NN , NNP NNP IN NNP , VBD VBN NNP ."
