The head of the Russian natural gas monopoly Gazprom says his firm is ready to merge with the state-run Rosneft oil firm .,O O O O B-gpe O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O,DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NN NN NNP VBZ PRP$ NN VBZ JJ TO VB IN DT JJ NNP NN NN .
Gazprom Chief Executive Alexei Miller said Wednesday the deal could be finalized in the near future .,B-per O O B-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP DT NN MD VB VBN IN DT JJ NN .
"The merger would follow Rosneft 's acquisition of Yuganskneftegaz , the main unit of Russia 's embattled giant oil firm Yukos .",O O O O B-org O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-org O,"DT NN MD VB NNP POS NN IN NNP , DT JJ NN IN NNP POS JJ JJ NN NN NNP ."
Rosneft gained Yuganskneftegaz after purchasing the mysterious Baikal Group for more than $ 9 billion last month after Baikal purchased Yuganskneftegaz at a court-ordered auction .,B-org O B-geo O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O,NNP VBD NNP IN VBG DT JJ NNP NNP IN JJR IN $ CD CD JJ NN IN NNP VBD NNP IN DT JJ NN .
Critics sharply criticized the transactions as a government sham .,O O O O O O O O O O,NNS RB VBD DT NNS IN DT NN NN .
Russian officials say the auction was part of efforts to reclaim billions of dollars that Yukos owes in back taxes .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP DT NN VBD NN IN NNS TO VB NNS IN NNS WDT NNP VBZ IN JJ NNS .
