"Iran 's state television says six people have been killed and several others wounded in two bomb blasts in the city of Ahvaz , the capital of the oil-rich southwestern province of Khuzestan .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP POS NN NN VBZ CD NNS VBP VBN VBN CC JJ NNS VBD IN CD NN NNS IN DT NN IN NNP , DT NN IN DT NN JJ NN IN NNP ."
The report says the blasts occurred Tuesday morning at a bank and a government building .,O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ DT NNS VBD NNP NN IN DT NN CC DT NN NN .
"Iranian President Mahmoud Ahmadinejad was due to visit the city , but his office says the trip was canceled because of bad weather .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD JJ TO VB DT NN , CC PRP$ NN VBZ DT NN VBD VBN IN IN JJ NN ."
"There have been several incidents of ethnic unrest in recent months in Ahvaz , which is near Iraq .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O,"EX VBP VBN JJ NNS IN JJ NN IN JJ NNS IN NNP , WDT VBZ IN NNP ."
The region is home to Iran 's minority Arab community .,O O O O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O,DT NN VBZ NN TO NNP POS NN JJ NN .
