"A draft report by a European Parliament committee says European Union countries knew about secret prisons for terror suspects the CIA ran on their territories , despite statements to the contrary .",O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN NN IN DT JJ NNP NN VBZ NNP NNP NNS VBD IN JJ NNS IN NN VBZ DT NNP VBD IN PRP$ NNS , IN NNS TO DT NN ."
The report also says nearly all European Union member states and many senior EU officials were reluctant to cooperate with the investigation .,O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O,DT NN RB VBZ RB DT JJ NNP NN NNS CC JJ JJ NNP NNS VBD JJ TO VB IN DT NN .
An interim report published in June named Poland and Romania as countries that may have allowed the CIA to operate the clandestine prisons on their territories .,O O O O O B-tim O B-gpe O B-per O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBN IN NNP VBD NNP CC NNP IN NNS WDT MD VB VBN DT NNP TO VB DT JJ NNS IN PRP$ NNS .
It also says others may have violated individual rights by allowing the CIA to use their facilities for secret prisoner transfers .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O,PRP RB VBZ NNS MD VB VBN JJ NNS IN VBG DT NNP TO VB PRP$ NNS IN JJ NN NNS .
International human rights groups have expressed concern over the possible torture of the detainees .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ JJ NNS NNS VBP VBN NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNS .
"U.S. officials , including Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice and President Bush , have defended the program as legal under international law but stressed that the United States does not permit torture .",B-geo O O O O O B-org B-per I-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O,"NNP NNS , VBG NNP IN NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP , VBP VBN DT NN IN JJ IN JJ NN CC VBD IN DT NNP NNPS VBZ RB VB NN ."
The final European Parliament report is expected early next year .,O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O,DT JJ JJ NNP NN VBZ VBN RB JJ NN .
