"President Bush has phoned Northern Ireland 's main Protestant leader Ian Paisley , offering to help the province strike a deal to revive power-sharing in the British province .",B-per I-per O O B-per I-per O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNP NNP POS JJ JJ NN NNP NNP , VBG TO VB DT NN NN DT NN TO VB NN IN DT JJ NN ."
Mr. Bush told reporters he wants to be part of the process to reach an agreement .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD NNS PRP VBZ TO VB NN IN DT NN TO VB DT NN .
Mr. Paisley said he told Mr. Bush any deal would have to address fundamental issues that have blocked progress .,B-per I-per O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD PRP VBD NNP NNP DT NN MD VB TO VB JJ NNS WDT VBP VBN NN .
"Earlier this week , Irish Prime Minister Bertie Ahern warned Northern Ireland 's parties they must decide within days whether to accept new proposals to break the deadlock over power-sharing .",O O O O B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RBR DT NN , JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP POS NNS PRP MD VB IN NNS IN TO VB JJ NNS TO VB DT NN IN NN ."
The proposals include monitoring by Catholic and Protestant clerics of the disarmament of the Catholic Irish Republican Army .,O O O O O B-per O B-per O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,DT NNS VBP NN IN NNP CC NNP NNS IN DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP .
"President Bush is also expected to phone Gerry Adams , the leader of the IRA 's political wing , Sinn Fein .",B-per I-per O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-org O O O O B-per I-per O,"NNP NNP VBZ RB VBN TO NN NNP NNP , DT NN IN DT NNP POS JJ NN , NNP NNP ."
