Syria 's State Security court has sentenced two men to death for their part in a bomb attack and gunbattle with police in Damascus last April .,B-geo O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O,NNP POS NNP NNP NN VBZ VBN CD NNS TO NN IN PRP$ NN IN DT NN NN CC NN IN NNS IN NNP JJ NNP .
"A lawyer for the men said Thursday that Ahmad Shalash and Ezzo al-Hussein were found guilty of taking part in the firefight that killed a policeman and a passer-by , as well as two gunmen in the capital 's diplomatic district .",O O O O O O B-tim O B-per I-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN DT NNS VBD NNP IN NNP NNP CC NNP NNP VBD VBN JJ IN VBG NN IN DT NN WDT VBD DT NN CC DT JJ , RB RB IN CD NNS IN DT NN POS JJ NN ."
"The attorney said the court also sentenced two other men to forced labor for life , while the remaining 18 defendants received jail terms of between one and 20 years on a variety of charges .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD DT NN RB VBD CD JJ NNS TO VBN NN IN NN , IN DT VBG CD NNS VBD NN NNS IN IN CD CC CD NNS IN DT NN IN NNS ."
The death sentences must be endorsed by President Bashar al-Assad .,O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O,DT NN NNS MD VB VBN IN NNP NNP NNP .
