A British maritime organization has called for the waters off Somalia to be declared a war zone following Saturday 's pirate attack on a luxury cruise ship .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN NN VBZ VBN IN DT NNS RP NNP TO VB VBN DT NN NN VBG NNP POS NN NN IN DT NN NN NN .
"The National Union of Marine , Aviation and Shipping Transport Officers says the situation off Somalia is anarchic and that it is time for governments to get involved .",O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP IN NNP , NNP CC NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT NN IN NNP VBZ JJ CC IN PRP VBZ NN IN NNS TO VB VBN ."
The union is also calling for a naval task force to be established to stop the attackers .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ RB VBG IN DT JJ NN NN TO VB VBN TO VB DT NNS .
Saturday 's attack on the Seabourne Spirit is the latest in more than 20 reported pirate attacks off Somalia since March .,B-tim O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim I-tim O,NNP POS NN IN DT NNP NNP VBZ DT JJS IN JJR IN CD VBN NN NNS IN NNP IN NNP .
"No one was seriously injured Saturday when pirates fired grenades at the cruise ship , which sped away from the attackers before they could board .",O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD RB VBN NNP WRB NNS VBD NNS IN DT NN NN , WDT VBD RB IN DT NNS IN PRP MD VB ."
"The ship was carrying American , British and Australian tourists .",O O O O B-gpe O B-gpe O B-gpe O O,"DT NN VBD VBG JJ , JJ CC JJ NNS ."
