Ukrainian officials have confirmed that the deadly H5N1 bird flu strain has been found in more Crimean villages .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN IN DT JJ NNP NN NN NN VBZ VBN VBN IN RBR JJ NNS .
The officials say tests carried out in Russia confirm the presence of the strain in 11 different villages .,O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP NNS VBN RP IN NNP VBP DT NN IN DT NN IN CD JJ NNS .
"Authorities have killed more than 50,000 birds in the region , which is a major stopping point for migratory birds .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP VBN JJR IN CD NNS IN DT NN , WDT VBZ DT JJ NN NN IN JJ NNS ."
Ukrainian health authorities also are monitoring more than 500 people in the area for evidence of bird flu .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN NNS RB VBP VBG JJR IN CD NNS IN DT NN IN NN IN NN NN .
"Despite the confirmation of the growing number of infected birds , Ukrainian Prime Minister Yuri Yekhanurov says he wants to look into lifting the state of emergency imposed to contain the disease .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN IN DT VBG NN IN JJ NNS , JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ TO VB IN VBG DT NN IN NN VBN TO VB DT NN ."
He says he believes a quarantine should be sufficient .,O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ PRP VBZ DT NN MD VB JJ .
The H5N1 strain has killed more than 70 people in East Asia since 2003 .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo B-tim I-tim O,DT NNP NN VBZ VBN JJR IN CD NNS IN NNP NNP IN CD .
