A Nigerian government official says gunmen have attacked an oil pipeline operated by a Nigerian subsidiary of Chevron in the country 's restive Niger Delta .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe B-org O,DT JJ NN NN VBZ NNS VBP VBN DT NN NN VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP IN DT NN POS JJ NNP NNP .
Authorities say it was not immediately known who was responsible for Friday 's attack .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,NNS VBP PRP VBD RB RB VBN WP VBD JJ IN NNP POS NN .
"Niger Delta pipelines have been vulnerable to attacks in the past by militants linked to the Movement for the Emancipation of the Niger Delta , or MEND .",B-gpe B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-gpe B-org O O O O,"NNP NNP NNS VBP VBN JJ TO NNS IN DT NN IN NNS VBN TO DT NN IN DT NN IN DT NNP NNP , CC NNP ."
Hopes for a lasting peace in the Niger Delta are starting to fade as militants are starting to attack oil facilities again after a brief truce .,O O O O O O O B-gpe B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP VBP VBG TO VB IN NNS VBP VBG TO VB NN NNS RB IN DT JJ NN .
"More than 8,000 militants had given up their weapons under a government amnesty program .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJR IN CD NNS VBD VBN RP PRP$ NNS IN DT NN NN NN .
But the hospitalization of Nigerian President Umaru Yar'Adua has delayed government negotiations with the region 's rebels .,O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,CC DT NN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN NN NNS IN DT NN POS NNS .
