The United Nations Children 's Fund says more than 210 million children worldwide are working full-time .,O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP POS NNP VBZ JJR IN CD CD NNS NN VBP VBG RB .
"In a harsh report released by the British branch of UNICEF Monday , officials say that most of these children between the ages of five and 15 are working as slaves , miners , prostitutes and soldiers .",O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-org B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP , NNS VBP IN JJS IN DT NNS IN DT NNS IN CD CC CD VBP VBG IN NNS , NNS , NNS CC NNS ."
"UNICEF maintains that the only way to end child labor is to end poverty , and is calling on wealthy industrialized nations to raise their development aid to poor countries by $ 50 billion .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ IN DT JJ NN TO VB NN NN VBZ TO VB NN , CC VBZ VBG IN JJ JJ NNS TO VB PRP$ NN NN TO JJ NNS IN $ CD CD ."
The highest rate of child labor is in Africa where 41 percent of the children work full time .,O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJS NN IN NN NN VBZ IN NNP WRB CD NN IN DT NNS VBP JJ NN .
"The report says Asia is next with 21 percent , followed by Latin America 's 17 percent .",O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O,"DT NN VBZ NNP VBZ JJ IN CD NN , VBN IN NNP NNP POS CD NN ."
"UNICEF stresses that not all working children are at severe risk , unless they are missing education .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ IN RB DT JJ NNS VBP IN JJ NN , IN PRP VBP VBG NN ."
