"The International Criminal Court says Uganda is obligated to arrest Joseph Kony , leader of the Lord 's Resistance Army rebel group .",O B-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O,"DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNP VBZ VBN TO VB NNP NNP , NN IN DT NNP POS NNP NNP NN NN ."
Thursday 's statement from the ICC comes one day after Ugandan President Yoweri Museveni offered protection to Kony if his group stops fighting by the end of July .,B-tim O O O O B-org O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O B-per O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,NNP POS NN IN DT NNP VBZ CD NN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD NN IN NNP IN PRP$ NN VBZ VBG IN DT NN IN NNP .
"The ICC says Uganda 's government referred Kony 's case to the court , and must honor that commitment .",O B-org O B-org O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP VBZ NNP POS NN VBD NNP POS NN TO DT NN , CC MD VB IN NN ."
"The court has issued arrest warrants for Kony and other LRA leaders , who face charges of crimes against humanity .",O O O O O O O B-per O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ VBN NN NNS IN NNP CC JJ NNP NNS , WP VBP NNS IN NNS IN NN ."
The group has been fighting in northern Uganda for 20 years .,O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O,DT NN VBZ VBN VBG IN JJ NNP IN CD NNS .
The fighting has forced some 1.6 million Ugandans to abandon their homes .,O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBN DT CD CD NNS TO VB PRP$ NNS .
