Israeli security sources say Israel and the Palestinian Authority are trying to work out a deal that would end the army 's offensive in the Gaza Strip in return for stopping militant rocket attacks on Israel .,B-gpe O O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NN NNS VBP NNP CC DT JJ NNP VBP VBG TO VB RP DT NN WDT MD VB DT NN POS NN IN DT NNP NNP IN NN IN VBG JJ NN NNS IN NNP .
"Security officials say the talks began late Monday through an intermediary , who was not identified .",O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,"NN NNS VBP DT NNS VBD JJ NNP IN DT JJ , WP VBD RB VBN ."
"More than 60 Palestinians and at least five Israelis have been killed since Israel pushed into Gaza last week , after rockets fired by Palestinian militants killed two Israeli children .",O O O B-gpe O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O,"JJR IN CD NNS CC IN JJS CD NNS VBP VBN VBN IN NNP VBD IN NNP JJ NN , IN NNS VBN IN JJ NNS VBD CD JJ NNS ."
"Meanwhile , at the United Nations Arab diplomats submitted a draft resolution to the Security Council condemning Israel 's offensive .",O O O O B-org I-org B-gpe O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-geo O O O,"RB , IN DT NNP NNPS JJ NNS VBD DT NN NN TO DT NNP NNP VBG NNP POS NN ."
"U.S. Secretary of State Colin Powell said Monday he hopes Israel 's military offensive will be "" proportionate "" to the threat the country is facing and will end soon .",B-org O O B-org I-org I-org O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP PRP VBZ NNP POS JJ NN MD VB RQU VB RQU TO DT NN DT NN VBZ VBG CC MD VB RB .
