Donors and investors have pledged $ 3.55 billion dollars to develop the impoverished eastern part of Sudan .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNS CC NNS VBP VBN $ CD CD NNS TO VB DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP .
"Officials say a two-day donors ' conference hosted by Kuwait resulted in pledges of $ 500 million from Kuwait , $ 200 million from Iran , and $ 35 million from China .",O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNS VBP DT JJ NNS POS NN VBN IN NNP VBD IN NNS IN $ CD CD IN NNP , $ CD CD IN NNP , CC $ CD CD IN NNP ."
Pledges from institutions include $ 200 million from the Islamic Development Bank and $ 300 million from the Arab Investment Guarantee Organization .,O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,NNS IN NNS VBP $ CD CD IN DT NNP NNP NNP CC $ CD CD IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP .
The funds are to go toward infrastructure development and social services .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP TO VB IN NN NN CC JJ NNS .
Sudan 's government agreed to develop eastern Sudan in a 2006 peace deal it signed with rebels in the region .,B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NN VBD TO VB JJ NNP IN DT CD NN NN PRP VBD IN NNS IN DT NN .
"The area is rich in natural resources , and contains the country 's only commercial port .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ JJ IN JJ NNS , CC VBZ DT NN POS JJ JJ NN ."
The rebellion in east Sudan was separate from Sudan 's long-running north-south civil war and the conflict in Sudan 's western Darfur region .,O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O,DT NN IN JJ NNP VBD JJ IN NNP POS JJ JJ JJ NN CC DT NN IN NNP POS JJ NNP NN .
