Saudi Arabia 's oil minister predicts oil prices will stay firm for the next four years because of rising demand and limited oil refining capacity .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP POS NN NN VBZ NN NNS MD VB NN IN DT JJ CD NNS IN IN VBG NN CC JJ NN NN NN .
"Speaking at an economic conference Tuesday in the Saudi capital of Riyadh , Minister Ali al-Naimi said obstacles to oil production in many countries will continue to be a problem for the next four years .",O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-org O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"VBG IN DT JJ NN NNP IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , NNP NNP NNP VBD NNS TO NN NN IN JJ NNS MD VB TO VB DT NN IN DT JJ CD NNS ."
The minister said global economic growth will boost demand for oil by about six million barrels a day by 2010 .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NN VBD JJ JJ NN MD VB NN IN NN IN RB CD CD NNS DT NN IN CD .
He is urging more spending on refineries to compensate for what he called underinvestment during the last two decades .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,PRP VBZ VBG JJR NN IN NNS TO VB IN WP PRP VBD NN IN DT JJ CD NNS .
"Meanwhile , crude oil prices steadied around $ 70 a barrel today as traders tracked developments related to Iran 's nuclear ambitions .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"RB , JJ NN NNS VBD RB $ CD DT NN NN IN NNS VBD NNS VBN TO NNP POS JJ NNS ."
"Oil experts believe Iran , facing pressure to modify its nuclear program , could cut supplies .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NN NNS VBP NNP , VBG NN TO VB PRP$ JJ NN , MD VB NNS ."
