"One of the accords signed Friday is a permanent cease-fire , while the other covers details of how the final peace deal will be implemented .",O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"CD IN DT NNS VBN NNP VBZ DT JJ NN , IN DT NN VBZ NNS IN WRB DT JJ NN NN MD VB VBN ."
"Sudanese President Omar al-Bashir and South African President Thabo Mbeki attended the ceremony in the Kenyan town of Naivasha , where previous talks have yielded several partial agreements .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , WRB JJ NNS VBP VBN JJ JJ NNS ."
Friday 's signing fulfills a pledge by the government and the rebel Sudan People 's Liberation Army to reach an agreement by the end of 2004 .,B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,NNP POS NN VBZ DT NN IN DT NN CC DT NN NNP NNP POS NNP NNP TO VB DT NN IN DT NN IN CD .
"Now , all that remains is for top negotiators from both sides to sign a final document .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , DT IN VBZ VBZ IN JJ NNS IN DT NNS TO VB DT JJ NN ."
Mediators say that will likely take place January 9 .,O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,NNS VBP WDT MD RB VB NN NNP CD .
