The man who shot Pope John Paul 24 years ago is today mourning the loss of a man whom he considers a brother .,O O O O O B-per I-per B-tim O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN WP VBD NNP NNP NNP CD NNS RB VBZ NN VBG DT NN IN DT NN WP PRP VBZ DT NN .
"According to his family , Mehmet Ali Agca is grief stricken by the pope 's death .",O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,"VBG TO PRP$ NN , NNP NNP NNP VBZ JJ NN IN DT NN POS NN ."
Agca gravely wounded the pope in a 1981 shooting in St. Peter 's Square .,B-per O O O O O O B-tim O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O,NNP RB VBD DT NN IN DT CD NN IN NNP NNP POS NNP .
"Two years later , the pope visited the gunman 's prison cell and forgave him .",B-tim O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"CD NNS RB , DT NN VBD DT NN POS NN NN CC VB PRP ."
"Since then , Agca 's brother and mother have been received by the pope during several Vatican visits .",O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN RB , NNP POS NN CC NN VBP VBN VBN IN DT NN IN JJ JJ NNS ."
Many hail the pope 's reconciliation with his assailant as an example of the Christian principle of forgiveness .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN DT NN POS NN IN PRP$ NN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN NN .
"After serving 19 years in an Italian prison for shooting the pope , Agca was extradited in 2000 to Turkey to serve a sentence for an unrelated crime .",O O B-tim O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-per O O O B-tim O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O,"IN VBG CD NNS IN DT JJ NN IN VBG DT NN , NNP VBD VBN IN CD TO NNP TO VB DT NN IN DT JJ NN ."
