Members of a U.N. nuclear monitoring agency rejected an Arab-sponsored resolution on Friday calling on Israel to join a global anti-atomic weapons treaty .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,NNS IN DT NNP JJ NN NN VBD DT JJ NN IN NNP VBG IN NNP TO VB DT JJ JJ NNS NN .
The United States had urged countries to vote down the symbolically important although non-binding resolution .,O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNPS VBD VBN NNS TO VB RP DT RB JJ IN JJ NN .
Washington warned the resolution could derail broader efforts to ban nuclear warheads in the Middle East .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP VBD DT NN MD VB JJR NNS TO VB JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNP .
"Forty-six delegations voted in favor of the resolution , 51 against and 23 others abstained in the general assembly of the 151-member International Atomic Energy Agency ( IAEA ) .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-org O O,"CD NNS VBD IN NN IN DT NN , CD IN CC CD NNS VBD IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP RRB ."
"It had approved a similar resolution expressing concern about "" Israel 's Nuclear Capabilities "" in a close vote last year .",O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O,PRP VBD VBN DT JJ NN VBG NN IN RQU NNP POS NNP NNPS LQU IN DT JJ NN JJ NN .
"Israel warned the Vienna gathering earlier on Friday that the Arab-led effort to single out the Jewish state could deal a "" fatal blow "" to any cooperation on improving security in the Middle East .",B-geo O O B-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP VBD DT NNP NN RBR IN NNP IN DT JJ NN TO VB RP DT JJ NN MD VB DT LQU JJ NN LQU TO DT NN IN VBG NN IN DT NNP NNP .
