"The government of Ivory Coast has ordered the suspension of FM broadcasts from France 's state radio station , Radio France International , saying recent reports show bias against the government .",O O O B-gpe I-gpe O O O O O B-org O O B-geo O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN NNP NNS IN NNP POS NN NN NN , NNP NNP NNP , VBG JJ NNS VBP NN IN DT NN ."
RFI aired a story last week about a massacre of more than 100 people in the western part of Ivory Coast in June .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo B-tim I-tim O,NNP VBD DT NN JJ NN IN DT NN IN JJR IN CD NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP IN NNP .
RFI 's story referred to a United Nations report that implicated the government .,B-org O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O,NNP POS NN VBD TO DT NNP NNP NN WDT VBD DT NN .
The U.N. mission has since denied that such a report exists .,O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBZ RB VBN IN JJ DT NN VBZ .
"Ivory Coast is demanding that the popular radio broadcasters retract the story and pay a $ 16,000 fine before broadcasts are allowed to resume .",B-gpe I-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBG IN DT JJ NN NNS VBP DT NN CC VB DT $ CD NN IN NNS VBP VBN TO VB .
An RFI statement defends its news coverage and asks Ivory Coast to quickly reconsider its decision .,O B-org O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBZ PRP$ NN NN CC VBZ NNP NNP TO RB VB PRP$ NN .
The former French colony has intermittently suspected RFI broadcasts over the years .,O O B-gpe O O O O B-org O O O O O,DT JJ JJ NN VBZ RB VBN NNP NNS IN DT NNS .
