Somali pirates have seized a merchant vessel and 24 of the ship 's crew members in the Gulf of Aden .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O,JJ NNS VBP VBN DT NN NN CC CD IN DT NN POS NN NNS IN DT NNP IN NNP .
Maritime monitoring officials say pirates boarded and hijacked the Iceberg I vessel Monday just 15 kilometers from the port of Aden on the Yemeni coast .,O O O O O O O O O B-art I-art O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O,NN NN NNS VBP NNS VBD CC VBD DT NNP NNP NN NNP RB CD NNS IN DT NN IN NNP IN DT JJ NN .
The pirates were reported to be sailing the ship toward Somalia .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNS VBD VBN TO VB VBG DT NN IN NNP .
"On Sunday , Somali pirates demanded a $ 3 million ransom for a North Korean-flagged cargo ship hijacked early last month .",O B-tim O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , JJ NNS VBD DT $ CD CD NN IN DT JJ JJ NN NN VBN RB JJ NN ."
Andrew Mwangura of the Kenya-based East African Seafarers Assistance Program said the pirates threatened to kill the 10 Syrian crew members on board the MV Rim .,B-per I-per O O B-geo I-geo B-gpe B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-art I-art O,NNP NNP IN DT JJ JJ JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NNS VBD TO VB DT CD JJ NN NNS IN NN DT NNP NNP .
Pirates seized the Libyan-owned ship on February 3 in the Gulf of Aden .,O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O,NNS VBD DT JJ NN IN NNP CD IN DT NNP IN NNP .
