"The Indus Valley civilization , one of the world 's oldest , flourished during the 3rd and 2nd millennia B.C. and extended into northwestern India .",O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim B-geo O O O O B-geo O,"DT NNP NNP NN , CD IN DT NN POS JJS , VBD IN DT CD CC CD NN NNP CC VBN IN JJ NNP ."
Aryan tribes from the northwest infiltrated onto the Indian subcontinent about 1500 B.C. ; their merger with the earlier Dravidian inhabitants created the classical Indian culture .,O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-tim B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,JJ NNS IN DT NN VBD IN DT JJ NN IN CD NNP ; PRP$ NN IN DT RBR JJ NNS VBD DT JJ JJ NN .
The Maurya Empire of the 4th and 3rd centuries B.C. - which reached its zenith under ASHOKA - united much of South Asia .,O B-org I-org O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O B-geo O O O O O O B-org O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT NNP NN IN DT JJ CC JJ NNS NNP : WDT VBD PRP$ NN IN NNP IN JJ NN IN NNP NNP .
"The Golden Age ushered in by the Gupta dynasty ( 4th to 6th centuries A.D. ) saw a flowering of Indian science , art , and culture .",O B-tim I-tim O O O O B-geo O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP VBN IN IN DT NNP NN LRB JJ TO JJ NNS NNP RRB VBD DT NN IN JJ NN , NN , CC NN ."
Islam spread across the subcontinent over a period of 700 years .,B-art O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD IN DT NN IN DT NN IN CD NNS .
"In the 10th and 11th centuries , Turks and Afghans invaded India and established the Delhi Sultanate .",O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O B-gpe B-org B-gpe O B-geo O O O B-org I-org O,"IN DT JJ CC JJ NNS , NNS CC NNS VBD NNP CC VBD DT NNP NNP ."
"In the early 16th century , the Emperor BABUR established the Mughal Dynasty which ruled India for more than three centuries .",O O O B-tim I-tim O O B-org I-org O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ JJ NN , DT NNP NNP VBD DT NNP NNP WDT VBD NNP IN JJR IN CD NNS ."
European explorers began establishing footholds in India during the 16th century .,O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim I-tim O,JJ NNS VBD VBG NNS IN NNP IN DT JJ NN .
"By the 19th century , Great Britain had become the dominant political power on the subcontinent .",O O B-tim I-tim O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN , NNP NNP VBD VBN DT JJ JJ NN IN DT NN ."
The British Indian Army played a vital role in both World Wars .,O B-gpe I-gpe B-org O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ JJ NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP .
"Nonviolent resistance to British rule , led by Mohandas GANDHI and Jawaharlal NEHRU , eventually brought about independence in 1947 .",O O O B-gpe O O O O B-per I-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-tim O,"JJ NN TO JJ NN , VBN IN NNP NNP CC NNP NNP , RB VBD RB NN IN CD ."
"Communal violence led to the subcontinent 's bloody partition , which resulted in the creation of two separate states , India and Pakistan .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,"JJ NN VBD TO DT NN POS JJ NN , WDT VBD IN DT NN IN CD JJ NNS , NNP CC NNP ."
India 's nuclear weapons tests in 1998 caused Pakistan to conduct its own tests that same year .,B-geo O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS JJ NNS NNS IN CD VBD NNP TO VB PRP$ JJ NNS DT JJ NN .
"In November 2008 , terrorists allegedly originating from Pakistan conducted a series of coordinated attacks in Mumbai , India 's financial capital .",O B-tim I-tim O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O,"IN NNP CD , NNS RB VBG IN NNP VBD DT NN IN JJ NNS IN NNP , NNP POS JJ NN ."
"Despite pressing problems such as significant overpopulation , environmental degradation , extensive poverty , and widespread corruption , rapid economic development is fueling India 's rise on the world stage .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"IN VBG NNS JJ IN JJ NN , JJ NN , JJ NN , CC JJ NN , JJ JJ NN VBZ VBG NNP POS NN IN DT NN NN ."
