The U.S. military says it has arrested four suspected militants in the northern Iraqi city of Mosul .,O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O,DT NNP NN VBZ PRP VBZ VBN CD JJ NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP .
"The military announced Wednesday that it had identified the militant killed October fifth as Abu Qaswarah , also known as Abu Sara .",O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-per I-per O O O O B-per I-per O,"DT NN VBD NNP IN PRP VBD VBN DT NN VBD NNP NN IN NNP NNP , RB VBN IN NNP NNP ."
U.S. officials say the Moroccan-born man was the second in command of al-Qaida in Iraq .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-geo O,NNP NNS VBP DT JJ NN VBD DT JJ IN NN IN NNP IN NNP .
The U.S.-led coalition said his death will cause a major disruption to the al-Qaida in Iraq network .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-geo O O,DT JJ NN VBD PRP$ NN MD VB DT JJ NN TO DT NNP IN NNP NN .
