The U.S. military in Iraq says a suicide bomber has killed seven people at a government facility in Baquba .,O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNP NN IN NNP VBZ DT NN NN VBZ VBN CD NNS IN DT NN NN IN NNP .
"It says the dead are a U.S. soldier , an American contractor and five Iraqi workers .",O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O,"PRP VBZ DT NN VBP DT NNP NN , DT JJ NN CC CD JJ NNS ."
"The blast also wounded 20 people , including nine Americans .",O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O,"DT NN RB VBD CD NNS , VBG CD NNS ."
"Tuesday 's attack came as Sunni , Shi'ite and Kurdish leaders continued negotiations to reach agreement on a new Iraqi constitution ahead of a parliament vote on the charter set for Thursday .",B-tim O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"NNP POS NN VBD IN NNP , NNP CC NNP NNS VBD NNS TO VB NN IN DT JJ JJ NN RB IN DT NN NN IN DT NN VBN IN NNP ."
"Sunnis want a centralized government , and warn that a draft constitution defining Iraq as a federal state could be rejected in October 's nationwide referendum .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O,"NNPS VBP DT JJ NN , CC VBP IN DT NN NN VBG NNP IN DT JJ NN MD VB VBN IN NNP POS JJ NN ."
"In Washington , U.S. Defense Secretary Donald Rumsfeld stressed that Iraqi leaders must draft a constitution that satisfies Shi'ites , Sunnis and Kurds .",O B-geo O B-geo O O B-per I-per O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,"IN NNP , NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD IN JJ NNS MD VB DT NN WDT VBZ NNS , NNP CC NNPS ."
