The U.S. military said nine suspected militants have been killed in separate operations in southern and central Afghanistan .,O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNP NN VBD CD JJ NNS VBP VBN VBN IN JJ NNS IN JJ CC JJ NNP .
"Separately , the military said seven militants were killed during an airstrike that followed a gunbattle in the central province of Ghazni Wednesday .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O,"RB , DT NN VBD CD NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN WDT VBD DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP ."
It also said a Taliban commander was detained .,O O O O B-org O O O O,PRP RB VBD DT NNP NN VBD VBN .
"U.S. President Barack Obama has ordered 21,000 additional troops to reinforce the 38,000 U.S. troops already in Afghanistan , where the Taliban-led insurgency is spreading .",B-geo B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN CD JJ NNS TO VB DT CD NNP NNS RB IN NNP , WRB DT JJ NN VBZ VBG ."
