Witnesses in the Somali capital of Mogadishu say six people were killed Saturday in fighting between Ethiopian forces and Islamist rebels .,O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O O O B-gpe O O O O O,NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NNP VBP CD NNS VBD VBN NNP IN VBG IN JJ NNS CC JJ NNS .
The rebels have been carrying out an insurgency against the Ethiopian troops .,O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT NNS VBP VBN VBG RP DT NN IN DT JJ NNS .
Ethiopia sent troops to Somalia last year to help the interim Somali government oust the Islamist militants who had taken control of much of the country .,B-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD NNS TO NNP JJ NN TO VB DT JJ JJ NN VB DT NNP NNS WP VBD VBN NN IN NN IN DT NN .
"The African Union has pledged to send a large peacekeeping force into the country , but only Uganda has committed troops to the mission .",O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB DT JJ NN NN IN DT NN , CC RB NNP VBZ VBN NNS TO DT NN ."
