"The trial in absentia of Iraq 's most wanted fugitive , Abu Musab al-Zarqawi , and 12 other terror suspects has opened in the Jordanian capital , Amman .",O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,"DT NN IN NN IN NNP POS RBS JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP , CC CD JJ NN NNS VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NN , NNP ."
"Jordanian-born al-Zarqawi - the acknowledged mastermind behind scores of terror attacks in Iraq - is being tried in absentia , along with three of the 13 defendants .",O B-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,"JJ NNP IN DT JJ NN IN NNS IN NN NNS IN NNP : VBZ VBG VBN IN NN , IN IN CD IN DT CD NNS ."
Prosecutors accuse al-Zarqawi and most of the others of plotting to launch suicide chemical attacks inside Jordan .,O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O,NNS VBP NNP CC JJS IN DT NNS IN VBG TO VB NN NN NNS IN NNP .
"Shortly after the trial opened Wednesday , nine defendants present in the courtroom brought proceedings to a standstill when they refused to answer routine questions from military judges .",O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB IN DT NN VBD NNP , CD NNS JJ IN DT NN VBD NNS TO DT NN WRB PRP VBD TO VB JJ NNS IN JJ NNS ."
The court adjourned the case until December 22 .,O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT NN VBD DT NN IN NNP CD .
"If convicted , 12 of the defendants , including al-Zarqawi , could be sentenced to death .",O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O,"IN VBN , CD IN DT NNS , VBG NNP , MD VB VBN TO NN ."
A 13th defendant has been charged with the lesser crime of aiding two of the fugitives .,O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBZ VBN VBN IN DT JJR NN IN VBG CD IN DT NNS .
