Brazilian President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva says that later this month he will announce a series of measures to stimulate the country 's growth .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per I-per I-per O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ IN RB DT NN PRP MD VB DT NN IN NNS TO VB DT NN POS NN .
"President da Silva was sworn in for a second term Monday , pledging to Congress to make Brazil 's economy grow .",B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-org O O B-geo O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP VBD VBN IN IN DT JJ NN NNP , VBG TO NNP TO VB NNP POS NN VB ."
"Mr. da Silva begins his final , four years in office with a record of having brought inflation under control and stabilizing the country 's boom-and-bust economic cycles .",B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP$ JJ , CD NNS IN NN IN DT NN IN VBG VBN NN IN NN CC VBG DT NN POS JJ JJ NNS ."
But Brazil 's 2.6-percent growth has lagged behind other countries in the region and is only a quarter of India 's and China 's .,O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O,CC NNP POS JJ NN VBZ VBN IN JJ NNS IN DT NN CC VBZ RB DT NN IN NNP POS CC NNP POS .
Mr. da Silva has pledged to increase Brazil 's growth to five percent .,B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB NNP POS NN TO CD NN .
Thousands of people gathered in the rain outside the presidential palace to celebrate Mr. da Silva 's inauguration .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per B-geo I-geo O O O,NNS IN NNS VBN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN TO VB NNP NNP NNP POS NN .
He won a landslide run-off election in October in spite of a series of corruption scandals that have plagued his Workers ' Party .,O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT NN NN NN IN NNP IN NN IN DT NN IN NN NNS WDT VBP VBN PRP$ NNS POS NN .
