"Sri Lanka 's air force says it has attacked a Tamil Tiger boat yard , destroying attack craft used by the rebels .",B-per B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP POS NN NN VBZ PRP VBZ VBN DT NNP NNP NN NN , VBG NN NN VBN IN DT NNS ."
"A military spokesman , Major Upali Rajapakse , said Saturday that a number of insurgents were killed in the overnight attack .",O O O O O B-per I-per O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP , VBD NNP IN DT NN IN NNS VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN ."
"A pro-rebel Web site accused the air force of dropping four bombs on a civilian boat yard , wounding two workers .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNP NN VBD DT NN NN IN VBG CD NNS IN DT JJ NN NN , VBG CD NNS ."
The site said the yard was set up after the devastating tsunami in the Indian Ocean to build and repair fishing boats .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD DT NN VBD VBN RP IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP TO VB CC VB NN NNS .
"The European Union has called on the Sri Lankan government and Tamil Tiger rebels to immediately stop violence , saying it is threatening the peace process .",O B-org I-org O O O O B-per I-per O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN DT NNP NNP NN CC NNP NNP NNS TO RB VB NN , VBG PRP VBZ VBG DT NN NN ."
"In a statement , the EU says the violence will not solve the ethnic conflict in the island nation .",O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN , DT NNP VBZ DT NN MD RB VB DT JJ NN IN DT NN NN ."
