U.S. stocks were down dramatically Thursday as fears grow about the faltering U.S. economy .,B-geo O O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-geo O O,NNP NNS VBD RB RB NNP IN NNS VBP IN DT VBG NNP NN .
"The S&P 500 was off almost three percent , and the Dow Jones lost a sharp 2.5 percent .",O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O,"DT NNP CD VBD IN RB CD NN , CC DT NNP NNP VBD DT JJ CD NN ."
"In congressional testimony , U.S. central bank chief Ben Bernanke expressed support for efforts to stimulate the economy , after a string of downbeat economic reports .",O O O O B-geo O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN JJ NN , NNP JJ NN NN NNP NNP VBD NN IN NNS TO VB DT NN , IN DT NN IN JJ JJ NNS ."
"A Federal Reserve report showed manufacturing declining sharply in a key area , while a separate government study said the number of new homes under construction in 2007 dropped by 25 percent , the steepest drop for that industry since 1980 .",O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,"DT NNP NNP NN VBD VBG VBG RB IN DT JJ NN , IN DT JJ NN NN VBD DT NN IN JJ NNS IN NN IN CD VBN IN CD NN , DT JJS NN IN DT NN IN CD ."
"And Merrill Lynch , one of the biggest brokers , reported a nearly $ 10 billion quarterly loss , the worst in the company 's history .",O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"CC NNP NNP , CD IN DT JJS NNS , VBD DT RB $ CD CD JJ NN , DT JJS IN DT NN POS NN ."
President Bush is scheduled to offer ideas for stimulating the economy in a speech on Friday .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB NNS IN VBG DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP .
