Thailand 's cabinet has given the military permission to create a special regiment to bring an end to the growing unrest in the majority Muslim south .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NN VBZ VBN DT JJ NN TO VB DT JJ NN TO VB DT NN TO DT VBG NN IN DT NN NN RB .
"Officials say the regiment will be stationed in the provinces of Narathiwat , Pattani and Yala , which have been racked by violence that has claimed the lives of more 500 people since last year .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,"NNS VBP DT NN MD VB VBN IN DT NNS IN NNP , NNP CC NNP , WDT VBP VBN VBN IN NN WDT VBZ VBN DT NNS IN JJR CD NNS IN JJ NN ."
Reports say the headquarters of the new regiment will likely be in Pattani .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNS VBP DT NN IN DT JJ NN MD RB VB IN NNP .
"Thai Prime Minister Thaksin Shinawatra says part of the new regiment 's task will be to develop relationships with the citizens in the south , including engaging in development projects and outreach activities .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ NN IN DT JJ NN POS NN MD VB TO VB NNS IN DT NNS IN DT NN , VBG VBG IN NN NNS CC JJ NNS ."
