Iraqi police say at least 18 people have been killed and nearly 40 others wounded in a series of bombings in northern Iraq .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBP VBN VBN CC RB CD NNS VBN IN DT NN IN NNS IN JJ NNP .
"Police say most of the attacks were carried out Tuesday by suicide car bombers who detonated their explosives-filled vehicles near security checkpoints around the town of Hawija , close to the oil city of Kirkuk In Baghdad , a car bomb exploded near a police patrol .",O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP JJS IN DT NNS VBD VBN IN NNP IN NN NN NNS WP VBD PRP$ JJ NNS IN NN NNS IN DT NN IN NNP , RB TO DT NN NN IN NNP IN NNP , DT NN NN VBD IN DT NN NN ."
"Meanwhile , the U.S. military says coalition forces are hunting down insurgents in the northwestern town of Tal Afar , near the Syrian border .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O B-gpe O O,"RB , DT NNP NN VBZ NN NNS VBP VBG RP NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP , IN DT JJ NN ."
"A U.S. television network ( CNN ) says dozens of tanks , bradley fighting vehicles and Apache helicopters have moved into the town , which is said to be stronghold of insurgents .",O B-geo O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NN NN LRB NNP RRB VBZ NNS IN NNS , NN NN NNS CC NNP NNS VBP VBN IN DT NN , WDT VBZ VBN TO VB NN IN NNS ."
"Separately , one U.S. Marine has died of wounds sustained in a roadside bomb blast Monday in the city of Fallujah .",O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-geo O,"RB , CD NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NNS VBN IN DT NN NN NN NNP IN DT NN IN NNP ."
