The Hong Kong government says it has found another dead bird that has tested positive for the H5N1 strain of avian flu .,O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-nat O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NN VBZ PRP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN WDT VBZ VBN JJ IN DT NNP NN IN JJ NN .
"The Agriculture , Fisheries and Conservation Department department said the latest case is another Oriental magpie robin found January 26 in a village near the border with mainland China .",O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NNP , NNS CC NNP NNP NN VBD DT JJS NN VBZ DT JJ NN NN VBN NNP CD IN DT NN IN DT NN IN JJ NNP ."
It said Sunday the bird was confirmed to be H5N1 positive after a series of laboratory tests .,O O B-tim O O O O O O B-nat O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD NNP DT NN VBD VBN TO VB NNP JJ IN DT NN IN NN NNS .
Hong Kong went one year without reporting any cases of H5N1 in birds .,B-geo I-geo O B-tim O O O O O O B-nat O O O,NNP NNP VBD CD NN IN VBG DT NNS IN NNP IN NNS .
But the streak ended 10 days ago ( January 19 ) when officials announced a dead Oriental magpie robin tested positive for the virus .,O O O O B-tim O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC DT NN VBD CD NNS RB LRB NNP CD RRB WRB NNS VBD DT JJ JJ NN NN VBD JJ IN DT NN .
That bird also was also found near the border with mainland China .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NN RB VBD RB VBN IN DT NN IN JJ NNP .
