"Suicide bombers have killed four police officers , including a commander , in an attack in the northern Iraqi city of Mosul .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O,"NN NNS VBP VBN CD NNS NNS , VBG DT NN , IN DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP ."
"Iraqi officials said the bombers wore explosive vests and that two of them got inside police headquarters , blowing themselves up near Lieutenant Colonel Shamel Ahmed Aughla .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,"JJ NNS VBD DT NNS VBD JJ NNS CC IN CD IN PRP VBD JJ NN NN , VBG PRP RP IN NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
"Reuters reported the police commander was targeted because of his crackdown on al-Qaida ,",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,"NNP VBD DT NN NN VBD VBN IN IN PRP$ NN IN NNP ,"
"Local officials say the slain police commander had organized recent operations against al-Qaida militants , and had escaped several previous assassination attempts .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP DT NN NN NN VBD VBN JJ NNS IN NNP NNS , CC VBD VBN JJ JJ NN NNS ."
Security officials said a third suicide bomber was shot and killed as he approached the complex .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBD DT JJ NN NN VBD VBN CC VBN IN PRP VBD DT NN .
"The attack came two days after suicide bombers detonated explosives near a provincial government compound in Ramadi , killing 17 people .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,"DT NN VBD CD NNS IN NN NNS VBD NNS IN DT JJ NN NN IN NNP , VBG CD NNS ."
