"Afghanistan 's fugitive Taleban leader Mullah Omar has rejected an offer by President Hamid Karzai to seek reconciliation , and vowed to step up attacks .",B-geo O O B-org O B-per I-per O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ NNP NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP TO VB NN , CC VBD TO VB RP NNS ."
"Mr. Karzai said Sunday he was willing to listen to what Omar had to say , but that the Taleban leader would first have to account for his actions .",B-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD NNP PRP VBD JJ TO VB TO WP NNP VBD TO VB , CC IN DT NNP NN MD RB VB TO VB IN PRP$ NNS ."
"A purported spokesman for the Taleban Monday rejected the offer , calling Mr. Karzai nothing but a mouthpiece of Americans .",O O O O O B-org B-tim O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-gpe O,"DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP VBD DT NN , VBG NNP NNP DT CC DT NN IN NNS ."
"Mullah Omar , in a message , repeated his call for jihad , or holy war , against the United States .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNP NNP , IN DT NN , VBD PRP$ NN IN NN , CC RB NN , IN DT NNP NNPS ."
Washington has posted a $ 10 million reward for Omar 's capture .,B-geo O O O O O O O O B-per O O O,NNP VBZ VBN DT $ CD CD NN IN NNP POS NN .
He and bin Laden are believed to be hiding in tribal areas along the Afghan-Pakistani border .,O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP CC NNP NNP VBP VBN TO VB VBG IN JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN .
