A roadside bomb has killed three policemen in southern Afghanistan and an artillery attack by Afghan and NATO forces has killed five suspected Taleban insurgents .,O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-gpe O B-org O O O O O B-org O O,DT NN NN VBZ VBN CD NNS IN JJ NNP CC DT NN NN IN JJ CC NNP NNS VBZ VBN CD JJ NNP NNS .
The three policemen were traveling on the main highway linking Murja and Lashkar Gah districts in Helmand province when they were killed .,O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O O,DT CD NNS VBD VBG IN DT JJ NN VBG NNP CC NNP NNP NNS IN NNP NN WRB PRP VBD VBN .
Local officials in the same province say five militants were killed in Musa Qala district on Sunday .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-tim O,JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN VBP CD NNS VBD VBN IN NNP NNP NN IN NNP .
This is in addition to some 71 militants who were slain in Kandahar province by NATO-backed fighting that began late Saturday and spilled into Sunday .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-tim O,DT VBZ IN NN TO DT CD NNS WP VBD VBN IN NNP NN IN JJ NN WDT VBD JJ NNP CC VBD IN NNP .
"Elsewhere , Britain 's Defense Ministry says a British soldier was killed and three others wounded during a clash with hostile forces in Helmand province on Sunday .",O O B-geo O B-org I-org O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O,"RB , NNP POS NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ NN VBD VBN CC CD NNS VBN IN DT NN IN JJ NNS IN NNP NN IN NNP ."
Violence has escalated in recent weeks after NATO forces moved to southern Afghanistan to destroy suspected Taleban hideouts .,O O O O O O O B-org O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-org O O,NN VBZ VBN IN JJ NNS IN NNP NNS VBD TO JJ NNP TO VB JJ NNP NNS .
