"A Siberian town marked the 60th anniversary of victory in Europe Sunday by unveiling a bust of Stalin , the Soviet dictator who led the country during the struggle against Nazi forces .",O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim B-geo B-tim O O O O O B-per O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O B-org O O,"DT JJ NN VBD DT JJ NN IN NN IN NNP NNP IN VBG DT NN IN NNP , DT JJ NN WP VBD DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNS ."
Russian media said a few thousand people joined the regional governor of the Republic of Yakutia-Sakha in the town of Mirny as the monument was unveiled .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBD DT JJ CD NNS VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NNP IN NNP IN DT NN IN NNP IN DT NN VBD VBN .
"Soviet officials removed statues and images of Stalin in the mid 1950s , but public displays of the former dictator have been reappearing in Russia amid controversy .",O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,"JJ NNS VBD NNS CC NNS IN NNP IN DT JJ NNS , CC JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN VBP VBN VBG IN NNP IN NN ."
"Russia 's Itar-Tass news agency says a Stalin bust that was unveiled in another Siberian city , Krasnoyarsk , on Saturday was removed just a few hours later on instructions from regional authorities .",B-geo O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ NN NN VBZ DT NNP NN WDT VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN , NNP , IN NNP VBD VBN RB DT JJ NNS RB IN NNS IN JJ NNS ."
Stalin has been blamed for the deaths of millions of people during his decades of domination of the Soviet Union .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP VBZ VBN VBN IN DT NNS IN NNS IN NNS IN PRP$ NNS IN NN IN DT NNP NNP .
