"Iranian police say they plan to begin a strict crackdown on social corruption issues , including women violating Islamic dress code .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP PRP VBP TO VB DT JJ NN IN JJ NN NNS , VBG NNS VBG JJ NN NN ."
"Iran 's Fars news agency quotes Tehran 's police chief as saying officers will arrest women who fail to cover their hair or who fail to wear long , loose fitting clothes .",B-geo O B-geo O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NNP NN NN VBZ NNP POS NN NN IN VBG NNS MD VB NNS WP VBP TO VB PRP$ NN CC WP VBP TO VB RB , JJ JJ NNS ."
"They say they also will look for taxis that transport women in improper dress , as well as popular shops that sell the outfits .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBP PRP RB MD VB IN NNS IN NN NNS IN JJ NN , RB RB IN JJ NNS WDT VBP DT NNS ."
Enforcement of strict moral codes was loosened when Mohammad Khatami became president in 1997 .,O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O B-tim O,NN IN JJ JJ NNS VBD VBN WRB NNP NNP VBD NN IN CD .
"But hard-liners and conservative clerics have urged the current president , Mahmoud Ahmadinejad , to re-enforce the Islamic laws .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O,"CC NNS CC JJ NNS VBP VBN DT JJ NN , NNP NNP , TO VB DT JJ NNS ."
