Five small bombs have exploded near highways in the Madrid area and another in northern Spain but none caused injuries .,O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,CD JJ NNS VBP VBN IN NNS IN DT NNP NN CC DT IN JJ NNP CC NN VBD NNS .
"The Madrid blasts , as Spain marked Constitution Day , followed telephone warnings from the Basque separatist group ETA .",O B-geo O O O B-geo O B-tim I-tim O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-org O,"DT NNP NNS , IN NNP VBD NNP NNP , VBD NN NNS IN DT NNP NN NN NNP ."
Interior Minister Jose Antonio Alonso called the blasts another example of senseless violence that only confirms the need to fight ETA with all the power of the democratic state .,O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O,NN NN NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NNS DT NN IN JJ NN WDT RB VBZ DT NN TO VB NNP IN PDT DT NN IN DT JJ NN .
The sixth explosion damaged a post office in the northern town of Navarra .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT JJ NN VBD DT NN NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
"Meanwhile , authorities evacuated the airport in the northern city of Santander after receiving a bomb threat believed to be from ETA .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-org O,"RB , NNS VBD DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP IN VBG DT NN NN VBN TO VB IN NNP ."
"Police searched the facility , but found no explosives .",O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBD DT NN , CC VBD DT NNS ."
