"Palestinian gunmen have ambushed a vehicle near a Gaza Strip border crossing , killing two Israelis and wounding four others .",B-gpe O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP VBN DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NN VBG , VBG CD NNS CC VBG CD NNS ."
Israeli troops returned fire and killed one gunman following the attack Saturday at the Kissufim border crossing in southern Gaza .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-org O O O B-geo I-geo O,JJ NNS VBD NN CC VBD CD NN VBG DT NN NNP IN DT NNP NN VBG IN JJ NNP .
"Three militant groups - Islamic Jihad , al-Aqsa Martyrs Brigade and the Popular Resistance Committee - all claimed responsibility for the attack .",O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O,"CD JJ NNS IN NNP NNP , NNP NNP NNP CC DT NNP NNP NNP IN DT VBN NN IN DT NN ."
"The violence came hours after Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice met Palestinian leader Mahmoud Abbas , and praised security efforts ahead of Israel 's planned withdrawal from Gaza .",O O O O O O O B-org B-per I-per O B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O,"DT NN VBD NNS IN NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBD JJ NN NNP NNP , CC VBD NN NNS RB IN NNP POS VBN NN IN NNP ."
"On Friday , Israeli troops captured a Palestinian man they say was planning to detonate a suicide bomb in Tel Aviv .",O B-tim O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"IN NNP , JJ NNS VBD DT JJ NN PRP VBP VBD VBG TO VB DT NN NN IN NNP NNP ."
