Senior Israeli officials say prime minister-designate Ehud Olmert will likely meet with Palestinian President Mahmoud Abbas later this month .,O B-gpe O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per B-tim O O O,JJ JJ NNS VBP JJ JJ NNP NNP MD RB VB IN JJ NNP NNP NNP RB DT NN .
They say the talks will probably take place after Mr. Olmert visits the United States to discuss his plan to withdraw from some isolated Israeli settlements in the West Bank while strengthening major settlement blocs there .,O O O O O O O O O B-per B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O,PRP VBP DT NNS MD RB VB NN IN NNP NNP VBZ DT NNP NNPS TO VB PRP$ NN TO VB IN DT JJ JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNP IN VBG JJ NN NNS RB .
Mr. Olmert 's government is to be sworn into office Thursday .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP NNP POS NN VBZ TO VB VBN IN NN NNP .
The last meeting between Mr. Abbas and an Israeli prime minister was in 2005 when he met with Ariel Sharon .,O O O O B-per I-per O O B-gpe O O O O B-tim O O O O B-per I-per O,DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP CC DT JJ JJ NN VBD IN CD WRB PRP VBD IN NNP NNP .
Israeli officials have said they will not hold negotiations with the Hamas-led Palestinian government .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN PRP MD RB VB NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN .
