Armenia prides itself on being the first nation to formally adopt Christianity ( early 4th century ) .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O,NNP VBZ PRP IN VBG DT JJ NN TO RB VB NNP LRB JJ JJ NN RRB .
"Despite periods of autonomy , over the centuries Armenia came under the sway of various empires including the Roman , Byzantine , Arab , Persian , and Ottoman .",O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O B-geo O,"IN NNS IN NN , IN DT NNS NNP VBD IN DT NN IN JJ NNS VBG DT NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP , CC NNP ."
"During World War I in the western portion of Armenia , Ottoman Turkey instituted a policy of forced resettlement coupled with other harsh practices that resulted in an estimated 1 million Armenian deaths .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"IN NNP NNP PRP IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN JJ NN VBN IN JJ JJ NNS WDT VBD IN DT VBN CD CD JJ NNS ."
"The eastern area of Armenia was ceded by the Ottomans to Russia in 1828 ; this portion declared its independence in 1918 , but was conquered by the Soviet Red Army in 1920 .",O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-tim O,"DT JJ NN IN NNP VBD VBN IN DT NNPS TO NNP IN CD ; DT NN VBD PRP$ NN IN CD , CC VBD VBN IN DT NNP NNP NNP IN CD ."
"Armenian leaders remain preoccupied by the long conflict with Azerbaijan over Nagorno-Karabakh , a primarily Armenian-populated region , assigned to Soviet Azerbaijan in the 1920s by Moscow .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-tim O,"JJ NNS VBP VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP IN NNP , DT RB JJ NN , VBN TO JJ NN IN DT NNS IN NNP ."
Armenia and Azerbaijan began fighting over the area in 1988 ; the struggle escalated after both countries attained independence from the Soviet Union in 1991 .,B-geo O B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-tim O,NNP CC NNP VBD VBG IN DT NN IN CD ; DT NN VBN IN DT NNS VBD NN IN DT NNP NNP IN CD .
"By May 1994 , when a cease-fire took hold , ethnic Armenian forces held not only Nagorno-Karabakh but also a significant portion of Azerbaijan proper .",O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"IN NNP CD , WRB DT NN VBD NN , JJ JJ NNS VBN RB RB JJ CC RB DT JJ NN IN NNP JJ ."
The economies of both sides have been hurt by their inability to make substantial progress toward a peaceful resolution .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS IN DT NNS VBP VBN VBN IN PRP$ NN TO VB JJ NN IN DT JJ NN .
"Turkey closed the common border with Armenia in 1994 because of the Armenian separatists ' control of Nagorno-Karabakh and surrounding areas , further hampering Armenian economic growth .",B-geo O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O B-gpe O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-gpe O O O,"NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN NNP IN CD IN IN DT JJ NNS POS NN IN NNP CC VBG NNS , RB VBG JJ JJ NN ."
"In 2009 , senior Armenian leaders began pursuing rapprochement with Turkey , aiming to secure an opening of the border ; this process is currently dormant .",O B-tim O O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN CD , JJ JJ NNS VBD VBG NN IN NNP , VBG TO VB DT NN IN DT NN ; DT NN VBZ RB JJ ."
