Voters in the Democratic Republic of Congo have overwhelmingly backed the new postwar constitution .,O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O,NNS IN DT JJ NNP IN NNP VBP RB VBN DT JJ JJ NN .
"Election officials said Saturday that 83 percent of voters said "" yes "" to the draft document , with more than more than two-thirds of the ballots counted .",O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NN NNS VBD NNP IN CD NN IN NNS VBD LQU UH LQU TO DT NN NN , IN JJR IN JJR IN NNS IN DT NNS VBN ."
International observers have called the vote free and fair .,O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN DT NN JJ CC JJ .
"Once approved , the constitution will clear the way for parliamentary and presidential elections to be held by June 2006 .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"RB VBN , DT NN MD VB DT NN IN JJ CC JJ NNS TO VB VBN IN NNP CD ."
Congo has been struggling to emerge from decades of instability and violence .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN VBG TO VB IN NNS IN NN CC NN .
A five-year war that ended in 2003 killed some four million people .,O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O,DT JJ NN WDT VBD IN CD VBD DT CD CD NNS .
The United Nations maintains its largest peacekeeping force in Congo .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNP NNP VBZ PRP$ JJS NN NN IN NNP .
