President Bush is urging Americans to thank and assist members of the United States military and their families .,B-per I-per O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBG NNS TO VB CC VB NNS IN DT NNP NNPS NN CC PRP$ NNS .
"The president made his appeal during a televised speech Tuesday at Camp Pendleton , a U.S. Marine base in the state of California .",O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo I-geo O O B-org I-org O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NN VBD PRP$ NN IN DT JJ NN NNP IN NNP NNP , DT NNP NN NN IN DT NN IN NNP ."
Mr. Bush asked Americans to visit a website ( americasupportsyou.mil ) for ideas on how to help military men and women .,B-per I-per O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD NNS TO VB DT NN LRB NNP RRB IN NNS IN WRB TO VB JJ NNS CC NNS .
Camp Pendleton has one of the highest casualty rates in Iraq of any U.S. military base or installation .,B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ CD IN DT JJS NN NNS IN NNP IN DT NNP JJ NN CC NN .
The president was scheduled to have lunch with the Marines and visit troops wounded in Iraq and Afghanistan .,O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,DT NN VBD VBN TO VB NN IN DT NNPS CC VB NNS VBN IN NNP CC NNP .
The speech came on the 63rd anniversary of the day the Japanese attacked Pearl Harbor and sent the United States into World War Two .,O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O B-tim O B-gpe O B-geo I-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O,DT NN VBD IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN DT NNS VBD NNP NNP CC VBD DT NNP NNPS IN NNP NNP CD .
