Authorities in Pakistan say at least six suspected militants died when a bomb they were making blew up in the North Waziristan tribal region near the Afghan border .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-gpe O O,NNS IN NNP VBP IN JJS CD JJ NNS VBD WRB DT NN PRP VBD VBG VBD RP IN DT NNP NNP JJ NN IN DT JJ NN .
"A military spokesman says residents of the area around Miranshah , where the explosion destroyed a house early Saturday , said the victims were foreigners , possibly Arabs .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-gpe O,"DT JJ NN VBZ NNS IN DT NN IN NNP , WRB DT NN VBD DT NN JJ NNP , VBD DT NNS VBD NNS , RB NNS ."
"Authorities say confirmed one of the six dead was a women , but had no definite information about their nationality .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP VBN CD IN DT CD NN VBD DT NNS , CC VBD DT JJ NN IN PRP$ NN ."
Many insurgents with links to Al-Qaida supposedly fled to Pakistan 's Waziristan tribal regions after U.S.-led forces ousted the Taliban from power in Afghanistan nearly four years ago .,O O O O O B-org O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O B-org O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O,JJ NNS IN NNS TO NNP RB VBD TO NNP POS NNP NN NNS IN JJ NNS VBD DT NNP IN NN IN NNP RB CD NNS RB .
