"China says it has sentenced to death five ethnic Uighur Muslims from the country 's restive far western region , who were convicted of separatist activities .",B-geo O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ PRP VBZ VBN TO NN CD JJ NNP NNPS IN DT NN POS JJ RB JJ NN , WP VBD VBN IN JJ NNS ."
"The official Xinhua news agency said Sunday that the Intermediate Court in Kashgar , in the province of Xinjiang , sentenced a sixth man to life in prison .",O O B-org O O O B-tim O O B-org I-org O B-geo O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNP NN NN VBD NNP IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP , IN DT NN IN NNP , VBD DT JJ NN TO NN IN NN ."
"The agency said of the five men who were sentenced to death , two had their sentences suspended for two years .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"DT NN VBD IN DT CD NNS WP VBD VBN TO NN , CD VBD PRP$ NNS VBN IN CD NNS ."
That means the death sentence will be commuted to life in jail if the prisoners show good behavior and remorse for two years .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,DT VBZ DT NN NN MD VB VBN TO NN IN NN IN DT NNS VBP JJ NN CC NN IN CD NNS .
Chinese authorities say the six ethnic Uighur Muslims were members of a terrorist organization .,B-gpe O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP DT CD JJ NNP NNPS VBD NNS IN DT JJ NN .
"China has cracked down hard on Uighurs , whom it accuses of trying to set up an independent state in Xinjiang .",B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,"NNP VBZ VBN RP RB IN NNP , WP PRP VBZ IN VBG TO VB RP DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
