"Iraqi troops have carried out house-to-house searches in the northern city of Mosul , as a new crackdown against al-Qaida in Iraq entered its second day Thursday .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-org O B-geo O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,"JJ NNS VBP VBN RP NN NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , IN DT JJ NN IN NNP IN NNP VBD PRP$ JJ NN NNP ."
It is unclear how many arrests took place .,O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ JJ WRB JJ NNS VBD NN .
Iraqi officials also eased some restrictions on movement that had been in force in Mosul .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNS RB VBD DT NNS IN NN WDT VBD VBN IN NN IN NNP .
"Iraqi Prime Minister Nouri al-Maliki is overseeing the new offensive against al-Qaida militants in Mosul , their last Iraqi stronghold .",B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-org B-geo O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O,"JJ JJ NN NNP NNP VBZ VBG DT JJ NN IN NNP NNS IN NNP , PRP$ JJ JJ NN ."
Iraqi officials say more than 500 suspected insurgents have been arrested in and around Mosul since the operation began earlier this week .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP JJR IN CD JJ NNS VBP VBN VBN IN CC IN NNP IN DT NN VBD RBR DT NN .
The U.S. military says it is giving support to Iraqi troops leading the operation .,O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBZ PRP VBZ VBG NN TO JJ NNS VBG DT NN .
"Meanwhile , the U.S. military says at least one militant was killed in overnight fighting in Baghdad 's Sadr City .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O,"RB , DT NNP NN VBZ IN JJS CD NN VBD VBN IN JJ NN IN NNP POS NNP NNP ."
The military says fighting in Sadr City between U.S.-backed forces and Shi'ite militiamen loyal to radical cleric Moqtada al-Sadr has eased in recent days .,O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-org O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBG IN NNP NNP IN JJ NNS CC NNP NNS JJ TO JJ NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN JJ NNS .
