"President Barack Obama is heading north , to Canada , for his first international trip as U.S. commander-in-chief .",B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBG RB , TO NNP , IN PRP$ JJ JJ NN IN NNP NN ."
White House spokesman Robert Gibbs said Wednesday Mr. Obama will meet with Canadian Prime Minister Stephen Harper during the trip on February 19 .,B-org I-org O B-per I-per O B-tim B-per I-per O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O B-tim I-tim O,NNP NNP NN NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP NNP MD VB IN JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP IN DT NN IN NNP CD .
The spokesman said the health of each economy and the global economy will be a large part of the agenda .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD DT NN IN DT NN CC DT JJ NN MD VB DT JJ NN IN DT NN .
He said trade will also likely be discussed .,O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD NN MD RB RB VB VBN .
"In other news , the spokesman said Mr. Obama has called South African President Kgalema Motlanthe - the latest in a series of world leaders that Mr. Obama has talked with since taking office January 20 .",O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"IN JJ NN , DT NN VBD NNP NNP VBZ VBN JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP IN DT JJS IN DT NN IN NN NNS IN NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN IN VBG NN NNP CD ."
