Ukrainians are observing a day of mourning for the 27 people killed in a suspected gas explosion that destroyed sections of a five-story apartment building Wednesday .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNS VBP VBG DT NN IN VBG IN DT CD NNS VBN IN DT JJ NN NN WDT VBD NNS IN DT JJ NN NN NNP .
Rescuers pulled out 21 survivors from the ruins before authorities began winding down their search in the Crimean Peninsula resort of Yevpatoria .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo O,NNS VBD RP CD NNS IN DT NNS IN NNS VBD VBG RP PRP$ NN IN DT JJ NNP NN IN NNP .
Officials say they found a family of five among the dead .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP PRP VBD DT NN IN CD IN DT NN .
Investigators believe oxygen canisters stored in the basement exploded .,O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP NN NNS VBN IN DT NN VBD .
President Viktor Yushchenko and Prime Minister Yulia Tymoshenko put aside their political bickering and traveled together to the scene of the disaster .,B-per I-per I-per O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD RP PRP$ JJ NN CC VBD RB TO DT NN IN DT NN .
Russian President Dmitri Medvedev offered to send personnel from Russia 's Black Sea fleet to help in the search for survivors .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD TO VB NNS IN NNP POS NNP NNP NN TO VB IN DT NN IN NNS .
