NATO said Tuesday Afghan and coalition forces conducting a joint patrol in southern Helmand province killed up to 23 insurgents in three separate engagements in the province .,B-org O B-tim B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD NNP JJ CC NN NNS VBG DT JJ NN IN JJ NNP NN VBD RP TO CD NNS IN CD JJ NNS IN DT NN .
"A NATO statement said a joint patrol requested artillery rocket fire to suppress insurgents , after sustaining small arms and machine gunfire late Monday .",O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"DT NNP NN VBD DT JJ NN VBD NN NN NN TO VB NNS , IN VBG JJ NNS CC NN NN JJ NNP ."
NATO also confirmed that its troops captured a Haqqani network sub-commander and two of his associates during an overnight operation in eastern Khost province .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O,NNP RB VBD IN PRP$ NNS VBD DT NNP NN NN CC CD IN PRP$ NNS IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NNP NN .
"The troops also recovered a pistol , a grenade and multiple bayonets and loaded magazines at the scene .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS RB VBD DT NN , DT NN CC JJ NNS CC VBN NNS IN DT NN ."
"In central Wardak province Tuesday , a joint Afghan and coalition force killed three insurgents in charge of manufacturing and distributing home-made bombs in the province .",O O B-org O B-tim O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN JJ NNP NN NNP , DT JJ JJ CC NN NN VBD CD NNS IN NN IN NN CC VBG JJ NNS IN DT NN ."
