"A new movie about Arab-Americans in Los Angeles , in the era after the September 11 , 2001 terrorist attacks , is putting a human face on a population that most Americans know little about .",O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O,"DT JJ NN IN NNS IN NNP NNP , IN DT NN IN DT NNP CD , CD JJ NNS , VBZ VBG DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN JJS NNS VBP JJ IN ."
""" AmericanEast "" is a comic drama highlighting the pressures felt by Arab-Americans as they try to fit into American society and battle negative stereotypes .",O B-art O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,LQU NNP RQU VBZ DT JJ NN VBG DT NNS VBN IN NNS IN PRP VBP TO VB IN JJ NN CC NN JJ NNS .
Mohamed Elshinnawi has more .,B-per I-per O O O,NNP NNP VBZ RBR .
