Eddie Van Halen plans to enter rehab .,B-per I-per I-per O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP VBZ TO VB NN .
"In a March 8 statement , the guitarist for the hard rock band Van Halen said he will seek treatment for unspecified reasons .",O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NNP CD NN , DT NN IN DT JJ NN NN NNP NNP VBD PRP MD VB NN IN JJ NNS ."
He says he presently feels incapable of giving fans his best performance .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ PRP RB VBZ JJ IN VBG NNS PRP$ JJS NN .
It 's not known whether Eddie Van Halen will be in New York City for Van Halen 's March 12 induction into the Rock and Roll Hall Of Fame .,O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O B-per I-per O B-tim I-tim O O O B-per O B-per I-per O O O,PRP VBZ RB VBN IN NNP NNP NNP MD VB IN NNP NNP NNP IN NNP NNP POS NNP CD NN IN DT NNP CC NNP NNP IN NNP .
