"About 4,000 people turned out in the Turkish capital , Ankara , Saturday to welcome home Prime Minister Recep Tayyip Erdogan from successful talks with the European Union .",O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O B-tim O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-org I-org O,"IN CD NNS VBD RP IN DT JJ NN , NNP , NNP TO VB NN NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP IN JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNP ."
"Near-freezing temperatures did not discourage the cheering crowd , many of whom waved EU flags .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O,"JJ NNS VBD RB VB DT NN NN , NN IN WP VBD NNP NNS ."
Confetti and fireworks rounded off the celebrations marking the European body 's decision Friday to begin membership talks with Turkey next October .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-tim O B-tim O,NNP CC NNS VBD RP DT NNS VBG DT JJ NN POS NN NNP TO VB NN NNS IN NNP JJ NNP .
Prime Minister Erdogan told the crowd that Turkey had turned a critical juncture and would have to work harder now to assure its entry into the Union .,B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN NNP VBD VBN DT JJ NN CC MD VB TO VB RB RB TO VB PRP$ NN IN DT NNP .
"The European Union has imposed tough conditions on Turkey 's membership before talks , which could last years , can open next October .",O B-org I-org O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN JJ NNS IN NNP POS NN IN NNS , WDT MD VB NNS , MD VB JJ NNP ."
