President Vladimir Putin says his country is developing and testing new nuclear missile systems that are not like those available to any other nuclear power .,B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP$ NN VBZ VBG CC VBG JJ JJ NN NNS WDT VBP RB IN DT JJ TO DT JJ JJ NN .
Russian news agencies quote the Russian leader who made the comments Wednesday in a speech to a group of high-ranking military officials .,B-gpe O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN NNS VBP DT JJ NN WP VBD DT NNS NNP IN DT NN TO DT NN IN JJ JJ NNS .
"The reports say Mr. Putin warned of the dangers of international terrorism , saying Russia will face new threats if it does not develop its nuclear and missile shield systems .",O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS VBP NNP NNP VBD IN DT NNS IN JJ NN , VBG NNP MD VB JJ NNS IN PRP VBZ RB VB PRP$ JJ CC NN NN NNS ."
