Thousands of supporters of Egypt 's banned Muslim Brotherhood demanded real political reform at protests across the country Wednesday .,O O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNS IN NNS IN NNP POS VBN NNP NNP VBD JJ JJ NN IN NNS IN DT NN NNP .
"Riot police surrounded a Cairo mosque where demonstrators gathered chanting demands for decades-old emergency laws to be repealed , and be replaced by Islamic law .",O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NN NN VBN DT NNP NN WRB NNS VBD VBG NNS IN JJ NN NNS TO VB VBN , CC VB VBN IN JJ NN ."
Large numbers of protesters also turned out in towns around the capital .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS IN NNS RB VBD RP IN NNS IN DT NN .
"In all , police detained some 200 protesters , but there were no confirmed reports of violence .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT , NNS VBD DT CD NNS , CC EX VBD DT VBN NNS IN NN ."
President Hosni Mubarak has proposed a constitutional amendment that would allow more than one candidate for president in upcoming elections .,O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN WDT MD VB JJR IN CD NN IN NN IN JJ NNS .
"Parliament is due to vote on the proposal next week , but opponents fear the ruling party will impose strict conditions on who can run , making the amendment meaningless .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ JJ TO VB IN DT NN JJ NN , CC NNS VBP DT VBG NN MD VB JJ NNS IN WP MD VB , VBG DT NN JJ ."
