Police say two suicide bombers targeting a minority community killed at least 20 people and wounded 30 others in northern Iraq 's restive Mosul province .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O,NNS VBP CD NN NNS VBG DT NN NN VBD IN JJS CD NNS CC VBD CD NNS IN JJ NNP POS JJ NNP NN .
Officials say the twin explosions occurred Thursday evening in a crowded cafe in the city of Sinjar .,O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNS VBP DT JJ NNS VBD NNP NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN NNP .
"Authorities say most of the victims were of the Yazidi religious sect , a Kurdish-speaking minority in the region .",O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP JJS IN DT NNS VBD IN DT NNP JJ NN , DT JJ NN IN DT NN ."
"The attack comes two years after four suicide truck bombs went off simultaneously in the same area , killing more than 400 Yazidis .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,"DT NN VBZ CD NNS IN CD NN NN NNS VBD RB RB IN DT JJ NN , VBG JJR IN CD NNP ."
"Bomb attacks have killed more than 100 people since Friday in Baghdad , Kirkuk and Mosul .",O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O,"NN NNS VBP VBN JJR IN CD NNS IN NNP IN NNP , NNP CC NNP ."
The bloodshed is the latest in a wave of violence that has occurred since American forces pulled back from urban areas in June .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NN VBZ DT JJS IN DT NN IN NN WDT VBZ VBN IN JJ NNS VBD RB IN JJ NNS IN NNP .
