"The World Health Organization has confirmed two more deaths in Indonesia from the deadly H5N1 strain of bird flu , bringing that country 's death toll from the disease to 16 , over the past two years .",O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-tim I-tim O O,"DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN CD JJR NNS IN NNP IN DT JJ NNP NN IN NN NN , VBG DT NN POS NN NN IN DT NN IN CD , IN DT JJ CD NNS ."
"The organization confirmed at least one other person infected with the virus , which raises Indonesia 's total confirmed cases since 2005 to 22 .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,"DT NN VBD IN JJS CD JJ NN VBN IN DT NN , WDT VBZ NNP POS NN VBD NNS IN CD TO CD ."
WHO officials say they remain on alert for any signs that the virus has mutated into one that can spread from human to human .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBP PRP VBP IN NN IN DT NNS IN DT NN VBZ VBN IN CD WDT MD VB IN JJ TO JJ .
They note that the appearance of human cases in Turkey signals that the dangerous H5N1 strain of bird flu has moved farther west .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBP IN DT NN IN JJ NNS IN NNP NNS IN DT JJ NNP NN IN NN NN VBZ VBN RB RB .
WHO officials also say Iraq will receive thousands of doses of the anti-viral drug Tamiflu in case of an outbreak .,B-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,NNP NNS RB VBP NNP MD VB NNS IN NNS IN DT JJ NN NNP IN NN IN DT NN .
Experts have confirmed a girl in Iraq died of bird flu last month .,O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,NNS VBP VBN DT NN IN NNP VBD IN NN NN JJ NN .
