"A new United Nations report urges a massive effort to combat HIV infection , which it says has reached the highest number of people ever resulting in 3 million deaths from AIDS in the past year .",O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-tim O O,"DT JJ NNP NNP NN VBZ DT JJ NN TO VB NNP NN , WDT PRP VBZ VBZ VBN DT JJS NN IN NNS RB VBG IN CD CD NNS IN NNP IN DT JJ NN ."
"Tuesday 's report said there are 39.4 million people infected with HIV worldwide , with an increase in infection levels in every area of the world .",B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NN VBD EX VBP CD CD NNS VBN IN NNP NN , IN DT NN IN NN NNS IN DT NN IN DT NN ."
"Sub-Saharan Africa remains the area worst-hit by the disease , followed by the Caribbean .",B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP NNP VBZ DT NN NN IN DT NN , VBN IN DT NNP ."
An increasing proportion of those infected are women .,O O O O O O O O O,DT VBG NN IN DT VBN VBP NNS .
"The problem persists , the report says , despite increased prevention efforts such as AIDS education and voluntary testing and counseling .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ , DT NN VBZ , IN VBN NN NNS JJ IN NNP NN CC JJ NN CC NN ."
"Despite a rise in funding , nine out of 10 people who need antiretroviral therapy are still not receiving it .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN IN NN , CD IN IN CD NNS WP VBP JJ NN VBP RB RB VBG PRP ."
"The study says ultimately , only controlling HIV infection can make AIDS treatment affordable and sustainable .",O O O O O O O B-org O O O B-org O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ RB , RB VBG NNP NN MD VB NNP NN JJ CC JJ ."
