"South Korea 's Unification Minister , Lee Jong-seok , is urging Pyongyang to resume stalled negotiations on its nuclear program .",B-geo I-geo O O O O B-per I-per O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP POS NNP NNP , NNP NNP , VBZ VBG NNP TO VB VBN NNS IN PRP$ JJ NN ."
"South Korean news reports say Lee made the request at the opening session of a new round of inter-Korean talks , which began Friday in Pyongyang .",B-geo B-gpe O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-org O,"JJ JJ NN NNS VBP NNP VBD DT NN IN DT NN NN IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS , WDT VBD NNP IN NNP ."
Details on North Korea 's reaction to the proposal were not available .,O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNP NNP POS NN TO DT NN VBD RB JJ .
Pyongyang says it will not return to the talks until the United States lifts financial sanctions imposed over allegations North Korea counterfeits U.S. currency .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O,NNP VBZ PRP MD RB VB TO DT NNS IN DT NNP NNPS VBZ JJ NNS VBN IN NNS NNP NNP VBZ NNP NN .
"Reports say that during the inter-Korean talks , Lee also urged Pyongyang to address the issue of South Korean civilians and prisoners of war that Seoul says are being held against their will in the North .",O O O O O O O O B-per O O B-org O O O O O B-geo B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNS VBP IN IN DT JJ NNS , NNP RB VBD NNP TO VB DT NN IN JJ JJ NNS CC NNS IN NN IN NNP VBZ VBP VBG VBN IN PRP$ NN IN DT NNP ."
Pyongyang denies the allegations .,B-org O O O O,NNP VBZ DT NNS .
