The U.S. military in Afghanistan says it has released 85 Afghan prisoners after deciding they no longer posed a threat to their government .,O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN IN NNP VBZ PRP VBZ VBN CD JJ NNS IN VBG PRP RB RB VBD DT NN TO PRP$ NN .
Military spokeswoman Cindy Moore says the men were brought from U.S. bases to Kabul and turned over to local authorities during a closed-door ceremony at the Afghan Supreme Court .,O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-org I-org O,NNP NN NNP NNP VBZ DT NNS VBD VBN IN NNP NNS TO NNP CC VBD RP TO JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP .
"She said the prisoners , who were captured during U.S.-led military operations against the former Taleban regime , were freed after pledging loyalty to the new government .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD DT NNS , WP VBD VBN IN JJ JJ NNS IN DT JJ NNP NN , VBD VBN IN VBG NN TO DT JJ NN ."
Afghan officials say the men have spent between two months and two years in custody on suspicion of a variety of crimes .,B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP DT NNS VBP VBN IN CD NNS CC CD NNS IN NN IN NN IN DT NN IN NNS .
"Sunday release comes less than two weeks after 17 Afghan prisoners were released from U.S. prisons in Guantanamo Bay , Cuba .",B-tim O O O O B-tim O O B-tim B-gpe O O O O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O,"NNP NN VBZ JJR IN CD NNS IN CD JJ NNS VBD VBN IN NNP NNS IN NNP NNP , NNP ."
