World oil prices declined Wednesday after a U.S. government report showed strong supplies of gasoline and heating fuel in the key U.S. market .,O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,NNP NN NNS VBD NNP IN DT NNP NN NN VBD JJ NNS IN NN CC NN NN IN DT JJ NNP NN .
"The Energy Department said inventories of heating oil and diesel grew by two million barrels last week , and the stock of gasoline grew by a similar amount .",O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP VBD NNS IN NN NN CC NN VBD IN CD CD NNS JJ NN , CC DT NN IN NN VBD IN DT JJ NN ."
"After the report , the Bloomberg financial news service reported the price of crude oil for future delivery fell 81 cents to $ 43.10 a barrel .",O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN , DT NNP JJ NN NN VBD DT NN IN JJ NN IN JJ NN VBD CD NNS TO $ CD DT NN ."
Concern about a shortage of heating fuel during winter in the U.S. market was a factor in pushing oil prices up in recent months .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NN IN DT NN IN NN NN IN NN IN DT NNP NN VBD DT NN IN VBG NN NNS RB IN JJ NNS .
