The Chilean government says the eldest daughter of former dictator Augusto Pinochet has requested political asylum in the United States .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT JJ NN VBZ DT JJS NN IN JJ NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN JJ NN IN DT NNP NNPS .
U.S. Customs and Border officials say Lucia Pinochet was sent to an immigrant detention center Wednesday after she arrived at Dulles International Airport outside Washington from Argentina .,B-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O B-geo O B-geo O,NNP NNP CC NNP NNS VBP NNP NNP VBD VBN TO DT JJ NN NN NNP IN PRP VBD IN NNP NNP NNP IN NNP IN NNP .
"Pinochet on Sunday fled Chile , where she has been charged with tax evasion .",B-per O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP IN NNP VBD NNP , WRB PRP VBZ VBN VBN IN NN NN ."
Chile 's Foreign Minister Ignacio Walker said in Santiago he expects U.S. officials to take a few days to consider Pinochet 's asylum request and he expects it to be rejected .,B-geo O O B-per I-per I-per O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O B-tim O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD IN NNP PRP VBZ NNP NNS TO VB DT JJ NNS TO VB NNP POS NN NN CC PRP VBZ PRP TO VB VBN .
General Pinochet also has been charged with tax fraud .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP RB VBZ VBN VBN IN NN NN .
