North Korea held a ceremony Monday to open an advanced mobile phone network in the reclusive and impoverished country .,B-geo I-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD DT NN NNP TO VB DT JJ JJ NN NN IN DT JJ CC JJ NN .
"The official Korean Central News Agency says North Korean officials celebrated the start of the third-generation network , which was built by an Egyptian company , at a ceremony in Pyongyang .",O O B-gpe B-org I-org I-org O B-geo B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT JJ JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ JJ JJ NNS VBD DT NN IN DT NN NN , WDT VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN , IN DT NN IN NNP ."
Cairo-based Orascom Telecom Holding SAE has been building the network since announcing its $ 400 million deal with North Korea earlier this year .,B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN VBG DT NN IN VBG PRP$ $ CD CD NN IN NNP NNP RBR DT NN .
It was unclear who would use the network or how much phones would cost .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD JJ WP MD VB DT NN CC WRB JJ NNS MD VB .
Third-generation networks provide mobile users with access to advanced mobile capabilities such as video calls and high-speed Internet access .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NN NNS VBP JJ NNS IN NN TO JJ JJ NNS JJ IN NN NNS CC JJ NN NN .
North Korea relies on international aid to feed its people and strictly controls its citizens ' access to information .,B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ IN JJ NN TO VB PRP$ NNS CC RB VBZ PRP$ NNS POS NN TO NN .
