The U.S. Commission on International Religious Freedom says Saudi Arabia and Iran are countries of particular concern .,O B-org I-org O B-org I-org I-org O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNP NNP CC NNP VBP NNS IN JJ NN .
The commission says religious freedom does not exist in Saudi Arabia .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT NN VBZ JJ NN VBZ RB VB IN NNP NNP .
It says the kingdom 's government promotes extreme religious intolerance around the world .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ DT NN POS NN VBZ JJ JJ NN IN DT NN .
"It says Iran engages in systematic violations of religious freedom , including torture and executions , and that its record on the matter has further deteriorated over the past year .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"PRP VBZ NNP VBZ IN JJ NNS IN JJ NN , VBG NN CC NNS , CC IN PRP$ NN IN DT NN VBZ RB VBN IN DT JJ NN ."
Both Iran and Saudi Arabia were listed as countries of particular concern last year and the commission is urging U.S. Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice to keep them on the list this year .,O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-org B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP CC NNP NNP VBD VBN IN NNS IN JJ NN JJ NN CC DT NN VBZ VBG NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP TO VB PRP IN DT NN DT NN .
It also says Egypt and Iraq are being closely monitored because of violations of religious freedom .,O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP RB VBZ NNP CC NNP VBP VBG RB VBN IN IN NNS IN JJ NN .
