"Up to 400 Ethiopians protested in front of the offices of the Norwegian parliament , foreign ministry and prime minister today .",O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-tim O,"IN TO CD NNS VBD IN NN IN DT NNS IN DT JJ NN , JJ NN CC JJ NN NN ."
They are calling for increased pressure by Norway – and Europe – on the government of Ethiopia in the wake of last month ’s contested parliamentary elections .,O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBP VBG IN VBN NN IN NNP ; CC NNP ; IN DT NN IN NNP IN DT NN IN JJ NN POS VBN JJ NNS .
"Results from the Ethiopian electoral board show the ruling party in the lead , but the opposition says the results are fraught with voting irregularities and fraud .",O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN VBP DT VBG NN IN DT NN , CC DT NN VBZ DT NNS VBP JJ IN VBG NNS CC NN ."
The official election tally is not expected until July 8th .,O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT JJ NN RB VBZ RB VBN IN NNP CD .
Ghidey Zeratsion is a spokesman for The United Ethiopian Democratic Front in the Norwegian capital .,B-per I-per O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-gpe O O,NNP NNP VBZ DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP IN DT JJ NN .
He ’s also one of the leaders of today ’s demonstration in Oslo .,O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O,PRP VBZ RB CD IN DT NNS IN NN POS NN IN NNP .
He told Voice of America reporter William Eagle that his party wants the EU to stop lending political and economic support to the government of Ethiopia .,O O B-org I-org I-org O B-org I-org O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,PRP VBD NNP IN NNP NN NNP NNP IN PRP$ NN VBZ DT NNP TO VB VBG JJ CC JJ NN TO DT NN IN NNP .
"That includes , he says , extending debt relief .",O O O O O O O O O O,"DT VBZ , PRP VBZ , VBG NN NN ."
