China says it will strengthen controls on the export of nuclear goods for both civilian and military use to help prevent nuclear terrorism and proliferation .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ PRP MD VB NNS IN DT NN IN JJ NNS IN DT JJ CC JJ NN TO VB VB JJ NN CC NN .
State media report Saturday the stronger regulations forbid buyers from using or duplicating China 's nuclear goods and technologies for activities not approved by the International Atomic Energy Agency .,O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,NNP NNS NN NNP DT JJR NNS VBD NNS IN VBG CC VBG NNP POS JJ NNS CC NNS IN NNS RB VBN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP .
The new regulations also prohibit the transfer of nuclear technology or equipment to a third party not identified in the export agreement .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNS RB VBP DT NN IN JJ NN CC NN TO DT JJ NN RB VBN IN DT NN NN .
"Chinese Premier Wen Jiabao signed the regulation Friday , replacing a document dating from 1998 .",B-gpe B-org I-org I-org O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-tim O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN NNP , VBG DT NN VBG IN CD ."
The previous regulations failed to address the reproduction of nuclear goods .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNS VBD TO VB DT NN IN JJ NNS .
