"A top U.N. official has wrapped up a four-day visit to Sri Lanka , saying the world body has no plans to replace Norway as a peace broker between the Colombo government and Tamil Tiger rebels .",O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org O O,"DT JJ NNP NN VBZ VBN RP DT JJ NN TO NNP NNP , VBG DT NN NN VBZ DT NNS TO VB NNP IN DT NN NN IN DT NNP NN CC NNP NNP NNS ."
"Responding Wednesday to reports in local media , Special U.N. envoy Lakhdar Brahimi said the world body has not been asked to intervene in the decades-old conflict .",O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"VBG NNP TO NNS IN JJ NNS , JJ NNP NN NNP NNP VBD DT NN NN VBZ RB VBN VBN TO VB IN DT JJ NN ."
Mr. Brahimi said his visit included meetings with political parties and European cease-fire monitors .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD PRP$ NN VBD NNS IN JJ NNS CC JJ NN NNS .
"He said the talks covered a wide range of issues , but declined to give details .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD DT NNS VBD DT JJ NN IN NNS , CC VBD TO VB NNS ."
Mr. Brahimi came to the island nation at the invitation of President Chandrika Kumaratunga to assess the country 's peace process following the assassination of Sri Lanka 's foreign minister last month by suspected rebels .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-tim O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD TO DT NN NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP TO VB DT NN POS NN NN VBG DT NN IN NNP NNP POS JJ NN JJ NN IN JJ NNS .
