Officials in China say the government plans to build 40 nuclear power plants over the next 15 years to increase the production of electricity .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNP VBP DT NN VBZ TO VB CD JJ NN NNS IN DT JJ CD NNS TO VB DT NN IN NN .
"Chinese state media quote officials from the Commission of Science , Technology and Industry as saying Beijing plans to increase the proportion of electricity generated by nuclear power from the current 2.5 percent to four percent in 15 years .",B-gpe O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"JJ NN NNS VBP NNS IN DT NNP IN NNP , NNP CC NNP IN VBG NNP NNS TO VB DT NN IN NN VBN IN JJ NN IN DT JJ CD NN TO CD NN IN CD NNS ."
Most of the plants will provide electricity for China 's east coast .,O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,JJS IN DT NNS MD VB NN IN NNP POS JJ NN .
China now relies on coal for some 70 percent of its energy demands .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP RB VBZ IN NN IN DT CD NN IN PRP$ NN NNS .
"But officials are increasingly worried about the pollution from coal fired power plants and the hazards of China 's coal mines , which are the deadliest in the world .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"CC NNS VBP RB JJ IN DT NN IN NN VBN NN NNS CC DT NNS IN NNP POS NN NNS , WDT VBP DT JJS IN DT NN ."
