Iraqi officials say at least one police officer was killed and 10 people wounded after a suicide bomber detonated explosives near a police checkpoint .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP IN JJS CD NN NN VBD VBN CC CD NNS VBN IN DT NN NN VBD NNS IN DT NN NN .
Authorities say the attack took place Thursday near the northern city of Mosul .,O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O,NNS VBP DT NN VBD NN NNP IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
"In political news , Iraq 's Al-Mada newspaper quotes Prime Minister Nouri al-Maliki as saying his political rivals who narrowly won the March 7 parliamentary election would not be able to form a new government .",O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN JJ NN , NNP POS NNP NN VBZ NNP NNP NNP NNP IN VBG PRP$ JJ NNS WP RB VBD DT NNP CD JJ NN MD RB VB JJ TO VB DT JJ NN ."
"The newspaper says Mr. Maliki called the efforts by former Prime Minister Ayad Allawi 's Iraqiya bloc a "" waste of time . """,O O O B-per B-org O O O O O B-per O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ NNP NNP VBD DT NNS IN JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP POS NNP NN DT LQU NN IN NN . LQU
Iraqi election officials say Mr. Allawi 's bloc won 91 parliamentary seats while Prime Minister Maliki 's State of Law coalition had 89 .,B-gpe O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN NNS VBP NNP NNP POS NN VBD CD JJ NNS IN NNP NNP NNP POS NN IN NN NN VBD CD .
Neither group had the majority needed to form a new government .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD DT NN VBD TO VB DT JJ NN .
"However , Mr. Maliki 's Shi'ite coalition recently announced that it had formed an alliance with another Shi'ite bloc that came in third in the election .",O O B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , NNP NNP POS NNP NN RB VBD IN PRP VBD VBN DT NN IN DT NNP NN WDT VBD IN JJ IN DT NN ."
