U.S. officials say Sudan has apologized to visiting Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice after members of her staff and reporters traveling with her were manhandled by Sudanese security personnel in Khartoum .,B-geo O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-org B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo O,NNP NNS VBP NNP VBZ VBN TO VBG NNP IN NNP NNP NNP IN NNS IN PRP$ NN CC NNS VBG IN PRP VBD VBN IN JJ NN NNS IN NNP .
Ms. Rice had expressed outrage following the incident which occurred as she met with President Omar Hassan al-Bashir at his residence for talks on the situation in Sudan 's Darfur region .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O,NNP NNP VBD VBN NN VBG DT NN WDT VBD IN PRP VBD IN NNP NNP NNP NNP IN PRP$ NN IN NNS IN DT NN IN NNP POS NNP NN .
"U.S. officials say security personnel shoved members of Ms. Rice 's staff , including senior advisor Jim Wilkinson , as well as members of the press , as they tried to enter the meeting .",B-geo O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNS VBP NN NNS VBD NNS IN NNP NNP POS NN , VBG JJ NN NNP NNP , RB RB IN NNS IN DT NN , IN PRP VBD TO VB DT NN ."
"Later , when Ms. Rice arrived in Darfur , her spokesman , Sean McCormack , said she had received a personal phone call from Sudan 's foreign minister , Mustafa Osman Ismail , apologizing for the incident .",B-tim O O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O,"RB , WRB NNP NNP VBD IN NNP , PRP$ NN , NNP NNP , VBD PRP VBD VBN DT JJ NN NN IN NNP POS JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP , VBG IN DT NN ."
"Ms. Rice is touring a refugee camp in Darfur , where government troops and militias have been battling rebels for more than two years .",B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBG DT NN NN IN NNP , WRB NN NNS CC NNS VBP VBN VBG NNS IN JJR IN CD NNS ."
