President Bush has signed landmark legislation that will make sweeping changes to the U.S. intelligence community .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN JJ NN WDT MD VB JJ NNS TO DT NNP NN NN .
"Before signing the legislation Friday , President Bush said the bill is the most dramatic overhaul of the U.S. intelligence community in more than 50 years .",O O O O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O O,"IN VBG DT NN NNP , NNP NNP VBD DT NN VBZ DT RBS JJ NN IN DT NNP NN NN IN JJR IN CD NNS ."
"He thanked Congress for passing the bill earlier this month , and said the new legislation will help protect Americans against the threat of terrorism .",O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,"PRP VBD NNP IN VBG DT NN RBR DT NN , CC VBD DT JJ NN MD VB VB NNS IN DT NN IN NN ."
The bill is designed to improve communication and the sharing of information between the country 's 15 intelligence agencies .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBN TO VB NN CC DT NN IN NN IN DT NN POS CD NN NNS .
"It will also create a national counterterrorism center and a national intelligence director , who will oversee all intelligence agencies , including the Central Intelligence Agency .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,"PRP MD RB VB DT JJ NN NN CC DT JJ NN NN , WP MD VB DT NN NNS , VBG DT NNP NNP NNP ."
"The bill resulted from recommendations by the independent commission that investigated the deadly September 11 , 2001 attacks on the United States .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O B-geo I-geo O,"DT NN VBD IN NNS IN DT JJ NN WDT VBD DT JJ NNP CD , CD NNS IN DT NNP NNPS ."
