A truck bomb attack against a police station in the Iraqi capital has killed at least 22 police and civilians and wounded about 25 .,O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN NN NN IN DT NN NN IN DT JJ NN VBZ VBN IN JJS CD NNS CC NNS CC VBN IN CD .
"Authorities say the suicide bomber detonated a flatbed truck with about 220 kilograms of explosives at the station in eastern Baghdad , incinerating at least 20 nearby vehicles and damaging shops .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP DT NN NN VBD DT JJ NN IN IN CD NNS IN NNS IN DT NN IN JJ NNP , VBG IN JJS CD JJ NNS CC JJ NNS ."
"It was the deadliest attack in Iraq since a suicide bomber ignited a fuel truck south of Baghdad July 16 , killing nearly 100 people .",O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim I-tim O O O O O O,"PRP VBD DT JJS NN IN NNP IN DT NN NN VBD DT NN NN NN IN NNP NNP CD , VBG RB CD NNS ."
"Elsewhere in the capital , at least three people were killed when a mortar round fell near the Interior Ministry .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"RB IN DT NN , IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN WRB DT NN NN VBD IN DT NNP NNP ."
And a police chief was assassinated as he drove to work .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC DT NN NN VBD VBN IN PRP VBD TO VB .
"Separately , the U.S. military says a Marine was killed by a roadside bomb during combat operations Saturday near the western town Ar Rutbah .",O O O B-geo O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-per I-per O,"RB , DT NNP NN VBZ DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NN NN IN NN NNS NNP IN DT JJ NN NNP NNP ."
