"Four car bombs rocked a Shi'ite neighborhood in the Iraqi capital early Thursday , killing at least 17 people and wounding dozens more .",O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"CD NN NNS VBD DT NNP NN IN DT JJ NN RB NNP , VBG IN JJS CD NNS CC VBG NNS RBR ."
"Hours earlier , a triple car bombing killed at least 18 others in another mainly Shi'ite Baghdad neighborhood .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS RB , DT JJ NN VBG VBN IN JJS CD NNS IN DT RB JJ NNP NN ."
Another 50 people were wounded .,O O O O O O,DT CD NNS VBD VBN .
"In other developments , insurgent leader Abu Musab al-Zarqawi says one of Saudi Arabia 's most wanted al-Qaida militants has been killed in a U.S. airstrike in northwestern Iraq .",O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-org O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O,"IN JJ NNS , JJ NN NNP NNP NNP VBZ CD IN NNP NNP POS RBS JJ NNP NNS VBZ VBN VBN IN DT NNP NN IN JJ NNP ."
An Internet statement said Abdullah Mohammed Rashid al-Roshoud was killed near Qaim .,O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O B-geo O,DT NNP NN VBD NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD VBN IN NNP .
It did not say when the death occurred .,O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD RB VB WRB DT NN VBD .
"Meanwhile , Iraqi Planning Minister Barham Saleh says he hopes that Wednesday 's international conference in Brussels translates into much-needed financial assistance .",O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O B-tim O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"RB , JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ IN NNP POS JJ NN IN NNP VBZ IN JJ JJ NN ."
"In an interview with VOA 's Kurdish service , Mr. Saleh called on Saudi Arabia and other Gulf countries to be more attentive to Iraq and its needs .",O O O O B-org O O O O B-per I-per O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"IN DT NN IN NNP POS NNP NN , NNP NNP VBD RP NNP NNP CC JJ NNP NNS TO VB RBR JJ TO NNP CC PRP$ NNS ."
