"A plane carrying 11 people aiding the African Union peacekeeping mission in Somalia has crashed near the Somali capital , Mogadishu .",O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O,"DT NN VBG CD NNS VBG DT NNP NNP VBG NN IN NNP VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NN , NNP ."
Several witnesses and officials say the aircraft was downed by a missile shortly after takeoff from the Mogadishu airport Friday .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo B-tim O,JJ NNS CC NNS VBP DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NN RB IN NN IN DT NNP NN NNP .
The plane was a Russian or Belarusian-built cargo plane used by the A.U. mission in Somalia .,O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O,DT NN VBD DT JJ CC JJ NN NN VBN IN DT NNP NN IN NNP .
A.U. and Somali government sources say the passengers included technicians who had been working to repair another plane at the airport .,B-geo O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP CC JJ NN NNS VBP DT NNS VBD NNS WP VBD VBN VBG TO VB DT NN IN DT NN .
There has been no word on whether anyone survived the crash .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,EX VBZ VBN DT NN IN IN DT VBD DT NN .
The apparent attack followed two days of intense clashes in Mogadishu that have killed at least 25 people .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBD CD NNS IN JJ NNS IN NNP WDT VBP VBN IN JJS CD NNS .
Fighting on the ground largely died down today after the powerful Hawiye clan said it had reached a ceasefire with Ethiopian forces who back the Somali government .,O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-gpe O O,VBG IN DT NN RB VBD RP NN IN DT JJ NNP NN VBD PRP VBD VBN DT NN IN JJ NNS WP VBP DT JJ NN .
Many of the Islamist fighters who have been fighting the government come from the clan .,O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,NN IN DT NNP NNS WP VBP VBN VBG DT NN VBD IN DT NN .
