"In an early morning raid Saturday , Israeli forces burst into Shaer 's home in the West Bank town of Ramallah and took him away for questioning .",O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O B-gpe O O O B-per O O O O B-org I-org O O B-org O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN NN NNP , JJ NNS VBD IN NNP POS NN IN DT NNP NNP NN IN NNP CC VBD PRP RB IN VBG ."
"An Israeli spokesman said the Palestinian leader was taken into custody because he is a member of Hamas , which Israel , the United States and the European Union consider a terrorist organization .",O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O B-org I-org O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBD DT JJ NN VBD VBN IN NN IN PRP VBZ DT NN IN NNP , WDT NNP , DT NNP NNPS CC DT NNP NNP VBP DT JJ NN ."
"In a separate incident , a Palestinian gunman and an Israeli soldier were killed in a firefight in the West Bank .",O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"IN DT JJ NN , DT JJ NN CC DT JJ NN VBD VBN IN DT NN IN DT NNP NNP ."
Israel began a crackdown against members of the Palestinian ruling group Hamas following the kidnapping of an Israeli soldier from an Israeli army post near the Gaza Strip in June .,B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-org O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O O O B-org I-org O B-tim O,NNP VBD DT NN IN NNS IN DT JJ NN NN NNP VBG DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN NN IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP .
