The 2005 Nobel Prize in Physics has been awarded to two Americans and one German for their work in the field of optics .,O B-tim I-tim I-tim O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O,DT CD NNP NNP IN NNP VBZ VBN VBN TO CD NNS CC CD JJ IN PRP$ NN IN DT NN IN NNS .
The Royal Swedish Academy of Sciences in Stockholm announced Tuesday that American Roy J. Glauber will receive one half of the $ 1.3 million prize for his theoretical description of the behavior of light particles .,O B-org B-gpe B-org I-org I-org O B-org O B-tim O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP JJ NNP IN NNPS IN NNP VBD NNP IN JJ NNP NNP NNP MD VB CD NN IN DT $ CD CD NN IN PRP$ JJ NN IN DT NN IN JJ NNS .
John L. Hall of the United States and Theodor W. Haensch of Germany will split the other half of the prize for their work in determining the color of the light of atoms and molecules with extreme precision .,B-per I-per I-per O O B-geo I-geo O B-per I-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP IN DT NNP NNPS CC NNP NNP NNP IN NNP MD VB DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN PRP$ NN IN VBG DT NN IN DT NN IN NNS CC NNS IN JJ NN .
The Nobel prize for medicine was presented Monday to Australian scientists Barry J. Marshall and J. Robin Warren for diagnosing the cause of stomach ulcers .,O O O O O O O B-tim O B-gpe O B-per I-per I-per O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN IN NN VBD VBN NNP TO JJ NNS NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP IN VBG DT NN IN NN NNS .
"Prizes for chemistry , literature , and peace also will be announced this week .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN NN , NN , CC NN RB MD VB VBN DT NN ."
The economic prize will be announced on October 10 .,O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT JJ NN MD VB VBN IN NNP CD .
