"Spiraling violence continues to mar Egypt 's parliamentary elections , with police and voters clashing in the northern part of the country , leaving two people dead .",O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"VBG NN VBZ TO VB NNP POS JJ NNS , IN NNS CC NNS VBG IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN , VBG CD NNS JJ ."
Hospital officials in the town of Damietta say two people have been killed since polls opened Wednesday for the final round of run-off voting .,O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O,NN NNS IN DT NN IN NNP VBP CD NNS VBP VBN VBN IN NNS VBD NNP IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NN .
Voters in other parts of the country also have complained that they have been barred from polling stations in areas where opposition candidates are expected to do well .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN JJ NNS IN DT NN RB VBP VBN IN PRP VBP VBN VBN IN VBG NNS IN NNS WRB NN NNS VBP VBN TO VB RB .
"President Hosni Mubarak 's National Democratic Party is expected to retain control in the 454-seat parliament , despite significant gains by candidates supported by the banned Muslim Brotherhood .",B-per I-per I-per O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"NNP NNP NNP POS NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB NN IN DT JJ NN , IN JJ NNS IN NNS VBN IN DT VBN NNP NNP ."
The United States said Tuesday that reports of violence and voter intimidation raise serious concerns about the path of political reform in Egypt .,O B-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNP NNPS VBD NNP IN NNS IN NN CC NN NN NN JJ NNS IN DT NN IN JJ NN IN NNP .
"In all , five people have been killed since the three-stage vote began November 9 .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"IN DT , CD NNS VBP VBN VBN IN DT JJ NN VBD NNP CD ."
