"Iraqi forces have taken complete control of the fortified Green Zone in Baghdad , as U.S. troops prepare to withdraw from the country .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP VBN JJ NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP IN NNP , IN NNP NNS VBP TO VB IN DT NN ."
"With the handover Tuesday , Iraq security forces will guard all entry points to the international zone , which houses government offices and foreign embassies .",O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN NNP , NNP NN NNS MD VB DT NN NNS TO DT JJ NN , WDT VBZ NN NNS CC JJ NNS ."
The Green Zone was demarcated after the 2003 U.S.-led invasion that toppled Iraqi dictator Saddam Hussein .,O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O B-gpe O B-per I-per O,DT NNP NNP VBD VBN IN DT CD JJ NN WDT VBD JJ NN NNP NNP .
"The United States is planning to withdraw all but 50,000 soldiers from Iraq by September , and to withdraw the rest next year .",O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNPS VBZ VBG TO VB DT CC CD NNS IN NNP IN NNP , CC TO VB DT NN JJ NN ."
