The Sri Lankan military says its troops have killed at least 150 Tamil Tiger rebels during heavy fighting since Friday .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NNP NNP JJ VBZ PRP$ NNS VBP VBN IN JJS CD NNP NNP NNS IN JJ NN IN NNP .
An army spokesman ( Udaya Nanayakkara ) said the Tigers launched a series of counterattacks against a military onslaught that has left them confined to a 45 square kilometer area on Sri Lanka 's northeastern coast .,O O O O B-per I-per O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O,DT NN NN LRB NNP NNP RRB VBD DT NNP VBD DT NN IN NNS IN DT JJ NN WDT VBZ VBN PRP VBD TO DT CD JJ NN NN IN NNP NNP POS JJ NN .
The military said it killed 100 rebels during fighting Friday and Saturday .,O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,DT NN VBD PRP VBD CD NNS IN VBG NNP CC NNP .
Officials say 50 bodies were recovered within the past day .,O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,NNS VBP CD NNS VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN .
"Journalists and independent observers are barred from the war zone , making it difficult to confirm reports from either side of the conflict .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS CC JJ NNS VBP VBN IN DT NN NN , VBG PRP JJ TO VB NNS IN DT NN IN DT NN ."
Tamil Tiger rebels have been fighting since 1983 to establish an independent homeland for Sri Lanka 's ethnic minority Tamils .,O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O,NNP NNP NNS VBP VBN VBG IN CD TO VB DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP POS JJ NN NNS .
The group claims Tamils face second-class treatment by the Sinhalese majority .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,DT NN VBZ NNS VBP JJ NN IN DT NNP NN .
