"An Afghan official said a rocket fired into Afghanistan from across the border in Pakistan hit a mosque near a NATO base , killing at least 3 people and wounding several others .",O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBD DT NN VBN IN NNP IN IN DT NN IN NNP VBD DT NN IN DT NNP NN , VBG IN JJS CD NNS CC VBG JJ NNS ."
"Abdul Qayum Batizoi , police chief of Khost province , said several rockets were fired into the Khost region , but only one hit an inhabited area .",B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP , NN NN IN NNP NN , VBD JJ NNS VBD VBN IN DT NNP NN , CC RB CD VBD DT JJ NN ."
"French newswire AFP said an American military official confirmed the attack , adding the NATO compound was not damaged and no troops were injured .",B-gpe O B-org O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN NNP VBD DT JJ JJ NN VBD DT NN , VBG DT NNP NN VBD RB VBN CC DT NNS VBD VBN ."
The compound is manned by the U.S. military .,O O O O O O B-geo O O,DT NN VBZ VBN IN DT NNP NN .
"Earlier this week , suicide bombers targeted government buildings in Khost and the NATO base nearby , killing at least 15 people and wounding many others .",O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RBR DT NN , NN NNS JJ NN NNS IN NNP CC DT NNP NN RB , VBG IN JJS CD NNS CC VBG JJ NNS ."
"A Kabul-based defense analyst , Khalid Maftoon , told VOA the latest attacks are part of the wider Taliban offensive aimed at derailing Afghanistan 's presidential elections scheduled for August .",O O O O O B-per I-per O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O,"DT JJ NN NN , NNP NNP , VBD NNP DT JJS NNS VBP NN IN DT JJR NNP NN VBN IN VBG NNP POS JJ NNS VBN IN NNP ."
