An Iraqi court has sentenced former vice president Taha Yassin Ramadan to death for his role in the killing of 148 Shi'ites from the town of Dujail in the 1980s .,O B-gpe O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O,DT JJ NN VBZ VBN JJ NN NN NNP NNP NNP TO NN IN PRP$ NN IN DT NN IN CD NNS IN DT NN IN NNP IN DT NNS .
The High Court in Baghdad sentenced Ramadan to death by hanging Monday .,O B-org I-org O B-geo O B-per O O O O B-tim O,DT NNP NNP IN NNP VBD NNP TO NN IN VBG NNP .
He was vice president in Saddam Hussein 's ousted government .,O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O,PRP VBD NN NN IN NNP NNP POS JJ NN .
"Ramadan had been sentenced to life in prison in November , but an appeals court recommended that he receive the death penalty and referred the case back to the trial court for a final decision .",B-per O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD VBN VBN TO NN IN NN IN NNP , CC DT NNS NN VBD IN PRP VBP DT NN NN CC VBD DT NN RB TO DT NN NN IN DT JJ NN ."
Saddam and two other top former officials have already been hanged for their role in the Dujail killings .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,NNP CC CD JJ JJ JJ NNS VBP RB VBN VBN IN PRP$ NN IN DT NNP NNS .
United Nations officials and international human rights groups have appealed for Ramadan 's life to be spared .,B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNS CC JJ JJ NNS NNS VBP VBN IN NNP POS NN TO VB VBN .
