"Lebanese troops have pounded the few remaining compounds of militants inside a Palestinian refugee camp in northern Lebanon , as fighting entered its eighth week .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O O,"JJ NNS VBP VBN DT JJ VBG NNS IN NNS IN DT JJ NN NN IN JJ NNP , IN NN VBD PRP$ JJ NN ."
"Lebanese military officials say at least three soldiers were killed in Monday 's clashes , bringing the total number of troop deaths to 100 .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ JJ NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN IN NNP POS NNS , VBG DT JJ NN IN NN NNS TO CD ."
"In the latest fighting , troops unleashed artillery shells and exchanged machine gun fire with Fatah al-Islam militants .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O,"IN DT JJS NN , NNS VBD NN NNS CC VBD NN NN NN IN NNP NNP NNS ."
The militants responded by launching at least five Katyusha rockets that landed in areas outside of the Nahr al-Bared camp .,O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-org O O O,DT NNS VBD IN VBG IN JJS CD NNP NNS WDT VBD IN NNS IN IN DT NNP JJ NN .
"In recent days , the Lebanese military has increased efforts to get the remaining militants in the camp to surrender .",O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN JJ NNS , DT JJ NN VBZ VBN NNS TO VB DT VBG NNS IN DT NN TO VB ."
More than 170 people have been killed since the standoff began May 20 .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,JJR IN CD NNS VBP VBN VBN IN DT NN VBD NNP CD .
