Mahmoud Ahmadinejad Several Americans held hostage in Iran more than 25 years ago say they remember Iran 's President-elect Mahmoud Ahmadinejad as playing a key role in the seizure .,B-org I-org O B-gpe O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP JJ NNS VBD NN IN NNP JJR IN CD NNS RB VBP PRP VBP NNP POS JJ NNP NNP IN VBG DT JJ NN IN DT NN .
"One former hostage , Kevin Hermening , -- who was a Marine guard at the embassy - - recalled the man he believed to be Mr. Ahmadinejad asked him for the combination to the embassy 's safe .",O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O,"CD JJ NN , NNP NNP , : WP VBD DT NN NN IN DT NN : : VBD DT NN PRP VBD TO VB NNP NNP VBD PRP IN DT NN TO DT NN POS JJ ."
He denies taking part in storming of the American compound .,O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,PRP VBZ VBG NN IN VBG IN DT JJ NN .
"Last week , he won Iran 's runoff presidential election by a landslide .",O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN , PRP VBD NNP POS NN JJ NN IN DT NN ."
