The Saudi Interior Ministry said Tuesday the al-Qaida leader was killed along with four other men wanted for last week 's failed attempt to bomb a massive oil processing plant .,O B-org I-org I-org O B-tim O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP DT NNP NN VBD VBN IN IN CD JJ NNS VBN IN JJ NN POS JJ NN TO VB DT JJ NN NN NN .
Saudi officials say a sixth suspected militant was arrested in a separate raid Monday and will be interrogated .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP DT JJ JJ NN VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN NNP CC MD VB VBN .
