"Crude oil prices fell slightly Tuesday , after the U.S. government said it would consider making up a short-fall in crude oil production from Alaska .",O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"JJ NN NNS VBD RB NNP , IN DT NNP NN VBD PRP MD VB VBG RP DT NN IN JJ NN NN IN NNP ."
The Bloomberg financial news service says oil prices fell 41 cents to trade at $ 76.57 a barrel in New York Tuesday morning .,O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo B-tim I-tim O,DT NNP JJ NN NN VBZ NN NNS VBD CD NNS TO VB IN $ CD DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP NN .
"London prices also eased , hitting $ 76.70 a barrel .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNS RB VBD , VBG $ CD DT NN ."
"Monday , crude oil prices soared in New York and hit a record high in London when BP said it will shut down its Prudhoe Bay , Alaska operations .",B-tim O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-geo O B-org O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O,"NNP , JJ NN NNS VBD IN NNP NNP CC VBD DT NN NN IN NNP WRB NNP VBD PRP MD VB RP PRP$ NNP NNP , NNP NNS ."
"Experts say the shutdown cuts U.S. oil production by nearly eight percent , or 400,000 barrels a day .",O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP DT NN VBZ NNP NN NN IN RB CD NN , CC CD NNS DT NN ."
BP says it must replace 26 kilometers of corroded pipeline .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ PRP MD VB CD NNS IN JJ NN .
Officials with London-based BP say they do not know how long it will take to resume production at the largest oil field in the United States .,O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,NNS IN JJ NNP VBP PRP VBP RB VB WRB JJ PRP MD VB TO VB NN IN DT JJS NN NN IN DT NNP NNPS .
