"A new survey indicates public opinion in the United States and Europe supports free trade , but most people are ambivalent about whether they will benefit .",O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBZ JJ NN IN DT NNP NNPS CC NNP VBZ JJ NN , CC JJS NNS VBP JJ IN IN PRP MD VB ."
"A survey published Tuesday by the German Marshall Fund , a transatlantic think tank , shows most respondents think increased global trade benefits big companies and rapidly developing countries like China and India .",O O O B-tim O O B-gpe B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,"DT NN VBN NNP IN DT JJ NNP NNP , DT JJ NN NN , VBZ JJS NNS VBP VBN JJ NN NNS JJ NNS CC RB VBG NNS IN NNP CC NNP ."
Fewer than half of those surveyed think they will personally benefit .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJR IN NN IN DT VBN VBP PRP MD RB VB .
"The findings come from interviews with thousands of people in the United States and five European countries ( France , Germany , Italy , Poland and Britain ) .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O,"DT NNS VBP IN NNS IN NNS IN NNS IN DT NNP NNPS CC CD JJ NNS LRB NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP CC NNP RRB ."
The data was issued before next week 's gathering of nearly 150 members of the World Trade Organization to discuss a global trade pact that was intended to slash trade barriers and boost the global economy .,O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBD VBN IN JJ NN POS NN IN RB CD NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP TO VB DT JJ NN NN WDT VBD VBN TO VB NN NNS CC VB DT JJ NN .
Talks have stalled amid bickering over efforts to cut agricultural subsidies in wealthy nations .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP VBN IN VBG IN NNS TO VB JJ NNS IN JJ NNS .
