"Formerly administered as part of the British Crown Colony of Mauritius , the British Indian Ocean Territory ( BIOT ) was established as an overseas territory of the UK in 1965 .",O O O O O O B-gpe B-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-gpe B-geo I-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-tim O,"RB VBN IN NN IN DT JJ NNP NN IN NNP , DT JJ NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP RRB VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP IN CD ."
A number of the islands of the territory were later transferred to the Seychelles when it attained independence in 1976 .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O,DT NN IN DT NNS IN DT NN VBD RB VBN TO DT NNS WRB PRP VBD NN IN CD .
"Subsequently , BIOT has consisted only of the six main island groups comprising the Chagos Archipelago .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"RB , NNP VBZ VBN RB IN DT CD JJ NN NNS VBG DT NNP NNP ."
"The largest and most southerly of the islands , Diego Garcia , contains a joint UK-US naval support facility .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJS CC RBS RB IN DT NNS , NNP NNP , VBZ DT JJ JJ JJ NN NN ."
All of the remaining islands are uninhabited .,O O O O O O O O,DT IN DT VBG NNS VBP JJ .
"Between 1967 and 1973 , former agricultural workers , earlier residents in the islands , were relocated primarily to Mauritius , but also to the Seychelles .",B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O,"IN CD CC CD , JJ JJ NNS , JJR NNS IN DT NNS , VBD VBN RB TO NNP , CC RB TO DT NNS ."
"Negotiations between 1971 and 1982 resulted in the establishment of a trust fund by the British Government as compensation for the displaced islanders , known as Chagossians .",O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-org O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN CD CC CD VBD IN DT NN IN DT NN NN IN DT JJ NN IN NN IN DT JJ NNS , VBN IN NNPS ."
"Beginning in 1998 , the islanders pursued a series of lawsuits against the British Government seeking further compensation and the right to return to the territory .",O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NN IN CD , DT NNS VBD DT NN IN NNS IN DT JJ NN VBG JJ NN CC DT NN TO VB TO DT NN ."
"In 2006 and 2007 , British court rulings invalidated the immigration policies contained in the 2004 BIOT Constitution Order that had excluded the islanders from the archipelago , but upheld the special military status of Diego Garcia .",O B-tim I-tim I-tim O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-tim B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"IN CD CC CD , JJ NN NNS VBD DT NN NNS VBN IN DT CD NNP NNP NNP WDT VBD VBN DT NNS IN DT NN , CC VBD DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP NNP ."
"In 2008 , the House of Lords , as the final court of appeal in the UK , ruled in favor of the British Government by overturning the lower court rulings and finding no right of return for the Chagossians .",O B-tim O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN CD , DT NNP IN NNPS , IN DT JJ NN IN NN IN DT NNP , VBD IN NN IN DT JJ NN IN VBG DT JJR NN NNS CC VBG DT NN IN NN IN DT NNPS ."
