"An aide to former Pakistani Prime Minister Benazir Bhutto says she has decided not to attend a conference of parties opposed to Pakistan 's president , Pervez Musharraf .",O O O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-org I-org O,"DT NN TO JJ JJ JJ NN NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ VBN RB TO VB DT NN IN NNS VBN TO NNP POS NN , NNP NNP ."
The aide says representatives from the Pakistan People 's Party would instead attend the conference later this month in London .,O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O,DT NN VBZ NNS IN DT NNP NNP POS NNP MD RB VB DT NN RB DT NN IN NNP .
President Pervez Musharraf has said he will not allow either exiled former prime minister to run for office in elections expected by next January .,B-per B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP MD RB VB CC VBN JJ JJ NN TO VB IN NN IN NNS VBN IN JJ NNP .
"General Musharraf has said Ms. Bhutto would be put on trial for alleged corruption if she returns to Pakistan , and Mr. Sharif would be put on a plane back to Saudi Arabia .",B-per B-org O O B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNP NNP MD VB VBN IN NN IN JJ NN IN PRP VBZ TO NNP , CC NNP NNP MD VB VBN IN DT NN RB TO NNP NNP ."
General Musharraf ousted him in a bloodless coup in 1999 .,B-per B-org O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP NNP VBD PRP IN DT JJ NN IN CD .
"After the coup , Mr. Sharif and Ms. Bhutto joined what they call an Alliance for the Restoration of Democracy .",O O O O B-per I-per O B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN , NNP NNP CC NNP NNP VBD WP PRP VBP DT NNP IN DT NN IN NN ."
