"Hundreds of demonstrators have marched through the Japanese capital , Tokyo , to protest the war in Iraq .",O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNS IN NNS VBP VBN IN DT JJ NN , NNP , TO VB DT NN IN NNP ."
Activists chanted calls for an end to the Iraq war and carried banners critical of U.S. President George W. Bush .,O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-org B-per I-per I-per I-per O,NNS VBD NNS IN DT NN TO DT NNP NN CC VBD NNS JJ IN NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP .
"Organizers say about two thousand people took the streets Sunday , ahead of the fourth anniversary Tuesday of the U.S. invasion of Iraq .",O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O B-geo O,"NNS VBP IN CD CD NNS VBD DT NNS NNP , RB IN DT JJ NN NNP IN DT NNP NN IN NNP ."
Japan deployed 600 troops to Iraq on a reconstruction mission - the military 's first overseas mission in a war zone since World War II .,B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-eve O,NNP VBD CD NNS TO NNP IN DT NN NN IN DT NN POS JJ JJ NN IN DT NN NN IN NNP NNP NNP .
Japan withdrew the troops last year but continues to help the war effort by flying supplies and personnel to Iraq .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP VBD DT NNS JJ NN CC VBZ TO VB DT NN NN IN VBG NNS CC NNS TO NNP .
