"Iranian President Mahmoud Ahmadinejad has lashed out at the United States , accusing Washington of trying to "" bully "" Iran into giving up its nuclear program .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN RP IN DT NNP NNPS , VBG NNP IN VBG TO RQU RB LQU NNP IN VBG RP PRP$ JJ NN ."
"In the southern Iranian city of Bushehr Wednesday , President Ahmadinejad said his country will resist until its right to develop nuclear energy is "" fully realized . """,O O O B-gpe O O B-geo B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP NNP , NNP NNP VBD PRP$ NN MD VB IN PRP$ NN TO VB JJ NN VBZ LQU RB VBN . LQU"
"Hours earlier , President Bush in his State of the Union address described Iran as a nation "" held hostage by a small clerical elite that is isolating and repressing its people . """,O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS RB , NNP NNP IN PRP$ NN IN DT NNP NN VBD NNP IN DT NN LQU VBN NN IN DT JJ JJ NN WDT VBZ VBG CC VBG PRP$ NNS . LQU"
He accused the Iranian government of sponsoring terrorists in the Palestinian territories and Lebanon - and said that must come to an end .,O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT JJ NN IN VBG NNS IN DT JJ NNS CC NNP : CC VBD DT MD VB IN DT NN .
"Mr. Ahmadinejad said the United States is "" tainted with the blood of nations "" from wars and oppression .",B-per I-per O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD DT NNP NNPS VBZ LQU VBN IN DT NN IN NNS LQU IN NNS CC NN .
"President Bush said the Iranian government is defying the world with its nuclear ambitions , and that other nations must not permit Tehran to develop nuclear weapons .",B-per I-per O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN VBZ VBG DT NN IN PRP$ JJ NNS , CC IN JJ NNS MD RB VB NNP TO VB JJ NNS ."
