Asian stocks have opened with mixed results in early trading - as investors try to recover from last week 's big sell-off in world markets .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN IN JJ NNS IN JJ NN IN IN NNS VBP TO VB IN JJ NN POS JJ NN IN NN NNS .
Tokyo 's Nikkei Index was slightly down and Sydney 's ASX was slightly higher Wednesday .,B-geo O O O O O O O B-per O B-org O O O B-tim O,NNP POS NNP NNP VBD RB RB CC NNP POS NNP VBD RB JJR NNP .
Hong Kong 's Heng Seng index finished the day Tuesday with a two-percent gain .,B-geo I-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-tim O O O O O,NNP NNP POS NNP NNP NN VBD DT NN NNP IN DT JJ NN .
The major U.S. and European indexes also finished the day with large gains .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNP CC JJ NNS RB VBD DT NN IN JJ NNS .
U.S. Treasury Secretary Henry Paulson is expected to visit China later today after stops in Japan and South Korea .,B-org I-org B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-geo B-tim I-tim O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB NNP RB NN IN NNS IN NNP CC NNP NNP .
"During his trip he said he feels very comfortable with the global economy , describing it as having very low inflation and high levels of liquidity .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN PRP$ NN PRP VBD PRP VBZ RB JJ IN DT JJ NN , VBG PRP IN VBG RB JJ NN CC JJ NNS IN NN ."
But some U.S. analysts say they believe a struggling housing market and stronger Japanese yen could prompt stock prices to drop further .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O,CC DT NNP NNS VBP PRP VBP DT VBG NN NN CC JJR JJ NNS MD VB NN NNS TO VB RB .
