The World Health Organization has confirmed the first human case of bird flu in Laos .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ JJ NN IN NN NN IN NNP .
"In a joint statement issued Tuesday , WHO and Laotian officials say a 15-year-old girl who fell ill earlier this month is infected with the bird flu virus .",O O O O O B-tim O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN VBN NNP , NNP CC JJ NNS VBP DT JJ NN WP VBD RB RBR DT NN VBZ VBN IN DT NN NN NN ."
"Officials say the girl was hospitalized in Vientiane and later transferred to Thailand , where she is in stable condition .",O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP DT NN VBD VBN IN NNP CC RB VBN TO VB , WRB PRP VBZ IN JJ NN ."
WHO officials have not confirmed whether the virus is the often-fatal H5N1 strain of bird flu .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBP RB VBN IN DT NN VBZ DT JJ NNP NN IN NN NN .
Bird flu broke out among poultry in the girl 's village near the capital two weeks ago .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,NN NN VBD RP IN NN IN DT NN POS NN IN DT NN CD NNS RB .
The disease first appeared in Laos in 2004 .,O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O,DT NN RB VBD IN NNP IN CD .
"It is known to have killed about 170 people worldwide since 2003 , mostly in Asia .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O,"PRP VBZ VBN TO VB VBN IN CD NNS JJ IN CD , RB IN NNP ."
