Sarah Jessica Parker says she 's okay with Maxim Magazine naming her the Unsexiest Woman Alive .,B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-org I-org O O O B-org I-org I-org O,NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ JJ IN NNP NNP VBG PRP$ DT NNP NNP NNP .
"Speaking to Britain 's Sunday Express , the Sex In The City actress said "" I believe in the old 'sticks and stones ' philosophy , so frankly their words do n't come close to hurting . """,O O B-geo O B-tim I-tim O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"VBG TO NNP POS NNP NNP , DT NN IN DT NNP NN VBD LQU PRP VBP IN DT JJ NNS CC NNS POS NN , RB RB PRP$ NNS VBP RB VB RB TO VBG . LQU"
"Said Parker , who topped Amy Winehouse , Sandra Oh , Madonna , and Britney Spears for the dubious title , "" I admit , I do n't think I've ever conformed to the Hollywood ideal of beauty , whatever that is .",B-per I-per O O O B-per I-per O B-per I-per O B-per O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP , WP VBD NNP NNP , NNP NNP , NNP , CC NNP NNPS IN DT JJ NN , LQU PRP VBP , PRP VBP RB VB NNP RB VBD TO DT NNP NN IN NN , WDT DT VBZ ."
"As I said , one day I 'll wake up really fat and that 'll be that .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN PRP VBD , CD NN PRP MD VBP RP RB JJ CC DT MD VB DT ."
I do n't really mind and it 's really not important to me to be skinny .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBP RB RB VB CC PRP VBZ RB RB JJ TO PRP TO VB JJ .
And it does n't bother me in the least if people do n't think I 'm sexy .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC PRP VBZ RB VB PRP IN DT JJS IN NNS VBP RB VB PRP VBP JJ .
"I do n't think I am , either . """,O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBP RB VB PRP VBP , CC . LQU"
