The U.S. military in Iraq says it killed 16 terrorists and detained 10 suspects while conducting operations in Baghdad and the town of Haditha early Tuesday .,O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O B-tim O,DT NNP NN IN NNP VBZ PRP VBD CD NNS CC VBD CD NNS IN VBG NNS IN NNP CC DT NN IN NNP RB NNP .
The military also said Iraqi and U.S. troops are taking a balanced approach in attacking Shi'ite and Sunni Arab militant groups .,O O O O B-gpe O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O,DT NN RB VBD JJ CC NNP NNS VBP VBG DT JJ NN IN VBG NNP CC NNP NNP JJ NNS .
"The military said that in the past 45 days , 52 raids targeted the Mahdi Army of radical Shi'ite cleric Moqtada al-Sadr and 42 focused on Sunni insurgents .",O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim I-tim O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-per O O,"DT NN VBD IN IN DT JJ CD NNS , CD NNS VBD DT NNP NNP IN JJ NNP NN NNP NNP CC CD VBD IN NNP NNS ."
"In the capital Tuesday , Iraqi officials say two car bombs killed at least three people .",O O O B-tim O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN NNP , JJ NNS VBP CD NN NNS VBD IN JJS CD NNS ."
The U.S. military said it is also investigating what appeared to be the crash of a civilian aircraft in the capital .,O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBD PRP VBZ RB VBG WP VBD TO VB DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN .
The U.S. said three more U.S. troops were killed in separate incidents .,O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,DT NNP VBD CD JJR NNP NNS VBD VBN IN JJ NNS .
"In the northern city of Mosul , five Iraqi policemen were killed and three others wounded in gunbattles with insurgents .",O O O O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , CD JJ NNS VBD VBN CC CD NNS VBN IN NNS IN NNS ."
