The main shareholder of Russia 's giant oil firm Yukos is reported to have filed suit for compensation from the upcoming forced sale of the company 's top production unit .,O O O O B-geo O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN IN NNP POS JJ NN NN NNP VBZ VBN TO VB VBN NN IN NN IN DT JJ JJ NN IN DT NN POS JJ NN NN .
"The managing director , Tim Osborne , of the holding company Menatep told Russia 's Interfax news agency his group will take every possible step to defend its stake in the Yuganskneftegaz production unit .",O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-per O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,"DT NN NN , NNP NNP , IN DT VBG NN NNP VBD NNP POS NNP NN NN PRP$ NN MD VB DT JJ NN TO VB PRP$ NN IN DT NNP NN NN ."
This followed Friday 's announcement by Russian authorities that the unit will be sold next month in a court-ordered auction to collect billions of dollars in back taxes from Yukos .,O O B-tim O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,DT VBD NNP POS NN IN JJ NNS IN DT NN MD VB VBN JJ NN IN DT JJ NN TO VB NNS IN NNS IN JJ NNS IN NNP .
Officials have set an $ 8.6 billion starting price .,O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP VBN DT $ CD CD VBG NN .
An independent investment bank has valued the unit at $ 14 billion to $ 17 billion .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN NN VBZ VBN DT NN IN $ CD CD TO $ CD CD .
Yukos head Steven Theede has called the sale a government-organized theft to settle a political score .,B-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN DT JJ NN TO VB DT JJ NN .
The Kremlin described the moves against Yukos and its subsidiaries as part of a crackdown on corporate crime .,O B-org O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP VBD DT NNS IN NNP CC PRP$ NNS IN NN IN DT NN IN JJ NN .
