A detainee in an outdoor solitary confinement cell talks with a military policeman at the Abu Ghraib prison,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NN NN NNS IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP NN
"The U.S. Army has cleared four top officers , including a former top U.S. commander in Iraq , of any wrongdoing in the Abu Ghraib prisoner abuse scandal .",O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O,"DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN CD JJ NNS , VBG DT JJ JJ NNP NN IN NNP , IN DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NN NN NN ."
Defense officials say the Army 's inspector general ultimately decided there was no basis for bringing charges against Lieutenant General Ricardo Sanchez and two generals and a colonel under his command .,O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,NN NNS VBP DT NNP POS NN NN RB VBD EX VBD DT NN IN VBG NNS IN NNP NNP NNP NNP CC CD NNS CC DT NN IN PRP$ NN .
"The officials said that another military official , Army Reserve Brigadier General Janis Karpinski , has been relieved of her command and given a written reprimand .",O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS VBD IN DT JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP , VBZ VBN VBN IN PRP$ NN CC VBN DT JJ NN ."
She oversaw the military police at the center of the prison scandal .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN DT NN NN .
The findings are to be released in an upcoming report .,O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP TO VB VBN IN DT JJ NN .
The Abu Ghraib prison scandal sparked outrage and condemnation in the United States and around the world after pictures emerged of American soldiers physically abusing and humiliating Iraqi prisoners .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT NNP NNP NN NN VBD NN CC NN IN DT NNP NNPS CC IN DT NN IN NNS VBD IN JJ NNS RB VBG CC VBG JJ NNS .
