A U.S. court has dismissed a lawsuit against a Canadian energy company accused of a role in human rights violations in southern Sudan .,O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT NNP NN VBZ VBN DT NN IN DT JJ NN NN VBN IN DT NN IN JJ NNS NNS IN JJ NNP .
"The judge in New York said there was no evidence to justify the claims made against Talisman Energy , which operated indirectly in Sudan from 1998 to 2003 .",O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O B-geo B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,"DT NN IN NNP NNP VBD EX VBD DT NN TO VB DT NNS VBN IN NNP NNP , WDT VBD RB IN NNP IN CD TO CD ."
The Presbyterian Church of Sudan filed the civil claim on behalf of villagers who were allegedly killed and injured to allow construction of oil fields in Sudan .,O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNP NNP IN NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN NN IN NNS WP VBD RB VBN CC VBN TO VB NN IN NN NNS IN NNP .
Sudan 's government also was named in the suit .,B-org O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NN RB VBD VBN IN DT NN .
The judge ruled that Sudan was in default after it failed to send attorneys to challenge the claims .,O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD IN NNP VBD IN NN IN PRP VBD TO VB NNS TO VB DT NNS .
"Canada 's government had criticized the lawsuit , saying the U.S. court had no authority in the matter .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NN VBD VBN DT NN , VBG DT NNP NN VBD DT NN IN DT NN ."
Southern Sudan is struggling to rebuild following a 2005 peace deal that ended two decades of civil war .,B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBG TO VB VBG DT CD NN NN WDT VBD CD NNS IN JJ NN .
