A former aide to Brazilian Finance Minister Antonio Palocci has accused him of accepting illegal contributions from contractors when Mr. Palocci was a city mayor several years ago .,O O O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-per B-org O O O O B-tim O O O,DT JJ NN TO JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP IN VBG JJ NNS IN NNS WRB NNP NNP VBD DT NN NN JJ NNS RB .
"Rogerio Buratti told prosecutors Friday that Mr. Palocci received about $ 21,000 a month from contractors handling trash collection in Ribeirao Preto .",B-per I-per O O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP NNP VBD NNS NNP IN NNP NNP VBD IN $ CD DT NN IN NNS VBG NN NN IN NNP NNP .
"Mr. Buratti said he suspected the money went to the Workers Party and its former treasurer , Delubio Soares .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O B-per I-per O,"NNP NNP VBD PRP VBD DT NN VBD TO DT NNP NNP CC PRP$ JJ NN , NNP NNPS ."
"At the time , the party did not control the presidency .",O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN , DT NN VBD RB VB DT NN ."
The allegations come two days after Mr. Buratti was arrested on money laundering and fraud charges in a separate matter .,O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP CD NNS IN NNP NNP VBD VBN IN NN NN CC NN NNS IN DT JJ NN .
"Mr. Palocci , for his part , "" vehemently denies "" Mr. Buratti 's allegations , which rocked local financial markets .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP , IN PRP$ NN , LQU RB VBZ LQU NNP NNP POS NNS , WDT VBD JJ JJ NNS ."
President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva 's administration faces accusations it paid legislators to support the government in Congress .,B-per I-per I-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP POS NN VBZ NNS PRP VBD NNS TO VB DT NN IN NNP .
"The party has apologized for the crisis , blaming it on rogue aides .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ VBN IN DT NN , VBG PRP IN NN NNS ."
