Lebanese security officials say Israeli troops firing across the border have killed one Lebanese man and wounded another .,B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,JJ NN NNS VBP JJ NNS VBG IN DT NN VBP VBN CD JJ NN CC VBD DT .
"Officials say the shooting occurred near the border village of Ghajar , which is near a suspected smuggling route .",O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP DT NN VBD IN DT NN NN IN NNP , WDT VBZ IN DT JJ NN NN ."
"Israeli officials claimed gunmen had first fired on the Israeli soldiers , who then returned fire .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBD NNS VBD JJ VBN IN DT JJ NNS , WP RB VBD NN ."
There were no Israeli casualties .,O O O B-gpe O O,EX VBD DT JJ NNS .
U.N. spokeswoman Yasmina Bouziane confirmed the incident .,B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O,NNP NN NNP NNP VBD DT NN .
She says the U.N. Interim Force in Lebanon took one of the victims to a hospital in the town of Marjayoun where he was pronounced dead .,O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,PRP VBZ DT NNP NNP NNP IN NNP VBD CD IN DT NNS TO DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP WRB PRP VBD VBN JJ .
"She says they are investigating allegations that the men were drug smugglers , as well as other details of the incident .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBZ PRP VBP VBG NNS IN DT NNS VBD NN NNS , RB RB IN JJ NNS IN DT NN ."
She is urging both sides to show maximum restraint .,O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ VBG DT NNS TO VB JJ NN .
Such cross-border violence has been rare following the end of Israel 's war with Hezbollah militants in 2006 .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-org I-org O B-tim O,JJ JJ NN VBZ VBN JJ VBG DT NN IN NNP POS NN IN NNP NNS IN CD .
