Brazilian President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva has announced plans to revive the country 's long-stalled nuclear program .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNS TO VB DT NN POS JJ JJ NN .
President da Silva told reporters in Sao Paulo state Tuesday that funds will be allocated for completion of another nuclear power plant and construction of a nuclear-powered submarine .,B-per I-per I-per O O O B-geo I-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP VBD NNS IN NNP NNP NN NNP IN NNS MD VB VBN IN NN IN DT JJ NN NN CC NN IN DT JJ NN .
Mr. da Silva also said Brazil could become one of the few countries in the world to control the entire uranium enrichment cycle .,B-per I-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP RB VBD NNP MD VB CD IN DT JJ NNS IN DT NN TO VB DT JJ NN NN NN .
"In June , the Brazilian energy council approved plans to complete the country 's third nuclear power plant , the Angra Three .",O B-tim O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-art I-art O,"IN NNP , DT JJ NN NN VBD NNS TO VB DT NN POS JJ JJ NN NN , DT NNP NNP ."
Construction has been stalled since the 1980s .,O O O O O O B-tim O,NN VBZ VBN VBN IN DT NNS .
Brazil has one of the world 's largest uranium reserves and is a signatory to the Nuclear Non-Proliferation Treaty .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,NNP VBZ CD IN DT NN POS JJS NN NNS CC VBZ DT NN TO DT NNP NNP NNP .
