"New anti-U.S. protests are reported in several countries , sparked by allegations U.S. military interrogators desecrated the Koran .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O,"JJ JJ NNS VBP VBN IN JJ NNS , VBN IN NNS NNP JJ NNS VBD DT NNP ."
"Thousands of Somalis led by Muslim clerics rallied in Mogadishu , chanting anti-American slogans and Islamic prayers .",O O B-gpe O O B-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN NNS VBN IN NNP NNS VBD IN NNP , VBG JJ NNS CC JJ NNS ."
"In Calcutta , India , some 300 Muslims burned and urinated on a U.S. flag , accusing Americans of desecrating the Koran .",O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo O,"IN NNP , NNP , DT CD NNS VBN CC VBN IN DT NNP NN , VBG NNS IN VBG DT NNP ."
"Muslim demonstrators burn American flags outside the U.S. Embassy in London And in London , some 100 people demonstrated outside the U.S. embassy and chanted anti-American slogans .",B-org O O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"NNP NNS VBP JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP CC IN NNP , DT CD NNS VBD IN DT NNP NN CC VBD JJ NNS ."
"The protests are continuing even though Newsweek magazine retracted its report that alleged interrogators flushed a Koran down a toilet at the U.S. military prison in Guantanamo Bay , Cuba .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O,"DT NNS VBP VBG RB IN NNP NN VBD PRP$ NN IN JJ NNS VBD DT NNP IN DT NN IN DT NNP JJ NN IN NNP NNP , NNP ."
The International Red Cross says the complaints stopped in 2003 after several discussions with defense officials .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT NNS VBD IN CD IN JJ NNS IN NN NNS .
