Morocco has appointed 50 women to be state religious preachers in an effort to promote moderate Islam in a country struggling with radical fundamentalism .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN CD NNS TO VB NN JJ NNS IN DT NN TO VB JJ NN IN DT NN VBG IN JJ NN .
"The women will teach Islam and its practice but will not be able to lead prayers in mosques , an activity reserved for men .",O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS MD VB NNP CC PRP$ NN CC MD RB VB JJ TO VB NNS IN NNS , DT NN VBN IN NNS ."
The government says it hopes the new religious teachers will help balance the influence of radical clerics who have been drawing support from the residents of poor slums .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ PRP VBZ DT JJ JJ NNS MD VB VB DT NN IN JJ NNS WP VBP VBN VBG NN IN DT NNS IN JJ NNS .
"Moroccan authorities have been working to curb Islamic extremism since 2003 , when a suicide bombing ripped through Casablanca , killing at least 41 people .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP VBN VBG TO VB JJ NN IN CD , WRB DT NN VBG VBN IN NNP , VBG IN JJS CD NNS ."
"King Mohammed has been promoting moderate Islam in the North African kingdom , which has been praised by the United States for its anti-terrorism efforts .",B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBN VBG JJ NN IN DT JJ JJ NN , WDT VBZ VBN VBN IN DT NNP NNPS IN PRP$ JJ NNS ."
