"The Dutch United Provinces declared their independence from Spain in 1579 ; during the 17th century , they became a leading seafaring and commercial power , with settlements and colonies around the world .",O B-gpe B-org I-org O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNP NNPS VBD PRP$ NN IN NNP IN CD ; IN DT JJ NN , PRP VBD DT JJ NN CC JJ NN , IN NNS CC NNS IN DT NN ."
"After a 20-year French occupation , a Kingdom of the Netherlands was formed in 1815 .",O O O B-gpe O O O B-org O O B-geo O O O B-tim O,"IN DT JJ JJ NN , DT NNP IN DT NNP VBD VBN IN CD ."
In 1830 Belgium seceded and formed a separate kingdom .,O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O,IN CD NNP VBD CC VBD DT JJ NN .
"The Netherlands remained neutral in World War I , but suffered invasion and occupation by Germany in World War II .",O B-geo O O O B-eve I-eve I-eve O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-eve O,"DT NNP VBD JJ IN NNP NNP NNP , CC VBD NN CC NN IN NNP IN NNP NNP NNP ."
"A modern , industrialized nation , the Netherlands is also a large exporter of agricultural products .",O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ , JJ NN , DT NNP VBZ RB DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS ."
"The country was a founding member of NATO and the EEC ( now the EU ) , and participated in the introduction of the euro in 1999 .",O O O O O O O B-org O O B-org O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"DT NN VBD DT JJ NN IN NNP CC DT NNP LRB RB DT NNP RRB , CC VBD IN DT NN IN DT NN IN CD ."
"In October 2010 , the former Netherlands Antilles was dissolved and the three smallest islands - Bonaire , Sint Eustatius , and Saba - became special municipalities in the Netherlands administrative structure .",O B-tim I-tim O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O,"IN NNP CD , DT JJ NNP NNP VBD VBN CC DT CD JJS NNS IN NNP , NNP NNP , CC NNP : VBD JJ NNS IN DT NNP JJ NN ."
The larger islands of Sint Maarten and Curacao joined the Netherlands and Aruba as constituent countries forming the Kingdom of the Netherlands .,O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O B-org O O B-geo O,DT JJR NNS IN NNP NNP CC NNP VBD DT NNP CC NNP IN JJ NNS VBG DT NNP IN DT NNP .
