Mexico 's Zapatista rebels emerged from their southern jungle hideouts Sunday to begin what they say will be a six-month nationwide tour .,B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,NNP POS NNP NNS VBD IN PRP$ JJ NN VBZ NNP TO VB WP PRP VBP MD VB DT JJ JJ NN .
"The rebels , who are traveling unarmed , hope to build support for indigenous people 's rights and the poor ahead of Mexico 's presidential election in July .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim O,"DT NNS , WP VBP VBG JJ , NN TO VB NN IN JJ NNS POS NNS CC DT NN RB IN NNP POS JJ NN IN NNP ."
"The tour was kicking off in the city of San Cristobal de las Casas in Chiapas state , where rebel leader Subcomandante Marcos was due to speak .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O,"DT NN VBD VBG RP IN DT NN IN NNP NNP IN NNP NNP IN NNP NN , WRB JJ NN NNP NNP VBD JJ TO VB ."
The mysterious ski mask-wearing leader plans to meet with other leftist organizations throughout Mexico in an effort to broaden the Zapatistas ' appeal .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-org O O O,DT JJ NN JJ NN VBZ TO VB IN JJ JJ NNS IN NNP IN DT NN TO VB DT NNP POS NN .
"The rebel leader is asking that he now be called "" Delegate Zero . """,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBZ VBG IN PRP RB VB VBN LQU NNP NNP . LQU
