"In a statement released Wednesday , the military said Neftaly Platero has also been charged with one count of attempted murder .",O O O O B-tim O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN VBN NNP , DT NN VBD NNP NNP VBZ RB VBN VBN IN CD NN IN JJ NN ."
"The military says the shootings were premeditated , and that it is continuing to investigate the incident .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ VBZ DT NNS VBD VBN , CC IN PRP VBZ VBG TO VB DT NN ."
Platero will be tried in a military court .,B-per O O O O O O O O,NNP MD VB VBN IN DT JJ NN .
