"The Indonesian government says it will begin withdrawing troops from Aceh province in September , following a tentative peace agreement that would end the region 's nearly 30-year separatist conflict .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBZ PRP MD VB VBG NNS IN NNP NN IN NNP , VBG DT JJ NN NN WDT MD VB DT NN POS RB JJ JJ NN ."
"Jakarta 's announcement came Wednesday , not long after a spokesman for the rebel Free Aceh Movement said at least 10 people have been killed in fighting since the peace agreement on Sunday .",B-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"NNP POS NN VBD NNP , RB RB IN DT NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD IN JJS CD NNS VBP VBN VBN IN VBG IN DT NN NN IN NNP ."
"The reported death toll includes five guerrillas , three soldiers and two civilians .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT VBN NN NN VBZ CD NNS , CD NNS CC CD NNS ."
An Indonesian military spokesman blames the rebels for the continued violence .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN NN VBZ DT NNS IN DT JJ NN .
"After peace talks in Helsinki , Finland , the government and rebel negotiators pledged to sign an accord August 15 to end the conflict that has killed tens of thousands of people , mostly civilians .",O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NN NNS IN NNP , NNP , DT NN CC NN NNS VBD TO VB DT NN NNP CD TO VB DT NN WDT VBZ VBN NNS IN NNS IN NNS , RB NNS ."
