Ivory Coast 's prime minister has resigned from his post as the head of the country 's main rebel group to concentrate on organizing the country 's long-delayed presidential elections .,B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP POS JJ NN VBZ VBN IN PRP$ NN IN DT NN IN DT NN POS JJ NN NN TO VB IN VBG DT NN POS JJ JJ NNS .
Guillaume Soro announced Friday he would no longer lead the New Forces rebels .,B-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O B-org I-org O O,NNP NNP VBD NNP PRP MD RB RB VB DT NNP NNP NNS .
"Mr. Soro became Ivory Coast 's prime minister in 2007 after the government of President Laurent Gbagbo signed a power- sharing deal with the rebels , ending a civil war that left the country divided between the rebel-controlled north and the government-controlled south .",B-per I-per O B-org I-org O O O O B-tim O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP POS JJ NN IN CD IN DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN NN IN DT NNS , VBG DT JJ NN WDT VBD DT NN VBN IN DT JJ NN CC DT JJ NN ."
The elections have been delayed since 2005 .,O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT NNS VBP VBN VBN IN CD .
The question of who is eligible to vote is at the heart of the country 's election dispute .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN WP VBZ JJ TO VB VBZ IN DT NN IN DT NN POS NN NN .
