Hundreds of Muslims in several Pakistani cities held street protests after prayers Friday to condemn Pope Benedict XVI for remarks that they consider anti-Islamic .,O O B-org O B-tim B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNPS IN JJ JJ NNS VBD NN NNS IN NNS NNP TO VB NNP NNP NNP IN NNS IN PRP VBP JJ .
An opposition alliance of religious-based parties called the Muttehida Majlis-e-Amal or United Action Front organized the protests .,O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-org I-org I-org O O O O,DT NN NN IN JJ NNS VBD DT NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NNS .
Prayer leaders also condemned the pope during Friday sermons around the country .,O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O,NNP NNS RB VBD DT NN IN NNP NNS IN DT NN .
Emotions have been high in the Muslim world since the Roman Catholic leader quoted a 14th century emperor who called some of the teachings of the Prophet Muhammad evil and inhumane .,O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O,NNS VBP VBN JJ IN DT NNP NN IN DT NNP NNP NN VBD DT JJ NN NN WP VBD DT IN DT NNS IN DT NNP NNP NN CC NN .
The pontiff spoke about the Prophet last week to scholars in Germany .,O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-geo O,DT NN VBD IN DT NNP JJ NN TO NNS IN NNP .
"Since then , he has acknowledged that his remarks were open to misinterpretation and he has apologized for them .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN RB , PRP VBZ VBN IN PRP$ NNS VBD JJ TO NN CC PRP VBZ VBN IN PRP ."
He insists that he did not intend to endorse a negative view of Islam and that the comments did not reflect his personal opinions .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ IN PRP VBD RB VB TO VB DT JJ NN IN NNP CC IN DT NNS VBD RB VB PRP$ JJ NNS .
