Malawi anti-corruption officials say they are probing allegations that former President Bakili Muluzi illegally pocketed millions of dollars during his time in office .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NN NNS VBP PRP VBP VBG NNS IN JJ NNP NNP NNP RB VBD NNS IN NNS IN PRP$ NN IN NN .
"A top anti-corruption official said Tuesday the investigation is focusing on transactions Mr. Muluzi had with Taiwan , Libya , Morocco , Rwanda and at least one unnamed foreign organization .",O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-per I-per O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN NN VBD NNP DT NN VBZ VBG IN NNS NNP NNP VBD IN NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP CC IN JJS CD JJ JJ NN ."
The official said his agency has summoned the former president for questioning on October 24 .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT NN VBD PRP$ NN VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN VBG IN NNP CD .
Mr. Muluzi was president from 1994 until last year .,B-per I-per O O O B-tim I-tim O O O,NNP NNP VBD NN IN CD IN JJ NN .
Current President Bingu Wa Mutharika has made fighting corruption a major focus of his administration .,O B-per B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN VBG NN DT JJ NN IN PRP$ NN .
Prosecutors have begun probes against former officials who served under Mr. Muluzi .,O O O O O O O O O O B-per B-geo O,NNS VBP VBN NNS IN JJ NNS WP VBD IN NNP NNP .
"The investigations have angered many of the former president 's allies , who have launched attempts to impeach Mr. Mutharika .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per B-geo O,"DT NNS VBP VBN NN IN DT JJ NN POS NNS , WP VBP VBN NNS TO VB NNP NNP ."
