Hundreds of opposition supporters and activists cheered Saturday as Pakistani opposition leader Javed Hashmi was released from prison .,O O O O O O O B-tim O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O,NNS IN NN NNS CC NNS VBD NNP IN JJ NN NN NNP NNP VBD VBN IN NN .
Hashmi is the president of the Pakistan Muslim League of former Prime Minister Nawaz Sharif 's .,B-per O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O,NNP VBZ DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP IN JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP POS .
He was jailed four years ago after criticizing the country 's military .,O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD VBN CD NNS RB IN VBG DT NN POS JJ .
"Upon his release , Hashmi told reporters that his fight was for the restoration of democracy .",O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN PRP$ NN , NNP VBD NNS IN PRP$ NN VBD IN DT NN IN NN ."
The Pakistan Supreme Court ruled Friday that he be released on bail pending the appeal of his conviction .,O B-org I-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP IN PRP VB VBN IN NN VBG DT NN IN PRP$ NN .
"The Supreme Court ruling was made by Chief Justice Iftikhar Mohammed Chaudhry , who recently won a highly publicized court victory overturning his own suspension by General Musharraf .",O B-org I-org O O O O B-per I-per B-org B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O,"DT NNP NNP NN VBD VBN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP , WP RB VBD DT RB VBN NN NN VBG PRP$ JJ NN IN NNP NNP ."
Hashmi was sentenced to 23 years in prison after being convicted on treason charges for circulating an unsigned letter criticizing Pakistan 's army .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O,NNP VBD VBN TO CD NNS IN NN IN VBG VBN IN NN NNS IN VBG DT JJ NN VBG NNP POS NN .
