"Friday 's explosion rocked a crowded bazaar in Khyber , home to a major supply route for NATO troops in neighboring Afghanistan .",B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-org O O O B-geo O,"NNP POS NN VBD DT JJ NN IN NNP , NN TO DT JJ NN NN IN NNP NNS IN JJ NNP ."
Authorities say at least 14 people were wounded when the bomb exploded near a shop .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN WRB DT NN VBD IN DT NN .
Pakistani tribal areas bordering Afghanistan are a known sanctuary for Taliban and al-Qaida-linked militants .,B-gpe O O O B-geo O O O O O B-org O O O O,JJ JJ NNS VBG NNP VBP DT VBN NN IN NNP CC JJ NNS .
"Security in the Khyber region is considered a top priority for Washington , since it is part of NATO 's supply route into Afghanistan .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-org O O O O B-geo O,"NN IN DT NNP NN VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN NNP , IN PRP VBZ NN IN NNP POS NN NN IN NNP ."
