"Israel 's justice minister says he has decided to resign , clearing the way for him to stand trial on charges of sexually harassing a teenage female soldier .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NN NN VBZ PRP VBZ VBN TO VB , VBG DT NN IN PRP TO VB NN IN NNS IN RB VBG DT NN NN NN ."
Haim Ramon is a leading member of the ruling Kadima Party and is considered a key ally of Prime Minister Ehud Olmert .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O,NNP NNP VBZ DT VBG NN IN DT NN NNP NNP CC VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP .
"Ramon issued a statement Friday , saying he will resign Sunday and has waived his parliamentary immunity and the right to a special hearing with the attorney general , Meni Mazuz .",B-per O O O B-tim O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O,"NNP VBD DT NN NNP , VBG PRP MD VB NNP CC VBZ VBN PRP$ JJ NN CC DT NN TO DT JJ NN IN DT NN NN , NNP NNP ."
"Ramon denied having forcibly kissed the soldier and said he has asked Mazuz to ensure a speedy trial both "" for personal reasons "" and "" public interest . """,B-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD VBG RB VBN DT NN CC VBD PRP VBZ VBN NNP TO VB DT JJ NN DT LQU IN JJ NNS LQU CC LQU JJ NN . LQU
"On Thursday , Attorney General Mazuz said he decided to indict Ramon because evidence leads to "" a reasonable chance of conviction . """,O B-tim O B-org I-org B-per O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , NNP NNP NNP VBD PRP VBD TO VB NNP IN NN VBZ TO LQU DT JJ NN IN NN . LQU"
