Police in Haiti say they have killed a rebel leader who helped oust former President Jean-Bertrand Aristide last year .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O,NNS IN NNP VBP PRP VBP VBN DT NN NN WP VBD VB JJ NNP NNP NNP JJ NN .
Police spokesmen say Remissainthe Ravix was shot dead during a gun battle Saturday between authorities and armed men in Port-au-Prince .,O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-geo O,NNS NNS VBP NNP NNP VBD VBN JJ IN DT NN NN NNP IN NNS CC JJ NNS IN NNP .
Authorities had been searching for Mr. Ravix for his alleged involvement in the killing of four police officers earlier this year .,O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBD VBN VBG IN NNP NNP IN PRP$ JJ NN IN DT NN IN CD NN NNS RBR DT NN .
"Since then , U.N. peacekeepers and Haiti 's interim government have been struggling to contain violence involving the ex-soldiers and several street gangs .",O O O B-org O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN RB , NNP NNS CC NNP POS JJ NN VBP VBN VBG TO VB NN VBG DT NNS CC JJ NN NNS ."
The former army soldiers still control several rural areas in Haiti .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT JJ NN NNS RB VBP JJ JJ NNS IN NNP .
