Iraqi political and religious leaders have held their first committee meeting aimed at promoting Prime Minister Naouri al-Maliki 's national reconciliation plan to end sectarian violence .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,JJ JJ CC JJ NNS VBP VBN PRP$ JJ NN NN VBN IN VBG NNP NNP NNP NNP POS JJ NN NN TO VB JJ NN .
But officials say little over half the group 's 30 members attended Saturday 's talks .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,CC NNS VBP RB IN PDT DT NN POS CD NNS VBD NNP POS NNS .
But Parliament speaker Mahmoud al-Mashhadani said Iraq should punish American soldiers who killed Iraqi civilians if the country is going to hold insurgents accountable for killing foreign troops .,O B-org O B-per I-per O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC NNP NN NNP NNP VBD NNP MD VB JJ NNS WP VBD JJ NNS IN DT NN VBZ VBG TO VB NNS JJ IN VBG JJ NNS .
The meeting was held as Mr. Maliki prepares for a Tuesday visit to Washington for talks with President Bush .,O O O O O B-per B-org O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O B-per I-per O,DT NN VBD VBN IN NNP NNP VBZ IN DT NNP NN TO NNP IN NNS IN NNP NNP .
"Violence continued in Iraq today , with gunmen killing seven workers in Baghdad .",O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NN VBD IN NNP NN , IN NNS VBG CD NNS IN NNP ."
Iraqi police also killed three insurgents during a raid in Mosul .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNS RB VBD CD NNS IN DT NN IN NNP .
And a roadside bomb killed a U.S. soldier in Baghdad .,O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O,CC DT NN NN VBD DT NNP NN IN NNP .
