"U.S. Secretary of State Colin Powell says he does not expect an increase in U.S. aid for tsunami-devastated southern Asia , as he begins a tour of the region to assess the disaster .",B-org O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ RB VB DT NN IN NNP NN IN JJ JJ NNP , IN PRP VBZ DT NN IN DT NN TO VB DT NN ."
"Mr. Powell and a U.S. team that includes President Bush 's brother , Florida Governor Jeb Bush , arrived in Bangkok Monday .",B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O B-per I-per O O O B-geo I-geo B-per I-per O O O B-geo B-tim O,"NNP NNP CC DT NNP NN WDT VBZ NNP NNP POS NN , NNP NNP NNP NNP , VBD IN NNP NNP ."
They will meet with Thai officials and tour damaged areas of the country before heading later this week to Indonesia and possibly Sri Lanka .,O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O B-per B-gpe O,PRP MD VB IN JJ NNS CC NN VBN NNS IN DT NN IN VBG RB DT NN TO NNP CC RB NNP NNP .
Secretary Powell told reporters today the U.S. aid donation of $ 350 million is adequate at this point .,O B-per O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD NNS NN DT NNP NN NN IN $ CD CD VBZ JJ IN DT NN .
The United States has faced criticism it was slow to respond to the disaster .,O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNPS VBZ VBN NN PRP VBD JJ TO VB TO DT NN .
"Mr. Powell will join world leaders and international donors in Jakarta , Indonesia , Thursday , for a summit on allocating donations , as well as assessing future needs .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP MD VB NN NNS CC JJ NNS IN NNP , NNP , NNP , IN DT NN IN VBG NNS , RB RB IN VBG JJ NNS ."
