The United Nations ' atomic watchdog agency has approved an agreement with Saudi Arabia that exempts its nuclear facilities from international inspections .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNPS POS JJ NN NN VBZ VBN DT NN IN NNP NNP WDT VBZ PRP$ JJ NNS IN JJ NNS .
"Western nations had lobbied for Saudi Arabia not to be included in the so-called Small Quantities Protocol , which allows nations with small nuclear programs to avoid inspections .",B-per O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBD VBN IN NNP NNP RB TO VB VBN IN DT JJ JJ NNS NNP , WDT VBZ NNS IN JJ JJ NNS TO VB NNS ."
"Diplomats said that in a time of heightened fears about the spread of nuclear weapons , the ability of the International Atomic Energy Agency to conduct inspections should not be restrained .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBD IN IN DT NN IN JJ NNS IN DT NN IN JJ NNS , DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP TO VB NNS MD RB VB VBN ."
"However , because the kingdom said it has no plans to develop nuclear arms and no significant stockpiles of nuclear material , the IAEA said it qualified for the protocol .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,"RB , IN DT NN VBD PRP VBZ DT NNS TO VB JJ NNS CC DT JJ NNS IN JJ NN , DT NNP VBD PRP VBD IN DT NN ."
"Since 1971 , some 75 nations throughout the world have signed the small quantities protocol .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN CD , DT CD NNS IN DT NN VBP VBN DT JJ NNS NN ."
