Senior U.S. officials say the Bush administration is ready to adopt a European proposal to offer Iran economic incentives to abandon its aggressive nuclear program .,O B-geo O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNS VBP DT NNP NN VBZ JJ TO VB DT JJ NN TO VB NNP JJ NNS TO VB PRP$ JJ JJ NN .
"The agreement , which has been widely anticipated since President Bush returned from Europe late last month , is expected to be formally announced later , Friday .",O O O O O O O O O B-per B-org O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,"DT NN , WDT VBZ VBN RB VBN IN NNP NNP VBD IN NNP RB JJ NN , VBZ VBN TO VB RB VBN RB , NNP ."
"Under the proposal , the United States would allow Iran to join the World Trade Organization and buy aircraft spare parts .",O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN , DT NNP NNPS MD VB NNP TO VB DT NNP NNP NNP CC VB NN JJ NNS ."
"In return , Britain , France and Germany will agree to refer Iran to the U.N. Security Council if Tehran fails to give up its suspected nuclear weapons program .",O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org I-org O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NN , NNP , NNP CC NNP MD VB TO VB NNP TO DT NNP NNP NNP IN NNP VBZ TO VB RP PRP$ JJ JJ NNS NN ."
Washington 's decision to embrace economic incentives is seen as a significant reversal from its refusal to reward Iran for what the United States regards as bad behavior .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O,NNP POS NN TO VB JJ NNS VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NN IN PRP$ NN TO VB NNP IN WP DT NNP NNPS VBZ IN JJ NN .
Washington accuses Tehran trying to build nuclear weapons .,B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O,NNP VBZ NNP VBG TO VB JJ NNS .
