Thousands of demonstrators have burned Danish and Dutch flags in the Afghan capital in the latest protests against cartoons and a film considered insulting to Islam .,O O O O O B-gpe O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNS IN NNS VBP VBN JJ CC JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJS NNS IN NNS CC DT NN VBN VBG TO NNP .
Angry protesters gathered in Kabul after Friday prayers to demand that Danish and Dutch troops withdraw from Afghanistan and that their embassies be shut down .,O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O B-gpe O B-gpe O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBD IN NNP IN NNP NNS TO VB DT JJ CC JJ NNS VB IN NNP CC IN PRP$ NNS VB VBN RP .
"They also burned an effigy of a Dutch filmmaker , who is due to release a film said to be critical of the Koran .",O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-art O,"PRP RB VBD DT NN IN DT JJ NN , WP VBZ JJ TO VB DT NN VBN TO VB JJ IN DT NNP ."
"Protesters are also angry at Danish newspapers that reprinted cartoons of the Prophet Muhammad , first published three years ago .",O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O B-tim O O O,"NNS VBP RB JJ IN JJ NNS WDT VBD NNS IN DT NNP NNP , RB VBN CD NNS RB ."
Similar protests have erupted over the past month in Pakistan .,O O O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O,JJ NNS VBP VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
"On Wednesday , al-Qaida leader Osama bin Laden released a message , warning the European Union will be punished for allowing the cartoons to be published .",O B-tim O B-org O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , NNP NN NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN , VBG DT NNP NNP MD VB VBN IN VBG DT NNS TO VB VBN ."
