"German Chancellor Angela Merkel met Saturday with Nelson Mandela , and afterwards urged the world to follow the former South African president 's legacy of peace to resolve Africa 's conflicts .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP IN NNP NNP , CC RB VBD DT NN TO VB DT JJ NNP NNP NN POS NN IN NN TO VB NNP POS NNS ."
The two talked about ways to broker peace across the continent and about efforts to fight AIDS .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT CD VBD IN NNS TO NN NN IN DT NN CC IN NNS TO VB NNP .
Ms. Merkel was scheduled to visit an HIV / AIDS project in Cape Town later in the day .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-tim O,NNP NNP VBD VBN TO VB DT NNP NNP NNP NN IN NNP NNP RB IN DT NN .
The German chancellor is on a five-day visit to Africa .,O B-gpe O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O,DT JJ NN VBZ IN DT JJ NN TO NNP .
She arrived in South Africa Thursday from Ethiopia .,O O O B-geo I-geo B-tim O B-geo O,PRP VBD IN NNP NNP NNP IN NNP .
She travels to Liberia on Sunday .,O O O B-geo O B-tim O,PRP VBZ TO NNP IN NNP .
"Ms. Merkel is working to lay the groundwork for a summit between leaders of the African Union and the European Union , set for December in Portugal .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-org I-org O O O B-tim O B-geo O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBG TO VB DT NN IN DT NN IN NNS IN DT NNP NNP CC DT NNP NNP , VBN IN NNP IN NNP ."
