Several people were injured in Indian Kashmir Tuesday in a clash between Muslim protesters and police in Srinagar .,O O O O O B-gpe O B-tim O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNS VBD VBN IN JJ NNP NNP IN DT NN IN NNP NNS CC NNS IN NNP .
Indian police fired tear gas to break up hundreds of Shi'ite Muslims protesting the publication of cartoons of the Prophet Muhammad in European newspapers .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O,JJ NN VBD JJ NN TO VB RP NNS IN NNP NNPS VBG DT NN IN NNS IN DT NNP NNP IN JJ NNS .
A police spokesman says more than 50 people were arrested .,O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN NN VBZ JJR IN CD NNS VBD VBN .
"The violence began when police stopped a procession , which began in observance of Ashoura .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NN VBD WRB NNS VBD DT NN , WDT VBD IN NN IN NNP ."
"Ashoura marks the anniversary of the death of Imam Hussein , the grandson of the Prophet Muhammad .",B-geo O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-org I-org O,"NNP VBZ DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP , DT NN IN DT NNP NNP ."
Police say they stopped the protesters because they began their procession without official permission .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP PRP VBD DT NNS IN PRP VBD PRP$ NN IN JJ NN .
