Iraq 's Interim President Ghazi al-Yawar is meeting at the White House with President Bush on security issues and arrangements for next month 's elections in Iraq .,B-org O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,NNP POS NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBG IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP NNP IN NN NNS CC NNS IN JJ NN POS NNS IN NNP .
"Mr. Yawar is against postponing the elections , scheduled for January 30 .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"NNP NNP VBZ IN VBG DT NNS , VBN IN NNP CD ."
"The Iraqi president told American journalists Sunday that delaying elections for a national assembly would only "" prolong the agony "" that Iraqis have suffered during months of insurgent attacks .",O B-gpe O O B-gpe O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBD JJ NNS NNP IN VBG NNS IN DT JJ NN MD RB LQU VB DT NN RQU WDT NNS VBP VBN IN NNS IN JJ NNS .
Mr. Yawar is an influential leader in the Sunni Muslim areas of Iraq where insurgent attacks have been the fiercest .,B-per I-per O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP NNS IN NNP WRB JJ NNS VBP VBN DT JJS .
President Bush agrees that Iraq 's elections should not be delayed .,B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ IN NNP POS NNS MD RB VB VBN .
"Later today , Mr. Bush also meets at the White House with Jordan 's King Abdullah .",O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-org I-org O B-org O B-per I-per O,"RB NN , NNP NNP RB VBZ IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP POS NNP NNP ."
