"The U.S. ambassador to the Vatican has voiced support for the Catholic Church 's push for more religious freedoms in China , saying Beijing should cooperate more openly with the Holy See .",O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"DT NNP NN TO DT NNP VBZ VBN NN IN DT NNP NNP POS NN IN JJR JJ NNS IN NNP , VBG NNP MD VB RBR RB IN DT NNP NNP ."
Ambassador Francis Rooney said he is supporting the Church 's mission to secure greater liberties for Catholics in China .,O B-per I-per O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP NNP VBD PRP VBZ VBG DT NNP POS NN TO VB JJR NNS IN NNS IN NNP .
"The announcement follows President Bush 's trip to China , where he urged Beijing to allow greater "" social , political and religious freedoms . """,O O O B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ NNP NNP POS NN TO NNP , WRB PRP VBD NNP TO VB JJR LQU JJ , JJ CC JJ NNS . LQU"
"Pope Benedict has said he is interested re-establishing diplomatic ties with China , which were severed in 1951 .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP VBZ JJ JJ JJ NNS IN NNP , WDT VBD VBN IN CD ."
"But tensions escalated between the two sides in October , when Chinese officials refused to allow local bishops to travel to a Church gathering in Rome .",O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-geo O,"CC NNS VBD IN DT CD NNS IN NNP , WRB JJ NNS VBD TO VB JJ NNS TO VB TO DT NN NN IN NNP ."
