U.S. officials say a suspicious material found in a passenger 's bag that triggered a security scare at a California airport on Tuesday actually turned out to be bottles of honey .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBP DT JJ NN VBN IN DT NN POS NN IN VBD DT NN NN IN DT NNP NN IN NNP RB VBD RP TO VB NNS IN NN .
The scare caused a shutdown at the Meadows Field Airport in the city of Bakersfield and a hazardous material crew and bomb squad were called to the scene .,O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP IN DT NN IN NNP CC DT JJ NN NN CC NN NN VBD VBN TO DT NN .
"Two Transportation Security Administration officers were also treated and released from the hospital after being exposed to what were described as "" fumes "" from the bottles .",O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CD NNP NNP NNP NNS VBD RB VBN CC VBN IN DT NN IN VBG VBN TO WP VBD VBN IN LQU NNS RQU IN DT NNS .
Police say they are investigating to determine why the incident happened .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP PRP VBP VBG TO VB WRB DT NN VBD .
They said the owner of the bag has been cooperating .,O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT NN IN DT NN VBZ VBN VBG .
Security at U.S. airports has been tightened since a Nigerian man 's botched attempt to blow up a U.S.-bound airliner on Christmas Day .,O O B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,NN IN NNP NNS VBZ VBN VBN IN DT JJ NN POS JJ NN TO VB RP DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP .
