China has rejected a U.S. appeal to reconsider a bill that would allow the use of force against Taiwan .,B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP VBZ VBN DT NNP NN TO VB DT NN WDT MD VB DT NN IN NN IN NNP .
China 's National People 's Congress is expected to pass the controversial anti-secession law on Monday .,B-geo O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP POS NNP NNP POS NNP VBZ VBN TO VB DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP .
"It would authorize military action if Taiwan , which Beijing considers a renegade province , moves toward formal independence .",O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP MD VB JJ NN IN NNP , WDT NNP VBZ DT NN NN , NNS IN JJ NN ."
"The White House Tuesday called the measure "" unhelpful "" and asked Beijing to reconsider .",O B-org I-org B-tim O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN LQU JJ LQU CC VBD NNP TO VB .
"A Chinese foreign ministry spokesman Thursday called the remark "" irresponsible . """,O B-gpe O O O B-tim O O O O O O O,DT JJ JJ NN NN NNP VBD DT NN LQU JJ . LQU
"Meanwhile , officials of Taiwan 's pro-independence party say they will organize a protest March 26th against the proposed Chinese law .",O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O B-gpe O O,"RB , NNS IN NNP POS JJ NN VBP PRP MD VB DT NN NNP CD IN DT VBN JJ NN ."
"Su Tseng-chang , chairman of the Democratic Progressive Party , said Thursday that China 's anti-secession bill poses an immediate threat to the democratically-ruled island .",B-per I-per O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP , NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP , VBD NNP IN NNP POS JJ NN VBZ DT JJ NN TO DT JJ NN ."
