The Trucial States of the Persian Gulf coast granted the UK control of their defense and foreign affairs in 19th century treaties .,O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,DT NNP NNPS IN DT NNP NNP NN VBD DT NNP NN IN PRP$ NN CC JJ NNS IN JJ NN NNS .
"In 1971 , six of these states - Abu Zaby , 'Ajman , Al Fujayrah , Ash Shariqah , Dubayy , and Umm al Qaywayn - merged to form the United Arab Emirates ( UAE ) .",O B-tim O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-org O B-org I-org O B-org I-org O B-org O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-org O O,"IN CD , CD IN DT NNS IN NNP NNP , NNP , NNP NNP , NNP NNP , NNP , CC NNP NNP NNP : VBD TO VB DT NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP RRB ."
They were joined in 1972 by Ra 's al Khaymah .,O O O O B-tim O B-org O B-org I-org O,PRP VBD VBN IN CD IN NNP POS NNP NNP .
The UAE 's per capita GDP is on par with those of leading West European nations .,O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP POS IN NN NN VBZ IN NN IN DT IN VBG JJ JJ NNS .
Its generosity with oil revenues and its moderate foreign policy stance have allowed the UAE to play a vital role in the affairs of the region .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP$ NN IN NN NNS CC PRP$ JJ JJ NN NN VBP VBN DT NNP TO VB DT JJ NN IN DT NNS IN DT NN .
"For more than three decades , oil and global finance drove the UAE 's economy .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O,"IN JJR IN CD NNS , NN CC JJ NN VBD DT NNP POS NN ."
"However , in 2008 - 09 , the confluence of falling oil prices , collapsing real estate prices , and the international banking crisis hit the UAE especially hard .",O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O,"RB , IN CD : CD , DT NN IN VBG NN NNS , VBG JJ NN NNS , CC DT JJ NN NN VBD DT NNP RB JJ ."
"In March 2011 , about 100 Emirati activists and intellectuals posted on the Internet and sent to the government a petition calling for greater political reform , including the establishment of a parliament with full legislative powers and the further expansion of the electorate and the rights of the Federal National Council , the UAE 's quasi-legislature .",O B-tim I-tim O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-org O O O,"IN NNP CD , IN CD JJ NNS CC NNS VBD IN DT NNP CC VBD TO DT NN DT NN VBG IN JJR JJ NN , VBG DT NN IN DT NN IN JJ JJ NNS CC DT JJ NN IN DT NN CC DT NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP , DT NNP POS NN ."
"In April 2011 , the Emirati Government arrested four activists - all of whom signed the petition - for their alleged criticisms of the UAE system of government .",O B-tim I-tim O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O,"IN NNP CD , DT JJ NN VBN CD NNS IN DT IN WP VBD DT NN : IN PRP$ JJ NNS IN DT NNP NN IN NN ."
