The U.S. Geological Survey said the earthquake had a magnitude of 7.5 and a depth of about 15 kilometers .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN VBD DT NN IN CD CC DT NN IN RB CD NNS .
"Its epicenter was 78 kilometers west of Indonesia 's Pagai Selantan island , off Sumatra 's western coast .",O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O B-geo O O O O,"PRP$ NN VBD CD NNS JJS IN NNP POS NNP NNP NN , IN NNP POS JJ NN ."
The quake happened Monday at 1442 UTC .,O O O B-tim O B-tim I-tim O,DT NN VBD NNP IN CD NNP .
Indonesian authorities initially issued a tsunami alert but later lifted it .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS RB VBD DT NN NN CC RB VBD PRP .
Indonesia straddles several fault lines that make the vast island nation vulnerable to volcanic and seismic activity .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ JJ NN NNS WDT VBP DT JJ NN NN JJ TO JJ CC JJ NN .
"A giant quake hit off Sumatra 's coast on December 26 , 2004 , triggering an Indian Ocean tsunami that killed 230,000 people , half of them in Indonesia 's Aceh province .",O O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O B-gpe B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBD RP NNP POS NN IN NNP CD , CD , VBG DT JJ NNP NNS WDT VBD CD NNS , NN IN PRP IN NNP POS NNP NN ."
