"The leader of Sri Lanka 's Tamil Tigers has issued an ultimatum to the government , warning his group will intensify the struggle for self-determination in 2006 if Colombo does not offer what he called a reasonable political settlement .",O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN NNP NNP POS NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN TO DT NN , VBG PRP$ NN MD VB DT NN IN NN IN CD IN NNP VBZ RB VB WP PRP VBD DT JJ JJ NN ."
"Velupillai Prabhakaran gave the warning in his annual policy speech Sunday , which concluded ceremonies honoring nearly 18,000 guerillas who died while battling government forces .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN PRP$ JJ NN NN NNP , WDT VBD NNS VBG RB CD NNS WP VBD IN VBG NN NNS ."
"Mr. Prabhakaran urged newly-elected President Mahinda Rajapakse to propose a framework that satisfies the aspirations of minority Tamils , adding Tamil people have lost patience , hope and reached the brink of utter frustration .",B-per I-per O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD JJ NNP NNP NNP TO VB DT NN WDT VBZ DT NNS IN NN NNS , VBG NNP NNS VBP VBN NN , NN CC VBD DT NN IN JJ NN ."
His appeal came two days after President Rajapakse demanded revisions of the government 's cease-fire with the rebels .,O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP$ NN VBD CD NNS IN NNP NNP VBD NNS IN DT NN POS NN IN DT NNS .
"The president said he was ready to open talks with the rebels , but rejected their demand for recognition of an autonomous homeland for Sri Lanka 's minority Tamils .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-per O,"DT NN VBD PRP VBD JJ TO VB NNS IN DT NNS , CC VBD PRP$ NN IN NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP POS NN NNS ."
