Iran has urged the International Atomic Energy Agency to ignore an exiled opposition group 's allegation that Tehran has a secret nuclear weapons facility .,B-geo O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP TO VB DT JJ NN NN POS NN IN NNP VBZ DT JJ JJ NNS NN .
"The chief Iranian delegate to the Vienna-based nuclear agency , Hossein Mousavian , said Friday the IAEA should not damage its prestige by listening to the charges of what he called a terrorist group .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O B-tim O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ JJ NN TO DT JJ JJ NN , NNP NNP , VBD NNP DT NNP MD RB VB PRP$ NN IN VBG TO DT NNS IN WP PRP VBD DT JJ NN ."
He told Reuters news agency the charge is baseless and will only harm relations between Tehran and IAEA members .,O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-org O O,PRP VBD NNP NN NN DT NN VBZ JJ CC MD RB VB NNS IN NNP CC NNP NNS .
"One member , the United States , has accused Iran of secretly developing atomic weapons .",O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"CD NN , DT NNP NNPS , VBZ VBN NNP IN RB VBG JJ NNS ."
"Tehran has consistently denied that accusation , saying its nuclear program is designed to generate electricity .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ RB VBN IN NN , VBG PRP$ JJ NN VBZ VBN TO VB NN ."
Outgoing U.S. Secretary of State Colin Powell said this week Iran could be developing nuclear capable missiles .,O B-org O O B-org I-org I-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,VBG NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN NNP MD VB VBG JJ JJ NNS .
The Washington Post newspaper says Mr. Powell 's assertion was based on information that has not been verified .,B-org I-org I-org O O B-per B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NN VBZ NNP NNP POS NN VBD VBN IN NN WDT VBZ RB VBN VBN .
