Burma 's military government has released the daughter of the country 's former dictator Ne Win after six years under house arrest .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O,NNP POS JJ NN VBZ VBN DT NN IN DT NN POS JJ NN NNP NNP IN CD NNS IN NN NN .
"Sandar Win had been under house arrest at her lakeside home in the main city of Rangoon since 2002 , after being convicted of treason for plotting a coup .",B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD VBN IN NN NN IN PRP$ NN NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP IN CD , IN VBG VBN IN NN IN VBG DT NN ."
She was released Friday .,O O O B-tim O,PRP VBD VBN NNP .
"Her husband Aye Zaw Win and three sons were sentenced to death for the same crime , but remain locked up in Rangoon 's notorious Insein prison .",O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O,"PRP$ NN NNP NNP NNP CC CD NNS VBD VBN TO NN IN DT JJ NN , CC VBP VBN RP IN NNP POS JJ NNP NN ."
Ne Win came to power in 1962 after a coup against Burma 's first elected post-independence prime minister U Nu .,O B-per O O O O B-tim O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-per I-per O,NNP NNP VBD TO NN IN CD IN DT NN IN NNP POS JJ VBN JJ JJ NN NNP NNP .
Ne Win 's socialist programs took Burma from one of the richest countries in Southeast Asia to poverty .,O B-per O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O,NNP NNP POS JJ NNS VBD NNP IN CD IN DT JJS NNS IN NNP NNP TO NN .
