Russian President Vladimir Putin says the United States is increasing the danger to world security by overstepping its national borders .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT NNP NNPS VBZ VBG DT NN TO NN NN IN VBG PRP$ JJ NNS .
"Mr. Putin spoke Saturday at an annual security conference in Munich , Germany .",B-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O B-org O B-geo O,"NNP NNP VBD NNP IN DT JJ NN NN IN NNP , NNP ."
He described U.S. actions as dangerous and he said other countries do not feel secure because of them .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD NNP NNS IN JJ CC PRP VBD JJ NNS VBP RB VB JJ IN IN PRP .
"The Russian leader did not mention the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan , but he rejected suggestions that NATO or the European Union had a right to intervene in such regional conflicts .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O B-org O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBD RB VB DT NNS IN NNP CC NNP , CC PRP VBD NNS IN NNP CC DT NNP NNP VBD DT NN TO VB IN JJ JJ NNS ."
He said the legitimate use of force could only be done by the United Nations .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,PRP VBD DT JJ NN IN NN MD RB VB VBN IN DT NNP NNPS .
"On the subject of Kosovo , Mr. Putin said Russia will not support any international plan to resolve the status of the Serb province without the agreement of both Kosovo 's minority Serbs and majority ethnic Albanians .",O O O O B-geo O B-per B-org O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org B-gpe O O O B-gpe O,"IN DT NN IN NNP , NNP NNP VBD NNP MD RB VB DT JJ NN TO VB DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN DT NNP POS NN NNS CC NN JJ NNS ."
Russia has veto power on the U.N. Security Council .,B-geo O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,NNP VBZ NN NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP .
