U.S. shipping giant Fed Ex says it will build a new Asia-Pacific shipping hub in southern China .,B-geo O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NN NN NNP NNP VBZ PRP MD VB DT JJ JJ NN NN IN JJ NNP .
"Fed Ex chairman Frederick Smith made the announcement Wednesday in Guangzhou , where the new $ 150 - million facility will be located .",B-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NN NNP NNP VBD DT NN NNP IN NNP , WRB DT JJ $ CD : CD NN MD VB VBN ."
"Mr. Smith says around 1,200 people will be employed at the new hub , which will handle up to 24,000 packages a day .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ IN CD NNS MD VB VBN IN DT JJ NN , WDT MD VB RP TO CD NNS DT NN ."
"The Guangzhou hub will replace Fed Ex 's current operation at Subic Bay , Philippines , which will be phased out when new center opens in December 2008 .",O B-geo O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"DT NNP NN MD VB NNP NNP POS JJ NN IN NNP NNP , NNP , WDT MD VB VBN RP WRB JJ NN VBZ IN NNP CD ."
The company is predicting that air freight from China to the U.S. will grow an average of 9.6 percent a year over the next 20 years .,O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-tim O O,DT NN VBZ VBG IN NN NN IN NNP TO DT NNP MD VB DT NN IN CD NN DT NN IN DT JJ CD NNS .
