An Iranian doctor who says he examined Canadian photojournalist Zahra Kazemi says she was tortured and raped before she died in Iranian police custody in 2003 .,O B-gpe O O O O O B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-tim O,DT JJ NN WP VBZ PRP VBD JJ NN NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBD VBN CC VBN IN PRP VBD IN JJ NN NN IN CD .
Doctor Shahram Azam says he examined Ms. Kazemi at an Iranian military hospital days after her arrest for taking pictures outside a Tehran prison .,O B-per I-per O O O B-per I-per O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O,NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBD NNP NNP IN DT JJ JJ NN NNS IN PRP$ NN IN VBG NNS IN DT NNP NN .
"He says her body showed signs of rape , and that she had a broken nose and fingers .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBZ PRP$ NN VBD NNS IN NN , CC IN PRP VBD DT JJ NN CC NNS ."
His account has not been independently confirmed and it contradicts Iranian officials who say she died after a fall and hitting her head .,O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP$ NN VBZ RB VBN RB VBN CC PRP VBZ JJ NNS WP VBP PRP VBD IN DT NN CC VBG PRP$ NN .
Doctor Azam recently received asylum in Canada .,O B-per O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP RB VBD NN IN NNP .
Canadian Foreign Affairs Minister Pierre Pettigrew says his statement shows that Iran is failing in guaranteeing basic human rights .,B-gpe O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP$ NN VBZ IN NNP VBZ VBG IN VBG JJ JJ NNS .
"Ms. Kazemi 's death sparked a diplomatic crisis , with Canada briefly recalling its ambassador from Iran .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP NNP POS NN VBD DT JJ NN , IN NNP RB VBG PRP$ NN IN NNP ."
