One of the most visible destinations in Washington is marking the capital 's summer tourist season this year with an exhibit dedicated to the environment and sustainability .,O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,CD IN DT RBS JJ NNS IN NNP VBZ VBG DT NN POS NN NN NN DT NN IN DT NN VBN TO DT NN CC NN .
People usually visit the U.S. Botanic Garden to see a variety of plants and greenery .,O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O,NNS RB VBP DT NNP NNP NNP TO VB DT NN IN NNS CC NN .
"This year , they can learn about personal ways to fight climate change .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN , PRP MD VB IN JJ NNS TO VB NN NN ."
Marissa Melton narrates .,B-per I-per O O,NNP NNP VBZ .
