"China has unveiled a new set of emergency measures meant to clear the polluted air in the capital , Beijing , before the Olympic Games start on August 8 .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN NN NNS VBN TO VB DT JJ NN IN DT NN , NNP , IN DT NNP NNPS NN IN NNP CD ."
"State media said Thursday that if air quality is poor , Chinese authorities will bring a halt to all construction projects and close more than 200 more factories in Beijing , Tianjin , and Hebei province .",O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O B-geo O O,"NNP NNS VBD NNP IN IN NN NN VBZ JJ , JJ NNS MD VB DT NN TO DT NN NNS CC VB JJR IN CD JJR NNS IN NNP , NNP , CC NNP NN ."
The Xinhua news agency says the emergency measures would also restrict more vehicles from the roads .,O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN NN VBZ DT NN NNS MD RB VB JJR NNS IN DT NNS .
"At the beginning of July , Beijing banned 300,000 heavy-polluting trucks from the roads .",O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN IN NNP , NNP VBD CD JJ NNS IN DT NNS ."
"Last week , China banned more than a million cars from the streets of Beijing .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"JJ NN , NNP VBD JJR IN DT CD NNS IN DT NNS IN NNP ."
The International Olympic Committee has said it may postpone long-distance endurance events if air pollution is too severe .,O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP MD VB JJ NN NNS IN NN NN VBZ RB JJ .
