"U.S. officials say President Bush is "" extremely pleased "" with the results of the Busan summit talks among Asian and Pacific leaders .",B-geo O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBP NNP NNP VBZ LQU RB JJ LQU IN DT NNS IN DT NNP NN NNS IN JJ CC JJ NNS .
"Faryar Shirzad , a presidential adviser on international economic affairs , says the leaders held extensive discussions on trade and economic issues , as well as security concerns during their two days of talks .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP , DT JJ NN IN JJ JJ NNS , VBZ DT NNS VBD JJ NNS IN NN CC JJ NNS , RB RB IN NN NNS IN PRP$ CD NNS IN NNS ."
"Speaking to reporters aboard Mr. Bush 's plane after departing Busan , Mr. Shirzad said the leaders met in private for two hours Saturday , "" with senior officials from each government able to listen in from a remote location . """,O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"VBG TO NNS IN NNP NNP POS NN IN VBG NNP , NNP NNP VBD DT NNS VBD IN JJ IN CD NNS NNP , LQU IN JJ NNS IN DT NN JJ TO VB IN IN DT JJ NN . LQU"
The White House adviser said discussions centered on the threat that militant extremist groups pose to members of the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation forum .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O,DT NNP NNP NN VBD NNS VBD IN DT NN IN JJ NN NNS VBP TO NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP NN .
