British authorities have filed charges against the first of four suspects in the attempted bombings on London 's public transport system on July 21 .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,JJ NNS VBP VBN NNS IN DT NN IN CD NNS IN DT JJ NNS IN NNP POS JJ NN NN IN NNP CD .
Officials say 24-year-old Yassin Hassan Omar is charged with conspiracy to murder and possession of an explosive substance .,O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NN TO NN CC NN IN DT JJ NN .
He was arrested July 27 in the northern city of Birmingham .,O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O B-geo O,PRP VBD VBN NNP CD IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
"Two other July 21 suspects are in custody in London , and a fourth is held in Italy .",O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O,"CD JJ NNP CD NNS VBP IN NN IN NNP , CC DT NN VBZ VBN IN NNP ."
