Turkish officials say a land mine killed two soldiers Saturday in the latest violence with separatist fighters in the country 's largely Kurdish southeast .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP DT NN NN VBD CD NNS NNP IN DT JJS NN IN JJ NNS IN DT NN POS RB JJ NN .
The officials say the blast wounded two other members of Turkey 's security forces .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,DT NNS VBP DT NN VBD CD JJ NNS IN NNP POS NN NNS .
"The explosion came one day after Turkish forces killed six members of the outlawed Kurdistan Workers Party during a clash in Sirnak , near the Iraqi border .",O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O,"DT NN VBD CD NN IN JJ NNS VBD CD NNS IN DT JJ NNP NNP NNP IN DT NN IN NNP , IN DT JJ NN ."
The Turkish army has stepped up operations in the southeast following a spike in violence in the region .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBZ VBN RP NNS IN DT NN VBG DT NN IN NN IN DT NN .
"Turkey , the United States and the European Union consider the Kurdistan Workers Party ( PKK ) a terrorist organization .",B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O B-org I-org O O B-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O,"NNP , DT NNP NNPS CC DT NNP NNP VBP DT NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP RRB DT JJ NN ."
"More than 30,000 people have been killed since the PKK started fighting a separatist campaign in 1984 .",O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-tim O,JJR IN CD NNS VBP VBN VBN IN DT NNP VBD VBG DT NN NN IN CD .
