Mexico is condemning the shooting death of a young Mexican man by a U.S. Border Patrol agent as he tried to sneak into California last week .,B-org O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,NNP VBZ VBG DT NN NN IN DT JJ JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NN IN PRP VBD TO VB IN NNP JJ NN .
A Border Patrol spokesman says the man was shot after he began throwing rocks at the agent .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NN VBZ DT NN VBD VBN IN PRP VBD VBG NNS IN DT NN .
"The shooting occurred after a small group of men , including the shooting victim , crossed a border fence into U.S. territory .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"DT NN VBD IN DT JJ NN IN NNS , VBG DT NN NN , VBD DT NN NN IN NNP NN ."
Mexican authorities say 18-year-old Guillermo Martinez fled back into Mexico and died the next day in a Tijuana hospital .,B-gpe O O O B-per I-per O O O B-org O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim O O,JJ NNS VBP JJ NNP NNP VBD RB IN NNP CC VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NN .
A spokesman for President Vicente Fox said the shooting proves that a law guaranteeing Mexicans legal entry to the United States is the only way to resolve the issue .,O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN VBZ IN DT NN VBG NNS JJ NN TO DT NNP NNPS VBZ DT JJ NN TO VB DT NN .
"U.S. lawmakers recently ordered construction of security fencing along the U.S.-Mexican border to curb illegal border-crossing , another move that Mexican authorities protested .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O,"NNP NNS RB VBD NN IN NN VBG IN DT JJ NN TO VB JJ NN , DT NN IN JJ NNS VBD ."
