The leader of Thailand 's coup says investigators have not yet found enough evidence to charge deposed Prime Minister Thaksin Shinawatra with corruption .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O,DT NN IN NNP POS NN VBZ NNS VBP RB RB VBN JJ NN TO VB JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP IN NN .
General Sondhi Boonyaratglin says it will be difficult to implicate Mr. Thaksin .,B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-per B-geo O,NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP MD VB JJ TO VB NNP NNP .
"He says the corruption probe is a long , difficult process that might not yield anything .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBZ DT NN NN VBZ DT RB , JJ NN WDT MD RB VB DT ."
Sondhi made the statements in an interview with reporters from the Nation Multimedia Group Tuesday .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org B-tim O,NNP VBD DT NNS IN DT NN IN NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP .
Sondhi had earlier justified the September coup against Mr. Thaksin by saying he and other military leaders wanted to unify the divided country and hold the Thai prime minister accountable for alleged graft and abuse of power .,B-per O O O O B-tim O O B-per B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD RBR VBN DT NNP NN IN NNP NNP IN VBG PRP CC JJ JJ NNS VBD TO VB DT VBN NN CC VB DT JJ JJ NN NN IN JJ NN CC NN IN NN .
"Sondhi said if Mr. Thaksin tried to return to Thailand , his plane would not be allowed to land .",B-per O O B-per B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD IN NNP NNP VBD TO VB TO VB , PRP$ NN MD RB VB VBN TO VB ."
The former prime minister has been living in London .,O O B-per O O O O O B-geo O,DT JJ JJ NN VBZ VBN VBG IN NNP .
