Greek President Costis Stephanopoulos has warned that Turkey 's entry into the European Union will require Ankara 's official recognition of the Greek Cypriot-led government on Cyprus .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O B-org O O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-tim O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NNP POS NN IN DT NNP NNP MD VB NNP POS JJ NN IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP .
"Mr. Stephanopoulos issued the warning Sunday while acknowledging that relations between his country and its traditional rival , Turkey , have improved in recent years .",B-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O B-tim O O,"NNP NNP VBD DT NN NNP IN VBG DT NNS IN PRP$ NN CC PRP$ JJ NN , NNP , VBP VBN IN JJ NNS ."
He promised Greece will help Turkey in gaining EU membership if Turkey helps resolve differences on Cyprus .,O O B-org O O B-org O O B-org O O B-org O O O O B-tim O,PRP VBD NNP MD VB NNP IN VBG NNP NN IN NNP VBZ VB NNS IN NNP .
Leaders of the 25 EU countries are due to decide at a December summit whether to formally open EU membership talks with Turkey .,O O O O B-org O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-org O O O B-org O,NNS IN DT CD NNP NNS VBP JJ TO VB IN DT NNP NN IN TO RB JJ NNP NN NNS IN NNP .
Cyprus has been divided since Turkish troops landed on the island in 1974 after a Greece-backed coup in Nicosia .,B-tim O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O,NNP VBZ VBN VBN IN JJ NNS VBD IN DT NN IN CD IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
"The Greek-led Cypriot government in the south of the island is recognized by all members of the global community except Turkey , which recognizes a government run by leaders of the Turkish community in the north .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,"DT JJ JJ NN IN DT NN IN DT NN VBZ VBN IN DT NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , WDT VBZ DT NN VBN IN NNS IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN ."
