"The death toll from a powerful car bomb in Thailand has risen to six , with at least 40 others injured , some seriously .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN NN IN DT JJ NN NN IN NNP VBZ VBN TO CD , IN IN JJS CD NNS VBN , DT RB ."
"Police say the explosion Thursday occurred outside a hotel in the bar district of Sungai Kolok , a town on the Malaysian border frequented by tourists .",O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,"NNS VBP DT NN NNP VBD IN DT NN IN DT NN NN IN NNP NNP , DT NN IN DT JJ NN VBN IN NNS ."
"The Narathiwat provincial governor , Pracha Tehrat , said the explosive was unlike others used in the region .",O B-org O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP JJ NN , NNP NNP , VBD DT JJ VBD IN NNS VBN IN DT NN ."
"Earlier bombs have been smaller , often attached to motorcycles .",O O O O O O O O O O O,"RBR NNS VBP VBN JJR , RB VBN TO NNS ."
"There has been no claim of responsibility for Thursday 's attack , which is believed to be the first car bombing during an ongoing separatist uprising .",O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"EX VBZ VBN DT NN IN NN IN NNP POS NN , WDT VBZ VBN TO VB DT JJ NN NN IN DT JJ NN NN ."
"Hours before the attack , Prime Minister Thaksin Shinawatra toured the southern provinces and vowed to end separatist violence by cutting off development funding to villages supporting the insurgents .",O O O O O B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN DT NN , NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NNS CC VBD TO VB JJ NN IN VBG RP NN NN TO NNS VBG DT NNS ."
But locals say the plan could backfire by encouraging more support for rebels .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC NNS VBP DT NN MD VB IN VBG JJR NN IN NNS .
