Former President Bill Clinton has promised to keep helping survivors of last year 's tsunami disaster to rebuild their communities .,O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB VBG NNS IN JJ NN POS NN NN TO VB PRP$ NNS .
"In a recorded message shown Monday at a ceremony in Indonesia , Mr. Clinton said he will not be satisfied until survivors have decent homes and job opportunities .",O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-geo O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN VBN NNP IN DT NN IN NNP , NNP NNP VBD PRP MD RB VB VBN IN NNS VBP JJ NNS CC NN NNS ."
"Nearly two million people were made homeless by the tsunami , and Mr. Clinton said tens of thousands are still living in inadequate shelters .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB CD CD NNS VBD VBN JJ IN DT NN , CC NNP NNP VBD NNS IN NNS VBP RB VBG IN JJ NNS ."
Mr. Clinton has helped raise money for tsunami recovery as a special U.N. envoy .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN VB NN IN NN NN IN DT JJ NNP NN .
"The United Nations says global donations have reached $ 13 billion , making it the most generous relief effort in history .",O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP VBZ JJ NNS VBP VBN $ CD CD , VBG PRP DT RBS JJ NN NN IN NN ."
"But , Asian countries are still struggling to set up a tsunami warning system for the Indian Ocean , and some coastal residents say they are afraid a tsunami will come again .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"CC , JJ NNS VBP RB VBG TO VB RP DT NN NN NN IN DT NNP NNP , CC DT JJ NNS VBP PRP VBP JJ DT NN MD VB RB ."
