North Korea says U.S. spy planes flew about 180 missions over the country in October .,B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP NNP VBZ NNP NN NNS VBD IN CD NNS IN DT NN IN NNP .
"The North 's official news agency said Monday that the spy flights are an example of how , privately , the United States seeks to militarily undermine Pyongyang .",O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-geo O,"DT NNP POS JJ NN NN VBD NNP IN DT NN NNS VBP DT NN IN WRB , RB , DT NNP NNPS VBZ TO RB VB NNP ."
The Pentagon declined to comment on the allegations .,O B-org O O O O O O O,DT NNP VBD TO VB IN DT NNS .
North Korea and the United States have attended four rounds of multiparty talks to resolve a standoff over Pyongyang 's nuclear weapons program .,B-geo I-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,NNP NNP CC DT NNP NNPS VBP VBN CD NNS IN JJ NNS TO VB DT NN IN NNP POS JJ NNS NN .
"At the last round in September , North Korea pledged to abandon those weapons programs in exchange for economic aid , security assurances and diplomatic recognition .",O O O O O B-tim O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , NNP NNP VBD TO VB DT NNS NNS IN NN IN JJ NN , NN NNS CC JJ NN ."
"However , Pyongyang later demanded a light-water reactor , raising doubts about its willingness to proceed .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , NNP RB VBD DT NN NN , VBG NNS IN PRP$ NN TO VB ."
"The next round of talks is scheduled for early November , but no date has been announced .",O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN IN NNS VBZ VBN IN JJ NNP , CC DT NN VBZ VBN VBN ."
