Officials in Cuba say they are unsure as to whether Cuban President Fidel Castro will participate in the country 's upcoming May Day celebrations .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O,NNS IN NNP VBP PRP VBP JJ IN TO IN JJ NNP NNP NNP MD VB IN DT NN POS JJ NNP NNP NNS .
"However , they say he is taking an active role in the country 's key decision-making .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , PRP VBP PRP VBZ VBG DT JJ NN IN DT NN POS JJ NN ."
Speculations on the Cuban leader 's participation came after Bolivian President Evo Morales said Saturday that Mr. Castro would resume his role as president on May 1 .,O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-gpe O B-per I-per O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,NNS IN DT JJ NN POS NN VBD IN JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP IN NNP NNP MD VB PRP$ NN IN NN IN NNP CD .
More than six million Cubans are expected to participate in the annual celebration which marks International Workers Day .,O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org B-tim O,JJR IN CD CD NNS VBP VBN TO VB IN DT JJ NN WDT VBZ NNP NNP NNP .
His brother Raul Castro has been temporary appointed as the country 's leader .,O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,PRP$ NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN JJ VBN IN DT NN POS NN .
