"The biggest U.S. automaker , General Motors , has announced it will boost production by 60,000 vehicles in response to rising sales , a result of the government 's Cash for Clunkers program .",O O B-geo O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJS NNP NN , NNP NNPS , VBZ VBN PRP MD VB NN IN CD NNS IN NN TO VBG NNS , DT NN IN DT NN POS NN IN NNS NN ."
"GM said Tuesday it is adding shifts at plants in Canada and the U.S. , bringing some 1,350 laid-off employees back to work .",B-org O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD NNP PRP VBZ VBG NNS IN NNS IN NNP CC DT NNP , VBG DT CD JJ NNS RB TO NN ."
Analysts say rising sales have contributed to a shortage of the most sought-after car models .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP VBG NNS VBP VBN TO DT NN IN DT RBS JJ NN NNS .
GM emerged from bankruptcy last month .,B-org O O O O O O,NNP VBD IN NN JJ NN .
Ford Motor Company also has announced it will increase production in response to brisk sales for its Ford Focus and Escape models .,B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O,NNP NNP NNP RB VBZ VBN PRP MD VB NN IN NN TO JJ NNS IN PRP$ NNP NNP CC NNP NNS .
