Pakistani officials say troops have killed at least 25 militants in fighting near the border with Afghanistan .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O,JJ NNS VBP NNS VBP VBN IN JJS CD NNS IN VBG IN DT NN IN NNP .
"A military spokesman , Major General Waheed Arshad , says the clashes began late Tuesday following the abduction of four Pakistani paramilitary soldiers in the South Waziristan region .",O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo I-geo O O,"DT JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP NNP , VBZ DT NNS VBD JJ NNP VBG DT NN IN CD JJ JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNP NN ."
"The soldiers had been moving on foot to their base in the tribal area , when they were overpowered and kidnapped by militants near the Afghan border .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"DT NNS VBD VBN VBG IN NN TO PRP$ NN IN DT JJ NN , WRB PRP VBD VBN CC VBN IN NNS IN DT JJ NN ."
Pakistani security forces launched artillery and mortar fire at militant positions in response .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN NNS VBN NN CC NN NN IN JJ NNS IN NN .
Pakistan 's government had earlier blamed South Waziristan-based militant leader Baitullah Mehsud for the assassination of opposition leader Benazir Bhutto in Rawalpindi .,B-geo O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-geo O,NNP POS NN VBD RBR VBN NNP JJ JJ NN NNP NNP IN DT NN IN NN NN NNP NNP IN NNP .
Mehsud has denied involvement in last week 's attack on Bhutto .,B-per O O O O O O O O O B-org O,NNP VBZ VBN NN IN JJ NN POS NN IN NNP .
Pakistani troops have been fighting intense battles with militants along the Afghan border .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN VBG JJ NNS IN NNS IN DT JJ NN .
