The Bush administration has moved to freeze the assets of a Syrian man it says is aiding the insurgency in Iraq .,O B-per O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNP NN VBZ VBN TO VB DT NNS IN DT JJ NN PRP VBZ VBZ VBG DT NN IN NNP .
The U.S. government Tuesday formally designated Sulayman Khalid Darwish as a supporter of terrorism under an executive order President Bush signed in 2001 .,O B-geo O B-tim O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O B-tim O,DT NNP NN NNP RB VBN NNP NNP NNP IN DT NN IN NN IN DT NN NN NNP NNP VBD IN CD .
"The Treasury Department said Mr. Darwish , who is now in Syria , has provided tens of thousands of dollars to wanted terrorist Abu Musab al-Zarqawi , the Jordanian suspected of leading the Iraq insurgency .",O B-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org B-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"DT NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP , WP VBZ RB IN NNP , VBZ VBN NNS IN NNS IN NNS TO JJ JJ NNP NNP NNP , DT JJ JJ IN VBG DT NNP NN ."
The department describes him as a close Zarqawi associate and says he also recruited fighters for Zarqawi 's organization .,O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,DT NN VBZ PRP IN DT JJ NNP NN CC VBZ PRP RB VBD NNS IN NNP POS NN .
Today 's action puts an automatic freeze on any assets Mr. Darwish may have in the United States .,B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-geo I-geo O,NN POS NN VBZ DT JJ NN IN DT NNS NNP NNP MD VB IN DT NNP NNPS .
The government has also submitted his name to a United Nations committee that will consider adding him to a consolidated list of terrorists tied to al-Qaida .,O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,DT NN VBZ RB VBN PRP$ NN TO DT NNP NNP NN WDT MD VB VBG PRP TO DT JJ NN IN NNS VBN TO NNP .
