"Last weekend the leading rebel group in Sudan , Justice and Equality Movement or JEM launched a surprise attack on the Sudanese cities of Omdurman and Khartoum .",O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-org I-org I-org O,"JJ NN DT VBG NN NN IN NNP , NNP CC NNP NNP CC NNP VBD DT NN NN IN DT JJ NNS IN NNP CC NNP ."
The government was able to repel the attack .,O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD JJ TO VB DT NN .
The head of strategic planning for JEM said the attack was successful .,O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O,DT NN IN JJ NN IN NNP VBD DT NN VBD JJ .
Peter Eichstaedt is Africa editor for the Institute for War and Peace Reporting .,B-per I-per O B-geo O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,NNP NNP VBZ NNP NN IN DT NNP IN NNP CC NNP NNP .
VOA ’s Akwei Thompson reached him by phone at his base in The Hague for an analysis of the attack .,B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NNP NNP VBD PRP IN NN IN PRP$ NN IN DT NNP IN DT NN IN DT NN .
"Eichstaedt said the most dramatic part of the story is not who won the battle , but rather the fact that the “ rebels were able to conduct a surprise strike ” at the capital Sudan .",B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP VBD DT RBS JJ NN IN DT NN VBZ RB WP VBD DT NN , CC RB DT NN IN DT LQU NNS VBD JJ TO VB DT NN NN RQU IN DT NN NNP ."
"“ This has literally burst the bubble , the security bubble of the Sudan government ” , he added .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"LQU DT VBZ RB VBN DT NN , DT NN NN IN DT NNP NN RQU , PRP VBD ."
Eichstaedt said both the UN and the Sudan government should be very concerned about what happened last week .,B-per O O O B-org O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD DT DT NNP CC DT JJ NN MD VB RB JJ IN WP VBD JJ NN .
