"South African Nobel Peace laureate , Archbishop Desmond Tutu , has accused world leaders of ignoring continued oppression in Burma .",B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP NN , NNP NNP NNP , VBZ VBN NN NNS IN VBG JJ NN IN NNP ."
"In an opinion piece published in Thursday 's International Herald Tribune , Archbishop Tutu said Burma 's military government believes it can get away with human rights abuses because global pressure on Rangoon is weak .",O O O O O O B-tim O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,"IN DT NN NN VBN IN NNP POS NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP VBD NNP POS JJ NN VBZ PRP MD VB RB IN JJ NNS NNS IN JJ NN IN NNP VBZ JJ ."
He said the global words of protest against Burma must translate into action .,O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,PRP VBD DT JJ NNS IN NN IN NNP MD VB IN NN .
"Archbishop Tutu said Burmese pro-democracy advocates want what he called the "" maximum diplomatic and economic pressures "" applied against Burma 's military government .",B-org I-org O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,NNP NNP VBD JJ JJ NNS VBP WP PRP VBD DT LQU JJ JJ CC JJ NNS LQU VBN IN NNP POS JJ NN .
"His message comes ahead of the upcoming Asia-Europe Meeting in Vietnam , which is being attended by a low-level delegation from Burma .",O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"PRP$ NN VBZ RB IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP , WDT VBZ VBG VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
