"Albania 's opposition Socialist Party says it wants the country to investigate how thousands of foreigners , including suspected associates of Osama bin Laden , were granted Albanian citizenship .",B-geo O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O B-gpe O O,"NNP POS NN NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ DT NN TO VB WRB NNS IN NNS , VBG JJ NNS IN NNP NNP NNP , VBD VBN JJ NN ."
Socialist officials say they will ask Albanian President Alfred Moisiu to review all grants of citizenship to foreigners between 1992 and 1997 .,O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,JJ NNS VBP PRP MD VB JJ NNP NNP NNP TO VB DT NNS IN NN TO NNS IN CD CC CD .
The development comes one day after the U.S. Treasury Department moved to financially isolate a man with dual Jordanian and Albanian citizenship on suspicion of cooperating with Osama bin Laden and other terrorist leaders .,O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O,DT NN VBZ CD NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP VBD TO RB VB DT NN IN JJ JJ CC JJ NN IN NN IN VBG IN NNP NNP NNP CC JJ JJ NNS .
The Treasury says Abdul Latif Saleh founded a group aimed at destabilizing Albania by fomenting conflict among the country 's religious groups .,O B-org O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP VBZ NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN VBN IN VBG NNP IN VBG NN IN DT NN POS JJ NNS .
It says he has been expelled from Albania and was last known to reside in the United Arab Emirates .,O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,PRP VBZ PRP VBZ VBN VBN IN NNP CC VBD JJ VBN TO VB IN DT NNP NNP NNPS .
