The International Monetary Fund ( IMF ) is expected to warn that the Organization of Oil Exporting Countries ( OPEC ) and oil companies are not investing enough in new oil production and refining .,O B-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP RRB VBZ VBN TO VB IN DT NNP IN NNP NNP NNPS LRB NNP RRB CC NN NNS VBP RB VBG RB IN JJ NN NN CC NN .
"In a front page story , The Financial Times newspaper says the warning is part of an IMF report to be published later this week .",O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O B-tim O O O,"IN DT JJ NN NN , DT NNP NNP NN VBZ DT NN VBZ NN IN DT NNP NN TO VB VBN RB DT NN ."
"According to the article , without more investment , production capacity is not likely grow enough to outpace future growth in consumption and create adequate spare capacity .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"VBG TO DT NN , IN RBR NN , NN NN VBZ RB JJ VB RB TO VB JJ NN IN NN CC VB JJ JJ NN ."
An IMF spokesman would not comment on the article .,O B-org O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN MD RB VB IN DT NN .
Another news report ( from the Associated Press ) says France will urge the United States and other wealthy nations to boost investments in oil refining and alternative energy .,O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN NN LRB IN DT NNP NNP RRB VBZ NNP MD VB DT NNP NNPS CC JJ JJ NNS TO VB NNS IN NN NN CC NN NN .
The Bloomberg financial news service also reports that top EU and OPEC officials have agreed to meet in November to discuss investments in energy production .,B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-org O B-org O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O,DT NNP JJ NN NN RB VBZ IN JJ NNP CC NNP NNS VBP VBN TO VB IN NNP TO VB NNS IN NN NN .
