"A court in Yemen 's capital , Sana'a , has sentenced six Somali pirates to death and six more to 10 years in jail for hijacking a Yemeni ship .",O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"DT NN IN NNP POS NN , NNP , VBZ VBN CD JJ NNS TO NN CC CD JJR TO CD NNS IN NN IN VBG DT JJ NN ."
The verdict on Tuesday convicts the 12 Somalis of killing two crew members and wounding four others while trying to seize the oil tanker off the coast of the seaport city of Aden .,O O O B-tim O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NN IN NNP VBZ DT CD NNS IN VBG CD NN NNS CC VBG CD NNS IN VBG TO VB DT NN NN IN DT NN IN DT NN NN IN NNP .
The incident occurred in April last year .,O O O O B-tim O O O,DT NN VBD IN NNP JJ NN .
"Piracy is a major problem off the coast of Somalia , where gangs of pirates have hijacked dozens of ships in the past few years .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O,"NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN NNP , WRB NNS IN NNS VBP VBN NNS IN NNS IN DT JJ JJ NNS ."
International naval patrols have largely not been able to stop the attacks .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP JJ NNS VBP RB RB VBN JJ TO VB DT NNS .
"Furthermore , many captured pirates have been released because no country would prosecute them .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , JJ VBN NNS VBP VBN VBN IN DT NN MD VB PRP ."
Kenya has conducted some pirate trials but recently said its justice system is overburdened .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN DT NN NNS CC RB VBD PRP$ NN NN VBZ VBN .
