Pakistani President Pervez Musharraf says the Muslim world must correct Western misperceptions created by clerics about Islam as a religion that fosters militant extremism .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O B-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT NNP NN MD VB JJ NNS VBN IN NNS IN NNP IN DT NN WDT VBZ JJ NN .
He told a meeting of the World Islamic Economic Forum in Islamabad the rise in extremism in the Muslim world has been caused by semi-literate clerics who hold sway over the masses .,O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-geo O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP IN NNP DT NN IN NN IN DT NNP NN VBZ VBN VBN IN JJ NNS WP VBP NN IN DT NNS .
He said this is the critical malaise that spawns terrorism .,O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT VBZ DT JJ NN WDT VBZ NN .
"In a wide-ranging speech , General Musharraf painted a bleak picture of the social and economic prospects facing the world 's 57 Muslim nations , pointing out that their combined gross national products were less than that of a single European nation , Germany .",O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"IN DT JJ NN , NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN DT JJ CC JJ NNS VBG DT NN POS CD NNP NNS , VBG RP IN PRP$ JJ JJ JJ NNS VBD JJR IN DT IN DT JJ JJ NN , NNP ."
"He also urged Muslim nations to fight corruption , set up good governance and empower women in order to achieve economic development .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP RB VBD NNP NNS TO VB NN , VBD RP JJ NN CC NN NNS IN NN TO VB JJ NN ."
