Pakistan 's President Pervez Musharraf has urged the nation 's lawyers to help ease the political crisis triggered by his removal of the country 's top judge .,B-geo O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN POS NNS TO VB VB DT JJ NN VBN IN PRP$ NN IN DT NN POS JJ NN .
"General Musharraf made the comment Friday in Islamabad , at a military parade held to mark the annual Pakistan Day holiday .",B-per I-per O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim I-tim O,"NNP NNP VBD DT NN NNP IN NNP , IN DT JJ NN VBN TO VB DT JJ NNP NNP NN ."
He also urged Pakistanis to help fight extremism and terrorism in their country .,O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,PRP RB VBD NNS TO VB VB NN CC NN IN PRP$ NN .
"Lawyers and opposition parties have held nationwide protests for the past two weeks , since General Musharraf removed the country 's chief justice , Iftikhar Muhammad Chaudhry .",O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O,"NNS CC NN NNS VBP VBN JJ NNS IN DT JJ CD NNS , IN NNP NNP VBD DT NN POS NN NN , NNP NNP NNP ."
Several legal professionals in Pakistan have resigned in protest of Chaudhry 's removal .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-per O O O,JJ JJ NNS IN NNP VBP VBN IN NN IN NNP POS NN .
Chaudhry 's supporters say the independent-minded justice was removed because of pending legal challenges related to General Musharraf 's dual posts as president and army chief of staff .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NNS VBP DT JJ NN VBD VBN IN IN VBG JJ NNS VBN TO NNP NNP POS JJ NNS IN NN CC NN NN IN NN .
