Hundreds of Koreans Monday have seen long-lost relatives for the first time in more than 50 years through a video link between divided North and South Korea .,O O B-gpe B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O,NNS IN NNS NNP VBP VBN JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN IN JJR IN CD NNS IN DT NN NN IN VBN NNP CC NNP NNP .
Eighty families are participating in the virtual reunions Monday and Tuesday .,O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-tim O,CD NNS VBP VBG IN DT JJ NNS NNP CC NNP .
The Associated Press reports that each family is given two hours to see and talk to relatives on the other side of the border .,B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNS IN DT NN VBZ VBN CD NNS TO VB CC VB TO NNS IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN .
"Millions of Korean families were separated following the division of the Korean Peninsula after the end of World War Two in 1945 , and again with the sealing of the border at the end of the Korean War in 1953 .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-org O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-gpe B-tim I-tim I-tim O,"NNS IN JJ NNS VBD VBN VBG DT NN IN DT JJ NNP IN DT NN IN NNP NNP CD IN CD , CC RB IN DT NN IN DT NN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NNP IN CD ."
"There is no direct mail , telephone service or other form of communication between ordinary citizens across the border .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"EX VBZ DT JJ NN , NN NN CC JJ NN IN NN IN JJ NNS IN DT NN ."
