"One day after hearing grievances from American troops in Kuwait heading to Iraq , U.S. Secretary of Defense Donald Rumsfeld has reacted positively , saying it is the job of officials to listen and act .",O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O B-geo O B-geo O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"CD NN IN VBG NNS IN JJ NNS IN NNP VBG TO NNP , NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN RB , VBG PRP VBZ DT NN IN NNS TO VB CC VB ."
"Mr. Rumsfeld , who was in India Thursday , said the questions by the troops covered a wide spectrum and that only a few were difficult .",B-per I-per O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP , WP VBD IN NNP NNP , VBD DT NNS IN DT NNS VBD DT JJ NN CC IN RB DT NN VBD JJ ."
"Others complained about deployments being extended , even though they were eligible to leave the military .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBD IN NNS VBG VBN , RB IN PRP VBD JJ TO VB DT NN ."
"At the White House , President Bush said the concerns of the troops are being addressed .",O O B-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NNP NNP , NNP NNP VBD DT NNS IN DT NNS VBP VBG VBN ."
"He said he did not blame the soldiers for raising the issue , saying he would have asked Mr. Rumsfeld the same question if he was a soldier fighting overseas .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD PRP VBD RB VB DT NNS IN VBG DT NN , VBG PRP MD VB VBN NNP NNP DT JJ NN IN PRP VBD DT NN VBG RB ."
