"A suspected al-Qaida terrorist facing charges in a 2002 grenade attack in Afghanistan has appeared before a military tribunal at the U.S. naval base at Guantanamo Bay , Cuba .",O O B-org O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O,"DT JJ NNP NN VBG NNS IN DT CD NN NN IN NNP VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP JJ NN IN NNP NNP , NNP ."
Afghan Abdul Zahir is accused of hurling a grenade at a car carrying three journalists .,B-gpe B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN VBG DT NN IN DT NN VBG CD NNS .
"A Toronto Star correspondent in the vehicle , Kathleen Kenna , suffered leg injuries in the attack .",O B-org I-org O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP NN IN DT NN , NNP NNP , VBD NN NNS IN DT NN ."
"Zahir , who also faces charges of conspiracy and aiding the enemy , did not enter a plea .",B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP , WP RB VBZ NNS IN NN CC VBG DT NN , VBD RB VB DT NN ."
Prosecutors allege Zahir aided the enemy by working as a translator and money courier for the al-Qaida terrorist network and by plotting attacks .,O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,NNS VBP NNP VBD DT NN IN VBG IN DT NN CC NN NN IN DT NNP NN NN CC IN VBG NNS .
Proceedings were also scheduled this week for three other Guantanamo detainees .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,NNS VBD RB VBN DT NN IN CD JJ NNP NNS .
Canadian teenager Omar Khadr is accused of throwing a grenade that killed a U.S. soldier in Afghanistan .,B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O,JJ NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN VBG DT NN WDT VBD DT NNP NN IN NNP .
"Ethiopian Binyam Muhammad stands accused of plotting attacks , and Yemeni Ali Hamza al Bahlul is linked to al-Qaida .",B-gpe B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O B-org O,"JJ NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN VBG NNS , CC JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO NNP ."
"So far , only 10 of the nearly 500 Guantanamo prisoners have been charged .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,"RB RB , RB CD IN DT RB CD NNP NNS VBP VBN VBN ."
"Last week , the U.S. Supreme Court heard arguments in a landmark case challenging the legality of military tribunals established by the Bush administration in the aftermath of the September 11 , 2001 terrorist attacks .",O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O,"JJ NN , DT NNP NNP NNP VBD NNS IN DT NN NN VBG DT NN IN JJ NNS VBN IN DT NNP NN IN DT NN IN DT NNP CD , CD JJ NNS ."
