Iranian university students demonstrated Wednesday in support of their government 's pursuit of nuclear technology .,B-gpe O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN NNS VBD NNP IN NN IN PRP$ NN POS NN IN JJ NN .
The students formed a human chain around the Natanz nuclear facility in central Iran and chanted slogans against the International Atomic Energy Agency .,O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,DT NNS VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NNP JJ NN IN JJ NNP CC VBD NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP .
"Last Thursday , the IAEA angered Iran when its board of governors passed a resolution expressing serious concern at Tehran 's decision to end a voluntary suspension of uranium enrichment .",O B-tim O O B-org O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP , DT NNP VBD NNP WRB PRP$ NN IN NNS VBD DT NN VBG JJ NN IN NNP POS NN TO VB DT JJ NN IN NN NN ."
"The Natanz facility is still closed , but last week , the uranium conversion plant at Isfahan resumed operations .",O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,"DT NNP NN VBZ RB JJ , CC JJ NN , DT NN NN NN IN NNP VBD NNS ."
"On Tuesday , hundreds of Iranians demonstrated outside that site , demanding their government continue its controversial nuclear program .",O B-tim O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , NNS IN NNS VBD IN DT NN , VBG PRP$ NN VB PRP$ JJ JJ NN ."
"The European Union has been in ongoing talks with Iran , trying to persuade the Iranians to permanently end their enrichment activities in exchange for a series of political and economic incentives .",O B-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN JJ NNS IN NNP , VBG TO VB DT NNS TO RB VB PRP$ NN NNS IN NN IN DT NN IN JJ CC JJ NNS ."
