An Amsterdam court has opened pre-trial hearings into the case of a Dutch-Moroccan man suspected in last year 's murder of prominent filmmaker Theo van Gogh .,O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O,DT NNP NN VBZ VBN JJ NNS IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN VBN IN JJ NN POS NN IN JJ NN NNP NNP NNP .
"The accused , Mohammed Bouyeri , was not present in court for the hearing .",O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,"DT VBN , NNP NNP , VBD RB JJ IN NN IN DT NN ."
"Prosecutors say he shot the filmmaker several times last November while he was bicycling to work in Amsterdam , stabbed him , then left a letter pinned to his body with a knife .",O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP PRP VBD DT NN JJ NNS JJ NNP IN PRP VBD VBG TO VB IN NNP , VBD PRP , RB VBD DT NN VBN TO PRP$ NN IN DT NN ."
They believe the attack was a response to the filmmaker 's criticism of Islam and its treatment of women .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,PRP VBP DT NN VBD DT NN TO DT NN POS NN IN NNP CC PRP$ NN IN NNS .
"The defendant is also charged with attempted murder , terrorism and threatening a politician .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ RB VBN IN JJ NN , NN CC VBG DT NN ."
Some of the charges involve the accused 's threats against Somali-born Dutch lawmaker Ayaan Hirsi Ali who wrote the script for Mr. van Gogh 's film .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O,DT IN DT NNS VBP DT VBN POS NNS IN JJ JJ NN NNP NNP NNP WP VBD DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP POS NN .
"The van Gogh murder sparked sectarian attacks against mosques , religious schools and churches in the Netherlands .",O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NNP NNP NN VBD JJ NNS IN NNS , JJ NNS CC NNS IN DT NNP ."
