Officials in Sri Lanka say a ferry carrying more than 150 foreign nationals and aid workers from the troubled northern Jaffna Peninsula has arrived at an eastern port .,O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNP NNP VBP DT NN VBG JJR IN CD JJ NNS CC NN NNS IN DT JJ JJ NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NN .
"The ferry , flying an International Committee of the Red Cross flag , docked at Trincomalee early Sunday .",O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-org I-org O O O O B-geo O B-tim O,"DT NN , VBG DT NNP NNP IN DT NNP NNP NN , VBD IN NNP RB NNP ."
It is one of several ferries planned to evacuate foreign passport holders from the war-torn region .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ CD IN JJ NNS VBN TO VB JJ NN NNS IN DT JJ NN .
"As the vessel pulled into port , artillery fire could be heard in the distance .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN VBD IN NN , NN NN MD VB VBN IN DT NN ."
"Many foreign aid agencies have been forced to stop work and pull staff out of Jaffna until it becomes clear whether a 2002 ceasefire will hold , or Sri Lanka returns to civil war .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O,"JJ JJ NN NNS VBP VBN VBN TO VB NN CC VB NN IN IN NNP IN PRP VBZ JJ IN DT CD NN MD VB , CC NNP NNP NNS TO JJ NN ."
The United Nations says intense fighting in the north and east between Tamil rebels and government forces has forced more than 200-thousand people from their homes .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ JJ NN IN DT NN CC NN IN NNP NNS CC NN NNS VBZ VBN JJR IN JJ NNS IN PRP$ NNS .
"More than two decades of fighting has killed 65,000 people in Sri Lanka .",B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,JJR IN CD NNS IN NN VBZ VBN CD NNS IN NNP NNP .
