Benin has postponed its presidential run-off election to Wednesday to give election officials more time to prepare .,B-org O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN PRP$ JJ NN NN TO NNP TO VB NN NNS JJR NN TO VB .
"The West African nation 's constitutional court Friday announced it had delayed the election , originally set for Sunday , by three days .",O O B-gpe O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-tim O O,"DT JJ JJ NN POS JJ NN NNP VBD PRP VBD VBN DT NN , RB VBN IN NNP , IN CD NNS ."
The decision upholds a motion by the National Elections Commission calling for a postponement .,O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O,DT NN VBZ DT NN IN DT NNP NNPS NNP VBG IN DT NN .
Political newcomer Yayi Boni won the first round of polls with 36 percent of the vote .,O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN NNS IN CD NN IN DT NN .
"The former head of the West African Development Bank will face off against former speaker of parliament Adrien Houngbedji , who took 24 percent in the initial balloting .",O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP MD VB RP IN JJ NN IN NN NNP NNP , WP VBD CD NN IN DT JJ NN ."
The two candidates are each trying to win endorsement from the 24 candidates who finished behind them .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT CD NNS VBP DT VBG TO VB NN IN DT CD NNS WP VBD IN PRP .
The winner will replace outgoing president Mathieu Kerekou .,O O O O O O B-per I-per O,DT NN MD VB JJ NN NNP NNP .
"President Kerekou , who is 72 , is barred by constitutional term limits , as well as an age cap , from seeking re-election .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP , WP VBZ CD , VBZ VBN IN JJ NN NNS , RB RB IN DT NN NN , IN VBG NN ."
