Kenyan Prime Minister Raila Odinga has taken the oath of office as part of a new power-sharing Cabinet formed after a deadly post-election crisis .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN NN IN NN IN DT JJ NN NNP VBD IN DT JJ NN NN .
Mr. Odinga was sworn in Thursday in front of President Mwai Kibaki and former United Nations Secretary-General Kofi Annan .,B-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O B-per I-per I-per O O B-org I-org I-org B-per I-per O,NNP NNP VBD VBN IN NNP IN NN IN NNP NNP NNP CC JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP .
"Mr. Annan brokered the agreement between Mr. Kibaki and Mr. Odinga , and has urged Kenyans to support the newly-appointed coalition government .",B-per I-per O O O O B-per I-per O B-per B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN NNP NNP CC NNP NNP , CC VBZ VBN NNS TO VB DT JJ NN NN ."
"The new minister for medical services Peter Anyang Nyongo tells VOA the Cabinet has already begun working together to help the country recover from the post-election crisis , particularly the problem of internally displaced people .",O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O B-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNP DT NNP VBZ RB VBN VBG RB TO VB DT NN VB IN DT JJ NN , RB DT NN IN RB JJ NNS ."
President Kibaki announced the power-sharing Cabinet Sunday .,B-per I-per O O O B-org B-tim O,NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NNP NNP .
"The move ended a deadlock that threatened to re-ignite weeks of deadly violence triggered by a dispute over December 's presidential vote , which the opposition says was rigged .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD DT NN WDT VBD TO VB NNS IN JJ NN VBN IN DT NN IN NNP POS JJ NN , WDT DT NN VBZ VBD VBN ."
