Thailand 's military-backed interim prime minister Surayud Chulanont is in Indonesia to meet with President Susilo Bambang Yudhoyono .,B-geo O O O O O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O B-per O B-per I-per O,NNP POS JJ JJ JJ NN NNP NNP VBZ IN NNP TO VB IN NNP NNP NNP NNP .
Mr. Surayud 's visit Saturday is the latest in a flurry of introductory diplomatic trips to Thailand 's neighbors following last month 's coup .,B-per I-per O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP POS NN NNP VBZ DT JJS IN DT NN IN JJ JJ NNS TO NNP POS NNS VBG JJ NN POS NN .
"The Thai interim prime minister has visited Malaysia , Laos and Cambodia and is scheduled to meet leaders in the Philippines and Vietnam next week .",O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O,"DT JJ JJ JJ NN VBZ VBN NNP , NNP CC NNP CC VBZ VBN TO VB NNS IN DT NNPS CC NNP JJ NN ."
"Mr. Surayud , a former army general , was appointed by a Thai military council that ousted former prime minister Thaksin Shinawatra in September .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-per I-per O B-tim O,"NNP NNP , DT JJ NN NN , VBD VBN IN DT JJ JJ NN WDT VBD JJ JJ NN NNP NNP IN NNP ."
