The commander of U.S. military forces in South Korea says Washington and Seoul can defeat any North Korean attack .,O O O B-geo O O O B-org I-org O B-geo O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O,DT NN IN NNP JJ NNS IN NNP NNP VBZ NNP CC NNP MD VB DT JJ JJ NN .
"In a radio interview Wednesday , General Leon LaPorte says he believes Pyongyang has one or two nuclear weapons , but insists the combined U.S. and South Korean forces would win no matter how many nuclear weapons North Korea possesses .",O O O O B-tim O B-per I-per I-per O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O,"IN DT NN NN NNP , NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ NNP VBZ CD CC CD JJ NNS , CC VBZ DT JJ NNP CC JJ JJ NNS MD VB DT NN WRB JJ JJ NNS NNP NNP VBZ ."
North Korea declared earlier this year that it possessed nuclear weapons and would not return to disarmament talks .,B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD RBR DT NN IN PRP VBD JJ NNS CC MD RB VB TO NN NNS .
But Tuesday Russia 's Interfax news agency quoted an unnamed North Korean official as saying that the stalled negotiations could possibly resume in the second half of next month .,O B-tim B-geo O B-geo O O O O O B-geo B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O,CC NNP NNP POS NNP NN NN VBD DT JJ JJ JJ NN IN VBG IN DT VBN NNS MD RB VB IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NN .
"South Korea 's Unification Minister , Chung Dong-young , is to meet with senior U.S. officials about his recent meeting with North Korean leader Kim Jong-il later this week .",B-org I-org O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo B-gpe O B-per I-per B-tim O O O,"NNP NNP POS NNP NNP , NNP NNP , VBZ TO VB IN JJ NNP NNS IN PRP$ JJ NN IN JJ JJ NN NNP NNP RB DT NN ."
