Bosnia Herzegovina 's war crimes court has confirmed charges against three Bosnian Croats accused of war crimes against Muslim civilians during the Balkan conflict .,B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O B-gpe I-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,NNP NNP POS NN NNS NN VBZ VBN NNS IN CD JJ NNS VBN IN NN NNS IN NNP NNS IN DT NNP NN .
"In an official statement released Monday , the court confirmed charges against the three former Bosnian Croat soldiers .",O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-gpe I-gpe O O,"IN DT JJ NN VBN NNP , DT NN VBD NNS IN DT CD JJ JJ JJ NNS ."
