Iraq 's newly sworn-in presidential council has named Shi'ite politician Ibrahim al-Jaafari interim prime minister .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O,NNP POS RB JJ JJ NN VBZ VBN NNP NN NNP NNP JJ JJ NN .
"Mr. al-Jaafari , the head of the influential Islamic Dawa party , told a news conference the day represents a big step forward for Iraq .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP NNP , DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NNP NN , VBD DT NN NN DT NN VBZ DT JJ NN RB IN NNP ."
He also said he hopes to form a government within two weeks .,O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,PRP RB VBD PRP VBZ TO VB DT NN IN CD NNS .
Mr. al-Jaafari 's appointment followed Thursday 's historic swearing-in of Kurdish politician Jalal Talabani as Iraq 's first freely-elected president in more than 50 years .,B-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O O,NNP NNP POS NN VBD NNP POS JJ NN IN JJ NN NNP NNP IN NNP POS JJ JJ NN IN JJR IN CD NNS .
"In remarks to legislators gathered at the ceremony inside Baghdad 's heavily protected Green Zone , President Talabani urged Sunni Arabs - who are believed to make up the backbone of the insurgency - to participate in the democratic process .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O B-per I-per O B-per B-gpe B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNS TO NNS VBN IN DT NN IN NNP POS RB VBN NNP NNP , NNP NNP VBD NNP NNS : WP VBP VBN TO VB RP DT NN IN DT NN : TO VB IN DT JJ NN ."
Two vice presidents also took the oath of office .,O O O O O O O O O O,CD NN NNS RB VBD DT NN IN NN .
They are Shi'ite Adel Abdul Mahdi and Sunni Arab Ghazi al-Yawar .,O O O B-per I-per I-per O B-per I-per I-per I-per O,PRP VBP JJ NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP NNP .
