Some 200 students at the conservative Brigham Young University peacefully protested Wednesday against a planned appearance by U.S. Vice President Dick Cheney .,O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo B-per I-per I-per I-per O,DT CD NNS IN DT JJ NNP NNP NNP RB VBD NNP IN DT VBN NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP .
Cheney is scheduled to be the main speaker at the Utah university 's graduation ceremony April 26 .,B-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim I-tim O,NNP VBZ VBN TO VB DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NN POS NN NN NNP CD .
"The protesters at the largely Mormon university complained about Cheney 's ties to the war in Iraq , among other issues .",O O O O O B-geo O O O B-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,"DT NNS IN DT RB NNP NN VBD IN NNP POS NNS TO DT NN IN NNP , IN JJ NNS ."
"Meanwhile , supporters of Cheney 's visit staged a counter-protest and circulated a petition thanking the vice president for his upcoming visit .",O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O,"RB , NNS IN NNP POS NN VBD DT NN CC VBD DT NN VBG DT NN NN IN PRP$ JJ NN ."
"Tuesday night , just over a dozen students at American University in Washington , D.C. protested an appearance by presidential aide Karl Rove .",B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O B-per I-per O,"NNP NN , RB IN DT NN NNS IN NNP NNP IN NNP , NNP VBD DT NN IN JJ NN NNP NNP ."
Officials said the students threw objects at Rove and tried to lie down in front of his car .,O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBD DT NNS VBD NNS IN NNP CC VBD TO VB RP IN NN IN PRP$ NN .
He was emerging from an invitation-only speaking engagement for the school 's College Republicans .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD VBG IN DT JJ NN NN IN DT NN POS NNP NNPS .
