"China is asking other nations to help it find and return foreign investors who flee the country , leaving behind empty factories and massive debts .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBG JJ NNS TO VB PRP VB CC VB JJ NNS WP VBP DT NN , VBG IN JJ NNS CC JJ NNS ."
"The state run Xinhua news agency says in eastern Shandong province alone , at least 87 companies funded by South Korean investors left this year without properly liquidating assets .",O O O B-org O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBN NNP NN NN VBZ IN JJ NNP NN RB , IN JJS CD NNS VBN IN JJ JJ NNS VBD DT NN IN RB VBG NNS ."
It says China will seek extradition of fugitive investors in cases where large sums of money are involved .,O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ NNP MD VB NN IN JJ NNS IN NNS WRB JJ NNS IN NN VBP VBN .
The global economic downturn has hit Chinese manufacturing and export industries especially hard as demand declines for Chinese products .,O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT JJ JJ NN VBZ VBN JJ NN CC NN NNS RB JJ IN NN NNS IN JJ NNS .
Thousands of factories have closed across the country and Chinese media reports millions of migrant workers have left factory jobs to return to the countryside .,O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNS VBP VBN IN DT NN CC JJ NNS VBZ NNS IN JJ NNS VBP VBN NN NNS TO VB TO DT NN .
