Gunmen in Iraq kidnapped a Catholic archbishop Monday and insurgents hit security forces in a series of attacks that killed at least 20 people .,O O B-geo O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNP VBD DT JJ NN NNP CC NNS VBD NN NNS IN DT NN IN NNS WDT VBD IN JJS CD NNS .
"The Vatican called the kidnapping of the Syrian Catholic Church 's Mosul archbishop , Basile Georges Casmoussa , a terrorist act .",O O O O O O O B-gpe B-org I-org O B-org O O B-per I-per B-org O O O O O,"DT NNP VBD DT NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP POS NNP NN , NNP NNP NNP , DT JJ NN ."
"Meanwhile , an attack on a checkpoint near Baquba killed seven Iraqi guardsmen and a civilian .",O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O O O,"RB , DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP VBD CD JJ NNS CC DT JJ ."
Terrorists loyal to al-Qaida-linked Abu Musab al-Zarqawi claimed responsibility .,O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O,NNS JJ TO JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD NN .
"Later , a car bomb outside a police station in Baiji killed at least seven Iraqi officers .",B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O,"RB , DT NN NN IN DT NN NN IN NNP VBD IN JJS CD JJ NNS ."
"Insurgents also attacked police in Sharqat and Dour , killing one officer in each city .",O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"NNS RB VBD NNS IN NNP CC NNP , VBG CD NN IN DT NN ."
"Near Fallujah , two U.S. soldiers were killed in action .",B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O,"NNP NNP , CD NNP NNS VBD VBN IN NN ."
No other details were released .,O O O O O O,DT JJ NNS VBD VBN .
"And in Basra , gunmen killed a security guard at a polling place for January 30th 's elections .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O,"CC IN NNP , NNS VBD DT NN NN IN DT VBG NN IN NNP NNP POS NNS ."
U.S. forces have detained 91 suspected insurgents since Saturday as they step up security for the vote .,B-geo O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBP VBN CD JJ NNS IN NNP IN PRP VBP RB NN IN DT NN .
