President Bush has returned to Washington after a five-day trip to Europe designed to mend ties damaged by the Iraq war .,B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO NNP IN DT JJ NN TO NNP VBN TO VB NNS VBN IN DT NNP NN .
"Mr. Bush is spending the day Friday resting up from the trip , and has no public events on his schedule .",B-per I-per O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBG DT NN NNP VBG RP IN DT NN , CC VBZ DT JJ NNS IN PRP$ NN ."
"His final stop was in Slovakia , where he raised concerns about Moscow 's commitment to democracy during talks with Russian President Vladimir Putin .",O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O,"PRP$ JJ NN VBD IN NNP , WRB PRP VBD NNS IN NNP POS NN TO NN IN NNS IN JJ NNP NNP NNP ."
"Mr. Putin strongly rejected any suggestion that his country was turning away from democratic rule , saying "" there can be no return to what we had before . """,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP RB VBD DT NN IN PRP$ NN VBD VBG RB IN JJ NN , VBG LQU EX MD VB DT NN TO WP PRP VBD IN . LQU"
"During his three-nation tour , President Bush won a pledge from European Union and NATO members to assist with the reconstruction of Iraq .",O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O O B-geo O,"IN PRP$ JJ NN , NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN NNP NNP CC NNP NNS TO VB IN DT NN IN NNP ."
"But some issues remain unresolved , such as Europe 's desire to lift an embargo on selling arms to China , which is opposed by the United States .",O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"CC DT NNS VBP JJ , JJ IN NNP POS NN TO VB DT NN IN VBG NNS TO NNP , WDT VBZ VBN IN DT NNP NNPS ."
