Anti-Bush demonstration in the center of Amsterdam,O O O O O O B-geo,JJ NN IN DT NN IN NNP
"Around 1,000 people , protesting the U.S.-led war in Iraq , have demonstrated in Amsterdam ahead of President Bush 's arrival in the Netherlands .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O B-per I-per O O O B-geo I-geo O,"IN CD NNS , VBG DT JJ NN IN NNP , VBP VBN IN NNP RB IN NNP NNP POS NN IN DT NNP ."
The protesters gathered on Museum Square outside the U.S. consulate carrying signs with slogans criticizing Mr. Bush 's Iraq policy .,O O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O O B-per I-per O B-geo O O,DT NNS VBD IN NNP NNP IN DT NNP NN VBG NNS IN NNS VBG NNP NNP POS NNP NN .
"Meanwhile , as many as 100 others demonstrated in Maastricht in the southern Netherlands , where Mr. Bush arrived Saturday evening .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O B-per I-per O B-tim I-tim O,"RB , RB JJ IN CD NNS VBD IN NNP IN DT JJ NNP , WRB NNP NNP VBD NNP NN ."
