The World Food Program says it has flown its final aid flight to Burma 's cyclone-ravaged Irrawaddy Delta .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ VBN PRP$ JJ NN NN TO NNP POS JJ NNP NNP .
A statement from the group says the flight took off Friday from Bangkok 's Don Mueang airport .,O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O B-per I-per O O,DT NN IN DT NN VBZ DT NN VBD RP NNP IN NNP POS NNP NNP NN .
"The airport has served as a staging point for sending supplies to Burma since the country 's military-rulers first allowed foreign aid flights in late May , weeks after the storm hit .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ VBN IN DT NN NN IN VBG NNS TO NNP IN DT NN POS NNS JJ VBN JJ NN NNS IN JJ NNP , NNS IN DT NN NN ."
"Cyclone Nargis hit Burma on May 2 and 3 , leaving at least 134,000 people dead or missing as it tore across the country 's agricultural belt .",B-eve I-eve O B-geo O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD NNP IN NNP CD CC CD , VBG IN JJS CD NNS JJ CC JJ IN PRP VBD IN DT NN POS JJ NN ."
"The WFP says that since its flights began on May 24 , it has flown nearly 4,000 tons of cargo to Burma , including shelter material , mosquito nets and water purification equipment .",O B-org O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP VBZ IN IN PRP$ NNS VBD IN NNP CD , PRP VBZ VBN RB CD NNS IN NN TO NNP , VBG NN NN , NN NNS CC NN NN NN ."
