"Ethiopia 's poverty-stricken economy is based on agriculture , accounting for almost 45 % of GDP , and 85 % of total employment .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ NN VBZ VBN IN NN , NN IN RB CD NN IN NN , CC CD NN IN JJ NN ."
The agricultural sector suffers from frequent drought and poor cultivation practices .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN NNS IN JJ NN CC JJ NN NNS .
"Coffee is critical to the Ethiopian economy with exports of some $ 350 million in 2006 , but historically low prices have seen many farmers switching to qat to supplement income .",O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ JJ TO DT JJ NN IN NNS IN DT $ CD CD IN CD , CC RB JJ NNS VBP VBN JJ NNS VBG TO VB TO VB NN ."
"Under Ethiopia 's constitution , the state owns all land and provides long-term leases to the tenants ; the system continues to hamper growth in the industrial sector as entrepreneurs are unable to use land as collateral for loans .",O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP POS NN , DT NN VBZ DT NN CC VBZ JJ NNS TO DT NNS ; DT NN VBZ TO VB NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNS VBP JJ TO VB NN IN NN IN NNS ."
"The global economic downturn led to balance of payments pressures , partially alleviated by recent emergency funding from the IMF .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,"DT JJ JJ NN VBD TO NN IN NNS NNS , RB VBN IN JJ NN NN IN DT NNP ."
"While GDP growth has remained high , per capita income is among the lowest in the world .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NN NN VBZ VBN JJ , IN NN NN VBZ IN DT JJS IN DT NN ."
