Iceland is defying an international ban and opened its commercial whale hunting season on Tuesday .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP VBZ VBG DT JJ NN CC VBD PRP$ JJ NN NN NN IN NNP .
Fishing Ministry officials say they have given whalers permission to hunt a limit of 40 minke whales for meat over the next six months .,B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,NNP NNP NNS VBP PRP VBP VBN NNS NN TO VB DT NN IN CD JJ NNS IN NN IN DT JJ CD NNS .
Many in Iceland defend whaling as a centuries-old tradition .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O,JJ IN NNP VBP VBG IN DT JJ NN .
They say whalers will be careful not to kill endangered species .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBP NNS MD VB JJ RB TO VB JJ NNS .
"But some , including members of the Social Democratic Alliance , the junior partner in the ruling coalition government , say whaling damages Iceland 's reputation abroad .",O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"CC DT , VBG NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP , DT JJ NN IN DT NN NN NN , VBP VBG NNS NNP POS NN RB ."
They also say it drives away tourists who want to see the mammals in their natural surroundings .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP RB VBP PRP VBZ RB NNS WP VBP TO VB DT NNS IN PRP$ JJ NNS .
Environmentalists decry whaling for commercial and scientific purposes .,O O O O O O O O O,NNS JJ NN IN JJ CC JJ NNS .
The International Whaling Commission banned commercial whale hunts in 1986 to preserve the dwindling population .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBD JJ NN NNS IN CD TO VB DT VBG NN .
Iceland began defying the ban two years ago .,B-gpe O O O O B-tim O O O,NNP VBD VBG DT NN CD NNS RB .
Japan and Norway also want the ban lifted .,B-gpe O B-gpe O O O O O O,NNP CC NNP RB VBP DT NN VBD .
