"The Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts is home to many of New York 's most famous artistic organizations including the Metropolitan Opera , New York Philharmonic and the New York City Ballet .",O B-org I-org O O B-org I-org O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O,"DT NNP NNP IN DT NNP NNP VBZ NN TO NN IN NNP NNP POS JJS JJ JJ NNS VBG DT NNP NNP , NNP NNP NNP CC DT NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
"Right now ( through July 27 ) the entertainment venue is hosting its annual Lincoln Center Festival , three weeks of special performances from around the world .",O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB RB LRB IN NNP CD RRB DT NN NN VBZ VBG PRP$ JJ NNP NNP NNP , CD NNS IN JJ NNS IN IN DT NN ."
