"A MEMBER of the Kansas Legislature meeting a Cake of Soap was passing it by without recognition , but the Cake of Soap insisted on stopping and shaking hands .",O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN DT NNP NNP VBG DT NNP IN NNP VBD VBG PRP IN IN NN , CC DT NNP IN NNP VBD IN NN CC VBG NNS ."
"Thinking it might possibly be in the enjoyment of the elective franchise , he gave it a cordial and earnest grasp .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"VBG PRP MD RB VB IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN , PRP VBD PRP DT JJ CC JJ NN ."
"On letting it go he observed that a portion of it adhered to his fingers , and running to a brook in great alarm he proceeded to wash it off .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN VBG PRP VB PRP VBD IN DT NN IN PRP VBD TO PRP$ NNS , CC VBG TO DT NN IN JJ NN PRP VBD TO VB PRP RP ."
"In doing so he necessarily got some on the other hand , and when he had finished washing , both were so white that he went to bed and sent for a physician .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN VBG RB PRP RB VBD DT IN DT JJ NN , CC WRB PRP VBD VBN VBG , DT VBD RB JJ IN PRP VBD TO NN CC VBD IN DT NN ."
