"South African President Jacob Zuma says the country has made "" good returns "" on the estimated $ 4.2 billion it spent to host the World Cup .",O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,JJ JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT NN VBZ VBN LQU JJ NNS LQU IN DT VBN $ CD CD PRP VBD TO VB DT NNP NNP .
"Speaking to a group of investors in Cape Town Tuesday , Mr. Zuma said the building of stadiums created 66,000 new construction jobs , and that security improvements added 40,000 new , permanent police positions .",O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim I-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"VBG TO DT NN IN NNS IN NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN NNS VBN CD JJ NN NNS , CC IN NN NNS VBD CD JJ , JJ NN NNS ."
"He said hosting the tournament has also produced social benefits , such as creating unity among South Africans and improving the country 's image as a tourist destination .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD VBG DT NN VBZ RB VBN JJ NNS , JJ IN VBG NN IN NNP NNS CC VBG DT NN POS NN IN DT NN NN ."
"Mr. Zuma said the government chose to bid for the World Cup because it "" wanted to show that Africa could do it . """,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD DT NN VBD TO VB IN DT NNP NNP IN PRP RQU VBD TO VB IN NNP MD VB PRP . LQU
"This is the first time any African nation has hosted the World Cup , one of the world 's biggest sporting events .",O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O,"DT VBZ DT JJ NN DT JJ NN VBZ VBN DT NNP NNP , CD IN DT NN POS JJS VBG NNS ."
The monthlong tournament ends on Sunday .,O O O O O B-tim O,DT JJ NN VBZ IN NNP .
