The mothers of three American hikers detained in Iran are pleading for them to be freed before this month 's one year anniversary of their arrest .,O O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim O O O O,DT NNS IN CD JJ NNS VBN IN NNP VBP VBG IN PRP TO VB VBN IN DT NN POS CD NN NN IN PRP$ NN .
"The mothers said Thursday they have sent a letter to the head of Iran 's judiciary calling for their children to be released from , as they put it , "" their unjust and arbitrary detention "" before the July 31 anniversary of their capture .",O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O,"DT NNS VBD NNP PRP VBP VBN DT NN TO DT NN IN NNP POS NN VBG IN PRP$ NNS TO VB VBN IN , IN PRP VBD PRP , LQU PRP$ JJ CC JJ NN LQU IN DT NNP CD NN IN PRP$ NN ."
"Iranian security forces arrested Shane Bauer , Sarah Shourd and Josh Fattal along the Iran-Iraq border last year .",B-gpe O O O B-per I-per O B-per I-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O,"JJ NN NNS VBN NNP NNP , NNP NNP CC NNP NNP IN DT NNP NN JJ NN ."
Family members say the trio may have accidentally strayed across the border into Iran .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NN NNS VBP DT NN MD VB RB VBN IN DT NN IN NNP .
"However , Iranian officials have accused the three of spying .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,"RB , JJ NNS VBP VBN DT CD IN VBG ."
