An Afghan peace delegation is traveling to Pakistan for talks on resolving the Afghan conflict .,O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT JJ NN NN VBZ VBG TO NNP IN NNS IN VBG DT JJ NN .
The delegation headed by former Afghan President Burhanuddin Rabbani is expected to hold talks with Pakistani President Asif Ali Zardari and other senior officials .,O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O,DT NN VBN IN JJ JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB NNS IN JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP CC JJ JJ NNS .
The discussions are expected to focus on efforts by the Afghan government to initiate negotiations with the Taliban .,O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-org O,DT NNS VBP VBN TO VB IN NNS IN DT JJ NN TO VB NNS IN DT NNP .
"Afghan President Hamid Karzai has called for reconciliation with members of the Taliban who renounce violence , but exploratory peace talks with the militant group have not resulted in any progress .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NN IN NNS IN DT NNP WP VBP NN , CC JJ NN NNS IN DT JJ NN VBP RB VBN IN DT NN ."
Recent talks brokered by NATO officials collapsed after it was revealed that a man claiming to be a Taliban representative was in fact an imposter who had been paid to attend meetings with Afghan officials .,O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,JJ NNS VBN IN NNP NNS VBD IN PRP VBD VBN IN DT NN VBG TO VB DT NNP NN VBD IN NN DT NN WP VBD VBN VBN TO VB NNS IN JJ NNS .
Pakistan backed the Taliban until 2001 .,B-geo O O B-org O B-tim O,NNP VBD DT NNP IN CD .
"Pakistani officials have admitted they maintain contact with some elements of the Taliban , but they say they do not support the insurgency in Afghanistan .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"JJ NNS VBP VBN PRP VBP NN IN DT NNS IN DT NNP , CC PRP VBP PRP VBP RB VB DT NN IN NNP ."
