Iraqi police say at least 25 people were wounded when three car bombs exploded in quick succession in the northern city of Kirkuk .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN WRB CD NN NNS VBD IN JJ NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
"The bombs went off early Saturday in the Kurdish area of the ethnically diverse city , which is at the center of a dispute between Arabs , Turkmen and Kurds .",O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-org I-org I-org O,"DT NNS VBD RB JJ NNP IN DT JJ NN IN DT RB JJ NN , WDT VBZ IN DT NN IN DT NN IN NNS , NNPS CC NNPS ."
"Kirkuk lies in the heart of Iraq 's oil-rich northern region , 240 kilometers north of Baghdad .",B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP VBZ IN DT NN IN NNP POS JJ JJ NN , CD NNS RB IN NNP ."
Tensions have been increased among ethnic groups by Kurdish efforts to incorporate the city into their semi-autonomous region .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP VBN VBN IN JJ NNS IN NNP NNS TO VB DT NN IN PRP$ JJ NN .
"Iraq 's main Sunni , Shi'ite and Kurdish factions have bee trying to reach an agreement on forming a new government .",B-geo O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ NNP , NNP CC NNP NNS VBP VBN VBG TO VB DT NN IN VBG DT JJ NN ."
The country has been stuck in a political deadlock since March elections .,O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,DT NN VBZ VBN VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNS .
"On Friday , Iraq delayed Monday 's scheduled parliament session to elect a speaker until later in the week .",O B-tim O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O,"IN NNP , NNP VBD NNP POS JJ NN NN TO VB DT NN IN RB IN DT NN ."
