"Health officials from across Southeast Asia are participating in a unique five-day exercise to see how well they would respond to a pandemic in a fictional continent called "" Pandemica . """,O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS IN IN NNP NNP VBP VBG IN DT JJ JJ NN TO VB WRB RB PRP MD VB TO DT NN IN DT JJ NN VBD RQU NNP . LQU
"The ASEAN-led exercise , which began Monday in Phnom Penh , Cambodia , is the first of its kind .",O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN , WDT VBD NNP IN NNP NNP , NNP , VBZ DT NN IN PRP$ NN ."
It also involves the World Health Organization and other U.N. agencies and has funding from the U.S. Agency for International Development .,O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,PRP RB VBZ DT NNP NNP NNP CC JJ NNP NNS CC VBZ NN IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP NNP .
Officials say the exercise deals not only with the health consequences of a pandemic .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP DT NN VBZ RB RB IN DT NN NNS IN DT NN .
Participants are also practicing how they would maintain essential services such as energy and mass transport in the face of widespread illness .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP RB VBG WRB PRP MD VB JJ NNS JJ IN NN CC NN NN IN DT NN IN JJ NN .
The region was hard-hit by SARS in 2003 and by a human form of bird flu in 2004 .,O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NN VBD JJ IN NNS IN CD CC IN DT JJ NN IN NN NN IN CD .
