A Lebanese military court has charged a Christian politician and former army general with spying for Israel .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT JJ JJ NN VBZ VBN DT JJ NN CC JJ NN NN IN VBG IN NNP .
Fayez Karam of the Free Patriotic Movement is the first political figure to be charged in a widening probe of alleged Israeli espionage activity in Lebanon .,B-per I-per O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP IN DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ JJ NN TO VB VBN IN DT NN NN IN JJ JJ NN NN IN NNP .
"He is accused of meeting with enemy intelligence agents abroad , and giving them information by phone .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBZ VBN IN NN IN NN NN NNS RB , CC VBG PRP NN IN NN ."
Prosecutors say he gave the Israelis information about his own party and about Hezbollah .,O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-org O,NNS VBP PRP VBD DT NNS NN IN PRP$ JJ NN CC IN NNP .
Lebanon has detained as many as 70 people in recent months for alleged spying for Israel .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP VBZ VBN RB JJ IN CD NNS IN JJ NNS IN JJ VBG IN NNP .
More than 20 have been charged and two have been sentenced to death .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJR IN CD VBP VBN VBN CC CD VBP VBN VBN TO NN .
A number of those in custody were military and telecom employees .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN DT IN NN VBD JJ CC JJ NNS .
Lebanese officials say they plan to raise the issue at the U.N. Security Council .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,JJ NNS VBP PRP VBP TO VB DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP .
