The wife of Serbian war crimes suspect Ratko Mladic is facing criminal charges for illegal weapons possession .,O O O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN JJ NN NNS VBP NNP NNP VBZ VBG JJ NNS IN JJ NNS NN .
Mladic family lawyer Milos Saljic said Tuesday that Bosiljka Mladic was taken to a court in Belgrade Tuesday .,B-org O O B-per I-per O B-tim O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O,NNP NN NN NNP NNP VBD NNP IN NNP NNP VBD VBN TO DT NN IN NNP NNP .
"She was questioned by a judge about an automatic gun , a hunting rifle and several pistols discovered in the Mladic family home in 2008 .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-tim O,"PRP VBD VBN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN , DT NN NN CC JJ NNS VBN IN DT NNP NN NN IN CD ."
"Mladic is charged with genocide for helping to carry out the 1995 Srebrenica massacre of about 8,000 Muslim men and for masterminding the siege of Sarajevo .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP VBZ VBN IN NN IN VBG TO VB RP DT CD NNP NN IN IN CD NN NNS CC IN VBG DT NN IN NNP .
The 68-year-old Mladic has not been seen for several years .,O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O O,DT JJ NNP VBZ RB VBN VBN IN JJ NNS .
Mladic 's family asked Serbian authorities last month to declare him officially dead .,B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NN VBD JJ NNS JJ NN TO VB PRP RB JJ .
"However , Serbian war crimes prosecutors dismissed speculation that Mladic is dead , and said the effort to find him will continue .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , JJ NN NNS NNS VBD NN IN NNP VBZ JJ , CC VBD DT NN TO VB PRP MD VB ."
