"A Russian re-supply ship docked at the International Space Station ( ISS ) Saturday , but the commander of the station - Russian cosmonaut Oleg Kotov - was forced to manually control the vehicle because its automatic docking system was not working .",O B-gpe O O O O O B-art I-art I-art O B-art O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ JJ NN VBN IN DT NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP RRB NNP , CC DT NN IN DT NN IN JJ NN NNP NNP : VBD VBN TO RB VB DT NN IN PRP$ JJ NN NN VBD RB VBG ."
"The ship , designated Progress M-05M , docked at the ISS at 10:30 pm Moscow time .",O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-art O O O B-tim I-tim O,"DT NN , VBN NNP NNP , VBD IN DT NNP IN CD NN NNP NN ."
"Among the 2.5 tons of supplies carried to the ISS by the Progress are food , water , fuel , equipment , as well as gifts and treats for the station 's multi-national crew .",O O O O O O O O O B-art O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT CD NNS IN NNS VBN TO DT NNP IN DT NN VBP NN , NN , NN , NN , RB RB IN NNS CC NNS IN DT NN POS JJ NN ."
"At present , the ISS has a crew of six .",O O O O B-org O O O O O O,"IN NN , DT NNP VBZ DT NN IN CD ."
"Three Russians , two Americans , and a Japanese .",O B-gpe O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O,"CD NNS , CD NNS , CC DT NN ."
