Scientists say the 8.8 magnitude earthquake that devastated the Chilean city of Concepcion shifted it more than three meters to the west .,O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP DT CD NN NN WDT VBD DT JJ NN IN NNP VBD PRP JJR IN CD NNS TO DT NN .
Researchers from several universities in the United States also say the February 27th quake was so powerful it moved the capital of Santiago about 27 centimeters to the west-southwest .,O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,NNS IN JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNPS RB VBP DT NNP CD NN VBD RB JJ PRP VBD DT NN IN NNP IN CD NNS TO DT NN .
"Even the Argentinian capital of Buenos Aires , located more than 1,400 kilometers east of Santiago , shifted more than two centimeters to the west .",O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"RB DT JJ NN IN NNP NNPS , VBN RBR IN CD NNS NN IN NNP , VBD JJR IN CD NNS TO DT NN ."
The researchers compared data taken by global positioning satellites before and after the earthquake to reach their conclusions .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBN NNS VBN IN JJ NN NNS IN CC IN DT NN TO VB PRP$ NNS .
The Chilean government says about 452 people were killed by the quake .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBZ IN CD NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN .
