"Ukraine 's parliament has set February 25 for the swearing in of President-elect Viktor Yanukovych , as defeated rival Yulia Tymoshenko continues efforts to overturn election results .",B-geo O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NN VBZ VBN NNP CD IN DT NN IN IN JJ NNP NNP , IN VBN JJ NNP NNP VBZ NNS TO VB NN NNS ."
A majority of 238 lawmakers in the 450-seat parliament voted Tuesday for the date .,O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O,DT NN IN CD NNS IN DT JJ NN VBD NNP IN DT NN .
"But factions loyal to Ms. Tymoshenko , the current prime minister , boycotted the vote as the fiery politician prepared to contest election results in court .",O O O O B-per B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"CC NNS JJ TO NNP NNP , DT JJ JJ NN , VBD DT NN IN DT NN NN VBD TO VB NN NNS IN NN ."
Ms. Tymoshenko claims vote rigging by the Yanukovych camp robbed her of one million votes in the February 7 runoff election .,B-per B-geo O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,NNP NNP VBZ NN VBG IN DT NNP NN VBN PRP$ IN CD CD NNS IN DT NNP CD NN NN .
"Final results show her losing by nearly 888,000 votes , and Tuesday an allied lawmaker said she repeated her vow not to leave office voluntarily .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP PRP$ VBG IN RB CD NNS , CC NNP DT JJ NN VBD PRP VBD PRP$ NN RB TO VB NN RB ."
