"Venezuela is repeating its accusation that the United States is using the Dutch islands of Aruba and Curacao , off the Caribbean coast , for a possible military attack against Venezuela .",B-geo O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-gpe B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP VBZ VBG PRP$ NN IN DT NNP NNPS VBZ VBG DT JJ NNS IN NNP CC NNP , IN DT NNP NN , IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP ."
"In a statement Thursday , the Venezuelan government accused the U.S. of working with the Netherlands to prepare an aggression against Venezuela .",O O O B-tim O O B-gpe O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O,"IN DT NN NNP , DT JJ NN VBD DT NNP IN VBG IN DT NNP TO VB DT NN IN NNP ."
Venezuelan President Hugo Chavez made the same claim earlier this month .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN RBR DT NN .
"The United States called the allegation "" baseless . """,O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNPS VBD DT NN LQU NN . LQU
Dutch authorities say U.S. staff have been based in Aruba and Curacao to conduct drug surveillance operations over the Caribbean .,B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNS VBP NNP NN VBP VBN VBN IN NNP CC NNP TO VB NN NN NNS IN DT NNP .
Venezuela also has been at odds with Colombia over an agreement allowing the U.S. to use seven Colombian military bases for anti-drug operations .,B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,NNP RB VBZ VBN IN NNS IN NNP IN DT NN VBG DT NNP TO VB CD JJ JJ NNS IN JJ NNS .
"President Chavez has called the deal a threat to his country , but the U.S. and Colombia say the agreement does not pertain to other nations .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN DT NN TO PRP$ NN , CC DT NNP CC NNP VBP DT NN VBZ RB VB TO JJ NNS ."
