The Zambian government is projecting an average of 6 % growth in its gross domestic product between 2006 and 2008 .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,DT JJ NN VBZ VBG DT NN IN CD NN NN IN PRP$ JJ JJ NN IN CD CC CD .
Analysts say mining and construction will continue to dominate the economy .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP NN CC NN MD VB TO VB DT NN .
"They say other sectors that should contribute to growth include manufacturing , tourism , transport , storage and communications .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBP JJ NNS WDT MD VB TO NN VBP NN , NN , NN , NN CC NNS ."
The government says it will focus on labor-intensive sectors such as agriculture and manufacturing .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ PRP MD VB IN JJ NNS JJ IN NN CC NN .
"Particular attention will be placed on expanding rural infrastructure , such as feeder roads , bridges and dams .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN MD VB VBN IN VBG JJ NN , JJ IN NN NNS , NNS CC NNS ."
"Zambia recorded a 4.6 percent GDP growth rate in 2004 , thanks mainly to increased copper production .",B-per O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD DT CD NN NN NN NN IN CD , NNS RB TO VBN NN NN ."
"Zambian finance minister Peter Magande spoke to English to Africa reporter Peter Clottey from the capital , Lusaka .",B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O B-org I-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O,"JJ NN NN NNP NNP VBD TO NNP TO NNP NN NNP NNP IN DT NN , NNP ."
