Egypt says Palestinian militants were responsible for a series of rocket strikes on Israel and Jordan this week .,B-org O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-gpe O O O,NNP VBZ JJ NNS VBD JJ IN DT NN IN NN NNS IN NNP CC NNP DT NN .
Egypt 's official MENA news agency reports Wednesday that Palestinian factions from the Gaza Strip launched five rockets Monday that struck the towns of Aqaba in Jordan and Eilat in Israel .,B-org O O B-org O O O B-tim O B-gpe O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O B-gpe O B-per O B-geo O,NNP POS JJ NNP NN NN VBZ NNP IN JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNP VBD CD NNS NNP WDT VBD DT NNS IN NNP IN NNP CC NNP IN NNP .
The attacks killed one Jordanian cab driver and injured at least four other people .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBD CD JJ NN NN CC NN IN JJS CD JJ NNS .
The Associated Press cited an Egyptian security official as saying debris from a misfired rocket was found in Egyptian territory .,B-org I-org I-org O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN NN IN VBG NN IN DT VBN NN VBD VBN IN JJ NN .
"The Palestinian militant group Hamas , which controls the Gaza Strip , denied the accusations that a Palestinian group was responsible .",B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O,"DT JJ JJ NN NNP , WDT VBZ DT NNP NNP , VBD DT NNS IN DT JJ NN VBD JJ ."
A Hamas spokesman said no Palestinian faction operates outside the occupied territories .,O B-org O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBD DT JJ NN VBZ IN DT JJ NNS .
