"Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov has sharply criticized what he terms "" attempts by Western countries to influence the outcome "" of the disputed Ukrainian presidential election .",B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ RB VBN WP PRP NNS LQU NNS IN JJ NNS TO VB DT NN LQU IN DT JJ JJ JJ NN .
"Mr. Lavrov told a Moscow news conference Friday , Russia is concerned at what he called "" Western efforts to steer the situation in Ukraine from the legal path and towards the West . """,B-per I-per O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"NNP NNP VBD DT NNP NN NN NNP , NNP VBZ VBN IN WP PRP VBD LQU JJ NNS TO VB DT NN IN NNP IN DT JJ NN CC IN DT NNP . LQU"
He said Ukrainian voters alone should decide their country 's future .,O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD JJ NNS RB MD VB PRP$ NN POS NN .
Western countries have rejected full official results that declared Ukraine 's Kremlin-backed Prime Minister Viktor Yanukovych the winner of Sunday 's election .,B-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-per O B-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN JJ NN NNS WDT VBD NNP POS JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP DT NN IN NNP POS NN .
They say the vote fell far short of international standards .,O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBP DT NN VBD RB JJ IN JJ NNS .
"Meanwhile , Lithuanian President Valdas Adamkus arrived in Kiev Friday to join international mediation efforts aimed at resolving the crisis .",O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD IN NNP NNP TO VB JJ NN NNS VBN IN VBG DT NN ."
"Also , Ukraine 's television networks have begun live coverage of the opposition demonstrations in Kiev , the first time they have presented opposition views .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , NNP POS NN NNS VBP VBN JJ NN IN DT NN NNS IN NNP , DT JJ NN PRP VBP VBN NN NNS ."
