The Israeli military says soldiers have shot and killed an armed Palestinian militant during a raid near the West Bank town of Jenin .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O,DT JJ NN VBZ NNS VBP VBN CC VBN DT JJ JJ NN IN DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NN IN NNP .
"Officials say soldiers also demolished the home of the militant , who was a member of the radical Islamic Jihad group and linked to last month 's suicide bombing in Tel Aviv that killed five Israelis .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O B-gpe O,"NNS VBP NNS RB VBD DT NN IN DT NN , WP VBD DT NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP NN CC VBN TO JJ NN POS NN VBG IN NNP NNP WDT VBD CD NNS ."
The killing could complicate Israeli-Palestinian talks on the handover of security for two West Bank towns - Jericho and Tulkarem - to the Palestinians .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-gpe O,DT NN MD VB JJ NNS IN DT NN IN NN IN CD NNP NNP NNS IN NNP CC NNP : TO DT NNS .
"At last month 's summit in Egypt , Israel agreed to transfer five West Bank towns , including Qalqilya , Bethlehem and Ramallah to the Palestinian Authority .",O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-org O B-org I-org I-org O O B-gpe O O,"IN JJ NN POS NN IN NNP , NNP VBD TO VB CD NNP NNP NNS , VBG NNP , NNP CC NNP TO DT JJ NNP ."
