"Authorities in the northeast Indian state of Tripura have begun a probe into the mysterious death of 91 children at a government hospital in the capital , Agartala .",O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNS IN DT NN JJ NN IN NNP VBP VBN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN CD NNS IN DT NN NN IN DT NN , NNP ."
"State health officials say the children , most of them infants , died during the past three months at the Indira Gandhi Memorial Hospital .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,"NNP NN NNS VBP DT NNS , JJS IN PRP NNS , VBD IN DT JJ CD NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
"They say up to 800 children aged 12 years and younger are admitted to the hospital each month , with an average mortality rate of about 15 per month .",O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBP RP TO CD NNS VBN CD NNS CC JJR VBP VBN TO DT NN DT NN , IN DT JJ NN NN IN IN CD IN NN ."
"Tripura 's health director , Satya Ranjan Debbarma , says authorities have ordered a three-member team of doctors to find the reason behind the sharp increase of mortality among children at the hospital .",B-geo O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NN NN , NNP NNP NNP , VBZ NNS VBP VBN DT JJ NN IN NNS TO VB DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN NN IN NNS IN DT NN ."
"Health care in Tripura , a poor state bordering Bangladesh , is below modern standards .",O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"NNP NN IN NNP , DT JJ NN VBG NNP , VBZ IN JJ NNS ."
