A British court has ruled that radical Muslim cleric Abu Hamza al-Masri can be extradited to the United States to face terrorism charges .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBZ VBN IN JJ NNP NN NNP NNP NNP MD VB VBN TO DT NNP NNPS TO VB NN NNS .
The court in London issued the ruling Thursday .,O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O,DT NN IN NNP VBD DT NN NNP .
"Al-Masri is currently serving a seven-year prison sentence in Britain , after his 2006 conviction for inciting murder and racial hatred .",B-per O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ RB VBG DT JJ NN NN IN NNP , IN PRP$ CD NN IN VBG NN CC JJ NN ."
He was originally arrested in Britain on an extradition warrant from U.S. authorities in 2004 .,O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O,PRP VBD RB VBN IN NNP IN DT NN NN IN NNP NNS IN CD .
But that process was put on hold until his London trial ended and his appeals were exhausted .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,CC DT NN VBD VBN IN NN IN PRP$ NNP NN VBD CC PRP$ NNS VBD VBN .
The decision still needs the approval of Britain 's Home Secretary Jacqi Smith .,O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-per I-per I-per O,DT NN RB VBZ DT NN IN NNP POS NNP NNP NNP NNP .
U.S. officials accuse the cleric of aiding a 1998 hostage-taking in Yemen and of trying to set up a terrorist training camp in the northwestern U.S. state of Oregon .,B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O,NNP NNS VBP DT NN IN VBG DT CD NN IN NNP CC IN VBG TO VB RP DT JJ NN NN IN DT JJ NNP NN IN NNP .
