"Commonwealth leaders are meeting on the Mediterranean island of Malta for talks on several issues , including the upcoming World Trade Organization talks .",B-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNS VBP VBG IN DT JJ NN IN NNP IN NNS IN JJ NNS , VBG DT JJ NNP NNP NNP NNS ."
"Terrorism and human rights concerns , including in member state Uganda , are on the agenda of the talks .",O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O,"NNP CC JJ NNS NNS , VBG IN NN NN NNP , VBP IN DT NN IN DT NNS ."
Finding ways to help poorer countries receive greater benefit from global markets is also among the topics for discussion .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,VBG NNS TO VB JJR NNS VBP JJR NN IN JJ NNS VBZ RB IN DT NNS IN NN .
Commonwealth Secretary-General Don McKinnon urged the body to take the lead by taking up the cause of the poorer nations during next month 's WTO talks in Hong Kong .,B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN TO VB DT NN IN VBG RP DT NN IN DT JJR NNS IN JJ NN POS NNP NNS IN NNP NNP .
Britain 's Queen Elizabeth II opened the biennial summit Friday .,B-geo O B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-tim O,NNP POS NNP NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN NNP .
"The 53 Commonwealth nations , including Australia , Canada , India and Pakistan , account for almost one-third of the world 's population .",O O B-org O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O B-tim O O O O O O,"DT CD NNP NNS , VBG NNP , NNP , NNP CC NNP , NN IN RB NN IN DT NN POS NN ."
"Most , but not all members , were once part of the British empire .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"JJS , CC RB DT NNS , VBD RB NN IN DT JJ NN ."
