Sri Lanka 's new foreign minister says his government is committed to a cease-fire with Tamil Tiger rebels and negotiations to politically settle the decades-old ethnic dispute .,B-per B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP POS JJ JJ NN VBZ PRP$ NN VBZ VBN TO DT NN IN NNP NNP NNS CC NNS TO RB VB DT JJ JJ NN .
Mangala Samaraweera made the remark in a joint statement issued after he met with Indian Prime Minister Manmohan Singh in New Delhi .,B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O B-geo I-geo O,NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN DT JJ NN VBN IN PRP VBD IN JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP IN NNP NNP .
He said his government will review the three-year-old truce with the Tamil separatists to make it more effective .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,PRP VBD PRP$ NN MD VB DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNS TO VB PRP RBR JJ .
The statement also extends a firm invitation to the Tamil Tigers to discuss a political solution .,O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O,DT NN RB VBZ DT NN NN TO DT NNP NNP TO VB DT JJ NN .
Mr. Samaraweera also said his government will keep India informed of the ways and means by which the peace process could be made more effective .,B-per B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP RB VBD PRP$ NN MD VB NNP VBN IN DT NNS CC NNS IN WDT DT NN NN MD VB VBN RBR JJ .
The joint statement says India supports the process of seeking a negotiated settlement within the framework of a united Sri Lanka .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per B-gpe O,DT JJ NN VBZ NNP VBZ DT NN IN VBG DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP .
