North Korea 's foreign minister has arrived in Burma for talks with his counterparts in that country 's ruling military government .,B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP POS JJ NN VBZ VBN IN NNP IN NNS IN PRP$ NNS IN DT NN POS VBG JJ NN .
Foreign Minister Pak Ui Chun 's arrival in the main city of Rangon Thursday comes amid concerns and speculation in the U.S. about the two authoritarian regimes ' deepening relationship .,O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-org B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP POS NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP VBZ IN NNS CC NN IN DT NNP IN DT CD JJ NNS POS VBG NN .
"During a regional Southeast Asia security forum last week , U.S. Secretary of State Hillary Clinton mentioned reports that Burma recently received a shipment of military equipment from North Korea .",O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo O O B-org B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"IN DT JJ NNP NNP NN NN JJ NN , NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBD NNS IN NNP RB VBD DT NN IN JJ NN IN NNP NNP ."
Clinton also said Washington is concerned about reports the Burmese military junta is seeking help from North Korea on a possible nuclear program .,B-per O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O,NNP RB VBD NNP VBZ JJ IN NNS DT JJ JJ NN VBZ VBG NN IN NNP NNP IN DT JJ JJ NN .
Pak Ui Chun will travel to the capital of Naypyidaw on Friday .,B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O,NNP NNP NNP MD VB TO DT NN IN NNP IN NNP .
Burma cut off diplomatic relations with Pyongyang in 1983 after North Korean agents tried and failed to assassinate then-South Korean President Chun Doo Hwan during the latter 's visit to Burma .,B-geo O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O B-geo B-gpe O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP VBD RP JJ NNS IN NNP IN CD IN JJ JJ NNS VBD CC VBD TO VB JJ JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP IN DT NN POS NN TO NNP .
Twenty-one people were killed in the attack .,O O O O O O O O,CD NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN .
