The first of 15 defendants on trial for their alleged roles in a May anti-government uprising in the eastern Uzbek town of Andijan says he plotted the rebellion with the help of foreign journalists .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN CD NNS IN NN IN PRP$ JJ NNS IN DT NNP NN NN IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP VBZ PRP VBD DT NN IN DT NN IN JJ NNS .
"Defendant Muidin Sobirov spoke before the Uzbek supreme court Wednesday , the second day of hearings .",O B-per I-per O O O B-gpe O O B-tim O O O O O O O,"NN NNP NNP VBD IN DT JJ NN NN NNP , DT JJ NN IN NNS ."
He said foreign reporters advised him and other alleged plotters on what clothing to wear and how to organize demonstrations to gain more public support .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD JJ NNS VBD PRP CC JJ JJ NNS IN WP NN TO VB CC WRB TO VB NNS TO VB JJR JJ NN .
"The defendants , who could face the death penalty , all pleaded guilty to charges including links to Islamic extremists and an attempted coup .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"DT NNS , WP MD VB DT NN NN , DT VBD JJ TO NNS VBG NNS TO NNP NNS CC DT VBN NN ."
London-based Human Rights Watch has said there was evidence that police forced confessions from people involved in the protests .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN EX VBD NN IN NNS VBD NNS IN NNS VBN IN DT NNS .
Rights workers say Uzbek security forces fired on demonstrators and killed as many as 750 people .,O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS NNS VBP JJ NN NNS VBN IN NNS CC VBN RB JJ IN CD NNS .
Uzbek officials deny the claims .,B-gpe O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP DT NNS .
