Prominent Sunni Muslim politicians in Iraq have again called for a postponement of the January 30 elections as violence continues in parts of the country .,O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNS IN NNP VBP RB VBN IN DT NN IN DT NNP CD NNS IN NN VBZ IN NNS IN DT NN .
"Despite Prime Minister Iyad Allawi 's insistence that elections will go forward on time , Sunni leaders repeated their calls Thursday for a delay due to the unstable security situation .",O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP NNP NNP NNP POS NN IN NNS MD VB RB IN NN , NNP NNS VBD PRP$ NNS NNP IN DT NN JJ TO DT JJ NN NN ."
"On Wednesday , the United States announced it will send some 1,500 additional troops to Iraq and extend the tours of another 10,000 to bolster security for the election .",O B-tim O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , DT NNP NNPS VBD PRP MD VB DT CD JJ NNS TO NNP CC VB DT NNS IN DT CD TO VB NN IN DT NN ."
"Meanwhile , at least one Iraqi was killed and several wounded in a wave of mortar attacks in Baghdad today .",O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O,"RB , IN JJS CD JJ VBD VBN CC JJ VBN IN DT NN IN JJ NNS IN NNP NN ."
"And to the north , in Beiji , at least two Iraqi National Guards were wounded when a car bomb exploded near a checkpoint .",O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"CC TO DT NN , IN NNP , IN JJS CD JJ NNP NNPS VBD VBN WRB DT NN NN VBD IN DT NN ."
