"The U.S. embassy has ordered increased security for American facilities in Germany , in response to what officials call a heightened threat situation .",O B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NN VBZ VBN VBN NN IN JJ NNS IN NNP , IN NN TO WP NNS VBP DT JJ NN NN ."
An embassy statement issued Friday urged Americans in Germany to use increased vigilance and take steps to ensure their own personal security .,O O O O B-tim O B-gpe O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBN NNP VBD NNS IN NNP TO VB VBN NN CC VB NNS TO VB PRP$ JJ JJ NN .
"Embassy officials did not specify the nature of the threat , but they said U.S. facilities constantly assess their security postures in response to a heightened threat environment .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNS VBD RB VB DT NN IN DT NN , CC PRP VBD NNP NNS RB VBP PRP$ NN NNS IN NN TO DT JJ NN NN ."
A spokesman for the embassy noted that German authorities have warned of an increased threat of terrorism against their country because of its participation in the NATO military mission in Afghanistan .,O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O B-geo O,DT NN IN DT NN VBD IN JJ NNS VBP VBN IN DT VBN NN IN NN IN PRP$ NN IN IN PRP$ NN IN DT NNP JJ NN IN NNP .
