The head of the Russian Orthodox Church says he hopes the next pope will work to improve relations between the Roman Catholic and Russian Orthodox Churches .,O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-org I-org I-org O,DT NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ DT JJ NN MD VB TO VB NNS IN DT NNP NNP CC JJ NNP NNP .
Patriarch Alexy made the comment in an interview with Italy 's Corriere della Sera newspaper .,O B-per O O O O O O O B-geo O B-org I-org I-org O O,NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP POS NNP NN NNP NN .
"He expressed respect for the late Pope John Paul II , but said many problems remain between the churches that split centuries ago .",O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP , CC VBD JJ NNS VBP IN DT NNS WDT VBD NNS RB ."
He called on the next pontiff to denounce proselytizing .,O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD IN DT JJ NN TO VB VBG .
The Russian Orthodox Church had long accused the Catholic Church of evangelizing in Russia and other predominantly Orthodox areas .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O O B-org I-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O,DT JJ NNP NNP VBD RB VBN DT NNP NNP IN VBG IN NNP CC JJ RB NNP NNS .
That was one of the issues that prevented Pope John Paul from fulfilling his long-desired wish to visit Russia .,O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT VBD CD IN DT NNS WDT VBD NNP NNP NNP IN VBG PRP$ JJ NN TO VB NNP .
