"Five Iraqi Cabinet ministers loyal to former Prime Minister Ayad Allawi say they will boycott government meetings , in another blow to national reconciliation efforts .",O B-gpe O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"CD JJ NNP NNS JJ TO JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBP PRP MD VB NN NNS , IN DT NN TO JJ NN NNS ."
Officials from the Iraqiya List said the five Cabinet ministers suspended their participation because Prime Minister Nouri al-Maliki had not responded to political demands issued earlier this year .,O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN DT NNP NNP VBD DT CD NNP NNS VBD PRP$ NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD RB VBN TO JJ NNS VBN RBR DT NN .
"The Iraqiya List includes Sunnis , Shi'ites , and Christians .",O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O,"DT NNP NNP VBZ NNP , NNP , CC NNPS ."
The announcement Monday is seen as another blow to Prime Minister Maliki 's efforts to reconcile Iraq 's different groups .,O O B-tim O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O,DT NN NNP VBZ VBN IN DT NN TO NNP NNP NNP POS NNS TO VB NNP POS JJ NNS .
"Last week , Iraq 's largest Sunni Arab bloc , the Accordance Front , pulled out of the unity government .",O O O B-geo O O B-per I-per O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN , NNP POS JJS NNP NNP NN , DT NNP NNP , VBD IN IN DT NN NN ."
"That group also was protesting what it said was Mr. Maliki 's refusal to respond to its list of demands , including a crackdown on Shi'ite militias .",O O O O O O O O O B-per B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN RB VBD VBG WP PRP VBD VBD NNP NNP POS NN TO VB TO PRP$ NN IN NNS , VBG DT NN IN NNP NNS ."
