"Venezuela 's oil minister , Rafael Ramirez , says ConocoPhillips and ExxonMobil will end their operations in the country after refusing to give the government control of their local oil business .",B-geo O O O O B-per I-per O O B-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NN NN , NNP NNP , VBZ NNP CC NNP MD VB PRP$ NNS IN DT NN IN VBG TO VB DT NN NN IN PRP$ JJ NN NN ."
A deadline for a deal passed on Tuesday .,O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NN IN DT NN VBN IN NNP .
"Venezuela 's state-run oil company , Petroleos de Venezuela or PDVSA , has raised its average ownership share in six oil ventures in the Orinoco basin from 39 percent to a controlling 78 percent .",B-geo O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ NN NN , NNP IN NNP CC NNP , VBZ VBN PRP$ JJ NN NN IN CD NN NNS IN DT NNP NN IN CD NN TO DT VBG CD NN ."
Venezuela has said it will not pay cash for the oil assets it takes over and will not compensate foreign companies for the $ 4 billion in debt they incurred on the projects .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN PRP MD RB VB NN IN DT NN NNS PRP VBZ RP CC MD RB VB JJ NNS IN DT $ CD CD IN NN PRP VBD IN DT NNS .
"Four other foreign oil companies : Chevron , Statoil , Total , and BP , have signed deals to continue work in Venezuela .",O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"CD JJ JJ NN NNS IN NNP , NNP , NNP , CC NNP , VBP VBN NNS TO VB NN IN NNP ."
