Hamid Karzai Afghan President Hamid Karzai says he will bring up the reported deaths of two Afghan prisoners at the hands of the U.S. military during talks with President Bush at the White House Monday .,B-org I-org B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-per I-per O O B-org I-org B-tim O,NNP NNP JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP MD VB RP DT VBN NNS IN CD JJ NNS IN DT NNS IN DT NNP JJ IN NNS IN NNP NNP IN DT NNP NNP NNP .
Mr. Karzai says he wants all prisoners in his country placed under Afghan government control and wants to be consulted on all U.S. military operations .,B-per B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ DT NNS IN PRP$ NN VBN IN JJ NN NN CC VBZ TO VB VBN IN DT NNP JJ NNS .
"The United Nations condemned the alleged abuse of detainees , as "" utterly unacceptable "" and urged the U.S. military to allow a probe by Afghan human rights investigators .",O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O,"DT NNP NNPS VBD DT JJ NN IN NNS , IN LQU RB JJ LQU CC VBD DT NNP NN TO VB DT NN IN JJ JJ NNS NNS ."
U.S. officials have condemned the misconduct and say seven soldiers have been punished .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBP VBN DT NN CC VB CD NNS VBP VBN VBN .
"The New York Times reported Friday that the U.S. Army has documented the abuse of detainees in Afghanistan in a 2,000 page report that has not yet been officially released .",O B-org I-org I-org O B-tim O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP IN DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN NNS IN NNP IN DT CD NN NN WDT VBZ RB RB VBN RB VBN .
