"Taiwan 's president is urging the European Union not to lift its arms embargo against China , saying the move could threaten stability and security in the region .",B-geo O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NN VBZ VBG DT NNP NNP RB TO VB PRP$ NNS NN IN NNP , VBG DT NN MD VB NN CC NN IN DT NN ."
Chen Shui-bian made his plea during a videoconference Tuesday with EU lawmakers .,B-per I-per O O O O O O B-tim O B-org O O,NNP NNP VBD PRP$ NN IN DT NN NNP IN NNP NNS .
"Mr. Chen says ending the arms ban could lead to "" a tilt of the military balance in the Taiwan Strait , "" and pointed out that China already has more than 700 missiles aimed at Taiwan .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBG DT NNS NN MD VB TO LQU DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP , LQU CC VBD RP IN NNP RB VBZ JJR IN CD NNS VBN IN NNP ."
"The United States is also expressing opposition to the EU proposal , saying it could put U.S. troops in the region at risk .",O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNPS VBZ RB VBG NN TO DT NNP NN , VBG PRP MD VB NNP NNS IN DT NN IN NN ."
United States is legally bound to come to Taiwan 's defense if China launches a military attack on the island .,B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,NNP NNPS VBZ RB VBN TO VB TO NNP POS NN IN NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN DT NN .
