The U.N. 's World Health Organization says 54 people in Indonesia with ties to a family decimated by bird flu have been placed in voluntary quarantine .,O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP POS NNP NNP NNP VBZ CD NNS IN NNP IN NNS TO DT NN VBN IN NN NN VBP VBN VBN IN JJ NN .
U.N. officials said Wednesday the group included relatives and others who came in contact with seven family members who died from the deadly H5N1 virus earlier this month .,B-org O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-nat O O O O O,NNP NNS VBD NNP DT NN VBD NNS CC NNS WP VBD IN NN IN CD NN NNS WP VBD IN DT JJ NNP NN RBR DT NN .
WHO officials say the quarantined subjects have been examined daily and receive doses of the anti-viral drug Tamiflu as a precaution .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-art O O O O,WP NNS VBP DT JJ NNS VBP VBN VBN RB CC VB NNS IN DT JJ NN NNP IN DT NN .
Officials say so far there have been no signs that the flu has spread .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP RB RB EX VBP VBN DT NNS IN DT NN VBZ VBN .
No new cases have been reported in Indonesia since May 22 .,O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim I-tim I-tim O,DT JJ NNS VBP VBN VBN IN NNP IN NNP CD .
Meanwhile Indonesian health officials say local test results show that a 15-year-old boy who died Tuesday was infected with the bird flu virus .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O,RB JJ NN NNS VBP JJ NN NNS VBP IN DT JJ NN WP VBD NNP VBD VBN IN DT NN NN NN .
The results have yet to be confirmed by the World Health Organization .,O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,DT NNS VBP RB TO VB VBN IN DT NNP NNP NNP .
