"Diplomatic sources say U.S. Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice will visit India , Pakistan and Afghanistan for talks expected to focus on regional and international issues .",O O O B-org O O B-org B-per I-per O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP MD VB NNP , NNP CC NNP IN NNS VBN TO VB IN JJ CC JJ NNS ."
There has been no official U.S. announcement of the trip .,O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,EX VBZ VBN DT JJ NNP NN IN DT NN .
"On Friday , an Indian foreign ministry spokesman told reporters Secretary Rice will arrive in New Delhi on March 16 for talks with Indian officials .",O B-tim O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-per O O O B-geo I-geo O B-tim I-tim O O O B-gpe O O,"IN NNP , DT JJ JJ NN NN VBD NNS NNP NNP MD VB IN NNP NNP IN NNP CD IN NNS IN JJ NNS ."
"The discussions are expected to include Nepal , where King Gyanendra has seized dictatorial powers in an effort to quell a Maoist insurgency .",O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS VBP VBN TO VB NNP , WRB NNP NNP VBZ VBN JJ NNS IN DT NN TO VB DT NN NN ."
The announcement of Ms. Rice 's trip came as Indian and U.S. officials wrapped up two days of talks in New Delhi on issues related to missile defense .,O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-gpe O B-geo O O O B-tim O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O,DT NN IN NNP NNP POS NN VBD IN JJ CC NNP NNS VBD RP CD NNS IN NNS IN NNP NNP IN NNS VBN TO NN NN .
The spokesman said U.S. officials briefed India on the newest developments in the U.S. Missile Defense program .,O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O,DT NN VBD NNP NNS VBD NNP IN DT JJS NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP NN .
There are no details on Secretary Rice 's scheduled visit to Afghanistan and Pakistan .,O O O O O O B-per O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,EX VBP DT NNS IN NNP NNP POS VBN NN TO NNP CC NNP .
