Two British journalists arrested in Zimbabwe have pleaded not guilty to violating the country 's media and immigration laws .,O B-gpe O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CD JJ NNS VBN IN NNP VBP VBN RB JJ TO VBG DT NN POS NNS CC NN NNS .
"If convicted , they face up to two years in prison .",O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O,"IN VBN , PRP VBP RP TO CD NNS IN NN ."
"But their lawyer , Beatrice Mtetwa , told the court the men were in Zimbabwe for a holiday , not to report on the elections .",O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"CC PRP$ NN , NNP NNP , VBD DT NN DT NNS VBD IN NNP IN DT NN , RB TO VB IN DT NNS ."
"On Monday , they were granted bail .",O B-tim O O O O O O,"IN NNP , PRP VBD VBN NN ."
"The state said it would appeal that ruling , forcing the men to remain in custody .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD PRP MD VB IN NN , VBG DT NNS TO VB IN NN ."
