"Pope Benedict has named the Vatican ambassador to Israel , Archbishop Pietro Sambi , as the new Apostolic Nuncio ( ambassador ) to the United States .",B-per I-per O O O B-org O O B-geo O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NNP NN TO NNP , NNP NNP NNP , IN DT JJ NNP NNP LRB NN RRB TO DT NNP NNPS ."
"Archbishop Sambi is replacing Archbishop Gabriel Montalvo , who retired .",B-org I-org O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBG NNP NNP NNP , WP VBD ."
Archbishop Sambi also will replace his predecessor as the Holy See 's permanent observer at the Organization of American States .,B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,NNP NNP RB MD VB PRP$ NN IN DT NNP NNP POS JJ NN IN DT NNP IN NNP NNPS .
"While serving as Apostolic Nuncio to Israel , Archbishop Sambi also held the posts of Nuncio to Cyprus and Apostolic Delegate to Jerusalem and the Palestinian territories .",O O O O O O B-geo O B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-geo O O B-gpe O O,"IN VBG IN JJ NNP TO NNP , NNP NNP RB VBD DT NNS IN NNP TO NNP CC NNP NNP TO NNP CC DT JJ NNS ."
