U.N. aid officials say the international response to the Pakistan earthquake must be intensified to provide relief for millions of survivors before the onslaught of winter .,B-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NN NNS VBP DT JJ NN TO DT NNP NN MD VB VBN TO VB NN IN NNS IN NNS IN DT NN IN NN .
"The world body 's humanitarian coordinator Jan Vandemoortele told reporters in Islamabad Saturday tents , emergency shelters and helicopters are the agency 's top priorities .",O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN NN POS JJ NN NNP NNP VBD NNS IN NNP NNP NNS , NN NNS CC NNS VBP DT NN POS JJ NNS ."
"Meanwhile , India has offered to set up three relief centers near the line of control separating Pakistani-controlled from Indian-controlled Kashmir .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , NNP VBZ VBN TO VB RP CD NN NNS IN DT NN IN NN VBG JJ IN JJ NNP ."
The move follows a call by Pakistan earlier this week to allow Kashmiris to travel across the line of control to help relatives affected by the quake .,O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ DT NN IN NNP RBR DT NN TO VB NNP TO VB IN DT NN IN NN TO VB NNS VBN IN DT NN .
"Also this week , Indian officials opened direct telephone lines with Pakistani Kashmir for the first time in 15 years .",O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O,"RB DT NN , JJ NNS VBD JJ NN NNS IN JJ NNP IN DT JJ NN IN CD NNS ."
NATO agreed on Friday to send soldiers to the affected regions .,B-org O O B-tim O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD IN NNP TO VB NNS TO DT JJ NNS .
"The powerful quake left more than 51,000 people dead and more than three million homeless .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBD JJR IN CD NNS JJ CC JJR IN CD CD NN .
