Mr. Chavez ordered the government to seize nearly 36 hectares of privately owned land near the national airport and authorized the building of thousands of housing units .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD DT NN TO VB RB CD NNS IN RB VBN NN IN DT JJ NN CC VBD DT NN IN NNS IN NN NNS .
He also authorized officials to take over unused hotel rooms and tourist resorts .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP RB VBD NNS TO VB RP JJ NN NNS CC NN NNS .
"At least 32 people have died and more than 70,000 left homeless by flooding due to heavy rains in recent days .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,IN JJS CD NNS VBP VBN CC JJR IN CD VBD JJ IN VBG JJ TO JJ NNS IN JJ NNS .
