"The U.S. State Department has issued a travel warning for Colombia , saying that Americans continue to be victims of threats , kidnappings and other criminal acts .",O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN NN IN NNP , VBG IN NNS VBP TO VB NNS IN NNS , NNS CC JJ JJ NNS ."
"In a statement issued Wednesday , the State Department said that terrorist groups , such as the Revolutionary Armed Forces of Colombia , or FARC , and the National Liberation Army ( ELN ) , continue to kidnap civilians for ransom or as political bargaining chips .",O O O O B-tim O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org B-geo O O B-org O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN VBN NNP , DT NNP NNP VBD IN JJ NNS , JJ IN DT NNP NNP NNS IN NNP , CC NNP , CC DT NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP RRB , VBP TO VB NNS IN NN CC IN JJ NN NNS ."
"It noted that at least five Americans were kidnapped in 2004 , and at least one in 2005 .",O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-tim O,"PRP VBD IN IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN IN CD , CC IN JJS CD IN CD ."
The State Department also said FARC has held three American contractors hostage since February 2003 .,O B-org I-org O O B-org O O O B-gpe O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT NNP NNP RB VBD NNP VBZ VBN CD JJ NNS NN IN NNP CD .
"The State Department is urging U.S. citizens traveling to Colombia to not use bus transportation , and to avoid traveling by road outside of urban areas at night .",O B-org I-org O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"DT NNP NNP VBZ VBG NNP NNS VBG TO NNP TO RB VB NN NN , CC TO VB VBG IN NN IN IN JJ NNS IN NN ."
