"Witnesses in Somalia 's capital say a roadside bomb explosion has killed at least 20 people , mostly women .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN NNP POS NN VBP DT NN NN NN VBZ VBN IN JJS CD NNS , RB NNS ."
Sunday 's early morning blast ripped through a group of female street cleaners .,B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS JJ NN NN VBD IN DT NN IN JJ NN NNS .
"Witnesses counted 15 bodies at the scene , while five other people died after being taken to Mogadishu 's Medina Hospital .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O,"NNS VBD CD NNS IN DT NN , IN CD JJ NNS VBD IN VBG VBN TO NNP POS NNP NNP ."
More than 40 others were injured .,O O O O O O O,JJR IN CD NNS VBD VBN .
No one has claimed responsibility for the blast .,O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBN NN IN DT NN .
"In a separate incident , Islamist insurgents attacked Ethiopian forces in Mogadishu 's Towfiq neighborhood early today .",O O O O O B-org O O B-gpe O O B-geo O B-geo O O B-tim O,"IN DT JJ NN , NNP NNS VBD JJ NNS IN NNP POS NNP NN RB NN ."
Witnesses say at least three soldiers were killed .,O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN .
Ethiopian troops are supporting the Somali transitional government in its fight against the Islamist insurgency .,B-gpe O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-org O O,JJ NNS VBP VBG DT JJ JJ NN IN PRP$ NN IN DT NNP NN .
