"The body of Uganda 's first prime minister and two-time president , Milton Obote , has arrived back in the country for his state funeral , scheduled to begin later this week .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,"DT NN IN NNP POS JJ JJ NN CC JJ NN , NNP NNP , VBZ VBN RB IN DT NN IN PRP$ NN NN , VBN TO VB RB DT NN ."
"Many supporters of Mr. Obote and officials from the political party he founded , the Uganda People 's Congress , gathered to receive his casket at Entebbe airport Tuesday .",O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo B-tim O,"JJ NNS IN NNP NNP CC NNS IN DT JJ NN PRP VBD , DT NNP NNP POS NNP , VBD TO VB PRP$ NN IN NNP NN NNP ."
Members of other political parties and Ugandan officials also were there .,O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,NNS IN JJ JJ NNS CC JJ NNS RB VBD RB .
Mr. Obote died last week at age 81 in a South African hospital .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,NNP NNP VBD JJ NN IN NN CD IN DT JJ JJ NN .
He is revered by many Ugandans for leading the country to independence in 1962 .,O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-tim O,PRP VBZ VBN IN JJ NNS IN VBG DT NN TO NN IN CD .
"But he is also reviled by those who hold him responsible for the deaths of some 500,000 Ugandans in a civil war from 1980 to 1985 .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,CC PRP VBZ RB VBN IN DT WP VBP PRP JJ IN DT NNS IN DT CD NNS IN DT JJ NN IN CD TO CD .
Mr. Obote was Uganda 's president during the war .,B-per I-per O B-org I-org O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD NNP POS NN IN DT NN .
