"Venezuelan President Hugo Chavez is in China , looking for political support and oil deals from one of the world 's largest energy consumers .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ IN NNP , VBG IN JJ NN CC NN NNS IN CD IN DT NN POS JJS NN NNS ."
Venezuela wants to take advantage of China 's interest in South American oil .,B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O B-org I-org O O,NNP VBZ TO VB NN IN NNP POS NN IN NNP NNP NN .
"The energy giant exports most of its oil to the United States , but the Chavez government is a staunch critic of Washington and hopes to expand its markets elsewhere .",O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"DT NN JJ NNS JJS IN PRP$ NN TO DT NNP NNPS , CC DT NNP NN VBZ DT JJ NN IN NNP CC VBZ TO VB PRP$ NNS RB ."
"Before embarking on his fourth trip to China since 1999 , Mr. Chavez mentioned plans last week to buy Chinese-made oil tankers .",O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim I-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,"IN VBG IN PRP$ JJ NN TO NNP IN CD , NNP NNP VBD NNS JJ NN TO VB JJ NN NNS ."
