Iraqi President Jalal Talabani says he is willing to talk with anti-government opposition figures and members of Saddam Hussein 's outlawed Baath party .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O B-tim O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ JJ TO VB IN JJ NN NNS CC NNS IN NNP NNP POS JJ NNP NN .
"However , Mr. Talabani told a reconciliation conference in Cairo Sunday that his government will not meet with those who continue to attack U.S. and Iraqi government forces .",O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-gpe O O O,"RB , NNP NNP VBD DT NN NN IN NNP NNP IN PRP$ NN MD RB VB IN DT WP VBP TO VB NNP CC JJ NN NNS ."
"Mr. Talabani said there have been no contacts so far with "" those whom some describe as the resistance . """,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD EX VBP VBN DT NNS RB RB IN LQU DT WP DT VBP IN DT NN . LQU
"Meanwhile , a British soldier was killed and four others wounded Sunday in a roadside bombing in the southern Iraqi city of Basra .",O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O,"RB , DT JJ NN VBD VBN CC CD NNS VBN NNP IN DT NN VBG IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP ."
"Separately , the U.S. military says an ambush late Saturday on a joint U.S.-Iraqi patrol killed a Marine and 15 civilians in the town of Haditha .",O O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O,"RB , DT NNP NN VBZ DT NN JJ NNP IN DT JJ JJ NN VBD DT NN CC CD NNS IN DT NN IN NNP ."
A wave of bombings in Baghdad and elsewhere in the country killed at least 48 Iraqis and wounded about 70 others earlier Saturday .,O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NN IN NNS IN NNP CC RB IN DT NN VBD IN JJS CD NNS CC VBD IN CD NNS RBR NNP .
