European delegation issued a statement saying Israeli authorities cited ' security grounds ' when they revoked permission for Wednesday 's visit to Gaza .,O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O,JJ NN VBD DT NN VBG JJ NNS VBD LQU NN NNS RQU WRB PRP VBN NN IN NNP POS NN TO NNP .
"A European Parliament delegation is demanding that Israel explain why it prevented European lawmakers from visiting the Gaza Strip , despite earlier Israeli assurances that the delegation would be allowed to visit Gaza .",O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT JJ NNP NN VBZ VBG IN NNP VBP WRB PRP VBD JJ NNS IN VBG DT NNP NNP , IN RBR JJ NNS IN DT NN MD VB VBN TO VB NNP ."
"The European delegation issued a statement saying Israeli authorities cited "" security grounds "" when they revoked permission for Wednesday 's visit to Gaza .",O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O,DT JJ NN VBD DT NN VBG JJ NNS VBD LQU NN NNS RQU WRB PRP VBN NN IN NNP POS NN TO NNP .
The delegation of at least eight people was denied access one day after the European Union said Jerusalem should be the shared capital of Israel and a future Palestinian state .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O,DT NN IN IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN NN CD NN IN DT NNP NNP VBD NNP MD VB DT JJ NN IN NNP CC DT JJ JJ NN .
EU foreign ministers issued a statement in Brussels Tuesday that said the European Commission does not recognize Israel 's annexation of the disputed area of East Jerusalem in 1967 .,B-org O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O B-org I-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-tim O,NNP JJ NNS VBD DT NN IN NNP NNP WDT VBD DT NNP NNP VBZ RB VB NNP POS NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP IN CD .
But the foreign ministers did not stipulate that East Jerusalem should be the capital of a Palestinian state .,O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O,CC DT JJ NNS VBD RB VB IN NNP NNP MD VB DT NN IN DT JJ NN .
