Court officials in Montenegro say an investigation into a suspected mass grave in the country has been closed after finding no evidence that remains of Kosovo Albanians were buried there .,B-org O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org B-gpe O O O O,NNP NNS IN NNP VBP DT NN IN DT JJ NN NN IN DT NN VBZ VBN VBN IN VBG DT NN IN VBZ IN NNP NNS VBD VBN RB .
"A court spokeswoman said Wednesday there is no evidence that a mass grave exists in the northern Montenegrin town of Andrijevica , near the Kosovo border .",O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O B-org O O,"DT NN NN VBD NNP EX VBZ DT NN IN DT NN NN VBZ IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP , IN DT NNP NN ."
Officials from Montenegro investigated the site at the request of the European Union-led rule-of-law mission EULEX in Kosovo .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-org O,NNS IN NNP VBD DT NN IN DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NN NN NNP IN NNP .
A mass grave containing the remains of 250 ethnic Kosovo Albanians had been uncovered in Serbia earlier this year .,O O O O O O O O O B-org B-gpe O O O O B-geo O O O O,DT NN NN VBG DT NNS IN CD JJ NNP NNS VBD VBN VBN IN NNP RBR DT NN .
"The victims were believed to have been killed during the 1998 - 1999 conflict in Kosovo , when Serbian forces fought ethnic Albanian separatists .",O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O,"DT NNS VBD VBN TO VB VBN VBN IN DT CD IN CD NN IN NNP , WRB JJ NNS VBD JJ JJ NNS ."
Ethnic Albanians make up about 90 percent of Kosovo 's population .,O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O O O,NNP NNS VBP RP IN CD NN IN NNP POS NN .
"Kosovo declared independence from Serbia in 2008 , but ethnic Serbs who constitute a majority in northern Kosovo refuse to recognize the ethnic Albanian government in Pristina .",B-geo O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O,"NNP VBD NN IN NNP IN CD , CC JJ NNS WP VBP DT NN IN JJ NNP NN TO VB DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP ."
