Afghan President Hamid Karzai is seeking help from influential Pashtun politicians in Pakistan in an effort to stem a growing Taleban insurgency .,B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-org O O,JJ NN NNP NNP VBZ VBG NN IN JJ NN NNS IN NNP IN DT NN TO VB DT VBG NNP NN .
Mr. Karzai is a Pashtun himself .,B-per I-per O O B-org O O,NNP NNP VBZ DT NN PRP .
He has sent letters to the leading pro-Taleban cleric and opposition leader Maulana Fazal-ur-Rehman and Pashtun nationalist leader Asfandayar Wali Khan .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O B-org O O B-per I-per I-per O,PRP VBZ VBN NNS TO DT VBG JJ NN CC NN NN NNP NNP CC NN NN NN NNP NNP NNP .
The letters urge them to help restore peace in southern Afghanistan .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNS VBP PRP TO VB VB NN IN JJ NNP .
"Rehman heads a party of Islamic clerics that is part of the government in two Pakistani provinces bordering Afghanistan - North West Frontier Province , and Baluchistan .",B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O O B-geo O,"NNP VBZ DT NN IN JJ NNS WDT VBZ NN IN DT NN IN CD JJ NNS VBG NNP : NNP NNP NNP NNP , CC NNP ."
"There are some 40,000 NATO and U.S. troops in Afghanistan .",O O O O B-org O B-gpe O O B-geo O,EX VBP DT CD NNP CC NNP NNS IN NNP .
"But despite their presence , Taleban remnants have intensified their anti-government drive by using road-side explosive devices and suicide bombers .",O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"CC IN PRP$ NN , NNP NNS VBP VBN PRP$ JJ NN IN VBG JJ JJ NNS CC NN NNS ."
Mr. Karzai often blames Pakistan for not doing enough to stop Taleban attackers from crossing over into Afghanistan .,B-per I-per O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP RB VBZ NNP IN RB VBG RB TO VB NNP NNS IN VBG RP IN NNP .
