Iraqi Prime Minister Nouri al-Maliki says he plans to announce the names of the candidates for the defense and interior ministers to parliament on Sunday .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ TO VB DT NNS IN DT NNS IN DT NN CC NN NNS TO NN IN NNP .
"Speaking to reporters after a Cabinet meeting , Mr. Maliki said he decided to present his nominations directly to lawmakers , after failing to reach a consensus among the main political blocs .",O O O O O B-org O O B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"VBG TO NNS IN DT NNP NN , NNP NNP VBD PRP VBD TO VB PRP$ NNS RB TO NNS , IN VBG TO VB DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NNS ."
Mr. Maliki said he feels reaching a consensus has become almost impossible .,B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD PRP VBZ VBG DT NN VBZ VBN RB JJ .
"Iraq 's new national unity government was sworn in on May 20 , without the interior and defense ministers .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ JJ NN NN VBD VBN IN IN NNP CD , IN DT NN CC NN NNS ."
"The two positions are key to improving the country 's security situation amid escalating sectarian , factional and terrorist violence .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT CD NNS VBP JJ TO VBG DT NN POS NN NN IN VBG NN , JJ CC JJ NN ."
