Hoshyar Zebari Iraqi Foreign Minister Hoshyar Zebari has met U.S. Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice in Washington for talks on the situation in war-torn Iraq .,O O B-gpe O B-per I-per I-per O O B-geo B-per O B-org B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP IN NNP IN NNS IN DT NN IN JJ NNP .
"Mr. Zebari and Ms. Rice told reporters Wednesday after the meeting the United States is committed to completing its mission in Iraq and , in Mr. Zebari 's words , "" standing by the Iraqi people . """,B-per B-org I-org B-per I-per O O B-tim O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-per B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O,"NNP NNP CC NNP NNP VBD NNS NNP IN DT NN DT NNP NNPS VBZ VBN TO VBG PRP$ NN IN NNP CC , IN NNP NNP POS NNS , RQU NN IN DT JJ NNS . LQU"
"On Tuesday , Mr. Zebari spoke at United Nations headquarters in New York , praising the work of U.S.-led troops to combat insurgent attacks in the country .",O B-tim O B-per B-org O O B-org I-org O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , NNP NNP VBD IN NNP NNP NN IN NNP NNP , VBG DT NN IN JJ NNS TO VB JJ NNS IN DT NN ."
"Meanwhile , Defense Secretary Donald Rumsfeld has warned Iraq 's neighbors not to offer medical aid or haven to insurgent leader Abu Musab al-Zarqawi .",O O B-org B-per I-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O,"RB , NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNP POS NNS RB TO VB JJ NN CC NN TO JJ NN NNP NNP NNP ."
He says any such effort would be associating with al-Qaida .,O O O O O O O O O B-org O,PRP VBZ DT JJ NN MD VB VBG IN NNP .
"In Iraq , a suicide bomber blew up his car at a checkpoint near Baghdad International Airport , wounding 15 civilians .",O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O,"IN NNP , DT NN NN VBD RP PRP$ NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP , VBG CD NNS ."
