President Bush says the United States remains committed to helping victims of the Indian Ocean tsunami rebuild their lives .,B-per I-per O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ DT NNP NNPS VBZ JJ TO VBG NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP VB PRP$ NNS .
"In a statement issued by the White House as the President left for a vacation at his Texas ranch , Mr. Bush says the thoughts and prayers of the American people are with those who suffered from the tragedy .",O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-per O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN VBN IN DT NNP NNP IN DT NNP VBD IN DT NN IN PRP$ NNP NN , NNP NNP VBZ DT NNS CC NNS IN DT JJ NNS VBP IN DT WP VBD IN DT NN ."
"He also praised the efforts and generosity of the U.S. armed services , relief workers and all those who contributed to the relief effort .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP RB VBD DT NNS CC NN IN DT NNP JJ NNS , NN NNS CC PDT DT WP VBD TO DT NN NN ."
