A former CIA official has acknowledged the United States has sent terrorism suspects to other countries for interrogation .,O O B-org O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNP NN VBZ VBN DT NNP NNPS VBZ VBN NN NNS TO JJ NNS IN NN .
The former head of the CIA 's unit in charge of pursuing al-Qaida Mike Scheuer admitted in an interview aired Sunday some terrorism suspects have been sent to countries where they might have been tortured .,O O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-org B-per I-per O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN IN DT NNP POS NN IN NN IN VBG NNP NNP NNP VBD IN DT NN VBN NNP DT NN NNS VBP VBN VBN TO NNS WRB PRP MD VB VBN VBN .
"In comments aired in the same program , former British ambassador to Uzbekistan Craig Murray accused Washington of knowingly accepting information from suspects tortured in the central Asian nation .",O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-org I-org I-org O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNS VBN IN DT JJ NN , JJ JJ NN TO NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP IN RB VBG NN IN NNS VBN IN DT JJ JJ NN ."
Mr. Scheuer said a process known as rendition began during the Clinton administration .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-per O O,NNP NNP VBD DT NN VBN IN NN VBD IN DT NNP NN .
The Bush administration has publicly stated the United States does not hand over people to countries that allow torture .,O B-org O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBZ RB VBN DT NNP NNPS VBZ RB VB IN NNS TO NNS WDT VBP NN .
