Rescue officials say at least 12 bodies have been recovered from a mudslide in northern Colombia that may have buried another 145 .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim I-tim O,NN NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBP VBN VBN IN DT NN IN JJ NNP WDT MD VB VBN DT CD .
"Torrential rains caused the mudslide that engulfed dozens of homes Sunday outside Colombia 's second-largest city , Medellin .",O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O B-per O,"NNP NNS VBD DT NN WDT VBD NNS IN NNS NNP IN NNP POS JJ NN , NNP ."
Colombian President Juan Manuel Santos said the unusually heavy rainfalls could leave more than 2 million people homeless .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT RB JJ NNS MD VB JJR IN CD CD NNS JJ .
"Before Sunday 's disaster , heavy rains had killed around 170 people this year in Colombia .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"IN NNP POS NN , JJ NNS VBD VBN IN CD NNS DT NN IN NNP ."
"In neighboring Venezuela , driving rains have triggered flooding and cave-ins that have killed 34 people and left an estimated 90,000 people homeless .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN VBG NNP , VBG NNS VBP VBN NN CC NNS WDT VBP VBN CD NNS CC VBD DT JJ CD NNS JJ ."
"Officials blame the downpours on the La Nina weather phenomenon , during which cooler-than-normal water temperatures exist in the Tropical Pacific Ocean .",O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNS VBP DT NNS IN DT NNP NNP NN NN , IN WDT JJ NN NNS VBP IN DT NNP NNP NNP ."
