"The World Health Organization has confirmed more than 20 new cases of polio in Indonesia , bringing the total in the two-month outbreak to 100 .",O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-tim O O O O,"DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN JJR IN CD JJ NNS IN NN IN NNP , VBG DT NN IN DT JJ NN TO CD ."
The latest cases were found in the provinces of Banten and West Java .,O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,DT JJS NNS VBD VBN IN DT NNS IN NNP CC NNP NNP .
"One case was recently reported on Sumatra Island , indicating the sometimes crippling disease has spread beyond the main island of Java .",O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,"CD NN VBD RB VBN IN NNP NNP , VBG DT RB JJ NN VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
"Millions of children in Indonesia have already received emergency vaccinations against polio , which has reappeared in the country after a 10-year absence .",O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"NNS IN NNS IN NNP VBP RB VBN NN NNS IN NN , WDT VBZ VBN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN ."
