Iran has rejected Western allegations that it has encouraged violent protests over the publication of cartoons depicting the Prophet Muhammad .,B-geo O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,NNP VBZ VBN JJ NNS IN PRP VBZ VBN JJ NNS IN DT NN IN NNS VBG DT NNP NNP .
"In Tehran , Foreign Ministry spokesman Hamid Reza Asefi singled U.S. Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice and Danish officials for making such accusations .",O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-per I-per I-per O B-geo O O B-org B-per I-per O B-gpe O O O O O O,"IN NNP , NNP NNP NN NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP CC JJ NNS IN VBG JJ NNS ."
"He called for Western apologies to the Muslim world for the cartoons , and promises not to make "" such blunders "" in the future .",O O O B-per O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD IN JJ NNS TO DT NNP NN IN DT NNS , CC VBZ RB TO VB LQU JJ NNS LQU IN DT NN ."
"In Turkey , thousands of people rallied Sunday in that country 's largest protest against the cartoons , first published in Denmark .",O B-org O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"IN NNP , NNS IN NNS VBD NNP IN DT NN POS JJS NN IN DT NNS , RB VBN IN NNP ."
"Violence and threats have led Denmark to withdraw its diplomats from Iran , Syria and Indonesia .",O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O,"NN CC NNS VBP VBN NNP TO VB PRP$ NNS IN NNP , NNP CC NNP ."
"In Pakistan , the United Nations has limited the movement of staff and supplies because of anti-Western protests .",O B-geo O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN NN CC NNS IN IN JJ NNS ."
Secretary of State Rice says the protests across the Muslim world could spin out of control if governments refuse to urge their citizens to remain calm .,O O B-org B-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP IN NNP NNP VBZ DT NNS IN DT NNP NN MD VB IN IN NN IN NNS VBP TO VB PRP$ NNS TO VB JJ .
