Lebanese authorities say 12 people were injured in a blast on a crowded street in predominantly Christian East Beirut Friday .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo B-tim O,JJ NNS VBP CD NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN RB JJ NNP NNP NNP .
Security officials say the bomb was placed near a car and destroyed several vehicles parked on Rue Monot Street filled with restaurants and nightclubs,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O,NN NNS VBP DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NN CC VBD JJ NNS VBN IN NNP NNP NNP VBD IN NNS CC NNS
"In the last few months , Lebanon has seen a wave of car bomb explosions , mainly assassinations of anti-Syrian politicians and journalists .",O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ JJ NNS , NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN NN NN NNS , RB NNS IN JJ NNS CC NNS ."
Friday 's blast followed by several hours the visit to Beirut of U.S. Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice .,B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O B-org B-per I-per O,NNP POS NN VBD IN JJ NNS DT NN TO NNP IN NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP .
"She was in the Lebanese capital on a brief , unannounced visit to meet with top government officials .",O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN , JJ NN TO VB IN JJ NN NNS ."
