"This week , the United Nations is expected to issue an appeal for up to 40 million dollars to help Somalia recover from last week ’s tsunami .",O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-nat O,"DT NN , DT NNP NNPS VBZ VBN TO VB DT NN IN RB TO CD CD NNS TO VB NNP VB IN JJ NN POS NN ."
"The latest death toll in Somalia is around 140 , according to figures from the transitional government .",O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJS NN NN IN NNP VBZ IN CD , VBG TO NNS IN DT JJ NN ."
Elballa Hagona is the Acting UN Humanitarian Coordinator for Somalia .,B-org I-org O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,NNP NNP VBZ DT VBG NNP NNP NNP IN NNP .
"From Nairobi , he told English to Africa reporter Joe De Capua that the assessment of the country continues and a final report should be available in a few days .",O B-geo O O O B-org O B-geo O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"IN NNP , PRP VBD NNP TO NNP NN NNP NNP NNP IN DT NN IN DT NN VBZ CC DT JJ NN MD VB JJ IN DT JJ NNS ."
