China 's minister for Taiwan affairs is in Washington for talks with U.S. officials .,B-geo O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O,NNP POS NN IN NNP NNS VBZ IN NNP IN NNS IN NNP NNS .
A U.S. State Department spokesman says Chen Yunlin met Wednesday with Deputy Secretary of State Richard Armitage .,O B-org I-org I-org O O B-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O B-per I-per O,DT NNP NNP NNP NN VBZ NNP NNP VBD NNP IN NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP .
The two sides have been ruled separately since the end of civil war in 1949 .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT CD NNS VBP VBN VBN RB IN DT NN IN JJ NN IN CD .
"The United States switched its diplomatic recognition from Taipei to Beijing in 1979 , but Washington remains Taiwan 's top arms supplier .",O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-tim O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O,"DT NNP NNPS VBD PRP$ JJ NN IN NNP TO NNP IN CD , CC NNP VBZ NNP POS JJ NNS NN ."
