"Former U.S. President Bill Clinton has donated a one-year supply of AIDS medication to treat 2,500 HIV-positive children in Rwanda .",O B-org B-per I-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN NNP NN TO VB CD JJ NNS IN NNP .
"The donation was made in Kigali Saturday on behalf of the Clinton Foundation , a charitable organization founded by the former president .",O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD VBN IN NNP NNP IN NN IN DT NNP NNP , DT JJ NN VBN IN DT JJ NN ."
"Mr. Clinton flew to Rwanda from Kenya , where he and the minister of health Charity Ngilu launched a program to double the number of children receiving the life-prolonging treatments .",B-per I-per O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD TO NNP IN NNP , WRB PRP CC DT NN IN NN NN NNP VBD DT NN TO VB DT NN IN NNS VBG DT JJ NNS ."
"Mr. Clinton 's foundation says it has a goal of giving 10,000 children in at least 10 countries access to AIDS medication by the end of the year .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O,NNP NNP POS NN VBZ PRP VBZ DT NN IN VBG CD NNS IN IN JJS CD NNS NN TO NNP NN IN DT NN IN DT NN .
The former president says Rwanda is a leader in the battle against HIV / AIDS .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBZ NNP VBZ DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP .
He says the number of people receiving AIDS medicine there has tripled over the past year .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,PRP VBZ DT NN IN NNS VBG NNP NN EX VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NN .
"Mr. Clinton is wrapping up a six-nation tour of Africa , where he is reviewing AIDS initiatives created by his foundation .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBG RP DT JJ NN IN NNP , WRB PRP VBZ VBG NNP NNS VBN IN PRP$ NN ."
