Iraqi officials say at least 19 people are dead after Sunni Arab insurgents clashed with police and members of a Shi'ite militia south of Baghdad Thursday .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O,JJ NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBP JJ IN NNP NNP NNS VBD IN NNS CC NNS IN DT NNP NN NN IN NNP NNP .
Among the dead were two policemen and 17 members of radical cleric Moqtada al-Sadr 's Mehdi Army .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O B-org I-org O,IN DT NN VBD CD NNS CC CD NNS IN JJ NN NNP NNP POS NNP NNP .
"Officials say the fighting erupted when militia members , with the help of police , tried to rescue a fellow fighter who was abducted by insurgents .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP DT NN VBD WRB NN NNS , IN DT NN IN NNS , VBD TO VB DT JJ NN WP VBD VBN IN NNS ."
"The fighting comes as Sunni Arab , Shi'ite and Kurdish political groups try to forge alliances ahead of Friday 's deadline to register for December 's parliamentary elections .",O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-tim O O O O,"DT NN VBZ IN NNP NNP , NNP CC NNP JJ NNS VBP TO VB NNS RB IN NNP POS NN TO VB IN NNP POS JJ NNS ."
"On Wednesday , three Sunni Arab groups agreed to form a coalition , and Thursday there are reports that Shi'ite leaders are close to reaching a deal .",O B-tim O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , CD NNP NNP NNS VBD TO VB DT NN , CC NNP EX VBP NNS IN NNP NNS VBP RB TO VBG DT NN ."
The main Kurdish parties have said they will keep their alliance from last January 's election .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,DT JJ JJ NNS VBP VBN PRP MD VB PRP$ NN IN JJ NNP POS NN .
