President Bush has met with representatives of major pharmaceutical companies to discuss ways of fighting a possible bird flu outbreak in humans .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NNS IN JJ JJ NNS TO VB NNS IN VBG DT JJ NN NN NN IN NNS .
"The U.S. Secretary of Health and Human Services , Michael Leavitt , said discussions at Friday 's White House meeting focused on the potential of a pandemic and preparedness for such a crisis .",O B-org O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O B-tim O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP IN NNP CC NNP NNPS , NNP NNP , VBD NNS IN NNP POS NNP NNP NN VBD IN DT NN IN DT JJ CC NN IN JJ DT NN ."
He said the vaccine industry has expressed vigorous support and willingness to help the country prepare .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT NN NN VBZ VBN JJ NN CC NN TO VB DT NN VB .
A White House spokesman said the goal is to expand the currently limited capacity for manufacturing a vaccine and to establish the necessary public health infrastructure .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NN VBD DT NN VBZ TO VB DT RB VBN NN IN VBG DT NN CC TO VB DT JJ JJ NN NN .
"Separately , the United States hosted an international conference in Washington on Thursday and Friday on ways to prevent an epidemic , including prompt reporting of virus outbreaks and donor funding for affected countries .",O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , DT NNP NNPS VBD DT JJ NN IN NNP IN NNP CC NNP IN NNS TO VB DT NN , VBG JJ NN IN NN NNS CC NN NN IN JJ NNS ."
"Experts warn the bird flu virus could mutate and pass easily among humans , possibly causing a global pandemic .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP DT NN NN NN MD VB CC VB RB IN NNS , RB VBG DT JJ NN ."
