Burmese authorities have arrested at least 39 supporters of pro-democracy leader Aung San Suu Kyi before they could reach temples to pray for her release .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN IN JJS CD NNS IN JJ NN NNP NNP NNP NNP IN PRP MD VB NNS TO VB IN PRP$ NN .
"A spokesman for the opposition National League for Democracy and witnesses say the activists were arrested Tuesday in different areas around the former capital , Rangoon .",O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-org O,"DT NN IN DT NN NNP NNP IN NNP CC NNS VBP DT NNS VBD VBN NNP IN JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN , NNP ."
Aung San Suu Kyi 's supporters began holding weekly prayer vigils on May 1 .,B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,NNP NNP NNP NNP POS NNS VBD VBG JJ NN NNS IN NNP CD .
The Nobel peace laureate has spent most of the past 17 years under house arrest .,O B-art O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O,DT NNP NN NN VBZ VBN JJS IN DT JJ CD NNS IN NN NN .
Her most recent term ends on May 27 .,O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,PRP$ RBS JJ NN VBZ IN NNP CD .
"On Monday , more than 50 former world leaders , including three former U.S. presidents called on Burma to free the pro-democracy leader .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"IN NNP , JJR IN CD JJ NN NNS , VBG CD JJ NNP NNS VBD IN NNP TO VB DT JJ NN ."
Aung San Suu Kyi 's opposition party made a similar appeal .,B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP POS NN NN VBD DT JJ NN .
