United Nations Secretary-General Ban Ki-moon heads to Sudan on Monday to press the government to clear the way for a U.N. peacekeeping force in the country 's troubled Darfur region .,B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ TO VB IN NNP TO VB DT NN TO VB DT NN IN DT NNP NN NN IN DT NN POS JJ NNP NN .
"Last week , Mr. Ban said he is deeply concerned about an escalation of violence that has caused hundreds of deaths in Darfur during the past few weeks .",O O O B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim I-tim O O,"JJ NN , NNP NNP VBD PRP VBZ RB JJ IN DT NN IN NN WDT VBZ VBN NNS IN NNS IN NNP IN DT JJ JJ NNS ."
"U.N. officials say he plans to urge Sudanese President Omar al-Bashir to accept the speedy deployment of 26,000 peacekeepers .",B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBP PRP VBZ TO VB JJ NNP NNP NNP TO VB DT JJ NN IN CD NNS .
Mr. Ban 's six-day trip to Africa will also include stops in Libya and Chad .,B-per B-org O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,NNP NNP POS JJ NN TO NNP MD RB VB NNS IN NNP CC NNP .
