"The Indonesian military says it is preparing to withdraw about 1,200 troops from Aceh province - its first pullout in accordance with a peace deal reached with separatist rebels there .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBZ PRP VBZ VBG TO VB IN CD NNS IN NNP NN IN PRP$ JJ NN IN NN IN DT NN NN VBN IN JJ NNS RB .
"The rebels turned in a second batch of more than 100 weapons Friday to international monitors in the provincial capital , Banda Aceh .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"DT NNS VBD IN DT JJ NN IN JJR IN CD NNS NNP TO JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN , NNP NNP ."
"An agreement reached last month calls for the withdrawal of about half the government 's 60,000 troops from the province and the disarming of the Free Aceh rebels by the end of the year .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBN JJ NN VBZ IN DT NN IN IN PDT DT NN POS CD NNS IN DT NN CC DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNS IN DT NN IN DT NN .
"On Thursday , the guerilla fighters turned in about 78 weapons .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , DT NN NNS VBD IN IN CD NNS ."
"More than 1,300 Indonesian police left Aceh on Wednesday ahead of the military troops withdrawals .",O O O B-gpe O O B-org O B-tim O O O O O O O,JJR IN CD JJ NNS VBD NNP IN NNP RB IN DT JJ NNS NNS .
The peace deal aims to end 29 years of fighting in Aceh .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NN NN VBZ TO VB CD NNS IN VBG IN NNP .
