Former Pakistani Prime Minister Benazir Bhutto narrowly escaped twin bombings in Karachi shortly after midnight local time that killed at least 125 people .,O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O B-tim O O O O O O O,JJ JJ JJ NN NNP NNP RB VBD JJ NNS IN NNP RB IN NN JJ NN WDT VBD IN JJS CD NNS .
Authorities say more than 260 others were wounded in what is being called one of the deadliest bombings in Pakistan 's history .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,NNS VBP JJR IN CD NNS VBD VBN IN WP VBZ VBG VBN CD IN DT JJS NNS IN NNP POS NN .
The attacks marred what was to have been Ms. Bhutto 's triumphant return to Pakistan after eight years in self-imposed exile .,O O O O O O O O B-per B-org O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O,DT NNS VBD WP VBD TO VB VBN NNP NNP POS NN NN TO NNP IN CD NNS IN JJ NN .
"The explosions struck near an armored truck carrying Ms. Bhutto , causing carnage and panic among hundreds of thousands of people gathered in the streets to witness her return .",O O O O O O O O B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS VBD IN DT JJ NN VBG NNP NNP , VBG NN CC NN IN NNS IN NNS IN NNS VBN IN DT NNS TO VB PRP$ NN ."
"Ms. Bhutto was not hurt in the suspected suicide attack and was evacuated safely to a family residence , Bilawal House in Karachi .",B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-geo O,"NNP NNP VBD RB VBN IN DT JJ NN NN CC VBD VBN RB TO DT NN NN , NNP NNP IN NNP ."
Islamic militants earlier threatened suicide bomb attacks against Ms. Bhutto .,O O O O O O O O B-per B-org O,JJ NNS RBR JJ NN NN NNS IN NNP NNP .
"But she denounced the threats , saying her return to Pakistan was a risk worth taking .",O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"CC PRP VBD DT NNS , VBG PRP$ NN TO NNP VBD DT NN JJ VBG ."
