"Pakistani President Pervez Musharraf has withdrawn a law that imposed curbs on the media , following criticism both in Pakistan and abroad .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN WDT VBD NNS IN DT NNS , VBG NN DT IN NNP CC RB ."
Government officials say General Musharraf agreed to the decision after meeting with a delegation of Pakistani broadcasters Saturday .,O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-tim O,NN NNS VBP NNP NNP VBD TO DT NN IN VBG IN DT NN IN JJ NNS NNP .
"Information Minister Mohammed Ali Durrani says that , in return , Pakistan 's Broadcasters Association has agreed to prepare a code of conduct that will ensure what he called "" respect for national institutions "" like the armed forces and the judiciary .",B-org O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ IN , IN NN , NNP POS NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB DT NN IN NN WDT MD VB WP PRP VBD LQU NN IN JJ NNS RQU IN DT JJ NNS CC DT NN ."
"The media legislation , which was issued last Monday , allowed authorities to seize equipment , revoke licenses , and seal the premises of broadcasters deemed to be operating illegally .",O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS NN , WDT VBD VBN JJ NNP , VBD NNS TO VB NN , VB NNS , CC VB DT NNS IN NNS VBN TO VB VBG RB ."
Broadcasters said the law was an effort to silence them for their extensive coverage of anti-government protests against the president 's decision to suspend Chief Justice Iftikhar Mohammed Chaudhry on charges of abuse of power .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org B-per I-per O O O O O O O,NNS VBD DT NN VBD DT NN TO VB PRP IN PRP$ JJ NN IN JJ NNS IN DT NN POS NN TO VB NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP IN NNS IN NN IN NN .
