Afghan officials say U.S.-led coalition and Afghan troops have recaptured a Taleban-occupied district killing at least 15 rebels .,B-gpe O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP JJ NN CC JJ NNS VBP VBN DT JJ NN VBG IN JJS CD NNS .
"The forces took control late Friday of the Chora district of southern Uruzgan province , days after the Taleban captured the area .",O O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O B-org O O O O,"DT NNS VBD NN JJ NNP IN DT NNP NN IN JJ NNP NN , NNS IN DT NNP VBD DT NN ."
"In another incident , security officials say they killed 12 suspected Taleban militants and captured 18 more when rebels attacked a police checkpoint in southern Afghanistan .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"IN DT NN , NN NNS VBP PRP VBD CD JJ NNP NNS CC VBD CD JJR WRB NNS VBD DT NN NN IN JJ NNP ."
"Suspected Taleban rebels stormed the checkpoint late Friday north of Kandahar city , setting off hours of fighting .",O B-org O O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"VBN NNP NNS VBD DT NN JJ NNP NN IN NNP NN , VBG RP NNS IN NN ."
A provincial spokesman says four police officers were wounded in the attack .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBZ CD NN NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN .
"Also Friday , rebels attacked police in neighboring Helmand province , wounding four officers .",O B-tim O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"RB NNP , NNS VBD NNS IN JJ NNP NN , VBG CD NNS ."
Authorities rounded up 18 men after the attack .,O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBD RP CD NNS IN DT NN .
