The son of Libyan leader Moammar Gadhafi says Libya expects to be taken off the U.S. list of nations that sponsor terrorism by the end of this year .,O O O B-gpe O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O,DT NN IN JJ NN NNP NNP VBZ NNP VBZ TO VB VBN RP DT NNP NN IN NNS WDT VBP NN IN DT NN IN DT NN .
Seif el-Islam told reporters late Monday that he also believes the United States and Libya will soon exchange ambassadors for the first time in more than three decades .,B-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,NNP NNP VBD NNS RB NNP IN PRP RB VBZ DT NNP NNPS CC NNP MD RB VB NNS IN DT JJ NN IN JJR IN CD NNS .
"However , a U.S. State Department spokesman says there are still issues to be addressed before Libya can be removed from the terror list and resume full diplomatic ties with Washington .",O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"RB , DT NNP NNP NNP NN VBZ EX VBP RB NNS TO VB VBN IN NNP MD VB VBN IN DT NN NN CC VB JJ JJ NNS IN NNP ."
"The United States and Libya restored low-level diplomatic relations in June 2004 , after a gap of 24 years .",O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O B-tim O O,"DT NNP NNPS CC NNP VBD JJ JJ NNS IN NNP CD , IN DT NN IN CD NNS ."
"The move came after Libya abruptly ended its pursuit of weapons of mass destruction , and admitted responsibility for the 1988 bombing of a U.S. Pan Am jetliner over Scotland .",O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-geo O,"DT NN VBD IN NNP RB VBD PRP$ NN IN NNS IN NN NN , CC VBD NN IN DT CD NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NN IN NNP ."
