Iraq 's interim President Ghazi al-Yawar has urged all parties - except those tainted by violence - to participate in the process of forming the country 's next government following Sunday 's landmark election .,B-geo O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O,NNP POS JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NNS IN IN DT VBN IN NN : TO VB IN DT NN IN VBG DT NN POS JJ NN VBG NNP POS NN NN .
"Mr. al-Yawar , who is a Sunni Arab , said Tuesday even Sunni Muslim parties that called for a boycott of the vote should participate .",B-per I-per O O O O B-per I-per O O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP , WP VBZ DT NNP NNP , VBD NNP RB NNP NNP NNS WDT VBD IN DT NN IN DT NN MD VB ."
"In a similar message Monday , interim Prime Minister Iyad Allawi urged Iraqis to unite after Sunday 's election , which he called a major blow to insurgents .",O O O O B-tim O O B-per O B-per I-per O B-gpe O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN NNP , JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNS TO VB IN NNP POS NN , WDT PRP VBD DT JJ NN TO NNS ."
"Also Tuesday , Iraqi authorities eased restrictions and reopened the country 's borders that were closed to curb violence during the vote .",O B-tim O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB NNP , JJ NNS VBD NNS CC VBD DT NN POS NNS WDT VBD VBN TO VB NN IN DT NN ."
