Georgia 's foreign minister says Russian forces have returned to a disputed village near the boundary of the country 's breakaway region of South Ossetia .,B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP POS JJ NN VBZ JJ NNS VBP VBN TO DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN DT NN POS JJ NN IN NNP NNP .
"Grigol Vashadze told journalists late Friday that Russian troops had re-established their positions in Perevi , just hours after European Union monitors negotiated and confirmed their withdrawal from the area .",B-per I-per O O O B-tim O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD NNS RB NNP IN JJ NNS VBD VBN PRP$ NNS IN NNP , RB NNS IN NNP NNP VBZ VBN CC VBN PRP$ NN IN DT NN ."
The EU mission did not comment on the latest development .,O B-org O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBD RB VB IN DT JJS NN .
Georgia had accused Russia of violating the EU-brokered ceasefire agreement by refusing to withdraw its forces from Perevi .,B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP VBD VBN NNP IN VBG DT JJ NN NN IN VBG TO VB PRP$ NNS IN NNP .
"Russia later withdrew its forces from most of Georgia , but kept them in South Ossetia and another breakaway region , Abkhazia .",B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP RB VBD PRP$ NNS IN JJS IN NNP , CC VBD PRP IN NNP NNP CC DT NN NN , NNP ."
"In Washington , the U.S. State Department issued a warning Friday against traveling to both regions due to an increased potential for violence .",O B-geo O O B-org I-org I-org O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , DT NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN NNP IN VBG TO DT NNS JJ TO DT VBN NN IN NN ."
