The upper house of Russia 's parliament has overwhelmingly approved extending the presidential term from four to six years .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,DT JJ NN IN NNP POS NN VBZ RB VBN VBG DT JJ NN IN CD CC CD NNS .
"Lawmakers in the upper house voted 144 - 1 in favor of the measure , less than a week after Russia 's lower house , the State Duma , voted in favor of the change .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN DT JJ NN VBD CD : CD IN NN IN DT NN , JJR IN DT NN IN NNP POS JJR NN , DT NNP NNP , VBD IN NN IN DT NN ."
President Dmitri Medvedev proposed the extension of the president 's term earlier this month .,B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN DT NN POS NN RBR DT NN .
"Opposition groups fear the change could be used as an excuse to call an early election in which Vladimir Putin , who now serves as prime minister , could run for the presidency .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NN NNS VBP DT NN MD VB VBN IN DT NN TO VB DT JJ NN IN WDT NNP NNP , WP RB VBZ IN JJ NN , MD VB IN DT NN ."
The constitutional amendment must now be approved by at least two-thirds of regional legislatures .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN MD RB VB VBN IN IN JJS NNS IN JJ NNS .
The bill also extends the term of Duma members from four to five years .,O O O O O O O B-org O O O O B-tim O O,DT NN RB VBZ DT NN IN NNP NNS IN CD CC CD NNS .
