Ecuador 's President Rafael Correa is expected to call for the shutdown of the opposition-controlled Congress as a new assembly begins to rewrite the country 's constitution .,B-geo O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB IN DT NN IN DT JJ NNP IN DT JJ NN VBZ TO VB DT NN POS NN .
The assembly launched its first session Thursday to start making the changes .,O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O,DT NN VBD PRP$ JJ NN NNP TO VB VBG DT NNS .
"Mr. Correa 's leftist political movement , Pais , controls more than 60 percent of the assembly .",B-per I-per O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP POS JJ JJ NN , NNP , VBZ JJR IN CD NN IN DT NN ."
"He has called on the body to dissolve Congress , which has blocked many of his proposed reforms .",O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBZ VBN IN DT NN TO VB NNP , WDT VBZ VBN NN IN PRP$ VBN NNS ."
The president says the current Congress is corrupt and inefficient .,O O O O O B-org O O O O O,DT NN VBZ DT JJ NNP VBZ JJ CC JJ .
He says he wants to use the assembly to curb the influence of traditional political parties .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ PRP VBZ TO VB DT NN TO VB DT NN IN JJ JJ NNS .
Mr. Correa 's opponents say he is trying to grab more power .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP POS NNS VBP PRP VBZ VBG TO VB JJR NN .
The assembly will have six months to prepare a final draft of a new constitution and present it to voters in a referendum .,O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN MD VB CD NNS TO VB DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN CC VB PRP TO NNS IN DT NN .
