A new opinion poll in Israel shows the country 's ruling Likud party would suffer a crushing defeat in parliamentary elections scheduled for March .,O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT JJ NN NN IN NNP VBZ DT NN POS NN NNP NN MD VB DT VBG NN IN JJ NNS VBN IN NNP .
"The survey , published in Wednesday 's edition of the daily Yedioth Ahronot newspaper , indicates the right-wing Likud would win only 10 seats in the Knesset , down from its current total of 40 .",O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O,"DT NN , VBN IN NNP POS NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP NN , VBZ DT JJ NNP MD VB RB CD NNS IN DT NNP , RB IN PRP$ JJ NN IN CD ."
"Prime Minister Ariel Sharon 's new centrist Kadima party would gain 34 seats , while Labor would win 27 seats .",B-per O B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP POS JJ NN NNP NN MD VB CD NNS , IN NNP MD VB CD NNS ."
The poll 's release comes hours before elder statesman Shimon Peres is expected to announce whether he will bolt from the Labor party and join forces with the prime minister .,O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN POS NN VBZ NNS IN NN NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB IN PRP MD VB IN DT NNP NN CC VB NNS IN DT JJ NN .
