"The U.S. Ambassador to China visited a U.S. citizen serving a 16-year prison sentence for tax fraud , and said he hoped the man would be released soon .",O B-org O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NN TO NNP VBD DT NNP NN VBG DT JJ NN NN IN NN NN , CC VBD PRP VBD DT NN MD VB VBN RB ."
"Ambassador Clark Randt said Friday , he is worried about the health of businessman Jude Shao , a graduate of a prestigious California business school at Stanford University who has served nearly half his sentence in a prison on the outskirts of Shanghai .",O B-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP , PRP VBZ VBN IN DT NN IN NN NNP NNP , DT NN IN DT JJ NNP NN NN IN NNP NNP WP VBZ VBN RB PDT PRP$ NN IN DT NN IN DT NNS IN NNP ."
Mr. Randt says he is deeply concerned about Shao 's medical condition and hoped the Chinese government would consider him for prompt medical parole .,B-per I-per O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ RB JJ IN NNP POS JJ NN CC VBD DT JJ NN MD VB PRP IN JJ JJ NN .
"Shao 's family has applied for his release on parole , citing heart conditions .",B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NN VBZ VBN IN PRP$ NN IN NN , VBG NN NNS ."
"The Chinese-born , naturalized U.S. citizen was detained in 1998 on charges that his medical equipment sales company based in San Francisco evaded taxes in China .",O O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-geo O,"DT JJ , JJ NNP NN VBD VBN IN CD IN NNS IN PRP$ JJ NN NNS NN VBN IN NNP NNP VBD NNS IN NNP ."
Shao 's supporters contend he was wrongly accused after refusing to accept bribes .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NNS VBP PRP VBD RB VBN IN VBG TO VB NNS .
