The Organization of American States has warned that Venezuela 's plans to close a privately-owned television station may undermine press freedom in that South American nation .,B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT NNP IN NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NNP POS NNS TO VB DT JJ NN NN MD VB NN NN IN DT JJ JJ NN .
OAS Secretary-General Jose Miguel Insulza Friday called on Venezuela 's government to reconsider the move against Radio Caracas Television .,B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD IN NNP POS NN TO VB DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP .
Venezuela 's President Hugo Chavez accuses the station of supporting a failed military coup against him in 2002 .,B-geo O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP POS NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT NN IN VBG DT VBN JJ NN IN PRP IN CD .
He has warned that he will not renew RCTV 's license when it expires in March .,O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-tim O,PRP VBZ VBN IN PRP MD RB VB NNP POS NN WRB PRP VBZ IN NNP .
Insulza said any alleged violations by the station should be addressed through the Venezuelan courts .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,NNP VBD DT VBN NNS IN DT NN MD VB VBN IN DT JJ NNS .
RCTV president Marcel Granier told VOA 's Foro Interamericano program that his firm has yet to see a formal explanation of the government 's decision to end its license .,B-org O B-per I-per O B-org O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NN NNP NNP VBD NNP POS NNP NNP NN IN PRP$ NN VBZ RB TO VB DT JJ NN IN DT NN POS NN TO VB PRP$ NN .
He says the broadcasting license is valid until 2022 .,O O O O O O O O B-tim O,PRP VBZ DT NN NN VBZ JJ IN CD .
Granier also accused Mr. Chavez of human rights violations for persecuting journalists at the station and other independent reporters in the country .,B-per O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP RB VBD NNP NNP IN JJ NNS NNS IN VBG NNS IN DT NN CC JJ JJ NNS IN DT NN .
