"United Nations Secretary General Kofi Annan has urged Sudan 's government and Darfur rebels to conclude a peace agreement this year to prevent Darfur from descending into what he called "" complete lawlessness . """,B-org I-org B-per I-per I-per I-per O O B-gpe O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNP POS NN CC NNP NNS TO VB DT NN NN DT NN TO VB NNP IN VBG IN WP PRP VBD LQU JJ NN . LQU
Mr. Annan said in his monthly report to the U.N. Security Council Monday that there has been a dangerous increase in violence in Darfur .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,NNP NNP VBD IN PRP$ JJ NN TO DT NNP NNP NNP NNP IN EX VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN NN IN NNP .
He said a further deterioration of the security situation can only be averted if quick progress is made in peace negotiations between Sudan 's government and Darfur rebels .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-org O O,PRP VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NN NN MD RB VB VBN IN JJ NN VBZ VBN IN NN NNS IN NNP POS NN CC NNP NNS .
"A seventh round of peace talks was due to resume Monday , but African Union officials say they have been postponed .",O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN IN NN NNS VBD JJ TO VB NNP , CC NNP NNP NNS VBP PRP VBP VBN VBN ."
It is not clear when they will resume .,O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ RB JJ WRB PRP MD VB .
