"Honduras , the second poorest country in Central America , suffers from extraordinarily unequal distribution of income , as well as high underemployment .",B-geo O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP , DT JJ JJS NN IN NNP NNP , VBZ IN RB JJ NN IN NN , RB RB IN JJ NN ."
"While historically dependent on the export of bananas and coffee , Honduras has diversified its export base to include apparel and automobile wire harnessing .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN RB JJ IN DT NN IN NNS CC NN , NNP VBZ VBN PRP$ NN NN TO VB NN CC NN NN NN ."
"Nearly half of Honduras 's economic activity is directly tied to the US , with exports to the US accounting for 30 % of GDP and remittances for another 20 % .",B-tim I-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB NN IN NNP POS JJ NN VBZ RB VBN TO DT NNP , IN NNS TO DT NNP NN IN CD NN IN NN CC NNS IN DT CD NN ."
"The US-Central America Free Trade Agreement ( CAFTA ) came into force in 2006 and has helped foster foreign direct investment , but physical and political insecurity , as well as crime and perceptions of corruption , may deter potential investors ; about 70 % of FDI is from US firms .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-org O O,"DT JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP RRB VBD IN NN IN CD CC VBZ VBN VB JJ JJ NN , CC JJ CC JJ NN , RB RB IN NN CC NNS IN NN , MD VB JJ NNS ; IN CD NN IN NNP VBZ IN NNP NNS ."
"The economy registered sluggish economic growth in 2010 , insufficient to improve living standards for the nearly 60 % of the population in poverty .",O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD JJ JJ NN IN CD , JJ TO VB VBG NNS IN DT RB CD NN IN DT NN IN NN ."
The LOBO administration inherited a difficult fiscal position with off-budget debts accrued in previous administrations and government salaries nearly equivalent to tax collections .,O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBD DT JJ JJ NN IN JJ NNS VBN IN JJ NNS CC NN NNS RB JJ TO NN NNS .
"His government has displayed a commitment to improving tax collection and cutting expenditures , and attracting foreign investment .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP$ NN VBZ VBN DT NN TO VBG NN NN CC NN NNS , CC VBG JJ NN ."
This enabled Tegucigalpa to secure an IMF Precautionary Stand-By agreement in October 2010 .,O O B-geo O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-tim I-tim O,DT VBD NNP TO VB DT NNP NNP NNP NN IN NNP CD .
The IMF agreement has helped renew multilateral and bilateral donor confidence in Honduras following the ZELAYA administration 's economic mismanagement and the 2009 coup .,O B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org O O O O O O B-tim O O,DT NNP NN VBZ VBN VB JJ CC JJ NN NN IN NNP VBG DT NNP NN POS JJ NN CC DT CD NN .
