Turkey 's Prime Minister Recep Tayyip Erdogan has warned Iraqi Kurds against interfering in Turkey 's mainly Kurdish southeast .,B-geo O B-per I-per I-per I-per I-per O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O O O O O,NNP POS NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN JJ NNPS IN VBG IN NNP POS RB JJ NN .
"Mr. Erdogan said Monday in Ankara that Iraqi Kurds will , in his words , pay a heavy price if they interfere in southeastern Turkey .",B-per I-per O B-tim O B-geo O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP NNP VBD NNP IN NNP IN JJ NNPS MD , IN PRP$ NNS , VB DT JJ NN IN PRP VBP IN JJ NNP ."
The Turkish prime minister was reacting to comments Saturday by Iraqi Kurdish leader Massoud Barzani .,O B-gpe B-per O O O O O B-tim O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O,DT JJ JJ NN VBD VBG TO NNS NNP IN JJ NNP NN NNP NNP .
Barzani said Iraqi Kurds could intervene in Kurdish-majority cities in Turkey if Ankara intervened in mainly-Kurdish northern Iraq .,B-per O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O B-geo O,NNP VBD JJ NNP MD VB IN JJ NNS IN NNP IN NNP VBD IN JJ JJ NNP .
"Mr. Erdogan said Barzani "" overstepped the line "" and said Iraqi Kurds could be "" crushed "" under their own words .",B-per I-per O B-per O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD NNP LQU VBD DT NN RQU CC VBD JJ NNP MD VB LQU VBN LQU IN PRP$ JJ NNS .
Turkey is battling a Kurdish insurgency in the southeastern region .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBG DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN .
