"Egyptian security forces have detained nine more members of the country 's largest Islamist opposition group , the Muslim Brotherhood .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"JJ NN NNS VBP VBN CD JJR NNS IN DT NN POS JJS NN NN NN , DT NNP NNP ."
Security officials say local Brotherhood leaders from Greater Cairo and the Nile Delta were detained late Monday .,O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-org I-org O O O B-tim O,NN NNS VBP JJ NN NNS IN NNP NNP CC DT NNP NNP VBD VBN JJ NNP .
"Those detained include Mahmoud Ghozlan , a member of the group 's executive Guidance Council .",O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"DT VBN VBP NNP NNP , DT NN IN DT NN POS NN NNP NNP ."
The arrests came hours after opposition lawmakers announced their rejection of constitutional amendments favored by Egyptian President Hosni Mubarak .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O,DT NNS VBD NNS IN NN NNS VBD PRP$ NN IN JJ NNS VBN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP .
Opposition lawmakers say the amendments are aimed at blocking Islamists from politics .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NN NNS VBP DT NNS VBP VBN IN VBG NNS IN NNS .
"Egyptians are to vote in a referendum next month on the amendments after they are approved by parliament , which is dominated by the president 's party .",B-gpe O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP TO VB IN DT NN JJ NN IN DT NNS IN PRP VBP VBN IN NN , WDT VBZ VBN IN DT NN POS NN ."
"Members of the Islamist movement , running as independents , became the largest opposition block in parliament in the 2005 elections , winning about one-fifth of the seats .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-tim O O O O,"NNS IN DT NNP NN , VBG IN NNS , VBD DT JJS NN NN IN NN IN DT CD NNS , VBG IN NN IN DT NNS ."
