"But , he said Fallujah is not quite secure yet .",O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"CC , PRP VBD NNP VBZ RB RB JJ RB ."
U.S. troops going building-to-building in Fallujah have found what is believed to be a safe house containing evidence linked to wanted militant Abu Musab al-Zarqawi .,B-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O,NNP NNS VBG JJ IN NNP VBP VBN WP VBZ VBN TO VB DT JJ NN VBG NN VBN TO JJ NN NNP NNP NNP .
"General Settler did not confirm the find , but reporters with the troops in the city say photographs , notes , ammunition and letters thought to be from al-Zarqawi were found .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O,"NNP NNP VBD RB VB DT NN , CC NNS IN DT NNS IN DT NN VBP NNS , NNS , NN CC NNS VBN TO VB IN NNP VBD VBN ."
