"Reports from Somalia 's capital , Mogadishu , say fresh violence has left at least seven people dead since late Tuesday .",O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"NNS IN NNP POS NN , NNP , VBP JJ NN VBZ VBN IN JJS CD NNS JJ IN JJ NNP ."
Witnesses in Mogadishu 's southern Bulo Hubey neighborhood say gunmen with pistols shot three men in the area early Wednesday .,O O B-geo O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNS IN NNP POS JJ NNP NNP NN VBP NNS IN NNS VBN CD NNS IN DT NN JJ NNP .
"Late Tuesday , security officials and witnesses say two insurgents were killed when they attacked a police station near the Bakara market .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"RB NNP , NN NNS CC NNS VBP CD NNS VBD VBN WRB PRP VBD DT NN NN IN DT NNP NN ."
The market has been the scene of almost daily violence in recent weeks .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,DT NN VBZ VBN DT NN IN RB JJ NN IN JJ NNS .
Gunbattles between Islamic insurgents and government forces have killed thousands of Somalis and prompted tens of thousands of Mogadishu residents to flee the city .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,NNP IN NNP NNS CC NN NNS VBP VBN NNS IN NNS CC VBD NNS IN NNS IN NNP NNS TO VB DT NN .
"In other news Wednesday , Prime Minister Ali Mohamed Gedi is meeting supporters in the provincial town of Baidoa following reports that President Abdullahi Yusuf is pushing for a vote of no-confidence against Mr. Gedi .",O O O B-tim O B-per O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-per B-org O,"IN JJ NN NNP , NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBG NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NNP VBG NNS IN NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBG IN DT NN IN NN IN NNP NNP ."
