"Iran is warning Western governments of a global oil and banking crisis , if it is hit with international sanctions over its suspect nuclear program .",B-geo O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBG JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN CC NN NN , IN PRP VBZ VBN IN JJ NNS IN PRP$ JJ JJ NN ."
The official Iranian news agency quotes Economy Minister Davoud Danesh-Jafari as saying other countries will suffer as well as Iran if the United Nations Security Council levies sanctions .,O O B-gpe O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O,DT JJ JJ NN NN VBZ NNP NNP NNP NNP IN VBG JJ NNS MD VB RB RB IN NNP IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNS .
"He said imposing sanctions would "" make oil-rich countries anxious to transfer their capital out of European banks and into safer places . """,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD VBG NNS MD LQU VB JJ NNS JJ TO VB PRP$ NN IN IN JJ NNS CC IN JJR NNS . LQU
"On Wednesday , the International Atomic Energy Agency called an emergency session for February 2 , to hear the European case for referring Iran to the Security Council .",O B-tim O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org O,"IN NNP , DT NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN NN IN NNP CD , TO VB DT JJ NN IN VBG NNP TO DT NNP NNP ."
