Electoral officials in Haiti say Rene Preval 's lead in Tuesday 's presidential election has dipped below the 50 percent needed for an outright victory .,O O O B-geo O B-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP NNS IN NNP VBP NNP NNP POS NN IN NNP POS JJ NN VBZ VBN IN DT CD NN VBN IN DT JJ NN .
"Haiti 's election council said late Saturday that Preval , a former president , has 49.6 percent of the vote , with about three-quarters of the ballots counted .",B-geo O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NN NN VBD JJ NNP IN NNP , DT JJ NN , VBZ CD NN IN DT NN , IN IN NNS IN DT NNS VBN ."
"Hours earlier , thousands of Preval supporters cheered and chanted as they marched from the Cite Soleil slum through Port-au-Prince .",O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O,"NNS RB , NNS IN NNP NNS VBD CC VBD IN PRP VBD IN DT NNP NNP NN IN NNP ."
