U.N. Secretary-General Ban Ki-moon has picked up support from member nations in his effort to reorganize parts of the world body .,B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN RP NN IN NN NNS IN PRP$ NN TO VB NNS IN DT NN NN .
Mr. Ban spelled out his revised plans Friday during a closed-door meeting with ambassadors of the 192-member General Assembly .,B-per B-org O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,NNP NNP VBD RP PRP$ JJ NNS NNP IN DT JJ NN IN NNS IN DT JJ NNP NNP .
"He dropped an earlier controversial plan to merge the U.N. 's disarmament department with the political affairs unit , and place a lower-ranking assistant secretary-general in charge of the new division .",O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD DT JJR JJ NN TO VB DT NNP POS NN NN IN DT JJ NNS NN , CC VB DT JJ NN NN IN NN IN DT JJ NN ."
"Mr. Ban now says he will keep the departments separate , and he is proposing to place a higher-ranked undersecretary in charge of the department .",B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP RB VBZ PRP MD VB DT NNS JJ , CC PRP VBZ VBG TO VB DT JJ NN IN NN IN DT NN ."
The former South Korean diplomat ran into strong opposition over his initial plans shortly after he succeeded Kofi Annan on January 1 .,O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O B-tim I-tim O,DT JJ JJ JJ NN VBD IN JJ NN IN PRP$ JJ NNS RB IN PRP VBD NNP NNP IN NNP CD .
"On Friday , he further explained his proposals to split the peacekeeping department in two , with the second division responsible for field support .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , PRP RB VBD PRP$ NNS TO VB DT NN NN IN CD , IN DT JJ NN JJ IN NN NN ."
