Peruvian President Alejandro Toledo says he would support Miami as the permanent headquarters of a proposed Free Trade Area of the Americas .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP MD VB NNP IN DT JJ NN IN DT VBN NNP NNP NNP IN DT NNPS .
President Toledo made the comment Thursday in Lima at a joint news conference with Florida Governor Jeb Bush .,B-per I-per O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O B-per I-per O,NNP NNP VBD DT NN NNP IN NNP IN DT JJ NN NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP .
The governor has been leading a business delegation to Peru and Ecuador to promote trade and investment and lobby support for Miami to be the home of an F.T.A.A . Secretariat .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBN VBG DT NN NN TO NNP CC NNP TO VB NN CC NN CC NN NN IN NNP TO VB DT NN IN DT NNP . NNP .
"His brother , President Bush , has been pushing for a hemispheric free trade agreement , but several large South American countries oppose the move .",O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,"PRP$ NN , NNP NNP , VBZ VBN VBG IN DT JJ JJ NN NN , CC JJ JJ JJ JJ NNS VBP DT NN ."
The governor 's trip to South America comes one month after Peru and the United States reached a free trade agreement after 18 months of negotiations .,O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-tim O O O O,DT NN POS NN TO NNP NNP VBZ CD NN IN NNP CC DT NNP NNPS VBD DT JJ NN NN IN CD NNS IN NNS .
The United States is also trying to negotiate a similar deal with Ecuador and Colombia .,O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,DT NNP NNPS VBZ RB VBG TO VB DT JJ NN IN NNP CC NNP .
