Conditions in Somalia have reportedly worsened to their lowest point in many years .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNP VBP RB VBN TO PRP$ JJS NN IN JJ NNS .
The United Nations Food and Agrigulture Organization says extensive drought is causing a deteriorating humanitarian situation .,O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNPS NNP CC NNP NNP VBZ JJ NN VBZ VBG DT VBG JJ NN .
The UN Office for the Coordination of Humanitarian Affairs says that the humanitarian situation in the strife-torn nation is deteriorating partly because of rising insecurity .,O B-org I-org O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP IN DT NN IN NNP NNP VBZ IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN VBZ VBG RB IN IN VBG NN .
The International Committee of the Red Cross says it is extremely concerned about the humanitarian situation in Somalia .,O B-org I-org I-org O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNP NNP IN DT NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ RB JJ IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
Hashim Isse Wardere is a journalist with Frontier FM . Nightline ’s Akwei Thompson asked him how dire the situation is in Somalia .,B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-org I-org O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT NN IN NNP NNP . NNP POS NNP NNP VBD PRP WRB JJ DT NN VBZ IN NNP .
"Wardere said that more than half a million people have fled their homes , many of them from Mogadischu and south-central Somalia .",B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O,"NNP VBD IN JJR IN PDT DT CD NNS VBP VBN PRP$ NNS , NN IN PRP IN NNP CC JJ NNP ."
He said a large number of the refugees “ are coming by different ways to Kenyan refugee camps without full registration ... ”,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NNS LQU VBP VBG IN JJ NNS IN JJ NN NNS IN JJ NN : RQU
