Europe 's top security organization says Uzbek authorities violated the country 's constitution when they blocked television programs and websites during last month 's deadly clashes in Andijan .,B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP POS JJ NN NN VBZ JJ NNS VBD DT NN POS NN WRB PRP VBD NN NNS CC NNS IN JJ NN POS JJ NNS IN NNP .
"Citing reports from several international news agencies , websites and an official response from Tashkent , the Organization for Security and Cooperation in Europe says government authorities illegally harassed journalists and imposed an information blockade during the crisis of May 13 .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"VBG NNS IN JJ JJ NN NNS , NNS CC DT JJ NN IN NNP , DT NNP IN NNP CC NNP IN NNP VBZ NN NNS RB VBD NNS CC VBD DT NN NN IN DT NN IN NNP CD ."
"In its report released Wednesday , the OSCE says coordination between the government and press is an important part of the peaceful solution to crisis situations .",O O O O B-tim O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN PRP$ NN VBN NNP , DT NNP VBZ NN IN DT NN CC NN VBZ DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN TO NN NNS ."
OSCE media freedom representative Miklos Haraszti says his office is willing to help organize training courses to assist Uzbek authorities in resolving such events peacefully .,B-org O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,NNP NNS NN NN NNP NNP VBZ PRP$ NN VBZ JJ TO VB VB NN NNS TO VB JJ NNS IN VBG JJ NNS RB .
