Egypt says it will allow Sudanese who are seeking asylum to stay in the country while their cases are being reviewed by the United Nations refugee agency .,B-org O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O,NNP VBZ PRP MD VB JJ WP VBP VBG NN TO VB IN DT NN IN PRP$ NNS VBP VBG VBN IN DT NNP NNP NN NN .
Officials had been threatening to deport more than 400 immigrants detained last month after police broke up a makeshift champ in Cairo .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNS VBD VBN VBG TO VB JJR IN CD NNS VBN JJ NN IN NNS VBD RP DT NN NN IN NNP .
Tuesday 's announcement followed a meeting between Egyptian President Hosni Mubarak and U.S. Vice President Dick Cheney in Cairo .,B-tim O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O B-geo B-per I-per I-per I-per O B-geo O,NNP POS NN VBD DT NN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP IN NNP .
A spokesman for Mr. Mubarak said the U.N. refugee agency has agreed to re-examine the cases of those whose asylum requests were rejected .,O O O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN NNP NNP VBD DT NNP NN NN VBZ VBN TO VB DT NNS IN DT WP$ NN NNS VBD VBN .
The violent clashes that resulted left 27 people dead .,O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNS WDT VBD VBN CD NNS JJ .
