World oil prices soared more than four dollars a barrel Monday as tropical storm Rita posed a potential new threat to oil production and refining along the U.S. Gulf Coast .,O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-nat O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O,NNP NN NNS VBD RBR IN CD NNS DT NN NNP IN JJ NN NNP VBD DT JJ JJ NN TO NN NN CC NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP .
"The price of crude oil for future delivery closed at 67 dollars and 39 cents a barrel in New York , about three dollars short of the all-time record high .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN JJ NN IN JJ NN VBD IN CD NNS CC CD NNS DT NN IN NNP NNP , IN CD NNS RB IN DT JJ NN NN ."
"Meantime , delegates to the Organization of Petroleum Exporting Countries say the group is set to allow members to supply up to two-million barrels a day of extra crude oil if the market needs it .",O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , VBZ TO DT NNP IN NNP NNP NNS VBP DT NN VBZ VBN TO VB NNS TO VB RP TO JJ NNS DT NN IN JJ JJ NN IN DT NN VBZ PRP ."
The proposal was discussed at a meeting Monday in Vienna .,O O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O,DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NN NNP IN NNP .
"The change would allow OPEC members to provide as much oil as refineries ask for , without regard for previous production limits or quotas .",O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN MD VB NNP NNS TO VB IN JJ NN IN NNS VBP IN , IN NN IN JJ NN NNS CC NNS ."
The decision is expected to be formally announced on Tuesday .,O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NN VBZ VBN TO VB RB VBN IN NNP .
