"United Nations Secretary-General Kofi Annan made a surprise visit to Iraq Saturday , arriving just as a bomb ripped through a market in the capital , killing at least five people .",B-org I-org I-org B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN NN TO NNP NNP , VBG RB IN DT NN VBD IN DT NN IN DT NN , VBG IN JJ CD NNS ."
Mr. Annan held a news conference with Prime Minister Ibrahim al-Jaafari after the two met in Baghdad .,B-per I-per O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP VBD DT NN NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP IN DT CD VBD IN NNP .
"He expressed support for a national reconciliation conference proposed by the Arab League to be held in Cairo , saying reconciliation is "" absolutely vital "" for Iraq .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"PRP VBD NN IN DT JJ NN NN VBN IN DT NNP NNP TO VB VBN IN NNP , VBG NN VBZ LQU RB JJ LQU IN NNP ."
"This is Mr. Annan 's first visit to the country since U.S.-led forces ousted Saddam Hussein in April , 2003 .",O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,"DT VBZ NNP NNP POS JJ NN TO DT NN IN JJ NNS VBN NNP NNP IN NNP , CD ."
"On Friday , U.S. Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice visited Iraq , and also urged Iraqis to set aside sectarian differences and participate in next month 's parliamentary elections .",O B-tim I-tim B-org O O B-org B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP , CC RB VBD NNS TO VB RP JJ NNS CC VB IN JJ NN POS JJ NNS ."
