"Comencini is best known for his 1953 film Pane , Amore e Fantasia ( Bread , Love and Dreams ) , which starred Gina Lollobrigida and Vittorio De Sica .",B-per O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O B-per I-per I-per O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O B-per I-per B-org I-org I-org I-org O,"NNP VBZ RB VBN IN PRP$ CD NN NN , NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP , NNP CC NNP RRB , WDT VBD NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP ."
The director often focused on children and childhood in his many films .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN RB VBD IN NNS CC NN IN PRP$ JJ NNS .
Two of Comencini 's daughters followed in his footsteps as filmmakers .,O O B-per O O O O O O O O O,CD IN NNP POS NNS VBD IN PRP$ NNS IN NNS .
"Cristina Comencini directed the highly acclaimed La Bestia Nel Cuore ( Do n't Tell ) , which was nominated for Best Foreign Language Film at Hollywood 's famed Academy Awards .",B-per I-per O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-geo O O B-org I-org O,"NNP NNP VBD DT RB VBN NNP NNP NNP NNP LRB VBP RB VB RRB , WDT VBD VBN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP IN NNP POS JJ NNP NNPS ."
