Non-governmental groups in Africa have launched a bid to prevent Sudan 's president from becoming chairman of the African Union .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,JJ NNS IN NNP VBP VBN DT NN TO VB NNP POS NN IN VBG NN IN DT NNP NNP .
"In a letter to African leaders , more than 40 such groups said giving the chairmanship to Sudan would undermine the AU 's credibility and jeopardize peacemaking efforts in Sudan 's Darfur region .",O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-org O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O,"IN DT NN TO JJ NNS , JJR IN CD JJ NNS VBD VBG DT NN TO NNP MD VB DT NNP POS NN CC VB VBG NNS IN NNP POS NNP NN ."
"The letter called Darfur 's humanitarian situation "" one of the worst in the world . "" and said Sudanese President Omar al-Bashir can not be trusted to lead a continental peace initiative .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD NNP POS JJ NN LQU CD IN DT JJS IN DT NN . LQU CC VBD JJ NNP NNP NNP MD RB VB VBN TO VB DT JJ NN NN .
The African Union is expected to vote on the issue at its summit next week in Khartoum .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB IN DT NN IN PRP$ NN JJ NN IN NNP .
The organization is currently chaired by Nigerian President Olusegun Obasanjo .,O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O,DT NN VBZ RB VBN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP .
"Traditionally , the country that hosts the annual AU summit assumes the chairmanship .",O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O,"RB , DT NN WDT VBZ DT JJ NNP NN VBZ DT NN ."
But that tradition was broken last year when Nigeria continued for a second 12-month term .,O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim I-tim O,CC DT NN VBD VBN JJ NN WRB NNP VBD IN DT JJ JJ NN .
