Uganda says peace talks with rebels of the Lord 's Resistance Army ( LRA ) will continue past Tuesday 's expiration of a unilateral government cease-fire .,B-org O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ NN NNS IN NNS IN DT NNP POS NNP NNP LRB NNP RRB MD VB IN NNP POS NN IN DT JJ NN NN .
Government officials in Kampala say Internal Affairs Minister Ruhakana Rugunda is traveling to Gulu for meetings with rebel leaders .,O O O B-geo O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O O O,NN NNS IN NNP VBP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBG TO NNP IN NNS IN JJ NNS .
"They say military operations will continue , but the door for talks remains open .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBP JJ NNS MD VB , CC DT NN IN NNS VBZ JJ ."
"The cease-fire began February 4 covering a limited area in the north , between the remote Gulu and Kitgum districts where LRA rebels are based .",O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O B-org O O O O,"DT NN VBD NNP CD VBG DT JJ NN IN DT NN , IN DT JJ NNP CC NNP NNS WRB NNP NNS VBP VBN ."
The limited truce was aimed at building trust following the first face-to-face talks in a decade in December .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,DT JJ NN VBD VBN IN VBG NN VBG DT JJ JJ NNS IN DT NN IN NNP .
