"The director of the U.S. Central Intelligence Agency , Porter Goss , says the al-Qaida terrorist network is vulnerable , but still dangerous .",O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP , VBZ DT NNP JJ NN VBZ JJ , CC RB JJ ."
"Testifying before a Senate panel Wednesday , Mr. Goss said while the United States and its allies have made gains against terrorism , it may only be a matter of time before al-Qaida or other groups try to use weapons of mass destruction .",O O O B-org O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O,"VBG IN DT NNP NN NNP , NNP NNP VBD IN DT NNP NNPS CC PRP$ NNS VBP VBN NNS IN NN , PRP MD RB VB DT NN IN NN IN NNP CC JJ NNS VBP TO VB NNS IN NN NN ."
"Mr. Goss said even if Osama bin Laden were captured , al-Qaida and other terrorist factions around the globe would remain resolute .",B-per I-per O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD RB IN NNP NNP NNP VBD VBN , NNP CC JJ JJ NNS IN DT NN MD VB JJ ."
The CIA director also named Iran and a nuclear-armed North Korea as threats to U.S. security .,O B-org O O O B-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-geo O O,DT NNP NN RB VBD NNP CC DT JJ NNP NNP IN NNS TO NNP NN .
"Mr. Goss said Pyongyang could resume testing of missiles capable of reaching the United States , and blamed Tehran for supporting what he called "" anti-coalition activities "" in Iraq .",B-per I-per O B-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP NNP VBD NNP MD VB NN IN NNS JJ IN VBG DT NNP NNPS , CC VBD NNP IN VBG WP PRP VBD LQU JJ NNS LQU IN NNP ."
