President Bush has issued an executive order that renews sanctions barring U.S. firms from conducting business with Iran .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN NN WDT VBZ NNS VBG NNP NNS IN VBG NN IN NNP .
The announcement Monday extends by one year sanctions initially imposed by then-President Bill Clinton in 1995 .,O O B-tim O O B-tim O O O O O O B-per I-per O B-tim O,DT NN NNP VBZ IN CD NN NNS RB VBN IN JJ NNP NNP IN CD .
"The executive order , which Mr. Bush has extended annually since 2003 , prohibits most imports and exports between the U.S. and Iran , including dealings in Iranian crude oil .",O O O O O B-per I-per O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O O,"DT NN NN , WDT NNP NNP VBZ VBN RB IN CD , VBZ RBS NNS CC NNS IN DT NNP CC NNP , VBG NNS IN JJ JJ NN ."
"A spokesman for the White House National Security Council , Frederick Jones , said the actions and policies of Tehran led to the continuation of sanctions .",O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP , VBD DT NNS CC NNS IN NNP VBD TO DT NN IN NNS ."
"He said those include its support for terrorists , its "" abysmal "" human rights record and its pursuit of nuclear weapons .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD DT VBP PRP$ NN IN NNS , PRP$ LQU JJ RQU JJ NNS NN CC PRP$ NN IN JJ NNS ."
The United States has maintained various sanctions against Iran since the seizure of the U.S. embassy in Tehran in 1979 .,O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo B-tim O B-tim I-tim O B-geo O O B-geo O B-tim O,DT NNP NNPS VBZ VBN JJ NNS IN NNP IN DT NN IN DT NNP NN IN NNP IN CD .
