"Niger is a landlocked , Sub-Saharan nation , whose economy centers on subsistence crops , livestock , and some of the world 's largest uranium deposits .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ DT JJ , JJ NN , WP$ NN VBZ IN NN NNS , NN , CC DT IN DT NN POS JJS NN NNS ."
"Niger also has sizable reserves of oil , and oil production , refining , and exports are expected to grow significantly between 2011 and 2016 .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,"NNP RB VBZ JJ NNS IN NN , CC NN NN , NN , CC NNS VBP VBN TO VB RB IN CD CC CD ."
"Drought , desertification , and strong population growth have undercut the economy .",B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP , NN , CC JJ NN NN VBP VBN DT NN ."
"Niger shares a common currency , the CFA franc , and a common central bank , the Central Bank of West African States ( BCEAO ) , with seven other members of the West African Monetary Union .",B-gpe O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,"NNP NNS DT JJ NN , DT NNP NN , CC DT JJ JJ NN , DT NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP RRB , IN CD JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
"In December 2000 , Niger qualified for enhanced debt relief under the International Monetary Fund program for Highly Indebted Poor Countries ( HIPC ) and concluded an agreement with the Fund on a Poverty Reduction and Growth Facility ( PRGF ) .",O B-tim I-tim O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O O B-org O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-org O O,"IN NNP CD , NNP VBD IN JJ NN NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNPS LRB NNP RRB CC VBD DT NN IN DT NN IN DT NN NN CC NN NN LRB NNP RRB ."
"Debt relief provided under the enhanced HIPC initiative significantly reduces Niger 's annual debt service obligations , freeing funds for expenditures on basic health care , primary education , HIV / AIDS prevention , rural infrastructure , and other programs geared at poverty reduction .",O O O O O O B-org O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NN NN VBN IN DT JJ NNP NN RB VBZ NNP POS JJ NN NN NNS , VBG NNS IN NNS IN JJ NN NN , JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP NN , JJ NN , CC JJ NNS VBN IN NN NN ."
"In December 2005 , Niger received 100 % multilateral debt relief from the IMF , which translates into the forgiveness of approximately US $ 86 million in debts to the IMF , excluding the remaining assistance under HIPC .",O B-tim I-tim O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-org O,"IN NNP CD , NNP VBD CD NN JJ NN NN IN DT NNP , WDT VBZ IN DT NN IN RB NNP $ CD CD IN NNS TO DT NNP , VBG DT VBG NN IN NNP ."
"In 2010 , the Niger economy was recovering from the effects of a 2009 drought that reduced grain and cowpea production and decimated livestock herds .",O B-tim O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN CD , DT NNP NN VBD VBG IN DT NNS IN DT CD NN WDT VBD NN CC NN NN CC VBN NN NNS ."
The economy was also hurt when the international community cut off non-humanitarian aid in response to TANDJA 's moves to extend his term as president .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD RB VBN WRB DT JJ NN VBD RP JJ NN IN NN TO NNP POS NNS TO VB PRP$ NN IN NN .
Nearly half of the government 's budget is derived from foreign donor resources .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,RB NN IN DT NN POS NN VBZ VBN IN JJ NN NNS .
"Future growth may be sustained by exploitation of oil , gold , coal , and other mineral resources .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN MD VB VBN IN NN IN NN , NN , NN , CC JJ NN NNS ."
