Zambia 's three main opposition parties have formed an alliance to oppose current President Levy Mwanawasa in elections later this year .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O B-tim O O O,NNP POS CD JJ NN NNS VBP VBN DT NN TO VB JJ NNP NNP NNP IN NNS RB DT NN .
The new United Democratic Alliance said Wednesday that it will select a single presidential candidate at a joint convention .,O O B-org I-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP IN PRP MD VB DT JJ JJ NN IN DT JJ NN .
"The new alliance is made up of three parties : the United Party for National Development , Forum for Democracy and Development , and United National Independence Party .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-org I-org B-tim I-tim O,"DT JJ NN VBZ VBN IN IN CD NNS IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP NNP , NNP IN NNP CC NNP , CC NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
"Some political experts see the new umbrella party as a significant threat to President Mwanawasa , who is seeking a second term .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNS VBP DT JJ NN NN IN DT JJ NN TO NNP NNP , WP VBZ VBG DT JJ NN ."
"No date has been set yet for Zambia 's presidential , parliamentary and local government elections .",O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ VBN VBN RB IN NNP POS JJ , JJ CC JJ NN NNS ."
