Iraqi authorities say at least 19 Iraqis - including 18 national guardsmen - have been killed in a suicide car bomb attack north of Baghdad .,B-gpe O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS : VBG CD JJ NNS : VBP VBN VBN IN DT NN NN NN NN NN IN NNP .
The officials say the bomber targeted a bus carrying the guardsmen near the town of Balad .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNS VBP DT NN VBD DT NN VBG DT NNS IN DT NN IN NNP .
"In a separate attack , the U.S. military says four Iraqi policemen were killed and another wounded Sunday in the nearby town Samarra .",O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-geo O,"IN DT JJ NN , DT NNP NN VBZ CD JJ NNS VBD VBN CC DT VBN NNP IN DT JJ NN NNP ."
"Meanwhile , U.S. military officials say two new brigade-sized military units of Iraqi and U.S. troops have been deployed in the northern city of Mosul , ahead of January 30th elections .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim I-tim O O,"RB , NNP JJ NNS VBP CD JJ JJ JJ NNS IN JJ CC NNP NNS VBP VBN VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , RB IN NNP JJ NNS ."
"A U.S. brigade consists of 2,000 to 4,000 troops .",O B-geo O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBZ IN CD TO CD NNS .
"Last month , the Pentagon ordered 12,000 more U.S. troops to Iraq to bolster security ahead of the polls .",O O O O B-org O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN , DT NNP VBD CD JJR NNP NNS TO NNP TO VB NN RB IN DT NNS ."
"U.S. General John Abizaid said as many as 8,000 members of the new force would be deployed in Mosul .",B-org I-org B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD RB JJ IN CD NNS IN DT JJ NN MD VB VBN IN NNP .
