Palestinian Authority President Mahmoud Abbas has canceled an appearance at a rally celebrating Israel 's withdrawal from the Gaza Strip .,B-gpe O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo I-geo O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN DT NN VBG NNP POS NN IN DT NNP NNP .
An aide told the Associated Press Mr. Abbas was concerned about the presence of gunmen in the crowd .,O O O O B-org I-org B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD DT NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD VBN IN DT NN IN NNS IN DT NN .
Organizers said the rally at an abandoned Jewish settlement in Gaza had been called to show unity among rival militant groups and support for the Palestinian Authority .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,NNS VBD DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP VBD VBN VBN TO VB NN IN JJ JJ NNS CC NN IN DT JJ NNP .
"Earlier Wednesday , a top aide to Mr. Abbas said the Palestinian leader will demand that armed militants disarm immediately after parliamentary elections early next year .",O B-tim O O O O O B-per I-per O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RBR NNP , DT JJ NN TO NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN MD VB IN JJ NNS VBP RB IN JJ NNS RB JJ NN ."
"Meanwhile , Palestinian police have begun sealing the Gaza-Egyptian border , to stop Palestinian revelers from crossing into Egypt .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O,"RB , JJ NNS VBP VBN VBG DT JJ NN , TO VB JJ NNS IN VBG IN NNP ."
