"Insurgents have attacked Shi'ite Muslims in Baghdad Friday , during that community 's most solemn religious period .",O O O B-org I-org O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP VBN NNP NNPS IN NNP NNP , IN DT NN POS RBS JJ JJ NN ."
"In two of them , suicide bombers approached worshippers leaving Friday prayers at two mosques and detonated their explosives .",O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,"IN CD IN PRP , NN NNS VBD NNS VBG NNP NNS IN CD NNS CC VBD PRP$ NNS ."
Authorities say the third attack was from a mortar shell that landed on a cafe near a mosque in a Shi'ite neighborhood .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O,NNS VBP DT JJ NN VBD IN DT NN NN WDT VBD IN DT NN IN DT NN IN DT NNP NN .
"The mosques were packed with Shi'ite worshippers marking the first two days of mourning for the revered Imam Hussein , who was the grandson of the Prophet Mohammed .",O O O O O B-org O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"DT NNS VBD VBN IN NNP NNS VBG DT JJ CD NNS IN VBG IN DT JJ NNP NNP , WP VBD DT NN IN DT NNP NNP ."
Observances will culminate Saturday .,O O O B-tim O,NNS MD VB NNP .
The attacks also come a day after Iraq 's Electoral Commission certified election results that solidify Shi'ite dominance in the new National Assembly .,O O O O O O O B-geo O B-org I-org O O O O O B-org O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT NNS RB VBP DT NN IN NNP POS NNP NNP VBD NN NNS WDT VBP NNP NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP .
