U.S. Defense Secretary Donald Rumsfeld is in Lithuania Sunday for a two-day NATO meeting .,B-org O O B-per I-per O O B-geo B-tim O O B-tim B-org O O,NNP NN NN NNP NNP VBZ IN NNP NNP IN DT JJ NNP NN .
"NATO defense ministers in the capital , Vilnius will focus their discussions on Ukraine 's defense policy .",B-org O O O O O O B-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"NNP NN NNS IN DT NN , NNP MD VB PRP$ NNS IN NNP POS NN NN ."
The meeting follows a visit to Ukraine last week by NATO Secretary General Jaap de Hoop Scheffer .,O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-org B-per B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,DT NN VBZ DT NN TO NNP JJ NN IN NNP NN NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP .
He told leaders in Kiev the opportunity to join NATO will remain open to Ukraine if the former Soviet republic makes essential democratic reforms .,O O O O B-geo O O O O B-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD NNS IN NNP DT NN TO VB NNP MD VB JJ TO VB IN DT JJ JJ NN VBZ JJ JJ NNS .
Ukrainian President Viktor Yushchenko has said gaining NATO and European Union membership are among his country 's top goals .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O B-org O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN VBG NNP CC NNP NNP NN VBP IN PRP$ NN POS JJ NNS .
Some analysts predict Ukraine could be admitted to the defense alliance as early as 2008 .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NNS VBP NNP MD VB VBN TO DT NN NN RB RB IN CD .
"Mr. Rumsfeld arrived Saturday in Lithuania after wrapping up an Asian tour that took him to China , South Korea and Mongolia .",B-per I-per O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O,"NNP NNP VBD NNP IN NNP IN VBG RP DT JJ NN WDT VBD PRP TO NNP , NNP NNP CC NNP ."
