"Croatian skiing great Janica Kostelic has announced she will compete in all five disciplines at the Winter Olympics , which open in Turin , Italy Friday .",B-gpe O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-geo O B-geo B-tim O,"JJ NN JJ NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP MD VB IN DT CD NNS IN DT NNP NNPS , WDT VBZ IN NNP , NNP NNP ."
Kostelic won three gold medals at the 2002 Salt Lake City Games .,B-geo O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo I-geo O O,NNP VBD CD NN NNS IN DT CD NNP NNP NNP NNPS .
"Despite battling bad knees throughout her career , Kostelic says she made the decision to compete in all five Olympic events after consulting with her father , Ante Kostelic and coach , Vedran Pavlek .",O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O B-per I-per O,"IN VBG JJ NNS IN PRP$ NN , NNP VBZ PRP VBD DT NN TO VB IN DT CD NNP NNS IN VBG IN PRP$ NN , NNP NNP CC NN , NNP NNP ."
"Kostelic won the slalom , giant slalom and combined four years ago to become only the third Alpine skier to win three golds at a single Olympics - Toni Sailer in 1956 and Jean-Claude Killy in 1968 are the others .",B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-tim O B-geo I-geo O B-tim O O O O,"NNP VBD DT NN , JJ NN CC VBN CD NNS RB TO VB RB DT JJ NNP NN TO VB CD NNS IN DT JJ NNP : NNP NNP IN CD CC NNP NNP IN CD VBP DT NNS ."
"In Turin , she will also race in the super-G and downhill .",O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , PRP MD RB VB IN DT NN CC NN ."
"This season on the World Cup tour , Kostelic became only the second woman to win five different disciplines in a season .",O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NN , NNP VBD RB DT JJ NN TO VB CD JJ NNS IN DT NN ."
