Nepal 's royal government has threatened to shut down a private radio station if it continues to defy a ban on broadcasting news .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS JJ NN VBZ VBN TO VB RP DT JJ NN NN IN PRP VBZ TO VB DT NN IN NN NN .
The Information and Communication Ministry said Thursday that Nepal FM could lose its license within a week for ignoring the ban .,B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-tim O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN CC NNP NNP VBD NNP IN NNP NNP MD VB PRP$ NN IN DT NN IN VBG DT NN .
"Nepal FM officials say they intend to fight the ban , adding that they will challenge the government order in a court , if necessary .",B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNS VBP PRP VBP TO VB DT NN , VBG IN PRP MD VB DT NN NN IN DT NN , IN JJ ."
Reporters are not allowed to criticize the government and security forces - or independently report on the communist insurgency .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP RB VBN TO VB DT NN CC NN NNS : CC RB NN IN DT NN NN .
"The king says the moves are necessary to deal with the Maoist insurgency that has killed more than 11,000 people since 1996 .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT NN VBZ DT NNS VBP JJ TO VB IN DT NNP NN WDT VBZ VBN JJR IN CD NNS IN CD .
