Leading Iraqi political groups have called for a delay in national elections scheduled for January 30 because of ongoing violence in the country .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O,VBG JJ JJ NNS VBP VBN IN DT NN IN JJ NNS VBN IN NNP CD IN IN JJ NN IN DT NN .
At least 15 mostly Sunni and Kurdish political groups say the elections should be delayed by up to six months .,O O O O B-per O B-per O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O,IN JJS CD RB NNP CC NNP JJ NNS VBP DT NNS MD VB VBN IN RB IN CD NNS .
"They issued their call Friday , after a meeting at the Baghdad home of influential Sunni politician Adnan Pachachi , who also has close ties to Washington .",O O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O,"PRP VBD PRP$ NN NNP , IN DT NN IN DT NNP NN IN JJ NNP NN NNP NNP , WP RB VBZ JJ NNS TO NNP ."
"The call for a postponement comes amid mounting violence , particularly in Sunni Muslim areas to the north and west of Baghdad .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NN IN DT NN VBZ IN VBG NN , RB IN NNP NNP NNS TO DT NN CC NN IN NNP ."
