President Bush and the U.S. State Department have sent greetings to those celebrating Nowruz - the Persian and Kurdish New Year .,B-per I-per O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O B-org I-org I-org O,NNP NNP CC DT NNP NNP NNP VBP VBN NNS TO DT VBG NNP IN DT NNP CC NNP NNP NNP .
"In a White House statement Monday , Mr. Bush called Nowruz a celebration of life and an opportunity to spend time with family and friends , and enjoy the beauty of nature .",O O B-org I-org O B-tim O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NNP NNP NN NNP , NNP NNP VBD NNP DT NN IN NN CC DT NN TO VB NN IN NN CC NNS , CC VB DT NN IN NN ."
The president and the State Department offered their best wishes for peace and prosperity in the New Year .,O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,DT NN CC DT NNP NNP VBD PRP$ JJS NNS IN NN CC NN IN DT NNP NNP .
"The Spring Equinox Monday marked the beginning of Nowruz , which is celebrated by people who trace their heritage to Iran , Afghanistan , Pakistan , Azerbaijan , Iraq , Turkey and Central Asia .",O B-org I-org B-tim O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-gpe O B-geo O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,"DT NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN NNP , WDT VBZ VBN IN NNS WP VBP PRP$ NN TO NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP CC NNP NNP ."
