China says it will begin holding jury trials next year as part of reforms aimed at getting the court system to give greater attention to financial fraud and other cases arising from the country 's sweeping economic changes .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ PRP MD VB VBG NN NNS JJ NN IN NN IN NNS VBN IN VBG DT NN NN TO VB JJR NN TO JJ NN CC JJ NNS VBG IN DT NN POS JJ JJ NNS .
State-run media including the official Xinhua news agency say jurors must have at least two years of university-level education .,O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O,JJ NNS VBG DT JJ NNP NN NN VBP NNS MD VB IN JJS CD NNS IN JJ NN .
"They would be elected to five-year terms , and then receive special training .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP MD VB VBN TO JJ NNS , CC RB VB JJ NN ."
"There was no explanation about how jury trials will differ from current proceedings , or how jurors ' elections will be conducted .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"EX VBD DT NN IN WRB NN NNS MD VB IN JJ NNS , CC WRB NNS POS NNS MD VB VBN ."
State media also quote the president of China 's Supreme People 's Court as saying the number of judges in the court system will rise by 10 percent .,O O O O O O O B-geo O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS RB VBP DT NN IN NNP POS NNP NNP POS NNP IN VBG DT NN IN NNS IN DT NN NN MD VB IN CD NN .
"The chief judge , Xiao Yang , promises a crackdown on offenses such as corruption and dereliction of duty , smuggling and intellectual-property theft .",O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN NN , NNP NNP , VBZ DT NN IN NNS JJ IN NN CC NN IN NN , VBG CC JJ NN ."
