"The officials said a drone aircraft fired two missiles Saturday at a compound east of Miranshah , in Pakistan 's North Waziristan tribal region .",O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O,"DT NNS VBD DT NN NN VBD CD NNS NNP IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , IN NNP POS NNP NNP JJ NN ."
They said some of those killed included foreigners .,O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT IN DT VBN VBD NNS .
"The suspected U.S. missile attack followed the arrival of the U.S. special envoy to Afghanistan and Pakistan , Richard Holbrooke , in Islamabad for talks with top Pakistani officials .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O,"DT JJ NNP NN NN VBD DT NN IN DT NNP JJ NN TO NNP CC NNP , NNP NNP , IN NNP IN NNS IN JJ JJ NNS ."
