Britain 's Foreign Secretary says China 's stand on Taiwan has made it more difficult for the European Union to end its embargo on weapons sales to Beijing .,B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP POS NNP NNP VBZ NNP POS NN IN NNP VBZ VBN PRP RBR JJ IN DT NNP NNP TO VB PRP$ NN IN NNS NNS TO NNP .
Jack Straw said in a British television interview Sunday that the political environment had worsened since China passed a law last week granting itself the right to attack Taiwan if it declared independence .,B-per I-per O O O B-gpe O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD IN DT JJ NN NN NNP IN DT JJ NN VBD VBN IN NNP VBD DT NN JJ NN VBG PRP DT NN TO VB NNP IN PRP VBD NN .
The European Union had been planning to lift the weapons ban this year .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBD VBN VBG TO VB DT NNS NN DT NN .
"But last Thursday , an EU official said the issue may now be delayed .",O O B-tim O O B-org O O O O O O O O O,"CC JJ NNP , DT NNP NN VBD DT NN MD RB VB VBN ."
Mr. Straw noted that the EU 's main policy-making body was not planning to consider the issue when it meets next Tuesday .,B-per I-per O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP NNP VBD IN DT NNP POS JJ NN NN VBD RB VBG TO VB DT NN WRB PRP VBZ JJ NNP .
"The United States has strongly opposed lifting the ban , saying the move could threaten Taiwan 's security .",O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,"DT NNP NNP VBZ RB VBN VBG DT NN , VBG DT NN MD VB NNP POS NN ."
The embargo goes back to China 's 1989 crackdown on pro-democracy protesters .,O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O,DT NN VBZ RB TO NNP POS CD NN IN JJ NNS .
