The relics of two early Christian saints have been returned to the seat of the Orthodox Church .,O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,DT NNS IN CD JJ NNP NNS VBP VBN VBN TO DT NN IN DT NNP NNP .
Ecumenical Patriarch Bartholomew escorted the relics of Saint John Chrysostom and Saint Gregory Nazianzen into the Cathedral of Saint George in Istanbul Saturday .,O B-per I-per O O O O B-per I-per I-per O B-per I-per I-per O O B-art O B-per I-per O B-geo B-tim O,NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NNS IN NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP IN DT NNP IN NNP NNP IN NNP NNP .
"Patriarch Bartholomew brought the relics back from Rome , where he received them from Pope John Paul during a joint service at the Vatican .",B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP NNP VBD DT NNS RB IN NNP , WRB PRP VBD PRP IN NNP NNP NNP IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP ."
Scholars say their remains were taken to Rome in 1204 after the Crusaders sacked Constantinople .,O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O B-org O B-geo O,NNS VBP PRP$ NNS VBD VBN TO NNP IN CD IN DT NNPS VBD NNP .
The return of the relics is part of Pope John Paul 's efforts to reconcile Rome with the Orthodox Churches .,O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org O,DT NN IN DT NNS VBZ NN IN NNP NNP NNP POS NNS TO VB NNP IN DT NNP NNP .
