Iraqi officials say 17 people were killed when three car bombs went off near Baghdad hotels that house foreign journalists .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP CD NNS VBD VBN WRB CD NN NNS VBD RB IN NNP NNS IN NN JJ NNS .
They say several other people were wounded by the blasts near the Palestine and Sheraton hotels .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O,PRP VBP JJ JJ NNS VBD VBN IN DT NNS IN DT NNP CC NNP NNS .
The third explosion was the largest and was videotaped by reporters at the scene .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBD DT JJS CC VBD VBN IN NNS IN DT NN .
"Meanwhile , Iraq 's election commission says it is examining votes in the province of Ninevah to determine if enough people there voted against the country 's draft constitution to veto it .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , NNP POS NN NN VBZ PRP VBZ VBG NNS IN DT NN IN NNP TO VB IN JJ NNS RB VBD IN DT NN POS NN NN TO VB PRP ."
Election officials say their audit shows that more than two-thirds of voters in two predominantly Sunni Arab provinces Anbar and Salahaddin voted no in the referendum .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim B-gpe B-tim I-tim O B-org O O O O O O,NN NNS VBP PRP$ NN VBZ IN JJR IN NNS IN NNS IN CD RB JJ JJ NNS NNP CC NNP VBD DT IN DT NN .
"But to fail , a third province must vote against the draft by the same margin .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"CC TO VB , DT JJ NN MD VB IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN ."
The constitution was approved in most other Iraqi provinces by an overwhelming majority .,O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,DT NN VBD VBN IN JJS JJ JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN .
