"Afghan officials say a suicide car bomber blew himself up near a convoy of foreign troops on the outskirts of Kabul , Tuesday , wounding at least three civilians and three foreign troops .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP DT NN NN NN VBD PRP RP IN DT NN IN JJ NNS IN DT NNS IN NNP , NNP , VBG IN JJS CD NNS CC CD JJ NNS ."
Authorities say the bomber targeted a NATO convoy outside a U.S. base on a main road out of Kabul .,O O O O O O B-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNS VBP DT NN VBD DT NNP NN IN DT NNP NN IN DT JJ NN IN IN NNP .
"Officials said the convoy was attacked on the road from the capital , Kabul , to Kandahar .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O,"NNS VBD DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NN IN DT NN , NNP , TO NNP ."
Sunday 's attack led to a long gun battle with insurgents that resulted in the death of five Taleban militants .,B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O,NNP POS NN VBD TO DT JJ NN NN IN NNS WDT VBD IN DT NN IN CD NNP NNS .
"In another development , Britain 's Defense Ministry said a British Royal Marine was killed during a military operation in southern Afghanistan on Sunday .",O O O O B-geo O B-org I-org O O B-gpe B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-tim O,"IN DT NN , NNP POS NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NNP NNP VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NNP IN NNP ."
The statement gave no other details .,O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD DT JJ NNS .
