Three Afghan civilians have been killed as NATO forces continue to battle Taleban insurgents in the southern part of the country .,O B-gpe O O O O O B-org O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O,CD JJ NNS VBP VBN VBN IN NNP NNS VBP TO VB NNP NNS IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN .
"In a written statement Tuesday , a NATO spokesman said two civilians were killed and four others were injured Monday during an artillery clash with Taleban militants .",O O O O B-tim O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-org O O,"IN DT JJ NN NNP , DT NNP NN VBD CD NNS VBD VBN CC CD NNS VBD VBN NNP IN DT NN NN IN NNP NNS ."
The statement said misdirected mortar fire near the town of Garmsir in Helmand province likely caused the deaths .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O,DT NN VBD VBN NN NN IN DT NN IN NNP IN NNP NN RB VBD DT NNS .
"In a separate incident today , coalition troops fired on a civilian vehicle speeding toward their position near Kandahar , killing its Afghan driver .",O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O,"IN DT JJ NN NN , NN NNS VBD IN DT JJ NN NN IN PRP$ NN IN NNP , VBG PRP$ JJ NN ."
"In a statement , NATO officials said the driver ignored several warnings to stop , prompting the troops to fire in self-defense .",O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN , NNP NNS VBD DT NN VBD JJ NNS TO VB , VBG DT NNS TO VB IN NN ."
Officials say both incidents are under investigation .,O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP DT NNS VBP IN NN .
