Afghan President Hamid Karzai has appointed a new cabinet that pushes out warlords and includes technocrats .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN WDT VBZ RP NNS CC VBZ NNS .
Mr. Karzai dropped two major figures from the Northern Alliance group of generals who helped the United States remove the Taleban from power in 2001 .,B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo B-org O O O B-tim O,NNP NNP VBD CD JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNP NN IN NNS WP VBD DT NNP NNPS VBP DT NNP IN NN IN CD .
"They are former Defense Minister Mohammed Qasim Fahim and Yunus Qanooni , who stepped down as education minister to run against Mr. Karzai for president .",O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O,"PRP VBP JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP , WP VBD RP IN NN NN TO VB IN NNP NNP IN NN ."
Abdul Rahim Wardak is the new defense minister .,B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ NN NN .
Mr. Karzai retained Interior Minister Ali Jalali and Foreign Minister Abdullah but he dropped Ashraf Ghani Ahmadzai as finance minister .,B-per I-per O O O B-per I-per O O B-per I-per O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O,NNP NNP VBD NN NN NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP CC PRP VBD NNP NNP NNP IN NN NN .
Anwar Ul-Haq Ahady is the new finance minister .,B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ NN NN .
"The president has included in the new cabinet the former warlord , Ismael Khan , who was ousted as governor of Herat in September .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-org O B-tim O,"DT NN VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NN DT JJ NN , NNP NNP , WP VBD VBN IN NN IN NNP IN NNP ."
