The Brazilian government says deforestation of the Amazon surged during the last five months of 2007 .,O B-gpe O O O O O B-org O O O O B-tim O B-tim I-tim O,DT JJ NN VBZ NN IN DT NNP VBD IN DT JJ CD NNS IN CD .
"The report , issued Wednesday , says that between August and December of last year more than 3,000 square kilometers of the world 's largest rain forest were cleared .",O O O O B-tim O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN , VBN NNP , VBZ IN IN NNP CC NNP IN JJ NN RBR IN CD JJ NNS IN DT NN POS JJS NN NN VBD VBN ."
Environment ministry officials say that number may be higher after they analyze satellite images with a higher resolution .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NN NNS VBP IN NN MD VB JJR IN PRP VBP JJ NNS IN DT JJR NN .
"Brazil 's environment minister , Marina Silva , and other ministers are meeting with President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva Thursday to discuss how to curb deforestation .",B-geo O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per I-per I-per B-tim O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NN NN , NNP NNP , CC JJ NNS VBP VBG IN NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP TO VB WRB TO VB NN ."
"Land in the Amazon is cleared to provide pasture for cattle , and later soy farmers move in to cultivate their crops .",O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NN IN DT NNP VBZ VBN TO VB NN IN NNS , CC RB JJ NNS VBP IN TO VB PRP$ NNS ."
