VOA-TV 's Craig Fitzpatrick talked with some people in the Washington area about their Olympics viewing habits and their impressions of China .,B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP POS NNP NNP VBD IN DT NNS IN DT NNP NN IN PRP$ NNS VBG NNS CC PRP$ NNS IN NNP .
Chris Simkins narrates the story .,B-per I-per O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ DT NN .
