"An Israeli soldier and a Palestinian militant have died in a shootout in the West Bank , further straining a three-month-old truce between militants and the army .",O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN CC DT JJ NN VBP VBN IN DT NN IN DT NNP NNP , RB VBG DT JJ NN IN NNS CC DT NN ."
"The Israeli army says the clash happened earlier Monday , while troops were searching for militants in a village near the Palestinian-controlled town of Tulkarem .",O B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT JJ NN VBZ DT NN VBD RBR NNP , IN NNS VBD VBG IN NNS IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
"Also Monday , the Israeli cabinet upgraded an Israeli college in the West Bank to university status .",O B-tim O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org O O O O,"RB NNP , DT JJ NN VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP TO NN NN ."
Prime Minister Ariel Sharon said the upgrade was part of a plan to strengthen Israeli settlements in the West Bank .,O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org O,JJ NN NNP NNP VBD DT NN VBD NN IN DT NN TO VB JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNP .
"Israeli building in the West Bank continues , despite the fact that the internationally-backed ( road map ) peace plan forbids such action .",B-gpe O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP VBZ , IN DT NN IN DT JJ LRB NN NN RRB NN NN VBP JJ NN ."
"Earlier , Israeli Cabinet minister Natan Sharansky resigned over Israel 's planned withdrawal from the Gaza Strip .",O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"RB , JJ NNP NN NNP NNP VBD IN NNP POS VBN NN IN DT NNP NNP ."
"He said the pullout would be "" a tragic mistake "" that leads to more violence .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT NN MD VB LQU DT JJ NN RQU WDT VBZ TO JJR NN .
