Iran 's government says it expects European Union foreign policy chief Javier Solana to visit the country soon for talks on a dispute about Iran 's nuclear program .,B-geo O O O O O B-org I-org O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,NNP POS NN VBZ PRP VBZ NNP NNP JJ NN NN NNP NNP TO VB DT NN RB IN NNS IN DT NN IN NNP POS JJ NN .
Iranian nuclear negotiator said officials are seriously considering a package of international incentives to convince Iran to abandon sensitive nuclear activities .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,JJ JJ NN VBD NNS VBP RB VBG DT NN IN JJ NNS TO VB NNP TO VB JJ JJ NNS .
Iran 's President Mahmoud Ahmadinejad has said his government will respond to the offer by mid-August .,B-geo O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP POS NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP$ NN MD VB TO DT NN IN NNP .
But Germany 's Foreign Minister Frank-Walter Steinmeier told Reuters news agency Monday that he doubts Western nations will wait so long for an answer .,O B-geo O O B-per I-per I-per O B-org O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC NNP POS NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP NN NN NNP IN PRP VBZ JJ NNS MD VB RB RB IN DT NN .
Tehran denies the allegation .,B-org O O O O,NNP VBZ DT NN .
