Ecuador has lodged a formal protest to the United States regarding the treatment last week of President Rafael Correa by U.S. immigration officials .,B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O B-geo O O O,NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN TO DT NNP NNPS VBG DT NN JJ NN IN NNP NNP NNP IN NNP NN NNS .
"Ecuador 's foreign ministry said Tuesday it had lodged the "" strongest protest "" to the U.S. government for the "" lack of basic manners "" shown to Mr. Correa at the international airport in Miami , Florida .",B-geo O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,"NNP POS JJ NN VBD NNP PRP VBD VBN DT LQU JJS NN RQU TO DT NNP NN IN DT LQU NN IN JJ NNS RQU VBN TO NNP NNP IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , NNP ."
It said the U.S. government had been told in advance of the president 's layover .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT NNP NN VBD VBN VBN IN NN IN DT NN POS NN .
"Mr. Correa refused to be searched by U.S. immigration officials last Thursday as he traveled through Miami on his way to Riyadh , Saudi Arabia , for the summit of the Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries .",B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-org O O B-org I-org I-org O,"NNP NNP VBD TO VB VBN IN NNP NN NNS JJ NNP IN PRP VBD IN NNP IN PRP$ NN TO NNP , NNP NNP , IN DT NN IN DT NNP IN DT NNP NNP NNPS ."
"Earlier this week , U.S. Ambassador to Quito Linda Jewell expressed regret over the incident , but said U.S. officials had not received advanced notice of Mr. Correa 's layover in Miami .",O O O O B-org I-org O B-org B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O B-geo O,"RBR DT NN , NNP NNP TO NNP NNP NNP VBD NN IN DT NN , CC VBD NNP NNS VBD RB VBN JJ NN IN NNP NNP POS NN IN NNP ."
