Central American defense and security ministers have agreed to form a rapid response force to cope with natural disasters .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ JJ NN CC NN NNS VBP VBN TO VB DT JJ NN NN TO VB IN JJ NNS .
The decision came Thursday at the end of a two-day conference in Miami hosted by U.S. Defense Secretary Donald Rumsfeld .,O O O B-tim O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim O O B-geo O O B-org I-org O B-per I-per O,DT NN VBD NNP IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP VBN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP .
"The ministers said they will take steps to set up joint military operations to respond to disasters such as Hurricane Stan , which recently devastated parts of Central America .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"DT NNS VBD PRP MD VB NNS TO VB RP JJ JJ NNS TO VB TO NNS JJ IN NNP NNP , WDT RB VBD NNS IN NNP NNP ."
"Secretary Rumsfeld also said Nicaraguan military officials gave assurances that some 1,000 Soviet-era surface to air missiles in their possession are secure .",O B-per O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP RB VBD JJ JJ NNS VBD NNS IN DT CD JJ NN TO VB NNS IN PRP$ NN VBP JJ .
U.S. officials fear the weapons could fall into the wrong hands .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBP DT NNS MD VB IN DT JJ NNS .
"The conference was also aimed at improving cooperation in maritime security , fighting drugs and crime , and other issues .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD RB VBN IN VBG NN IN JJ NN , VBG NNS CC NN , CC JJ NNS ."
Mexico and several other countries sent observers .,B-geo O O O O O O O,NNP CC JJ JJ NNS VBD NNS .
