The Sudanese government and the United Nations have signed an agreement Wednesday to boost humanitarian work in the volatile Darfur region .,O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O O,DT JJ NN CC DT NNP NNPS VBP VBN DT NN NNP TO VB JJ NN IN DT JJ NNP NN .
"Under the agreement , Khartoum is expected to give better access to aid groups trying to operate in Darfur .",O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"IN DT NN , NNP VBZ VBN TO VB JJR NN TO NN NNS VBG TO VB IN NNP ."
U.N. humanitarian chief John Holmes toured Darfur this week and warned that the effort to aid refugees is fragile and could fail if the situation in the western region deteriorates .,B-geo O O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP JJ NN NNP NNP VBD NNP DT NN CC VBD IN DT NN TO VB NNS VBZ JJ CC MD VB IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN NNS .
"Meanwhile , Sudanese President Omar al-Bashir has underlined his rejection of U.N. efforts to send a peacekeeping force into Darfur .",O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O,"RB , JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP$ NN IN NNP NNS TO VB DT NN NN IN NNP ."
He told the Arab summit in Saudia Arabia Wednesday that Sudan would only accept financial and logistic support from the United Nations .,O O O B-gpe O O B-geo I-geo B-tim O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,PRP VBD DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP NNP IN NNP MD RB VB JJ CC JJ NN IN DT NNP NNPS .
An ill-equipped African Union force has not been able to stop the violence in Darfur .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT JJ NNP NNP NN VBZ RB VBN JJ TO VB DT NN IN NNP .
"Fighting between Darfur rebels and militias backed by the Sudanese government has killed more than 200,000 people and displaced at least two million since 2003 .",O O B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,VBG IN NNP NNS CC NNS VBN IN DT JJ NN VBZ VBN JJR IN CD NNS CC VBN IN JJS CD CD IN CD .
