U.S. Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice says she hopes Congress will be able to act quickly on President Bush 's proposals for immigration reform .,B-org O O B-org B-per I-per O O O B-org O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O,NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ NNP MD VB JJ TO VB RB IN NNP NNP POS NNS IN NN NN .
"She spoke Wednesday to the Spanish-language television network Univision , one day before traveling to Mexico to discuss immigration and other issues .",O O B-tim O O O O O B-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD NNP TO DT JJ NN NN NNP , CD NN IN VBG TO NNP TO VB NN CC JJ NNS ."
"Ms. Rice said she is certain that over time , progress will be made on President Bush 's proposal for a temporary worker program .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD PRP VBZ JJ IN IN NN , NN MD VB VBN IN NNP NNP POS NN IN DT JJ NN NN ."
But she said it has to be implemented the right way .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC PRP VBD PRP VBZ TO VB VBN DT JJ NN .
"Mr. Bush has said it is time for an immigration policy that permits temporary guest workers to fill jobs Americans do not want , while rejecting amnesty for those who have broken the law and closing the borders to drug dealers and terrorists .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP VBZ NN IN DT NN NN WDT VBZ JJ NN NNS TO VB NNS NNS VBP RB VB , IN VBG NN IN DT WP VBP VBN DT NN CC VBG DT NNS TO NN NNS CC NNS ."
