Pakistani police say they have arrested six operatives of a banned Sunni Muslim extremist group who allegedly were planning to carry out a suicide attack on a Shi'ite mosque .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP PRP VBP VBN CD NNS IN DT VBN NNP NNP NN NN WP RB VBD VBG TO VB RP DT NN NN IN DT NNP NN .
Police arrested the suspects Friday in an early morning raid on their hideout in the rural town of Rahim Yar Khan in central Punjab province .,O O O O B-tim O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-geo O O,NNS VBN DT NNS NNP IN DT JJ NN NN IN PRP$ NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP NNP IN JJ NNP NN .
They say explosives and three explosive belts were recovered .,O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBP NNS CC CD JJ NNS VBD VBN .
Police say they were planning to target a Shi'ite place of worship in Rahim Yar Khan with a suicide attack when they were captured .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP PRP VBD VBG TO VB DT JJ NN IN NN IN NNP NNP NNP IN DT NN NN WRB PRP VBD VBN .
The would-be bomber was said to be among the six suspects .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBD VBN TO VB IN DT CD NNS .
"All of them are said to belong to Lashkar-e-Jhangvi , a group outlawed in 2001 .",O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O,"DT IN PRP VBP VBN TO VB TO NNP , DT NN VBN IN CD ."
Pakistan 's majority Sunni and minority Shi'ite communities largely co-exist in peace .,B-geo O O B-per O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NN NNP CC NN JJ NNS RB JJ IN NN .
But militants from the two sides have a history of violence that has claimed thousands of lives in the past decade .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,CC NNS IN DT CD NNS VBP DT NN IN NN WDT VBZ VBN NNS IN NNS IN DT JJ NN .
