The U.S. military in Iraq says U.S. forces killed nine Shi'ite insurgents during battles in the Sadr City and Mansur districts of Baghdad late Sunday and early Monday .,O B-geo O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O B-geo O B-tim O O B-tim O,DT NNP NN IN NNP VBZ NNP NNS VBD CD NNP NNS IN NNS IN DT NNP NNP CC NNP NNS IN NNP JJ NNP CC JJ NNP .
The clashes came hours after the wife of Iraqi President Jalal Talabani escaped unhurt from a roadside bomb attack that hit her motorcade in Baghdad .,O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNS VBD NNS IN DT NN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD NN IN DT NN NN NN WDT VBD PRP$ NN IN NNP .
The motorcade was taking Hiro Ibrahim Ahmed to a cultural event when the bomb went off in the capital 's Karrada district .,O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O,DT NN VBD VBG NNP NNP NNP TO DT JJ NN WRB DT NN VBD RB IN DT NN POS NNP NN .
"In Tehran Monday , Iranian Foreign Ministry spokesman Ali Hosseini said Iran will not hold a fourth round of talks with the U.S. on security in Iraq , as long as U.S. forces continue to attack Shi'ite militias in Baghdad .",O B-per B-tim O B-gpe B-org I-org O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O,"IN NNP NNP , JJ NNP NNP NN NNP NNP VBD NNP MD RB VB DT JJ NN IN NNS IN DT NNP IN NN IN NNP , RB RB IN NNP NNS VBP TO VB NNP NNS IN NNP ."
"The U.S. ambassador to Iraq , Ryan Crocker , and his Iranian counterpart , Hassan Kazemi Qomi , held three rounds of talks in Baghdad last year in the first direct diplomatic contacts between Washington and Tehran in nearly 30 years .",O B-geo O O B-geo O B-per I-per O O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-per O O B-tim O O,"DT NNP NN TO NNP , NNP NNP , CC PRP$ JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP , VBD CD NNS IN NNS IN NNP JJ NN IN DT JJ JJ JJ NNS IN NNP CC NNP IN RB CD NNS ."
