Local authorities say the blast occurred early Saturday .,O O O O O O O B-tim O,JJ NNS VBP DT NN VBD JJ NNP .
The military also reported the death of a soldier in a roadside bomb attack Friday .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NN RB VBD DT NN IN DT NN IN DT NN NN NN NNP .
The Iraqi government had imposed a curfew in Baghdad to help security forces control surging violence in the capital .,O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBD VBN DT NN IN NNP TO VB NN NNS VBP JJ NN IN DT NN .
"People and cars were ordered off the streets Friday after clashes broke out between insurgents , Shi'ite militia and U.S. and Iraqi security forces near the heavily-fortified Green Zone in Baghdad .",O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-gpe O O O O O B-org I-org O B-geo O,"NNS CC NNS VBD VBN IN DT NNS NNP IN NNS VBD RP IN NNS , NNP NN CC NNP CC JJ NN NNS IN DT JJ NNP NNP IN NNP ."
Several people were reported killed .,O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBD VBN VBN .
Prime Minister Nouri al-Maliki 's office said the curfew was lifted two hours after it began .,B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP POS NN VBD DT NN VBD VBN CD NNS IN PRP VBD .
