The price of crude oil is lower for a second day following a truce between Israel and Hezbollah .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-org O,DT NN IN JJ NN VBZ JJR IN DT JJ NN VBG DT NN IN NNP CC NNP .
"The market also had calmed on news from B.P. that oil will continue to flow , although at half-capacity , from North America 's largest oil field , Prudhoe Bay .",O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"DT NN RB VBD VBN IN NN IN NNP IN NN MD VB TO VB , IN IN NN , IN NNP NNP POS JJS NN NN , NNP NNP ."
B.P. earlier said it anticipated a complete shutdown of the Alaskan oil field during pipeline repairs .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP RB VBD PRP VBD DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN NN IN NN NNS .
Prices in New York dropped 38 cents to $ 73 a barrel Tuesday .,O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNS IN NNP NNP VBD CD NNS TO $ CD DT NN NNP .
New York 's crude oil market saw record highs July 14 of more than $ 78 a barrel on fears that the conflict in Lebanon could widen throughout the region .,B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,NNP NNP POS JJ NN NN VBD NN NNS NNP CD IN JJR IN $ CD DT NN IN NNS IN DT NN IN NNP MD VB IN DT NN .
