Afghan officials say 76 suspected Taleban militants were killed and some 30 were captured in a joint Afghan-U.S. military attack on rebel hideouts in the south of the country .,B-gpe O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP CD JJ NNP NNS VBD VBN CC DT CD VBD VBN IN DT JJ JJ JJ NN IN NN NNS IN DT NN IN DT NN .
Afghan officials described the fighting as some of the heaviest since the fall of the Taleban regime three and a half years ago .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-org B-tim I-tim I-tim O B-tim O O O,JJ NNS VBD DT NN IN DT IN DT JJS IN DT NN IN DT NNP NN CD CC DT JJ NNS RB .
The fighting took place in a region straddling the provinces of Kandahar and Zabol .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,DT NN VBD NN IN DT NN VBG DT NNS IN NNP CC NNP .
"Afghan officials said the battle began late Tuesday and lasted well into Wednesday , when Afghan and U.S. forces backed by warplanes and attack helicopters took on Taleban positions near the Pakistani border .",B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-tim O O B-gpe O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O B-gpe O O,"JJ NNS VBD DT NN VBD JJ NNP CC VBD RB IN NNP , WRB JJ CC NNP NNS VBN IN NNS CC NN NNS VBD RP NNP NNS IN DT JJ NN ."
"Officials said seven Afghan soldiers and five Afghan policemen were also killed during the fierce fighting , while five U.S. soldiers and two Afghan police officers were wounded .",O O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O,"NNS VBD CD JJ NNS CC CD JJ NNS VBD RB VBN IN DT JJ NN , IN CD NNP NNS CC CD JJ NNS NNS VBD VBN ."
