Beijing has criticized the European Parliament 's decision to maintain an arms sales embargo against China until the country improves its human rights record .,B-geo O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN DT NNP NNP POS NN TO VB DT NNS NNS NN IN NNP IN DT NN VBZ PRP$ JJ NNS NN .
"A Chinese Foreign Ministry spokeswoman , Zhang Qiyue , said the embargo is a Cold War relic that strains relations between China and the European Union .",O B-gpe B-org I-org O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org O,"DT JJ NNP NNP NN , NNP NNP , VBD DT NN VBZ DT NNP NNP NN WDT VBZ NNS IN NNP CC DT NNP NNP ."
She says China has made progress in human rights in recent years .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O O,PRP VBZ NNP VBZ VBN NN IN JJ NNS IN JJ NNS .
"The European Parliament resolution , approved Wednesday , said the arms sale embargo should continue until China takes concrete steps to improve human rights .",O B-org I-org O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNP NN , VBN NNP , VBD DT NNS NN NN MD VB IN NNP VBZ JJ NNS TO VB JJ NNS ."
