Officials in Afghanistan say at least eight civilians have been killed in a NATO airstrike against militants in a village in the southern part of the country .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNP VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBP VBN VBN IN DT NNP NN IN NNS IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN .
Afghan officials say those killed in the attack Wednesday in the Zherrai district in Kandahar province included several women and children .,B-gpe O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP DT VBN IN DT NN NNP IN DT NNP NN IN NNP NN VBD JJ NNS CC NNS .
At least 10 others were wounded in the airstrike .,O O O O O O O O O O,IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN .
It said it makes every effort to minimize the risk of what it calls collateral damage from its operations .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD PRP VBZ DT NN TO VB DT NN IN WP PRP VBZ JJ NN IN PRP$ NNS .
Afghan President Hamid Karzai has repeatedly demanded NATO and U.S.-led troops take more care when conducting military operations in residential areas to avoid civilian casualties .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ RB VBN NNP CC JJ NNS VBP JJR NN WRB VBG JJ NNS IN JJ NNS TO VB JJ NNS .
