A top British official has urged the Internet industry to cooperate with the government in targeting Islamic extremists in the same way it helps identify pedophiles .,O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ JJ NN VBZ VBN DT NN NN TO VB IN DT NN IN VBG JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN PRP VBZ VB NNS .
Home Secretary Jacqui Smith Thursday compared recruitment of impressionable young people by militants to on-line stalking of children by sexual predators .,O O B-per I-per B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NN IN JJ JJ NNS IN NNS TO JJ NN IN NNS IN JJ NNS .
Smith told a meeting in London she plans to consult with the Internet industry in the coming weeks to devise ways of removing illegal material from Islamist Web sites .,B-per O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD DT NN IN NNP PRP VBZ TO VB IN DT NN NN IN DT VBG NNS TO VB NNS IN VBG JJ NN IN NNP NNP NNS .
"In November , the head of the British intelligence unit MI-5 said al-Qaida was grooming Muslim children in Britain to become terrorists .",O B-tim O O O O O B-gpe O O B-org O B-org O O B-org O O B-geo O O O O,"IN NNP , DT NN IN DT JJ NN NN NNP VBD NNP VBD VBG NNP NNS IN NNP TO VB NNS ."
"Those comments by spy chief Jonathan Evans drew sharp criticism from the head of Britain 's largest Muslim group , the Muslim Council of Britain .",O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org O O B-org I-org O B-geo O,"DT NNS IN NN NN NNP NNP VBD JJ NN IN DT NN IN NNP POS JJS NN NN , DT NNP NNP IN NNP ."
Muhammad Abdul Bari said British politicians are creating a climate of fear within Britain 's huge Muslim community by spending too much time focusing on wrongdoings of young Muslims .,B-per I-per I-per O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP VBD JJ NNS VBP VBG DT NN IN NN IN NNP POS JJ NN NN IN VBG RB JJ NN VBG IN NNS IN JJ NNPS .
