Soldiers and local volunteers in northern Afghanistan have found more bodies and survivors from recent avalanches along a well-traveled mountain road .,O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS CC JJ NNS IN JJ NNP VBP VBN JJR NNS CC NNS IN JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN NN .
"Afghan officials said Wednesday that at least 165 people died from the avalanches in the Salang Pass - a 3,400-meter-high mountain road that connects Kabul to the northern city of Mazar-i-Sharif .",B-gpe O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNS VBD NNP IN IN JJS CD NNS VBD IN DT NNS IN DT NNP NNP IN DT JJ NN NN WDT VBZ NNP TO DT JJ NN IN NNP .
"Officials said rescue workers using helicopters and heavy machinery have rescued more than 2,500 people .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBD NN NNS VBG NNS CC JJ NN VBP VBN JJR IN CD NNS .
"Days of heavy snowfall triggered the avalanches , burying parts of the road and blocking a tunnel .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN JJ NN VBD DT NNS , VBG NNS IN DT NN CC VBG DT NN ."
Media reports say the force of the avalanches pushed two buses and several cars into a deep gorge .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS NNS VBP DT NN IN DT NNS VBD CD NNS CC JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN .
