One hundred ethnic Albanians have protested outside the Kosovo parliament against planned talks with Serbia on the province 's future .,O O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,CD CD JJ NNS VBP VBN IN DT NNP NN IN JJ NNS IN NNP IN DT NN POS NN .
The protesters want the mostly ethnic Albanian province to be an independent country .,O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP DT RB JJ JJ NN TO VB DT JJ NN .
"They spilled fake blood on the steps leading to the building , saying it symbolized those who died in the 1998 to 1999 war with Serbia .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O B-geo O,"PRP VBD JJ NN IN DT NNS VBG TO DT NN , VBG PRP VBD DT WP VBD IN DT CD TO CD NN IN NNP ."
The demonstration came one day after Kosovo 's Albanian-dominated parliament approved a plan to create a team to talk with Serbia on the province 's political status .,O O O B-tim I-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD CD NN IN NNP POS JJ NN VBD DT NN TO VB DT NN TO VB IN NNP IN DT NN POS JJ NN .
Kosovo is legally part of Serbia .,B-geo O O O O B-geo O,NNP VBZ RB NN IN NNP .
"But it has been under United Nations administration since 1999 , when Serbian forces withdrew after a campaign of NATO air strikes aimed at ending Belgrade 's crackdown on ethnic Albanians .",O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-tim O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O,"CC PRP VBZ VBN IN NNP NNP NN IN CD , WRB JJ NNS VBD IN DT NN IN NNP NN NNS VBN IN VBG NNP POS NN IN JJ NNS ."
The province 's Serbian minority and Serbia want it to remain part of Serbia .,O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NN POS JJ NN CC NNP VBP PRP TO VB NN IN NNP .
