"U.S. officials say they have obtained a letter sent from Osama bin Laden 's top deputy to the leader of Iraq 's insurgency , outlining a goal of forming an Islamic state in Iraq .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP NNS VBP PRP VBP VBN DT NN VBN IN NNP NNP NNP POS JJ NN TO DT NN IN NNP POS NN , VBG DT NN IN VBG DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
"A Defense Department spokesman said Thursday , a lengthy letter from Ayman al-Zawahri details a strategy of pushing the United States out of Iraq , then setting up an Islamic state and expanding into neighboring countries .",O B-org I-org O O B-tim O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP NN VBD NNP , DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP NNS DT NN IN VBG DT NNP NNPS IN IN NNP , RB VBG RP DT JJ NN CC VBG IN JJ NNS ."
"The letter to Abu Musab al-Zarqawi also concedes that al-Qaida has lost many key leaders , and is resigned to defeat in Afghanistan .",O O O B-org I-org B-per O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NN TO NNP NNP NNP RB VBZ IN NNP VBZ VBN JJ JJ NNS , CC VBZ VBN TO VB IN NNP ."
"The Pentagon spokesman says the letter makes a plea for financial support , admitting that funding has been severely disrupted .",O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NN VBZ DT NN VBZ DT NN IN JJ NN , VBG IN NN VBZ VBN RB VBN ."
Al-Qaida 's deputy leader warns Iraqi insurgents not to alienate the Islamic world by such tactics as beheading hostages and carrying out suicide bombings that kill Muslim civilians .,B-org O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NN NN VBZ JJ NNS RB TO VB DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS IN VBG NNS CC VBG RP NN NNS WDT VBP NNP NNS .
The spokesman did not say how or when U.S. officials obtained the letter .,O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,DT NN VBD RB VB WRB CC WRB NNP NNS VBD DT NN .
