The Iraqi government has condemned the killing of a defense lawyer in the trial of deposed leader Saddam Hussein .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O,DT JJ NN VBZ VBN DT NN IN DT NN NN IN DT NN IN JJ NN NNP NNP .
"Government officials reacted to the assassination of Saadoun al-Janabi , who was found dead from gunshot wounds on Friday in Baghdad .",O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O,"NN NNS VBD TO DT NN IN NNP NNP , WP VBD VBN JJ IN NN NNS IN NNP IN NNP ."
Gunmen seized him late Thursday from his office .,O O O O B-tim O O O O,NNS VBD PRP JJ NNP IN PRP$ NN .
"Meanwhile , Arab League Secretary-General Amr Moussa met Friday with Sunni Arab religious leaders in Baghdad -- his first visit to Iraq since the U.S.-led invasion two years ago .",O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim O O O,"RB , NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP IN NNP NNP JJ NNS IN NNP IN PRP$ JJ NN TO NNP IN DT JJ NN CD NNS RB ."
Mr. Moussa said he wants to promote a national reconciliation dialogue in Iraq .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP VBD PRP VBZ TO VB DT JJ NN NN IN NNP .
"Some Sunni Arab leaders say any talks depend on certain conditions , among them a timetable for the withdrawal of coalition troops from Iraq .",O B-per B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NNP JJ NNS VBP DT NNS VBP IN JJ NNS , IN PRP DT NN IN DT NN IN NN NNS IN NNP ."
"Also , reports on Friday quoted election officials as saying they expect to announce the results of last Saturday 's constitutional referendum within one to two days .",O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-tim O O,"RB , NNS IN NNP VBD NN NNS IN VBG PRP VBP TO VB DT NNS IN JJ NNP POS JJ NN IN CD CC CD NNS ."
