Prime Minister Ariel Sharon 's office says the Israeli leader has accepted an Egyptian invitation to meet Palestinian leader Mahmoud Abbas next week in the Red Sea resort of Sharm el-Sheikh .,B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP NNP NNP NNP POS NN VBZ DT JJ NN VBZ VBN DT JJ NN TO VB JJ NN NNP NNP JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP NN IN NNP NNP .
"Mr. Sharon 's office said Egyptian President Hosni Mubarak is to host the summit Tuesday , which would be the highest-level Israeli-Palestinian meeting in nearly four years .",B-per I-per O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"NNP NNP POS NN VBD JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ TO VB DT NN NNP , WDT MD VB DT JJ JJ NN IN RB CD NNS ."
There was no immediate comment from the Palestinians .,O O O O O O O B-gpe O,EX VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NNS .
"And in Cairo , an senior Egyptian official said was too early to talk about a summit .",O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O,"CC IN NNP , DT JJ JJ NN VBD VBD RB JJ TO VB IN DT NN ."
"A summit has been expected since Mr. Abbas , who was elected to succeed late Yasser Arafat last month , took steps to stop Palestinian militants from attacking Israelis .",O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O,"DT NN VBZ VBN VBN IN NNP NNP , WP VBD VBN TO VB JJ NNP NNP JJ NN , VBD NNS TO VB JJ NNS IN VBG NNS ."
Israel responded by cutting back on military operations .,B-geo O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD IN VBG RP IN JJ NNS .
Israel is also discussing plans for a pullback from several West Bank cities .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O,NNP VBZ RB VBG NNS IN DT NN IN JJ NNP NNP NNS .
