FIFA vice president Chung Mong-joon of South Korea has arrived in Qatar to make a final push in his re-election campaign ahead of this week 's Asian Football Confederation meeting in Doha .,B-org O O B-per I-per O B-geo I-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-geo O,NNP NN NN NNP NNP IN NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NNP TO VB DT JJ NN IN PRP$ NN NN RB IN DT NN POS NNP NNP NNP NN IN NNP .
"Chung , the former head of the Korea Football Association , is running against Jordan 's Prince Ali bin Al Hussein in Thursday 's election for the Asian Confederation 's vice presidential seat on football 's world governing body .",B-per O O O O O O B-geo B-org I-org O O O O B-gpe O B-per I-per I-per I-per I-per O B-tim O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP , DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP , VBZ VBG IN NNP POS NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP IN NNP POS NN IN DT NNP NNP POS NN JJ NN IN NN POS NN VBG NN ."
"The Asian Confederation holds four seats on the 24-member FIFA executive committee , including one of its eight vice presidencies .",O B-org I-org O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP VBZ CD NNS IN DT JJ NNP NN NN , VBG CD IN PRP$ CD NN NNS ."
"Chung , 56 , has held the post since 1994 , and was unopposed in 2007 .",B-per O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O B-tim O,"NNP , CD , VBZ VBN DT NN IN CD , CC VBD VBN IN CD ."
"Prince Ali is the head of the West Asian Football Federation , and is attempting to rally the Arab world to support him in overthrowing Chung .",B-per I-per O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-per O,"NNP NNP VBZ DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP , CC VBZ VBG TO VB DT JJ NN TO VB PRP IN VBG NNP ."
"If he succeeds , the 35-year-old Prince Ali will be the youngest member of FIFA 's Executive Committee .",O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-org O B-org I-org O,"IN PRP VBZ , DT JJ NNP NNP MD VB DT JJS NN IN NNP POS NNP NNP ."
