Public health officials have confirmed a five-year-old boy in central Thailand has died of bird flu .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,JJ NN NNS VBP VBN DT JJ NN IN JJ NNP VBZ VBN IN NN NN .
The Thai Health Ministry said Friday the boy died Wednesday in Nakhon Nayok province .,O B-gpe B-org I-org O B-tim O O O B-tim O B-geo I-geo O O,DT JJ NNP NNP VBD NNP DT NN VBD NNP IN NNP NNP NN .
Lab tests confirmed he had the deadly H5N1 strain of avian flu .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBD PRP VBD DT JJ NNP NN IN JJ NN .
The death takes Thailand 's human death toll from bird flu to 14 since the virus emerged in Asia in late 2003 .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O,DT NN VBZ NNP POS JJ NN NN IN NN NN TO CD IN DT NN VBD IN NNP IN JJ CD .
The strain of flu has now killed 70 people in Asia .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NN IN NN VBZ RB VBN CD NNS IN NNP .
"Meanwhile , health officials in Vietnam have reported bird flu outbreaks among poultry in the central province of Quang Tri and in Son La province in the north .",O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O,"RB , NN NNS IN NNP VBP VBN NN NN NNS IN NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP CC IN NNP NNP NN IN DT NN ."
And officials in Ukraine say bird flu now appears to have spread throughout the Crimean peninsula after first being confirmed in the north east last Saturday .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,CC NNS IN NNP VBP NN NN RB VBZ TO VB VBN IN DT JJ NN IN RB VBG VBN IN DT JJ NN JJ NNP .
