Burma 's veteran pro-democracy politician and physician Saw Mara Aung has died at the age of 91 .,B-geo O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O,NNP POS JJ JJ NN CC NN NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN DT NN IN CD .
His colleagues said he passed away at his home in Rangoon on Monday and was buried on Tuesday .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O B-tim O,PRP$ NNS VBD PRP VBD RP IN PRP$ NN IN NNP IN NNP CC VBD VBN IN NNP .
The veteran ethnic politician was chairman of the Arakan League for Democracy .,O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,DT NN JJ NN VBD NN IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP .
"He was elected as a member of parliament during Burma 's 1990 general election , a race the country 's ruling military leaders refused to recognize .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD VBN IN DT NN IN NN IN NNP POS CD JJ NN , DT NN DT NN POS VBG JJ NNS VBD TO VB ."
"In 1998 , the main opposition National League for Democracy and its allied parties , including his Arakan League for Democracy , formed the Committee Representing the People 's Parliament and elected Saw Mara Aung as their chairman .",O B-tim O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O B-org I-org O B-org I-org I-org O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O,"IN CD , DT JJ NN NNP NNP IN NNP CC PRP$ JJ NNS , VBG PRP$ NNP NNP IN NNP , VBD DT NNP VBG DT NNS POS NNP CC VBN NNP NNP NNP IN PRP$ NN ."
"Like many other Burmese pro-democracy leaders , Saw Mara Aung was arrested and held by the military for his political activities .",O O O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN JJ JJ JJ JJ NNS , NNP NNP NNP VBD VBN CC VBN IN DT NN IN PRP$ JJ NNS ."
He was released in 2001 .,O O O O B-tim O,PRP VBD VBN IN CD .
