Senior U.S. officials have disclosed that Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice will pay a historic visit to Libya next month .,O B-geo O O O O O O B-org B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O,JJ NNP NNS VBP VBN IN NNP IN NNP NNP NNP MD VB DT JJ NN TO NNP JJ NN .
The disclosure Tuesday came just weeks after the U.S. and Libya signed an agreement to compensate American victims of Libyan-backed terrorist attacks during the 1980s .,O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NN NNP VBD RB NNS IN DT NNP CC NNP VBD DT NN TO VB JJ NNS IN JJ JJ NNS IN DT NNS .
Rice has said she looks forward to visiting Libya now that relations between the two countries have been normalized .,B-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN PRP VBZ RB TO VBG NNP RB IN NNS IN DT CD NNS VBP VBN VBN .
Her visit will mark the first time a U.S. secretary of state will visit Libya since the 1950s .,O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O,PRP$ NN MD VB DT JJ NN DT NNP NN IN NN MD VB NNP IN DT NNS .
"In mid-August , the U.S. and Libya agreed on plans to compensate the U.S. victims of the 1988 bombing of a Pan American flight over Lockerbie , Scotland , and a Berlin nightclub bombing two years earlier .",O B-org O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O B-geo O O O B-org I-org O B-tim O O O,"IN NNP , DT NNP CC NNP VBD IN NNS TO VB DT NNP NNS IN DT CD NN IN DT NNP NNP NN IN NNP , NNP , CC DT NNP NN VBG CD NNS RBR ."
The deal also compensates Libyans who were killed in 1986 in U.S. revenge attacks on Tripoli and Benghazi .,O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O B-geo O B-geo O,DT NN RB VBZ NNS WP VBD VBN IN CD IN NNP NN NNS IN NNP CC NNP .
The agreement also gives Libya immunity against further lawsuits related to the attacks .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,DT NN RB VBZ NNP NN IN JJ NNS VBN TO DT NNS .
