"Iran 's new president , Mahmoud Ahmadinejad , has unveiled his cabinet , naming hard-liners to head key ministries .",B-geo O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ NN , NNP NNP , VBZ VBN PRP$ NN , VBG NNS TO VB JJ NNS ."
"The new foreign minister is Manouchehr Mottaki , a former ambassador and conservative member of parliament .",O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ JJ NN VBZ NNP NNP , DT JJ NN CC JJ NN IN NN ."
"Another hardliner , Mostafa Pourmohammadi , was named to the Interior Ministry , and the former head of a strict religious tribunal , Gholam Hossein Mohseni-Ejei , was given the Intelligence Ministry portfolio .",O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O B-org I-org O O,"DT NN , NNP NNP , VBD VBN TO DT NNP NNP , CC DT JJ NN IN DT JJ JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP , VBD VBN DT NNP NNP NN ."
"The new oil minister is Ali Saeedloo , who is acting mayor of Tehran .",O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT JJ NN NN VBZ NNP NNP , WP VBZ VBG NN IN NNP ."
"Another hardliner , Ali Larijani , will head Iran 's nuclear negotiations with the West .",O O O B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NN , NNP NNP , MD VB NNP POS JJ NNS IN DT NNP ."
"President Ahmadinejad did not name any women to his cabinet and retained only one minister Transport Minister Mohammad Rahmati appointed by his predecessor , reformist Mohammad Khatami .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-per I-per O,"NNP NNP VBD RB VB DT NNS TO PRP$ NN CC VBD RB CD NN NNP NNP NNP NNP VBN IN PRP$ NN , NN NNP NNP ."
"Iran 's conservative-dominated parliament is expected to approve the 21 ministers later this week , as is Iran 's supreme leader , Ayatollah Ali Khamenei .",B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-org B-per I-per O,"NNP POS JJ NN VBZ VBN TO VB DT CD NNS RB DT NN , IN VBZ NNP POS JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP ."
