Ailing Cuban President Fidel Castro has published his second editorial in a week criticizing U.S. President George Bush 's bio-fuel policies .,O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-per I-per I-per O O O O,NNP JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP$ JJ NN IN DT NN VBG NNP NNP NNP NNP POS JJ NNS .
"In the state-run newspaper Granma Wednesday , Mr. Castro repeated his argument that using agricultural crops to produce ethanol for cars could deprive developing nations of food and condemn millions of people to hunger and death .",O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN NNP NNP , NNP NNP VBD PRP$ NN IN VBG JJ NNS TO VB NN IN NNS MD VB VBG NNS IN NN CC VB NNS IN NNS TO NN CC NN ."
"Mr. Castro has not appeared in public since temporarily handing power to his brother , Raul , last July before undergoing intestinal surgery .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O B-tim O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ RB VBN IN JJ IN RB VBG NN TO PRP$ NN , NNP , JJ NNP IN VBG JJ NN ."
"Cuban officials have said the 80-year-old leader is recovering , and could soon take a more active role in government .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP VBN DT JJ NN VBZ VBG , CC MD RB VB DT RBR JJ NN IN NN ."
"Cuban media have released photographs and video of the president , however , to put down rumors of his demise .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP VBN NNS CC NN IN DT NN , RB , TO VB RP NNS IN PRP$ NN ."
