Indian officials say at least 93 people are dead and scores of others are missing from widespread floods caused by monsoon rains in western India .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,JJ NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBP JJ CC NNS IN NNS VBP VBG IN JJ NNS VBN IN NN NNS IN JJ NNP .
"The normally drought-prone desert state of Rajasthan has been hit by unprecedented rain that has destroyed thousands of hectares of crops , submerged large areas , and killed tens of thousands of farm animals .",O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT RB JJ NN NN IN NNP VBZ VBN VBN IN JJ NN WDT VBZ VBN NNS IN NNS IN NNS , VBD JJ NNS , CC VBD NNS IN NNS IN NN NNS ."
"Navy divers and army soldiers have been called in to rescue people stranded atop houses , vehicles and sand dunes .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNS CC NN NNS VBP VBN VBN IN TO VB NNS VBN IN NNS , NNS CC NN NNS ."
Officials say the death toll could reach 300 .,O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP DT NN NN MD VB CD .
Annual monsoon rains have battered much of western and southern India in recent weeks .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O,JJ NN NNS VBP VBN NN IN JJ CC JJ NNP IN JJ NNS .
Indian Prime Minister Manmohan Singh has promised federal help for flood victims .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN JJ NN IN NN NNS .
