"Thai officials say a small fire broke out Saturday at Bangkok 's international airport , while Thailand continues to welcome guests from around the world to celebrate the king 's 60-year reign .",B-gpe O O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP DT JJ NN VBD IN NNP IN NNP POS JJ NN , IN NNP VBZ TO VB NNS IN IN DT NN TO VB DT NN POS JJ NN ."
An electrical short circuit caused the fire early Saturday morning in the Immigration Department 's document room .,O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O B-org I-org O O O O,DT JJ JJ NN VBD DT NN JJ NNP NN IN DT NNP NNP POS NN NN .
The flames filled a terminal with smoke and disrupted the check-in process for passengers .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBD DT NN IN NN CC VBD DT JJ NN IN NNS .
Airport officials say the fire was extinguished within a half hour .,O O O O O O O B-tim O B-tim I-tim O,NNP NNS VBP DT NN VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN .
"No one was hurt , and only minor damage was reported .",O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD VBN , CC RB JJ NN VBD VBN ."
"Thailand is hosting royalty and other guests from around the world , arriving in Bangkok to attend celebrations marking King Bhumibol Adulyadej 's 60 years on the Thai throne .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-gpe O O,"NNP VBZ VBG NN CC JJ NNS IN IN DT NN , VBG IN NNP TO VB NNS VBG NNP NNP NNP POS CD NNS IN DT JJ NN ."
