"President Bush has congratulated Guatemala 's newly elected president , saying he wants to work closely with the new leader .",B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNP POS RB VBN NN , VBG PRP VBZ TO VB RB IN DT JJ NN ."
White House spokeswoman Dana Perino said Tuesday Mr. Bush called President-Elect Alvaro Colom to congratulate him on his victory in the November 4 presidential election .,B-org I-org O B-per I-per O B-tim B-per I-per O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O,NNP NNP NN NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP NNP VBD JJ NNP NNP TO VB PRP IN PRP$ NN IN DT NNP CD JJ NN .
She said President Bush told Mr. Colom the U.S. would like to expand the good relationship between the two countries .,O O B-per I-per O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP DT NNP MD VB TO VB DT JJ NN IN DT CD NNS .
"Mr. Colom , who had made two previous bids for the presidency , based his campaign on pledges to reduce poverty and confront the country 's economic and social problems .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP , WP VBD VBN CD JJ NNS IN DT NN , VBN PRP$ NN IN NNS TO VB NN CC VB DT NN POS JJ CC JJ NNS ."
He will replace outgoing President Oscar Berger on January 14 .,O O O O B-per I-per I-per O B-tim I-tim O,PRP MD VB JJ NNP NNP NNP IN NNP CD .
