"China is fielding its largest-ever Olympic team at the upcoming Beijing Games , with 639 athletes competing in all 28 sports .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBG PRP$ JJ NNP NN IN DT JJ NNP NNPS , IN CD NNS VBG IN DT CD NNS ."
"The team was unveiled Friday , at a rally in Beijing .",O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NN VBD VBN NNP , IN DT NN IN NNP ."
"The contingent includes Yao Ming , a member of the U.S. National Basketball Association 's Houston Rockets , and defending 110 meters hurdling gold medalist Liu Xiang .",O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-geo B-org O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O,"DT JJ VBZ NNP NNP , DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP POS NNP NNPS , CC VBG CD NNS VBG NN NN NNP NNP ."
"Of the 639 members of the Chinese team , 165 participated in the Athens Games four years ago , while 40 of them took part in the 2000 Sydney Games .",O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,"IN DT CD NNS IN DT JJ NN , CD VBD IN DT NNP NNPS CD NNS RB , IN CD IN PRP VBD NN IN DT CD NNP NNPS ."
"The delegation will also include 460 coaches and other officials , bringing the total size to nearly 1100 .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN MD RB VB CD NNS CC JJ NNS , VBG DT JJ NN TO RB CD ."
"The Chinese team will attempt to surpass the 32 gold medals won at the Athens Olympics , four less than the United States .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"DT JJ NN MD VB TO VB DT CD NN NNS VBN IN DT NNP NNP , CD JJR IN DT NNP NNPS ."
