Representatives of French presidential candidate Nicholas Sarkozy and President Jacques Chirac have denied a newspaper report that they made a deal to protect the outgoing president from prosecution in a corruption probe .,O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN JJ JJ NN NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP VBP VBN DT NN NN IN PRP VBD DT NN TO VB DT NN NN IN NN IN DT NN NN .
Sarkozy 's office Wednesday categorically dismissed the report in Le Canard Enchaine weekly as untrue .,B-per O O B-tim O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O,NNP POS NN NNP RB VBD DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP JJ IN JJ .
The president 's office also denied the report .,O O O O O O O O O,DT NN POS NN RB VBD DT NN .
"The newspaper said Mr. Chirac endorsed Sarkozy 's candidacy in the April 22 election in exchange for a promise that if he wins , the conservative candidate will sponsor a bill that would spare the outgoing president from prosecution .",O O O B-per I-per O B-per O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD NNP NNP VBD NNP POS NN IN DT NNP CD NN IN NN IN DT NN IN IN PRP VBZ , DT JJ NN MD VB DT NN WDT MD VB DT NN NN IN NN ."
The article says a new anti-crime bill would set a 10-year limit on the time a judge has to close a case .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ DT JJ JJ NN MD VB DT JJ NN IN DT NN DT NN VBZ TO VB DT NN .
This would end a corruption probe involving Mr. Chirac 's activities while serving as Paris mayor before he assumed the French presidency in 1995 .,O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O B-tim O,DT MD VB DT NN NN VBG NNP NNP POS NNS IN VBG IN NNP NN IN PRP VBD DT JJ NN IN CD .
