"The Indian army has denied Pakistani allegations that soldiers in Indian Kashmir fired across the de~facto border into the Pakistani side of the divided region , wounding two civilians .",O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBZ VBN JJ NNS IN NNS IN NNP NNP VBD IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT VBN NN , VBG CD NNS ."
"The Pakistani military says the incident occurred Tuesday at the Line of Control , and that the wounded were taken to a hospital .",O B-gpe O O O O O B-tim O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBZ DT NN VBD NNP IN DT NN IN NNP , CC IN DT VBN VBD VBN TO DT NN ."
But a spokesman for the Indian army said not a single shot was fired from Indian Kashmir and that there has been no violation of the cease-fire from the Indian side .,O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,CC DT NN IN DT JJ NN VBD RB DT JJ NN VBD VBN IN JJ NNP CC IN EX VBZ VBN DT NN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN .
India and Pakistan agreed on a cease-fire along the tense Himalayan frontier in 2003 .,B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP CC NNP VBD IN DT NN IN DT NN JJ NN IN CD .
Violations have been rare .,O O O O O,NNS VBP VBN JJ .
