Greece 's main labor unions are holding another strike to protest a parliamentary vote on pension reforms that are part of government austerity measures .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS JJ NN NNS VBP VBG DT NN TO VB DT JJ NN IN NN NNS WDT VBP NN IN NN NN NNS .
"Greek police say more than 10,000 people demonstrated in Athens Thursday , while about 5,000 others marched in the northern city of Thessaloniki .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"JJ NNS VBP JJR IN CD NNS VBN IN NNP NNP , IN RB CD NNS VBD IN DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
"Flights were canceled for most of the day , and public transportation throughout Greece halted .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"NNS VBD VBN IN JJS IN DT NN , CC JJ NN IN NNP VBD ."
Hospitals were open for emergencies only .,O O O O O O O,NNS VBD JJ IN NNS RB .
Lawmakers approved pension reform in a preliminary vote Wednesday to gauge how much support the measure has .,O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBD NN NN IN DT JJ NN NNP TO VB WRB JJ NN DT NN VBZ .
