"Muslim majority Pakistan has sworn in a senior Hindu judge as acting chief justice amid a judicial crisis that has jolted the country 's president , Pervez Musharraf .",B-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"NNP NN NNP VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NNP NN IN VBG NN NN IN DT JJ NN WDT VBZ VBN DT NN POS NN , NNP NNP ."
"Rana Bhagwandas replaced justice Javed Iqbal Saturday , who was acting as chief judge after President Musharraf removed Supreme Court Chief Justice Iftikhar Mohammed Chaudhry on March 9 for alleged abuse of authority .",B-per I-per O O B-per I-per B-tim O O O O O O O O B-per B-org O B-org I-org O B-org I-org B-per I-per O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD NN NNP NNP NNP , WP VBD VBG IN JJ NN IN NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP IN NNP CD IN JJ NN IN NN ."
Chaudhry has denied the charges .,B-per O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN DT NNS .
Lawyers and opposition parties have held nationwide protests since Chaudhry was removed .,O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O,NNS CC NN NNS VBP VBN JJ NNS IN NNP VBD VBN .
"On Friday , General Musharraf urged the nation 's lawyers to help ease the political crisis and urged Pakistanis to help fight extremism and terrorism in the country .",O B-tim O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , NNP NNP VBD DT NN POS NNS TO VB VB DT JJ NN CC VBD NNS TO VB VB NN CC NN IN DT NN ."
Several legal professionals in Pakistan have resigned in protest of Chaudhry 's removal .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-per O O O,JJ JJ NNS IN NNP VBP VBN IN NN IN NNP POS NN .
