Venezuelan authorities have seized 1.3 metric tons of cocaine hidden inside a cargo container at a seaport near Caracas .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNS VBP VBN CD JJ NNS IN NN VBN IN DT NN NN IN DT NN IN NNP .
"A Venezuelan military official , General Marcos Rojas , said Thursday that the cocaine was discovered in paint cans at La Guaira seaport , north of the Venezuelan capital .",O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O B-gpe O O,"DT JJ JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP , VBD NNP IN DT NN VBD VBN IN NN NNS IN NNP NNP NN , NN IN DT JJ NN ."
He said smugglers had planned to load the drugs onto a cargo ship bound for Mexico .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,PRP VBD NNS VBD VBN TO VB DT NNS IN DT NN NN VBN IN NNP .
The discovery comes two months after Mexican soldiers seized 5.5 tons of cocaine found on board a commercial plane that arrived from Caracas without passengers .,O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,DT NN VBZ CD NNS IN JJ NNS VBD CD NNS IN NN VBN IN NN DT JJ NN WDT VBD IN NNP IN NNS .
The cocaine was hidden in 128 black suitcases and had a street value of $ 100 million .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD VBN IN CD JJ NNS CC VBD DT NN NN IN $ CD CD .
"The pilot escaped , but the co-pilot was arrested , along with two Mexicans who arrived in another aircraft .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD , CC DT NN VBD VBN , IN IN CD NNS WP VBD IN DT NN ."
Venezuela neighbors Colombia - the world 's largest cocaine producer - and is often used as a transit route for cocaine destined for other countries .,B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS NNP IN DT NN POS JJS NN NN : CC VBZ RB VBN IN DT NN NN IN NN VBN IN JJ NNS .
