Insurgents pressing a campaign of violence in Iraq ahead of next month 's constitutional referendum have killed five more people Friday in a suicide bombing at a Baghdad bus terminal .,O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-geo O O O,NNS VBG DT NN IN NN IN NNP RB IN JJ NN POS JJ NN VBP VBN CD JJR NNS NNP IN DT NN VBG IN DT NNP NN NN .
Authorities say at least eight other people were hurt in the blast on a city bus .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP IN JJS CD JJ NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN IN DT NN NN .
"In Washington , Saudi Arabia 's foreign minister warned Thursday that Iraq is hurtling toward disintegration .",O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O,"IN NNP , NNP NNP POS JJ NN VBD NNP IN NNP VBZ VBG IN NN ."
Prince Saud al-Faisal told reporters he does not believe elections or a constitution alone will bring Iraqis together .,B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,NNP NNP NNP VBD NNS PRP VBZ RB VB NNS CC DT NN RB MD VB NNS RB .
"He said if Iraq is split into Shi'ite , Sunni and Kurdish states , it could drag other countries in the region into the conflict .",O O O B-geo O O O O O B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD IN NNP VBZ VBN IN NNP , NNP CC NNP NNS , PRP MD VB JJ NNS IN DT NN IN DT NN ."
