Pakistan 's President Pervez Musharraf has again urged tribal elders to evict foreign militants from regions near the Afghan border .,B-geo O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,NNP POS NNP NNP NNP VBZ RB VBN JJ NNS TO VB JJ NNS IN NNS IN DT JJ NN .
"Speaking at a tribal council ( or jirga ) in Peshawar Tuesday , General Musharraf warned the elders that there would be undesirable consequences if militants remained in the area .",O O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"VBG IN DT JJ NN LRB CC NN RRB IN NNP NNP , NNP NNP VBD DT NNS IN EX MD VB JJ NNS IN NNS VBD IN DT NN ."
Taleban and al-Qaida fighters are believed to shelter in Pakistan 's remote border regions .,B-org O B-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,NNP CC NNP NNS VBP VBN TO NN IN NNP POS JJ NN NNS .
"Last year , the Pakistani government signed a controversial deal with pro-Taleban tribal leaders in North and South Waziristan , empowering them to drive foreign militants from the region .",O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN , DT JJ NN VBD DT JJ NN IN JJ JJ NNS IN NNP CC NNP NNP , VBG PRP TO VB JJ NNS IN DT NN ."
"Elsewhere Tuesday , near the Afghan border , police say suspected Islamic militants blew up several music shops in North West Frontier Province .",O B-tim O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O,"RB NNP , IN DT JJ NN , NNS VBP JJ NNP NNS VBD RP JJ NN NNS IN NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
Police say the attackers detonated explosives overnight in a market .,O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP DT NNS VBD NNS RB IN DT NN .
There were no reports of casualties .,O O O O O O O,EX VBD DT NNS IN NNS .
Conservative militants in remote border regions of Pakistan have become increasingly bold in their efforts to enforce strict Islamic law .,O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS IN JJ NN NNS IN NNP VBP VBN RB JJ IN PRP$ NNS TO VB JJ JJ NN .
