"A Russian lawmaker probing the 2004 Beslan school massacre says he can not rule out the possibility that Russian soldiers , rather than militants , triggered the final battle that left more than 300 people dead .",O B-gpe O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBG DT CD NNP NN NN VBZ PRP MD RB VB RP DT NN IN JJ NNS , RB IN NNS , VBD DT JJ NN WDT VBD JJR IN CD NNS JJ ."
"Authorities have maintained that Chechen militants holding more than 1,000 hostages set off a series of explosions that forced Russian troops to storm a school building in the city of Beslan .",O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNS VBP VBN IN JJ NNS VBG JJR IN CD NNS VBD RP DT NN IN NNS WDT VBD JJ NNS TO NN DT NN NN IN DT NN IN NNP .
"But a published report by lawmaker Yuri Savelyev , described as an expert in explosions and fire , says military grenade fire may have sparked the string of explosions that preceded a military charge .",O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"CC DT VBN NN IN NN NNP NNP , VBN IN DT NN IN NNS CC NN , VBZ JJ NN NN MD VB VBN DT NN IN NNS WDT VBD DT JJ NN ."
"The Russian prosecutor-general 's office declined comment on the Savelyev report , published Tuesday by the Russian news media .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-per O O O B-tim O O B-gpe O O O,"DT JJ NN POS NN VBD NN IN DT NNP NN , VBN NNP IN DT JJ NN NNS ."
"The 700-page report also claims that Russian commanders waited more than two hours to give orders to put out a gymnasium fire , in which many hostages were burned alive .",O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN RB VBZ IN JJ NNS VBD JJR IN CD NNS TO VB NNS TO VB RP DT NN NN , IN WDT JJ NNS VBD VBN JJ ."
