NATO Secretary General Jaap de Hoop Scheffer says the alliance expects to deploy several thousand more troops in Afghanistan as part of its plans to expand operations into the volatile southern regions of the country .,B-org B-per I-per I-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP IN NNP NNP VBZ DT NN VBZ TO VB JJ CD JJR NNS IN NNP IN NN IN PRP$ NNS TO VB NNS IN DT JJ JJ NNS IN DT NN .
"Mr. de Hoop Scheffer spoke to reporters in Kabul Thursday , after talks with Afghan President Hamid Karzai .",B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD TO NNS IN NNP NNP , IN NNS IN JJ NNP NNP NNP ."
He said the alliance has yet to resolve differences over its plans to run both peacekeeping and counter-insurgency operations alongside U.S.-led coalition forces in the region .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT NN VBZ RB TO VB NNS IN PRP$ NNS TO VB DT NN CC NN NNS IN JJ NN NNS IN DT NN .
"A 20,000-strong coalition force is operating mostly in southern and eastern Afghanistan , fighting Taleban insurgency and hunting al-Qaida terrorists .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org O O O B-org O O,"DT JJ NN NN VBZ VBG RB IN JJ CC JJ NNP , VBG NNP NN CC VBG NNP NNS ."
"The NATO-led International Security Assistance Force is currently enforcing security in the capital , Kabul , and across parts of northern and western provinces .",O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ RB VBG NN IN DT NN , NNP , CC IN NNS IN JJ CC JJ NNS ."
