Palestinian Prime Minister Ismail Haniyeh of the militant Hamas group says he would refrain from heading a unity government if that would clear the way for restoration of Western aid to the Palestinian Authority .,B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP IN DT JJ NNP NN VBZ PRP MD VB IN VBG DT NN NN IN DT MD VB DT NN IN NN IN JJ NN TO DT JJ NNP .
"Speaking after Friday prayers at a Gaza mosque , Mr. Haniyeh said Western powers do not want him in a new administration and that he is prepared to step aside to end the suffering of the Palestinian people .",O O B-tim O O O B-geo I-geo O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"VBG IN NNP NNS IN DT NNP NN , NNP NNP VBD JJ NNS VBP RB VB PRP IN DT JJ NN CC IN PRP VBZ VBN TO VB RB TO VB DT NN IN DT JJ NNS ."
Palestinian President Mahmoud Abbas ' Fatah faction has been holding talks with Hamas on creating a unity government .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP POS NNP NN VBZ VBN VBG NNS IN NNP IN VBG DT NN NN .
But the process deadlocked over Hamas ' refusal to agree on a moderate political platform that would recognize Israel and accept interim Israeli-Palestinian accords .,O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,CC DT NN VBD IN NNP POS NN TO VB IN DT JJ JJ NN WDT MD VB NNP CC VB JJ JJ NNS .
The West and Israel cut off funding to the Palestinian government after Hamas took power in March .,O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O B-org O O O B-tim O,DT NNP CC NNP VBD RP NN TO DT JJ NN IN NNP VBD NN IN NNP .
