"Former Liberian Finance Minister Ellen Johnson-Sirleaf has widened her strong lead in the country 's presidential run-off vote , moving closer to becoming Africa 's first democratically-elected woman president .",O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"JJ JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP$ JJ NN IN DT NN POS JJ NN NN , VBG RBR TO VBG NNP POS JJ JJ NN NN ."
"With nearly 90 percent of the ballots counted , Ms. Johnson-Sirleaf leads with 59 percent of the vote .",O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O,"IN RB CD NN IN DT NNS VBN , NNP NNP VBZ IN CD NN IN DT NN ."
"Her opponent , former soccer star George Weah , has 41 percent .",O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O,"PRP$ NN , JJ NN NN NNP NNP , VBZ CD NN ."
"Meanwhile , election officials are investigating fraud allegations made by Mr. Weah .",O O O O O O O O O O B-per B-org O,"RB , NN NNS VBP VBG NN NNS VBN IN NNP NNP ."
"His party has lodged a formal complaint with the National Election Commission , saying there was cheating , including pre-marked ballots , in Tuesday 's run-off .",O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,"PRP$ NN VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP , VBG EX VBD NN , VBG JJ NNS , IN NNP POS NN ."
"Supporters of Mr. Weah have held rallies at his headquarters , chanting "" no Weah , no peace , "" despite calls for calm from the candidate .",O O B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN NNP NNP VBP VBN NNS IN PRP$ NN , VBG RQU DT NN , DT NN , LQU IN NNS IN NN IN DT NN ."
"International observers say there were minor procedural problems in the run-off , but add it was conducted overall in a positive manner with no pattern of cheating .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNS VBP EX VBD JJ JJ NNS IN DT NN , CC VB PRP VBD VBN JJ IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN NN ."
