Palestinian officials say power-sharing talks between rival factions Hamas and Fatah were deadlocked Saturday because of disagreements over the shape of a prospective unity government .,B-gpe O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP JJ NNS IN JJ NNS NNP CC NNP VBD VBN NNP IN IN NNS IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN NN .
Representatives of the two factions have been meeting in Cairo this past week to sort out their disagreements .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O,NNS IN DT CD NNS VBP VBN VBG IN NNP DT JJ NN TO VB RP PRP$ NNS .
Among the major issues is whether to recognize Israel - a condition the militant group Hamas has refused to accept .,O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-org O O O O O,IN DT JJ NNS VBZ IN TO VB NNP IN DT NN DT JJ NN NNP VBZ VBN TO VB .
"However , much of the international community says it will not work with a Palestinian unity government unless it recognizes Israel .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O,"RB , NN IN DT JJ NN VBZ PRP MD RB VB IN DT JJ NN NN IN PRP VBZ NNP ."
"International donors have pledged more than $ 5 billion to help aid the Palestinian economy and to rebuild the Gaza Strip after Israel 's 3-week offensive there , which ended earlier this year .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP VBN JJR IN $ CD CD TO VB VB DT JJ NN CC TO VB DT NNP NNP IN NNP POS JJ NN RB , WDT VBD RBR DT NN ."
"But they have refused to let the money go through Hamas , which rules Gaza .",O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O B-geo O,"CC PRP VBP VBN TO VB DT NN VB IN NNP , WDT VBZ NNP ."
"Hamas seized power in Gaza in 2007 , while Fatah has set up a moderate government based out of the West Bank .",B-org O O O B-geo O B-tim O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"NNP VBD NN IN NNP IN CD , IN NNP VBZ VBN RP DT JJ NN VBN IN IN DT NNP NNP ."
