World leaders have denounced the deadly bombings on the Indonesian resort island of Bali .,O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo O,NNP NNS VBP VBN DT JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN NN IN NNP .
"She said the United States condemns the terrorist bombings , and will continue to work with Indonesia in the common fight against terror .",O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD DT NNP NNPS VBZ DT JJ NNS , CC MD VB TO VB IN NNP IN DT JJ NN IN NN ."
British Prime Minister Tony Blair denounced the attacks and applauded what he called the Indonesian government 's determination to defeat the terrorists .,O B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NNS CC VBD WP PRP VBD DT JJ NN POS NN TO VB DT NNS .
He said his government stands ready to help in any way possible .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD PRP$ NN VBZ JJ TO VB IN DT NN JJ .
Australian Foreign Minister Alexander Downer said he believes the attacks were the work of a group like the Islamic extremist Jemaah Islamiyah - but he stressed no one has claimed responsibility and there is no evidence as to who may have carried out the attack .,B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD PRP VBZ DT NNS VBD DT NN IN DT NN IN DT NNP NN NNP NNP : CC PRP VBD DT NN VBZ VBN NN CC EX VBZ DT NN IN TO WP MD VB VBN RP DT NN .
