The radical Palestinian group Hamas says it will boycott next month 's election for a successor to the late Palestinian Authority President Yasser Arafat .,O O B-gpe O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-per I-per I-per O,DT JJ JJ NN NNP VBZ PRP MD VB JJ NN POS NN IN DT NN TO DT JJ JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP .
"Speaking Wednesday in Gaza City , senior Hamas leader Ismail Haniyeh says his movement is appealing to its members not to vote in the January 9 poll .",O B-tim O B-geo I-geo O O B-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O,"VBG NNP IN NNP NNP , JJ NNP NN NNP NNP VBZ PRP$ NN VBZ VBG TO PRP$ NNS RB TO VB IN DT NNP CD NN ."
"However , earlier this week , another senior Hamas leader Sheikh Hassan Yousef said his organization is ready to halt attacks on Israel while Palestinians prepare for the polls .",O O O O O O O O B-org O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-gpe O O O O O,"RB , RBR DT NN , DT JJ NNP NN NNP NNP NNP VBD PRP$ NN VBZ JJ TO VB NNS IN NNP IN NNS VBP IN DT NNS ."
Hamas has claimed responsibility for dozens of suicide bombings against Israeli civilian targets in the past four years .,B-org O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-tim I-tim O O,NNP VBZ VBN NN IN NNS IN NN NNS IN JJ JJ NNS IN DT JJ CD NNS .
