"Israel 's acting Prime Minister Ehud Olmert has met with key members of the staff of stricken Prime Minister Ariel Sharon , and says the Israeli government is fully operational .",B-geo O O B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-per O B-per I-per O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,"NNP POS VBG NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN JJ NNS IN DT NN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP , CC VBZ DT JJ NN VBZ RB JJ ."
"Mr. Olmert spoke Thursday after a special cabinet session called as surgeons in Jerusalem battled to save Mr. Sharon 's life , following a massive stroke .",B-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD NNP IN DT JJ NN NN VBD IN NNS IN NNP VBD TO VB NNP NNP POS NN , VBG DT JJ NN ."
"In brief comments , Mr. Olmert called the events of the past 24 hours "" a very difficult situation . """,O O O O B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN JJ NNS , NNP NNP VBD DT NNS IN DT JJ CD NNS LQU DT RB JJ NN . LQU"
But he said the fortitude of Israel will carry it through .,O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,CC PRP VBD DT NN IN NNP MD VB PRP IN .
"Attorney General Meni Mazuz said elections set for March 28 will be held on time , and said government operations will not be affected by the Sharon health crisis .",O B-org I-org I-org O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNS VBN IN NNP CD MD VB VBN IN NN , CC VBD NN NNS MD RB VB VBN IN DT NNP NN NN ."
"Under Israeli law , Mr. Olmert can serve as acting prime minister for up to 100 days - a provision that will allow him to lead the country through the elections .",O B-gpe O O B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN JJ NN , NNP NNP MD VB IN JJ JJ NN IN RB TO CD NNS IN DT NN WDT MD VB PRP TO VB DT NN IN DT NNS ."
