Italy 's highest court has thrown out charges against U.S. and Italian intelligence agents accused of kidnapping an Egyptian Islamist cleric in Milan in 2003 .,B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-gpe O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo O B-tim O,NNP POS JJS NN VBZ VBN RP NNS IN NNP CC JJ NN NNS VBN IN VBG DT JJ NN NN IN NNP IN CD .
The court Wednesday backed the Italian government 's argument that prosecutors illegally used classified intelligence information as evidence .,O O B-tim O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN NNP VBD DT JJ NN POS NN IN NNS RB VBD JJ NN NN IN NN .
Prosecutors contended the state was using the secrecy argument to obstruct justice .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBD DT NN VBD VBG DT NN NN TO VB NN .
The case involves 26 Americans - most of them believed to be Central Intelligence Agency operatives - and Italian defendants .,O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O B-gpe O O,DT NN VBZ CD NNS IN JJS IN PRP VBN TO VB NNP NNP NNP VBZ : CC JJ NNS .
"They include the former head of Italy 's military intelligence agency , Nicolo Pollari .",O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-per I-per O,"PRP VBP DT JJ NN IN NNP POS JJ NN NN , NNP NNP ."
The defendants are accused of kidnapping Egyptian imam Abu Omar from Milan and flying him to Egypt where he says he was tortured in prison .,O O O O O O B-gpe O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP VBN IN VBG JJ NN NNP NNP IN NNP CC VBG PRP TO VB WRB PRP VBZ PRP VBD VBN IN NN .
The Americans were being tried in absentia .,O B-gpe O O O O O O,DT NNS VBD VBG VBN IN NN .
"The Italian government has not asked for their extradition , and the CIA has refused comment on the case .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBZ RB VBN IN PRP$ NN , CC DT NNP VBZ VBN NN IN DT NN ."
