Israeli doctors are discussing when to stop giving Prime Minister Ariel Sharon sedatives that have kept him in a coma since he suffered a massive stroke last week .,B-gpe O O O O O O O B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBG WRB TO VB VBG NNP NNP NNP NNP NNS WDT VBP VBN PRP IN DT NN IN PRP VBD DT JJ NN JJ NN .
Officials at Jerusalem 's Hadassah hospital say doctors plan to perform another brain scan on Mr. Sharon to try to assess damage caused by the stroke .,O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNP POS NNP NN VBP NNS VBP TO VB DT NN NN IN NNP NNP TO VB TO VB NN VBN IN DT NN .
"Mr. Sharon 's condition showed "" slight improvements "" Wednesday .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP NNP POS NN VBD LQU JJ NNS LQU NNP .
But doctors have expressed doubt that the 77-year-old leader will be able to return to work as prime minister .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC NNS VBP VBN NN IN DT JJ NN MD VB JJ TO VB TO VB IN JJ NN .
"Meanwhile , Israel 's right-wing Likud party leader Benjamin Netanyahu has asked four remaining Likud cabinet ministers to resign , as the party chooses a list of candidates for the March 28 elections .",O O B-geo O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O,"RB , NNP POS JJ NNP NN NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN CD VBG NNP NN NNS TO VB , IN DT NN VBZ DT NN IN NNS IN DT NNP CD NNS ."
"Israeli media say it is not clear if the ministers will step down ahead of a crucial cabinet meeting Sunday , when they are to decide whether to permit voting in Arab East Jerusalem for the January 25 Palestinian parliamentary elections .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O B-tim I-tim B-gpe O O O,"JJ NNS VBP PRP VBZ RB JJ IN DT NNS MD VB RB RB IN DT JJ NN NN NNP , WRB PRP VBP TO VB IN TO VB NN IN NNP NNP NNP IN DT NNP CD JJ JJ NNS ."
