The U.S. Commission on International Religious Freedom says sectarian and religiously motivated violence persists in Pakistan and that the government 's response continues to be insufficient .,O B-org I-org O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBZ NN CC RB JJ NN NNS IN NNP CC IN DT NN POS NN VBZ TO VB JJ .
"The Commission 's annual report says in Uzbekistan , restrictive laws on religion severely limit the ability of religious communities to function , and the government controls the manner in which the Islamic faith is practiced .",O B-org O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP POS JJ NN VBZ IN NNP , JJ NNS IN NN RB VBP DT NN IN JJ NNS TO VB , CC DT NN VBZ DT NN IN WDT DT JJ NN VBZ VBN ."
The report says President Saparmurat Niyazov 's monopoly of power and absolute control in Turkmenistan render any independent religious activity in the country impossible .,O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ NNP NNP NNP POS NN IN NN CC JJ NN IN NNP VB DT JJ JJ NN IN DT NN JJ .
"Afghanistan , where the former Taleban regime was once designated as a particularly severe violator , has been added to a watch list of countries that violate religious freedom .",B-geo O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP , WRB DT JJ NNP NN VBD RB VBN IN DT RB JJ NN , VBZ VBN VBN TO DT NN NN IN NNS WDT VBP JJ NN ."
Also on the list is Bangladesh where religious extremism threatens freedom of religion .,O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O,RB IN DT NN VBZ NNP WRB JJ NN VBZ NN IN NN .
"Though not on the watch list , the commission says it is closely monitoring the situation in India and Sri Lanka .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O,"IN RB IN DT NN NN , DT NN VBZ PRP VBZ RB VBG DT NN IN NNP CC NNP NNP ."
