"Taleban militants in Afghanistan have threatened to kill a kidnapped Lebanese engineer working on a U.S.-funded road project , unless his Turkish employer leaves the country within 24 hours .",B-org O O B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-tim O O,"NNP NNS IN NNP VBP VBN TO VB DT VBN JJ NN VBG IN DT JJ NN NN , IN PRP$ JJ NN VBZ DT NN IN CD NNS ."
"A purported Taleban spokesman Abdul Latif Hakimi said that Ahmed Reza will be killed on Wednesday if the Turkish construction company he works for does not leave , or prepares to leave , by then .",O O B-org O B-per I-per I-per O O B-per I-per O O O O B-tim O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNP NN NNP NNP NNP VBD IN NNP NNP MD VB VBN IN NNP IN DT JJ NN NN PRP VBZ IN VBZ RB VB , CC VBZ TO VB , IN RB ."
Officials say no contact has been made with the kidnappers so far but that the government is working to secure Mr. Reza 's release .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O,NNS VBP DT NN VBZ VBN VBN IN DT NNS RB RB CC IN DT NN VBZ VBG TO VB NNP NNP POS NN .
