Taleban militants say they have kidnapped two French aid workers and their three Afghan colleagues in the southwest of the country .,B-org O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBP PRP VBP VBN CD JJ NN NNS CC PRP$ CD JJ NNS IN DT JJS IN DT NN .
"The governor of Nimroz province , Ghulam Dastagir said Thursday there are 200 security personnel searching for the captives .",O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN NNP NN , NNP NNP VBD NNP EX VBP CD NN NNS VBG IN DT NNS ."
Reuters news agency reports that Taleban militants identified the French nationals in a statement posted on the Internet .,B-org O O O O B-org O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O,NNP NN NN VBZ IN NNP NNS VBD DT JJ NNS IN DT NN VBN IN DT NN .
The French and Afghan aid workers were kidnapped Tuesday as the group traveled in a car in Nimroz toward neighboring Farah province .,O B-gpe O B-gpe O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-per O O,DT JJ CC JJ NN NNS VBD VBN NNP IN DT NN VBD IN DT NN IN NNP IN VBG NNP NN .
"The French aid workers are employed by Terre d'Enfance ( A World for Our Children ) , a French-based aid group that works on educational projects for children .",O B-gpe O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN NNS VBP VBN IN NNP NNP LRB NNP NNP IN NNP NNP RRB , DT JJ NN NN WDT VBZ IN JJ NNS IN NNS ."
"In another development , Afghan officials say Taleban insurgents killed a policeman and wounded seven others in a roadside bomb attack Wednesday in the southern province of Kandahar .",O O O O B-gpe O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O,"IN DT NN , JJ NNS VBP NNP NNS VBD DT NN CC VBD CD NNS IN DT NN NN NN NNP IN DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
