Pakistan 's military says a roadside bomb has killed two soldiers in the country 's North Waziristan tribal region .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O,NNP POS JJ VBZ DT NN NN VBZ VBN CD NNS IN DT NN POS JJ NNP JJ NN .
"Four other soldiers were wounded in Thursday 's attack on a military convoy in Spinwam , near the border with Afghanistan .",O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O,"CD JJ NNS VBD VBN IN NNP POS NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , IN DT NN IN NNP ."
"The government has deployed 90,000 troops along the Afghan border to hunt down Taleban and al-Qaida fugitives .",O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-org O B-org O O,DT NN VBZ VBN CD NNS IN DT JJ NN TO VB RP NNP CC NNP NNS .
