Authorities in western India say at least 48 people were killed and about 30 injured when the large water tank they were sitting on collapsed during a village fair .,O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN JJ NNP VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN CC IN CD NN WRB DT JJ NN NN PRP VBD VBG IN VBN IN DT NN NN .
Local officials say the accident happened late Sunday in Baratpur district of Rajasthan state .,O O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O B-org O O,JJ NNS VBP DT NN VBD JJ NNP IN NNP NN IN NNP NN .
They say about 200 people climbed atop the water tank to watch a wrestling match and the structure supporting it gave way .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBP IN CD NNS VBD IN DT NN NN TO VB DT NN NN CC DT NN VBG PRP VBD NN .
The victims fell into the water-filled concrete tank and it came crashing down .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBD IN DT JJ NN NN CC PRP VBD VBG RP .
"The area 's top administrator , R. Venkateshwaran , said the injured were taken to hospitals .",O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN POS JJ NN , NNP NNP , VBD DT NN VBD VBN TO NNS ."
"He said eight people remain hospitalized , while the rest had been discharged .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD CD NNS VBP JJ , IN DT NN VBD VBN VBN ."
The Rajasthan government has ordered an investigation .,O B-org O O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBZ VBN DT NN .
