Mexico has a free market economy in the trillion dollar class .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ DT JJ NN NN IN DT CD NN NN .
"It contains a mixture of modern and outmoded industry and agriculture , increasingly dominated by the private sector .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBZ DT NN IN JJ CC JJ NN CC NN , RB VBN IN DT JJ NN ."
"Recent administrations have expanded competition in seaports , railroads , telecommunications , electricity generation , natural gas distribution , and airports .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP VBN NN IN NNS , NNS , NNS , NN NN , JJ NN NN , CC NNS ."
Per capita income is roughly one-third that of the US ; income distribution remains highly unequal .,O O O O O B-tim O O O B-org O O O O O O O,IN NN NN VBZ RB JJ IN IN DT NNP ; NN NN VBZ RB JJ .
"Since the implementation of the North American Free Trade Agreement ( NAFTA ) in 1994 , Mexico 's share of US imports has increased from 7 % to 12 % , and its share of Canadian imports has doubled to 5 % .",O O O O O B-art I-art I-art I-art I-art O B-art O O B-tim O B-org O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP RRB IN CD , NNP POS NN IN NNP NNS VBZ VBN IN CD NN CC CD NN , CC PRP$ NN IN JJ NNS VBZ VBN TO CD NN ."
"Mexico has free trade agreements with over 50 countries including , Guatemala , Honduras , El Salvador , the European Free Trade Area , and Japan , putting more than 90 % of trade under free trade agreements .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ JJ NN NNS IN IN CD NNS VBG , NNP , NNP , NNP NNP , DT JJ NNP NNP NNP , CC NNP , VBG JJR IN CD NN IN NN IN JJ NN NNS ."
"In 2007 , during its first year in office , the Felipe CALDERON administration was able to garner support from the opposition to successfully pass pension and fiscal reforms .",O B-tim O O O B-tim O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN CD , IN PRP$ JJ NN IN NN , DT NNP NNP NN VBD JJ TO VB NN IN DT NN TO RB VB NN CC JJ NNS ."
The administration passed an energy reform measure in 2008 and another fiscal reform in 2009 .,O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-tim O,DT NN VBD DT NN NN NN IN CD CC DT JJ NN IN CD .
"Mexico 's GDP plunged 6.5 % in 2009 as world demand for exports dropped , asset prices tumbled , and remittances and investment declined .",B-org O B-art O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NN VBD CD NN IN CD IN NN NN IN NNS VBD , NN NNS VBD , CC NNS CC NN VBD ."
"GDP posted positive growth of 5 % in 2010 , with exports - particularly to the United States - leading the way , while domestic consumption and investment lagged .",O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NN VBD JJ NN IN CD NN IN CD , IN NNS : RB TO DT NNP NNPS : VBG DT NN , IN JJ NN CC NN VBN ."
"The administration continues to face many economic challenges , including improving the public education system , upgrading infrastructure , modernizing labor laws , and fostering private investment in the energy sector .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ TO VB JJ JJ NNS , VBG VBG DT JJ NN NN , VBG NN , VBG NN NNS , CC VBG JJ NN IN DT NN NN ."
CALDERON has stated that his top economic priorities remain reducing poverty and creating jobs .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN IN PRP$ JJ JJ NNS VBP VBG NN CC VBG NNS .
