A top Russian official says a state-owned bank obtained $ 6 billion in loans from Chinese banks to help finance the takeover of the main oil production unit of the embattled Yukos energy company .,O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O,DT JJ JJ NN VBZ DT JJ NN VBD $ CD CD IN NNS IN JJ NNS TO VB VB DT NN IN DT JJ NN NN NN IN DT VBN NNP NN NN .
Finance Minister Alexei Kudrin says Vnesheconombank bank borrowed the money to help Rosneft - a state-owned oil firm - purchase Yuganskneftegaz .,O B-per I-per I-per O B-org O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNP NN VBD DT NN TO VB NNP IN DT JJ NN NN : NN NNP .
"The controversial sale culminated a long legal campaign waged by the Kremlin against Yukos and its billionaire owner , Mikhail Khodorkovsky .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-org O O O O O B-per I-per O,"DT JJ NN VBD DT JJ JJ NN VBN IN DT NNP IN NNP CC PRP$ NN NN , NNP NNP ."
Russian authorities auctioned off some of Yukos ' major assets to pay off a $ 28 billion bill for back taxes .,B-gpe O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBD RP DT IN NNP POS JJ NNS TO VB RP DT $ CD CD NN IN JJ NNS .
Analysts say the loan may help ensure China of badly needed oil to satisfy its ever-growing demand .,O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP DT NN MD VB VB NNP IN RB VBN NN TO VB PRP$ JJ NN .
