Dominica was the last of the Caribbean islands to be colonized by Europeans due chiefly to the fierce resistance of the native Caribs .,B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-org O,NNP VBD DT JJ IN DT NNP NNS TO VB VBN IN NNS JJ RB TO DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NNS .
"France ceded possession to Great Britain in 1763 , which made the island a colony in 1805 .",B-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"NNP VBD NN TO NNP NNP IN CD , WDT VBD DT NN DT NN IN CD ."
"In 1980 , two years after independence , Dominica 's fortunes improved when a corrupt and tyrannical administration was replaced by that of Mary Eugenia CHARLES , the first female prime minister in the Caribbean , who remained in office for 15 years .",O B-tim O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-tim O O,"IN CD , CD NNS IN NN , NNP POS NNS VBD WRB DT JJ CC JJ NN VBD VBN IN DT IN NNP NNP NNP , DT JJ JJ JJ NN IN DT NNP , WP VBD IN NN IN CD NNS ."
"Some 3,000 Carib Indians still living on Dominica are the only pre-Columbian population remaining in the eastern Caribbean .",O O B-org B-gpe O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT CD NNP NNS RB VBG IN NNP VBP DT JJ JJ NN VBG IN DT JJ NNP .
