"Israeli aircraft carried out more air strikes in the Gaza Strip Tuesday , continuing an offensive following last week 's cross-border rocket attacks by Palestinian militants .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"JJ NN VBD IN JJR NN NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP , VBG DT JJ NN JJ NN POS JJ NN NNS IN JJ NNS ."
There were no immediate reports of casualties from the pre-dawn missile strikes on Gaza 's Beit Hanoun region .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O,EX VBD DT JJ NNS IN NNS IN DT JJ NN NNS IN NNP POS NNP NNP NN .
The Israeli military says it destroyed bridges used by Palestinian militants .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT JJ NN VBZ PRP VBD NNS VBN IN JJ NNS .
"In the West Bank , Israeli troops arrested 82 more Palestinian militants in overnight sweeps , raising the number of suspects arrested since Sunday to nearly 300 .",O O B-org I-org O B-gpe O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O,"IN DT NNP NNP , JJ NNS VBN CD JJR JJ NNS IN JJ NNS , VBG DT NN IN NNS VBN IN NNP TO RB CD ."
Israel 's Defense Minister Shaul Mofaz vowed that Israel will press on with the offensive .,B-geo O O O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O,NNP POS NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD IN NNP MD VB IN IN DT NN .
"Meanwhile , Israeli Prime Minister Ariel Sharon won a narrow victory within his Likud party late Monday , when members voted down a proposal to hold primary elections in November .",O O B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"RB , JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN PRP$ NNP NN JJ NNP , WRB NNS VBD RP DT NN TO VB JJ NNS IN NNP ."
Former Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu had pressed for a November primary to punish Mr. Sharon for evacuating the Gaza Strip .,O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-tim O O O B-per I-per O O O B-geo I-geo O,JJ JJ NN NNP NNP VBD VBN IN DT NNP NN TO VB NNP NNP IN VBG DT NNP NNP .
