"Iranian state media said the country 's electoral oversight council has approved four candidates , including incumbent Mahmoud Ahmadinejad , to compete in next month 's presidential election .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN NNS VBD DT NN POS JJ NN NN VBZ VBN CD NNS , VBG JJ NNP NNP , TO VB IN JJ NN POS JJ NN ."
"The official IRNA news agency reported Wednesday that the Guardian Council approved Mr. Ahmadinejad , former prime minister Mir Hossein Mousavi , ex-parliament speaker Mehdi Karroubi and the former head of the Revolutionary Guards Mohsen Rezai .",O O B-org O O O B-tim O O B-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O O B-per I-per O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,"DT JJ NNP NN NN VBD NNP IN DT NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP , JJ JJ NN NNP NNP NNP , NN NN NNP NNP CC DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNPS NNP NNP ."
The 12-member council approved the candidates after screening them for their allegiance to Iran 's Islamic government system and official religion .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBD DT NNS IN VBG PRP IN PRP$ NN TO NNP POS JJ NN NN CC JJ NN .
"More than 450 Iranians had registered to run for president , including 42 women .",O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJR IN CD NNS VBD VBN TO VB IN NN , VBG CD NNS ."
"Mr. Ahmadinejad 's rivals have criticized his handling of the economy , which suffers from high inflation .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP POS NNS VBP VBN PRP$ NN IN DT NN , WDT VBZ IN JJ NN ."
"However , the president has won praise at home for trying to raise Iran 's profile in rocket and satellite technology .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"RB , DT NN VBZ VBN NN IN NN IN VBG TO VB NNP POS NN IN NN CC NN NN ."
The election is June 12 .,O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT NN VBZ NNP CD .
