"U.S. officials are urging all democratic nations to call for an end to the "" violence and intimidation "" in Cuba , after Cuban authorities raided a church this week to arrest demonstrators .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNS VBP VBG DT JJ NNS TO VB IN DT NN TO DT LQU NN CC NN LQU IN NNP , IN JJ NNS VBD DT NN DT NN TO VB NNS ."
"A U.S. State Department spokesman , Gonzalo Gallegos , issued a statement late Friday , saying the "" escalation in repression "" by the Cuban government against activists should be of concern to all nations who embrace human rights .",O B-org I-org I-org O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP NNP NN , NNP NNP , VBD DT NN JJ NNP , VBG DT RQU NN IN NN LQU IN DT JJ NN IN NNS MD VB IN NN TO DT NNS WP VBP JJ NNS ."
"The Archbishop of the Cuban city of Santiago , Monsignor Dionisio Garcia Ibanez , said Cuban authorities apologized to the Roman Catholic Church for Tuesday 's raid on a parish church .",O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo B-per I-per O O B-gpe O O O O B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , NNP NNP NNP NNP , VBD JJ NNS VBD TO DT NNP NNP NNP IN NNP POS NN IN DT JJ NN ."
Police entered the church 's grounds to arrest an unknown number of people after they held a protest march outside .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD DT NN POS NNS TO VB DT JJ NN IN NNS IN PRP VBD DT NN NN NN .
They reportedly have been released .,O O O O O O,PRP RB VBP VBN VBN .
