Pakistan 's army chief has vowed to restore government authority to the militancy-hit Swat valley .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,NNP POS NN NN VBZ VBN TO VB NN NN TO DT JJ NNP NN .
"A military statement said General Ashfaq Parvez Kayani traveled to Swat Wednesday to be briefed by local leaders , field commanders and troops .",O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN NN VBD NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD TO VB NNP TO VB VBN IN JJ NNS , NN NNS CC NNS ."
"The statement said Kayani gave new directions to the troops , who have been fighting Taliban militants for more than a year , but it did not elaborate .",O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD NNP VBD JJ NNS TO DT NNS , WP VBP VBN VBG NNP NNS IN JJR IN DT NN , CC PRP VBD RB VB ."
"Local Taliban fighters loyal to radical cleric Maulana Fazlullah control most parts of the scenic northwestern valley , where they are trying to impose strict Islamic law .",O B-org O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNS JJ TO JJ NN NNP NNP VB RBS NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN , WRB PRP VBP VBG TO VB JJ JJ NN ."
They have banned girls ' education and blown up nearly 200 schools to enforce that order .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBP VBN NNS POS NN CC VBN RP RB CD NNS TO VB DT NN .
Authorities said they found eight bullet-ridden bodies in the area Wednesday .,O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNS VBD PRP VBD CD JJ NNS IN DT NN NNP .
It was not clear who killed them .,O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD RB JJ WP VBD PRP .
