The World Health Organization is warning that one million people throughout East Asia and the Pacific contract tuberculosis each year but fail to get treatment .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo O O B-tim O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBG IN CD CD NNS IN NNP NNP CC DT NNP NN NN DT NN CC VBP TO VB NN .
The United Nations agency also says it estimates half of all the new cases in the region go undetected .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNPS NN RB VBZ PRP VBZ NN IN PDT DT JJ NNS IN DT NN VB JJ .
"The WHO says tuberculosis kills four people worldwide every minute and in Asia , 1,000 people daily - accounting for more deaths than any other infectious disease , including AIDS .",O B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP VBZ NN NNS CD NNS JJ DT NN CC IN NNP , CD NNS JJ : NN IN JJR NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN , VBG NNP ."
"The agency says the main causes for the spread of tuberculosis are poor awareness among the public , limited access to health care , and low quality laboratory services .",O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ DT JJ NNS IN DT NN IN NNS VBP JJ NN IN DT NN , JJ NN TO NN NN , CC JJ NN NN NNS ."
"Thursday has been declared "" World Stop TB Day . """,B-tim O O O O B-eve I-eve I-eve I-eve O O,NNP VBZ VBN VBN LQU NNP NNP NNP NNP . RQU
