"A U.S. newspaper says Iran has withdrawn most of its Revolutionary Guards from Lebanon , where they were deployed more than 20 years ago and helped create the Shi'ite Muslim movement Hezbollah .",O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-org O,"DT NNP NN VBZ NNP VBZ VBN JJS IN PRP$ JJ NNS IN NNP , WRB PRP VBD VBN RBR IN CD NNS RB CC VBD VB DT NNP NNP NN NNP ."
"Citing U.S. and European officials , the Washington Post says only 15 to 20 Iranian military personnel remain in Lebanon , where at one point Iran was estimated to have as many as two-thousand of its elite troops .",O B-geo O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"VBG NNP CC JJ NNS , DT NNP NNP VBZ RB CD CC CD JJ JJ NNS VBP IN NNP , WRB IN CD NN NNP VBD VBN TO VB RB JJ IN CD IN PRP$ JJ NNS ."
"Iran is said to have begun the phased withdrawal more than five years ago , but did not publicly announce it .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBN TO VB VBN DT VBN NN JJR IN CD NNS RB , CC VBD RB RB VB PRP ."
"Iran had deployed troops to protect Lebanon 's Shi'ite population , after Israel 's 1982 invasion of Lebanon .",B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O B-geo O,"NNP VBD VBN NNS TO VB NNP POS NNP NN , IN NNP POS CD NN IN NNP ."
Syria has promised to finish the withdrawal of thousands of its troops from Lebanon by the end of the month .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim I-tim O O O,NNP VBZ VBN TO VB DT NN IN NNS IN PRP$ NNS IN NNP IN DT NN IN DT NN .
