"Burundi President Domitien Ndayizeye has signed a series of laws , creating a new national defense force that includes former rebel fighters .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN NNS , VBG DT JJ JJ NN NN WDT VBZ JJ NN NNS ."
"A presidential spokesman , Pancrace Cimpaye , says since the New Year , the Burundi Armed Forces - as it was formerly called - no longer exists .",O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-org I-org O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN , NNP NNP , VBZ IN DT NNP NNP , DT NNP NNP NNPS : IN PRP VBD RB VBN : DT RB VBZ ."
"The new National Defense Force will have 30,000 troops - evenly split among the nation 's minority ethnic Tutsis and majority Hutus .",O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNP NNP NNP MD VB CD NNS : RB VBN IN DT NN POS NN JJ NNS CC NN NNS .
Twenty-thousand officers will make up the new National Police Force - also evenly divided between Tutsis and Hutus .,O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-gpe O B-gpe O,CD NNS MD VB RP DT JJ NNP NNP NNP : RB RB VBN IN NNS CC NNS .
"As part of a peace deal to end Burundi 's decade-long war , several former Hutu rebel groups have joined a transitional government designed to end years of dominance by minority Tutsis .",O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NN IN DT NN NN TO VB NNP POS JJ NN , JJ JJ NNP NN NNS VBP VBN DT JJ NN VBN TO VB NNS IN NN IN NN NN ."
"However , Burundi 's oldest Hutu rebel group , the National Liberation Forces , continues to fight the government .",O O B-gpe O O B-gpe O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O,"RB , NNP POS JJS NNP NN NN , DT NNP NNP NNP , VBZ TO VB DT NN ."
