China is warning that Taiwan is stirring new tension with its massive protest march against Beijing 's new anti-secession law .,B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBG IN NNP VBZ VBG JJ NN IN PRP$ JJ NN NN IN NNP POS JJ JJ NN .
"Mainland newspapers ran a dispatch from the official Xinhua news agency Sunday , saying Taiwan 's independence forces are the biggest threat to peace and stability in the Taiwan Strait .",O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNP NNS VBD DT NN IN DT JJ NNP NN NN NNP , VBG NNP POS NN NNS VBP DT JJS NN TO NN CC NN IN DT NNP NNP ."
"The commentary says the non-peaceful means mentioned in Beijing 's anti-secession law is targeted at secessionist forces , and not at Taiwan compatriots .",O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"DT NN VBZ DT JJ NNS VBN IN NNP POS JJ NN VBZ VBN IN JJ NNS , CC RB IN NNP NNS ."
Taiwan President Chen Shui-bian and hundreds of thousands of protesters took to the streets of Taipei Saturday to oppose the law .,B-geo B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP CC NNS IN NNS IN NNS VBD TO DT NNS IN NNP NNP TO VB DT NN .
"The United States , among other countries , is concerned Beijing may use the law to declare war on Taiwan , which China considers part of its territory .",O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNPS , IN JJ NNS , VBZ JJ NNP MD VB DT NN TO VB NN IN NNP , WDT NNP VBZ NN IN PRP$ NN ."
