Egypt 's opposition Muslim Brotherhood says it has won more seats in the nation 's month-long parliamentary elections .,B-geo O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NN NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ VBN JJR NNS IN DT NN POS JJ JJ NNS .
"A Brotherhood spokesman , Issam al-Aryan , said Sunday unofficial results from Saturday 's second phase runoffs gave his movement 28 more seats , adding to the 47 won in previous rounds of voting .",O B-per O O B-per I-per O O B-tim O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NN , NNP NNP , VBD NNP JJ NNS IN NNP POS JJ NN NNS VBD PRP$ NN CD JJR NNS , VBG TO DT CD NN IN JJ NNS IN NN ."
Official results have yet to be released .,O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP RB TO VB VBN .
"The ruling National Democratic Party still dominates the 444-seat parliament , having won at least 120 seats .",O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN NNP NNP NNP RB VBZ DT JJ NN , VBG VBN IN JJS CD NNS ."
A final round of voting will be held Thursday .,O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT JJ NN IN NN MD VB VBN NNP .
The Muslim Brotherhood has accused the ruling party of obstructing the election after hundreds of the group 's members were arrested .,O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT VBG NN IN VBG DT NN IN NNS IN DT NN POS NNS VBD VBN .
"The group accuses police of intimidating voters , dispersing crowds with tear gas and rubber bullets and shutting polling stations where police suspected support for Islamist candidates .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O,"DT NN VBZ NNS IN VBG NNS , VBG NNS IN JJ NN CC NN NNS CC VBG NN NNS WRB NNS VBD NN IN NNP NNS ."
"The Brotherhood is banned as a political party , but endorses candidates who support the party 's Islamist platform .",O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O,"DT NNP VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NN , CC VBZ NNS WP VBP DT NN POS NN NN ."
