"The European Union has formally launched an investigation into surging Chinese textile sales , a move that could lead the EU to limit those imports .",O B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP VBZ RB VBN DT NN IN VBG JJ NN NNS , DT NN WDT MD VB DT NNP TO VB DT NNS ."
"European Commission members approved the investigation Thursday , amid growing concerns by EU members that Chinese textile imports have flooded European markets since a worldwide quota system expired January 1 .",B-org I-org O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-org O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"NNP NNP NNS VBD DT NN NNP , IN VBG NNS IN NNP NNS IN JJ NN NNS VBP VBN JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN NN VBD NNP CD ."
Officials say the investigation can last up to 60 days - and after that period limits could then be imposed .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP DT NN MD VB RP TO CD NNS : CC IN DT NN NNS MD RB VB VBN .
"France , however , is calling for the EU to bypass the investigation and instead take emergency actions to limit the quantity of imports .",B-org O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP , RB , VBZ VBG IN DT NNP TO VB DT NN CC RB VB NN NNS TO VB DT NN IN NNS ."
"China has criticized the EU move , warning it could have a negative impact on relations .",B-geo O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBN DT NNP NN , VBG PRP MD VB DT JJ NN IN NNS ."
