"Several people were wounded in northwest Pakistan Thursday , after roadside bombs exploded in attacks against security forces .",O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBD VBN IN JJ NNP NNP , IN NN NNS VBD IN NNS IN NN NNS ."
"In the first incident , a bomb struck a police van taking people to jail in the district of Dir in North West Frontier Province .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,"IN DT JJ NN , DT NN VBD DT NN NN VBG NNS TO NN IN DT NN IN NNP IN NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
At least three officers and two prisoners were hurt .,O O O O O O O O O O,IN JJS CD NNS CC CD NNS VBD VBN .
"Elsewhere , police officials say two roadside bombs exploded near a military convoy in North Waziristan , wounding one soldier .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O,"RB , NN NNS VBP CD NN NNS VBD IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP , VBG CD NN ."
Pro-Taleban militants in North Waziristan have pulled out of a peace deal with the Pakistani government designed to drive out foreign extremists .,O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS IN NNP NNP VBP VBN IN IN DT NN NN IN DT JJ NN VBN TO VB RP JJ NNS .
A U.S. intelligence report issued last week said al-Qaida terrorists have been given safe haven in the remote tribal region along the Afghan border .,O B-geo O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT NNP NN NN VBN JJ NN VBD NNP NNS VBP VBN VBN JJ NN IN DT JJ JJ NN IN DT JJ NN .
"Militants have increased attacks in Pakistan over the last two weeks , killing around 200 people in a series of suicide bombings since the government raided a radical Islamic mosque in Islamabad .",O O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNS VBP VBN NNS IN NNP IN DT JJ CD NNS , VBG IN CD NNS IN DT NN IN NN NNS IN DT NN VBD DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP ."
