"More strong aftershocks rattled parts of Indian and Pakistani Kashmir early Wednesday , triggering more landslides in the already devastated region .",O O O O O O B-geo O B-gpe B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,"RBR JJ NNS VBD NNS IN NNP CC JJ NNP JJ NNP , VBG JJR NNS IN DT RB VBN NN ."
"Pakistani officials say the tremors of 5.8 and 5.6 magnitude were the strongest since the massive October 8 earthquake that killed more than 40,000 people in Pakistani Kashmir .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-geo O,JJ NNS VBP DT NNS IN CD CC CD NN VBD DT JJS IN DT JJ NNP CD NN WDT VBD JJR IN CD NNS IN JJ NNP .
India says about 1400 people were killed in its side of the Himalayan region .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ IN CD NNS VBD VBN IN PRP$ NN IN DT JJ NN .
The United Nations World Food Program says almost half-a-million earthquake survivors in Pakistan have yet to receive relief supplies .,O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ RB JJ NN NNS IN NNP VBP RB TO VB NN NNS .
"Tuesday , Pakistani President Musharraf appealed to the international community for more tents to shelter the homeless .",B-tim O B-gpe B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP , JJ NNP NNP VBD TO DT JJ NN IN JJR NNS TO NN DT NN ."
He also offered to open up the military Line of Control in Kashmir - allowing Indian Kashmiris to cross into Pakistan 's portion and assist in reconstruction efforts .,O O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-geo I-geo I-geo B-gpe B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,PRP RB VBD TO VB RP DT JJ NN IN NNP IN NNP IN VBG JJ NNP TO VB IN NNP POS NN CC VB IN NN NNS .
India has welcomed the offer .,B-geo O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN DT NN .
But the two sides have yet to work out procedural details .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC DT CD NNS VBP RB TO VB RP JJ NNS .
