Chinese rescue crews have recovered the bodies of all 83 miners killed in Monday 's mine blast in northwestern Xinjiang region .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O O,JJ NN NNS VBP VBN DT NNS IN DT CD NNS VBN IN NNP POS NN NN IN JJ NNP NN .
China 's official Xinhua news agency says only four of the 87 miners underground at the time survived the tragedy at the Shenlong Coal Mine in Fukang County .,B-geo O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-geo I-geo O,NNP POS JJ NNP NN NN VBZ RB CD IN DT CD NNS RB IN DT NN VBD DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP IN NNP NNP .
Xinhua says the explosion was caused by a buildup of gas in the mine shaft .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NN IN NN IN DT NN NN .
Officials say this is the worst coal mine accident in Xinjiang 's history .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,NNS VBP DT VBZ DT JJS NN NN NN IN NNP POS NN .
The regional government has asked other area coal mine operators to suspend production and make needed safety improvements .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBZ VBN JJ NN NN NN NNS TO VB NN CC VB VBN NN NNS .
"China 's coal mines are the world 's most dangerous , with explosions , floods and fires killing thousands of workers each year .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"NNP POS NN NNS VBP DT NN POS RBS JJ , IN NNS , NNS CC NNS VBG NNS IN NNS DT NN ."
Inadequate safety equipment and lax safety rules are often blamed for the accidents .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NN NN CC NN NN NNS VBP RB VBN IN DT NNS .
