"Iran 's nuclear ambitions are the main topic of discussion Saturday at the World Economic Forum in Davos , Switzerland .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-org I-org I-org O B-geo O B-geo O,"NNP POS JJ NNS VBP DT JJ NN IN NN NNP IN DT NNP NNP NNP IN NNP , NNP ."
British Foreign Secretary Jack Straw says chances Iran can avoid being referred to the U.N. Security Council for possible sanctions are low if Tehran continues its controversial nuclear research .,B-gpe O B-per I-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNS NNP MD VB VBG VBN TO DT NNP NNP NNP IN JJ NNS VBP JJ IN NNP VBZ PRP$ JJ JJ NN .
"Straw says Iran 's chief nuclear negotiator , Ali Larijani , is expected to confer with British and other officials Monday in London .",B-per O B-geo O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-tim O B-geo O,"NNP VBZ NNP POS JJ JJ NN , NNP NNP , VBZ VBN TO VB IN JJ CC JJ NNS NNP IN NNP ."
Ministers at the Davos conference also are expected to work Saturday on setting a timetable for future talks on cutting farm subsidies and opening markets to developing nations .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN DT NNP NN RB VBP VBN TO VB NNP IN VBG DT NN IN JJ NNS IN VBG NN NNS CC VBG NNS TO VBG NNS .
Ministers representing more than 25 World Trade Organization members are scheduled to conclude the two-day meeting Saturday .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNS VBG JJR IN CD NNP NNP NNP NNS VBP VBN TO VB DT JJ NN NNP .
