U.S. public diplomacy chief Karen Hughes meets Egyptian Prime Minister Ahmed Nazif in Cairo Monday - the second day of a tour aimed at polishing America 's image in the Middle East .,B-geo O O O B-per I-per O B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O B-geo B-tim I-tim O B-tim I-tim I-tim O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O,NNP JJ NN NN NNP NNP VBZ JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP IN NNP NNP IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN VBN IN VBG NNP POS NN IN DT NNP NNP .
"Sunday , Ms. Hughes met with the head of Cairo 's Al Azhar mosque , Sheikh Mohammed Sayyed Tantawi , who is an influential Islamic leader .",B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org B-per I-per O O O O O O O O,"NNP , NNP NNP VBD IN DT NN IN NNP POS NNP NNP NN , NNP NNP NNP NNP , WP VBZ DT JJ JJ NN ."
"Speaking with reporters , Ms. Hughes has acknowledged she faces a "" huge challenge "" in her efforts to win greater foreign public support for U.S. policies .",O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"VBG IN NNS , NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP VBZ DT LQU JJ NN LQU IN PRP$ NNS TO VB JJR JJ NN NN IN NNP NNS ."
"She said she understands there are many "" deep-seated "" differences and concerns about American policies .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,PRP VBD PRP VBZ EX VBP JJ RQU JJ RQU NNS CC NNS IN JJ NNS .
Ms. Hughes also is traveling this week to Saudi Arabia and Turkey on her first foreign trip as Undersecretary of State for Public Diplomacy .,B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,NNP NNP RB VBZ VBG DT NN TO NNP NNP CC NNP IN PRP$ JJ JJ NN IN NNP IN NNP IN NNP NNP .
"She calls her trip a "" listening tour , "" to acquaint her with America 's image abroad .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"PRP VBZ PRP$ NN DT LQU VBG NN , LQU TO VB PRP$ IN NNP POS NN RB ."
