"Australia is warning its citizens to avoid travel to Pakistan due to what it calls a "" very high threat "" of terrorist attack , including a possible plot against Western hotels in the capital .",B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBG PRP$ NNS TO VB NN TO NNP JJ TO WP PRP VBZ DT LQU RB JJ NN LQU IN JJ NN , VBG DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS IN DT NN ."
"In the warning issued Monday , the Department of Foreign Affairs said Australian officials continue to receive reports that terrorists are planning attacks against a range of targets , including areas frequented by foreigners .",O O O O B-tim O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN VBN NNP , DT NNP IN NNP NNP VBD JJ NNS VBP TO VB NNS IN NNS VBP VBG NNS IN DT NN IN NNS , VBG NNS VBN IN NNS ."
The statement says recent credible reporting indicates a potential threat against Western hotels in Islamabad .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-geo O,DT NN VBZ JJ JJ NN VBZ DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS IN NNP .
"It also says recent reports suggest that terrorists are planning attacks against Western , including Australian , individuals and interests in Peshawar .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O,"PRP RB VBZ JJ NNS VBP IN NNS VBP VBG NNS IN NNP , VBG JJ , NNS CC NNS IN NNP ."
"But it warns that attacks "" could occur at any time , anywhere "" in Pakistan .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"CC PRP VBZ IN NNS LQU MD VB IN DT NN , RB LQU IN NNP ."
Pakistan Foreign Ministry spokeswoman Tasnim Aslam is quoted saying that Pakistan does not have any information about any plot to attack Western hotels .,B-org I-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,NNP NNP NNP NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN VBG IN NNP VBZ RB VB DT NN IN DT NN TO VB JJ NNS .
