"Two explosions are reported outside the Lao capital , Vientiane , as the country prepares to host a major summit of regional countries .",O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"CD NNS VBP VBN IN DT JJ NN , NNP , IN DT NN VBZ TO VB DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS ."
Witnesses say the blasts occurred Friday near the border with Thailand .,O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-geo O,NNS VBP DT NNS VBD NNP IN DT NN IN NNP .
"No casualties were reported , and it is not clear what caused the blasts .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS VBD VBN , CC PRP VBZ RB JJ WP VBD DT NNS ."
The United States has warned that opponents of the Lao government may be plotting bomb attacks in Vientiane and elsewhere in the country during next week 's summit .,O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NNS IN DT JJ NN MD VB VBG NN NNS IN NNP CC RB IN DT NN IN JJ NN POS NN .
