"Six Lebanese soldiers have been killed in firefights as troops shelled a Palestinian refugee camp in northern Lebanon , where Islamic militants have been holed up for nearly eight weeks .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"CD JJ NNS VBP VBN VBN IN NNS IN NNS VBD DT JJ NN NN IN JJ NNP , WRB JJ NNS VBP VBN VBN RP IN RB CD NNS ."
"The bombardment targeting Fatah al-Islam militants began early Thursday , after more of the few remaining refugees in the camp fled .",O O O B-org I-org O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBG NNP NNP NNS VBD RB NNP , IN RBR IN DT JJ VBG NNS IN DT NN VBD ."
Reports say it is some of the heaviest shelling of the Nahr al-Bared camp since the standoff began .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,NNS VBP PRP VBZ DT IN DT JJS NN IN DT NNP JJ NN IN DT NN VBD .
"The militants responded with gunfire , ambushing soldiers on the ground .",O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS VBD IN NN , VBG NNS IN DT NN ."
It is not clear if the shelling marks the start of a planned Lebanese army offensive against the militants .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,PRP VBZ RB JJ IN DT VBG NNS DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NN NN IN DT NNS .
A military source told reporters the operation is meant to increase pressure on the militants to surrender .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBD NNS DT NN VBZ VBN TO VB NN IN DT NNS TO VB .
"More than 170 people , including about 90 Lebanese soldiers , have been killed since the standoff began May 20 .",O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"JJR IN CD NNS , VBG IN CD JJ NNS , VBP VBN VBN IN DT NN VBD NNP CD ."
