A report says North Korea has reactivated a nuclear reactor that could be used to refine materials for nuclear warheads .,O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN WDT MD VB VBN TO VB NNS IN JJ NNS .
"Japan 's Asahi daily newspaper said Sunday that a U.S. spy satellite detected steam coming from a boiler at the Yongbyon nuclear plant , north of the capital , Pyongyang .",B-geo O B-geo O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP POS NNP JJ NN VBD NNP IN DT NNP NN NN VBD NN VBG IN DT NN IN DT NNP JJ NN , NN IN DT NN , NNP ."
"The paper says the vapor was detected before the resumption of six-way nuclear talks in late July , and the issue of the reactivation was discussed during the negotiations .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NN IN JJ JJ NNS IN JJ NNP , CC DT NN IN DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NNS ."
"Asahi quotes an unidentified U.S. official as saying North Korea has indicated it will give up on the nuclear reactor , yet continues to steadily expand nuclear development .",B-geo O O O B-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ DT JJ NNP NN IN VBG NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP MD VB RP IN DT JJ NN , RB VBZ TO RB VB JJ NN ."
The six-party talks are scheduled to resume sometime next week .,O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNS VBP VBN TO VB RB JJ NN .
