President Bush is defending his decision to halt troop withdrawals from Iraq while military leaders assess how a reduced American presence will affect security there .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBG PRP$ NN TO VB NN NNS IN NNP IN JJ NNS VBP WRB DT JJ JJ NN MD VB NN RB .
"During his weekly radio address Saturday , the president said America must stand with the Iraqi government as it makes the transition to responsibility for its own security and political affairs .",O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN PRP$ JJ NN NN NNP , DT NN VBD NNP MD VB IN DT JJ NN IN PRP VBZ DT NN TO NN IN PRP$ JJ NN CC JJ NNS ."
Mr. Bush said a U.S. troop surge 15 months ago has significantly improved security .,B-per I-per O O B-geo O O B-tim O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD DT NNP NN NN CD NNS RB VBZ RB VBN NN .
He said he has given the U.S. commander in Iraq all the time he needs to decide if security conditions are stable enough to continue withdrawing U.S. troops .,O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,PRP VBD PRP VBZ VBN DT NNP NN IN NNP PDT DT NN PRP VBZ TO VB IN NN NNS VBP JJ JJ TO VB VBG NNP NNS .
"Meanwhile , U.S. Representative John Yarmuth blamed the cost of the Iraq war for America 's sluggish economy .",O O B-org I-org B-per B-org O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O,"RB , NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN DT NNP NN IN NNP POS JJ NN ."
"In the Democrats ' weekly radio address Saturday , Yarmuth said money being spent on the war should instead be used to deal with pressing needs at home .",O O B-org O O O O B-tim O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NNPS POS JJ NN NN NNP , NNP VBD NN VBG VBN IN DT NN MD RB VB VBN TO VB IN VBG NNS IN NN ."
