The U.N. Food and Agriculture Organization says the number of hungry people in the world increased by about 50 million last year due to high food prices .,O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP CC NNP NNP VBZ DT NN IN JJ NNS IN DT NN VBN IN IN CD CD JJ NN JJ TO JJ NN NNS .
"FAO Director-General Jacques Diouf , speaking in Brussels Thursday , said prices have risen as population growth increased demand .",B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP , NN IN NNP NNP , VBD NNS VBP VBN IN NN NN VBD NN ."
"He also said climate change , particularly droughts and floods , has hurt food production .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP RB VBD NN NN , RB NNS CC NNS , VBZ VBN NN NN ."
The FAO says global food production needs to double by 2050 in order to meet growing demand .,O B-org O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O,DT NNP VBZ JJ NN NN VBZ TO VB IN CD IN NN TO VB VBG NN .
"The group says production increases should take place mostly in developing countries , where more than 95 percent of the projected population increase will occur .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ NN NNS MD VB NN RB IN VBG NNS , WRB JJR IN CD NN IN DT VBN NN NN MD VB ."
"Diouf said increasing agricultural production in developing countries will require about $ 24 billion a year to be spent on water management , improving rural roads , and research .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD VBG JJ NN IN VBG NNS MD VB IN $ CD CD DT NN TO VB VBN IN NN NN , VBG JJ NNS , CC NN ."
