Colombia 's largest Marxist rebel group has ruled out a prisoner exchange with the government as long as Alvaro Uribe is president .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O,NNP POS JJS JJ NN NN VBZ VBN RP DT NN NN IN DT NN RB RB IN NNP NNP VBZ NN .
"In a statement on its website , the Revolutionary Armed Forces of Colombia accused President Uribe of lacking the political will to resolve the situation and instead has focused on the military aspect of the war .",O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O B-per B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN IN PRP$ NN , DT NNP NNP NNS IN NNP VBD NNP NNP IN VBG DT JJ NN TO VB DT NN CC RB VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN ."
The Colombian government has previously offered to meet with FARC rebels to discuss a possible prisoner swap .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBZ RB VBN TO VB IN NNP NNS TO VB DT JJ NN NN .
"The rebel group is holding scores of hostages , including a presidential candidate and three American contractors .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"DT NN NN VBZ VBG NNS IN NNS , VBG DT JJ NN CC CD JJ NNS ."
"Meanwhile , police in the southern Putumayo region accuse FARC rebels of blowing up oil wells and an electricity tower near the Ecuadorian border over the last few days .",O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-tim O O,"RB , NNS IN DT JJ NNP NN VBP NNP NNS IN VBG RP NN NNS CC DT NN NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ JJ NNS ."
"FARC has been at war with the Colombian government for more than four decades , in a conflict that has claimed tens of thousands of lives .",B-org O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBN IN NN IN DT JJ NN IN JJR IN CD NNS , IN DT NN WDT VBZ VBN NNS IN NNS IN NNS ."
