Gunmen in Somalia 's capital have seriously wounded a member of parliament and killed his driver .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNP POS NN VBP RB VBN DT NN IN NN CC VBD PRP$ NN .
Officials said the attack on Amir Mohamed Jaketi took place Wednesday morning in northern Mogadishu .,O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-tim I-tim O O B-geo O,NNS VBD DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP VBD NN NNP NN IN JJ NNP .
"Witnesses said unidentified men sprayed the lawmaker 's car with gunfire , leaving him with several wounds , including one in the chest .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBD JJ NNS VBD DT NN POS NN IN NN , VBG PRP IN JJ NNS , VBG CD IN DT NN ."
"The driver was killed on the spot , while Jaketi was rushed to a hospital .",O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NN , IN NNP VBD VBN TO DT NN ."
This was the first attack on a Somali legislator since a new unity government was formed earlier this year .,O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT VBD DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN NN VBD VBN RBR DT NN .
"Hardline Islamist groups have vowed to continue fighting the government , which is led by a moderate Islamist , President Sheikh Sharif Sheikh Ahmed .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim B-geo O B-per I-per I-per I-per I-per O,"JJ JJ NNS VBP VBN TO VB VBG DT NN , WDT VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
"Last week , a roadside bomb blast wounded Interior Minister Abdulkadir Ali Omar .",O O O O O O O O O B-per O B-per I-per O,"JJ NN , DT NN NN NN VBD NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
He suffered only minor injuries .,O O O O O O,PRP VBD RB JJ NNS .
