"Relatives of people wounded in the riots in the eastern Uzbekistan town of Andijan , crowd against the gates of the city hospital Uzbekistan 's government has taken a group of foreign diplomats and journalists on a tour of Andijan , the site of deadly clashes between security forces and anti-government demonstrators last week .",O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN NNS VBN IN DT NNS IN DT JJ NNP NN IN NNP , NN IN DT NNS IN DT NN NN NNP POS NN VBZ VBN DT NN IN JJ NNS CC NNS IN DT NN IN NNP , DT NN IN JJ NNS IN NN NNS CC JJ NNS JJ NN ."
"Government officials accompanied the foreigners , who were not allowed to roam freely , and introduced them to residents who backed the official version of events .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NN NNS VBD DT NNS , WP VBD RB VBN TO VB RB , CC VBD PRP TO NNS WP VBD DT JJ NN IN NNS ."
"Uzbekistan 's government maintains that rebels - not security forces - fired on demonstrators , killing 169 people , including 32 government troops , but an opposition group says it has compiled a list of 745 dead .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NN VBZ IN NNS IN RB NN NNS : VBD IN NNS , VBG CD NNS , VBG CD NN NNS , CC DT NN NN VBZ PRP VBZ VBN DT NN IN CD JJ ."
"In Geneva Wednesday , the U.N. High Commissioner for Human Rights Louise Arbour called for an independent probe into the events in Andijan .",O B-per B-tim O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"IN NNP NNP , DT NNP NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNS IN NNP ."
"Many countries , including the United States , have expressed concern at the heavy-handed crackdown against protesters .",O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS , VBG DT NNP NNPS , VBP VBN NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNS ."
