Australian police have searched two hospitals in Western Australia in connection with last week 's failed car-bomb attacks in London and Glasgow .,B-gpe O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,JJ NNS VBP VBN CD NNS IN NNP NNP IN NN IN JJ NN POS VBN NN NNS IN NNP CC NNP .
Federal police commissioner Mick Keelty said police seized computer files and other materials from hospitals in the state capital Perth and the gold mining town of Kalgoorlie Friday .,O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O,JJ NN NN NNP NNP VBD NNS VBD NN NNS CC JJ NNS IN NNS IN DT NN NN NNP CC DT NN NN NN IN NNP NNP .
The raids came after an Indian doctor was arrested Monday in the eastern Australian city of Brisbane .,O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-tim O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O,DT NNS VBD IN DT JJ NN VBD VBN NNP IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP .
The 27-year old Mohamed Haneef is one of eight suspects who are all doctors or worked for Britain 's national health service .,O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,DT JJ JJ NNP NNP VBZ CD IN CD NNS WP VBP DT NNS CC VBD IN NNP POS JJ NN NN .
He is the only one held outside Britain .,O O O O O O O B-geo O,PRP VBZ DT RB CD VBN IN NNP .
"Australian police said their investigation into the British bomb plot has widened into a third state , New South Wales , where several foreign doctors are being questioned Friday .",B-gpe O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"JJ NNS VBD PRP$ NN IN DT JJ NN NN VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP , WRB JJ JJ NNS VBP VBG VBN NNP ."
