Thousands of Israeli troops and soldiers have stopped opponents of the Gaza withdrawal from marching into the Palestinian territory .,O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O,NNS IN JJ NNS CC NNS VBP VBN NNS IN DT NNP NN IN VBG IN DT JJ NN .
The massive Israeli force prevented the demonstrators from marching south of the Israeli town of Ofakim .,O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O,DT JJ JJ NN VBD DT NNS IN VBG NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
Witnesses say many protesters sat on the street when they were stopped from advancing .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP JJ NNS VBD IN DT NN WRB PRP VBD VBN IN VBG .
"Israel closed the Gaza Strip to all Israelis but settler residents last month , as it sought to minimize right-wing resistance to its mid-August withdrawal .",B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD DT NNP NNP TO DT NNS CC JJR NNS JJ NN , IN PRP VBD TO VB JJ NN TO PRP$ JJ NN ."
