The environmental group Greenpeace says China 's three largest power companies created more greenhouse gas emissions last year than the entire United Kingdom .,O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT JJ NN NNP VBZ NNP POS CD JJS NN NNS VBD JJR NN NN NNS JJ NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP .
"In a new report , Greenpeace says China 's reliance on coal is hurting Beijing 's fight against global warming .",O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN , NNP VBZ NNP POS NN IN NN VBZ VBG NNP POS NN IN JJ NN ."
Greenpeace recommends a new tax on coal for power companies .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN NN IN NN NNS .
"It also calls on China to double its renewable energy goal so that by 2020 , 30 percent of its power comes from solar and wind .",O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP RB VBZ IN NNP TO VB PRP$ JJ NN NN RB IN IN CD , CD NN IN PRP$ NN VBZ IN JJ CC NN ."
"With its burgeoning economy and growing demand for cars , China has rapidly become one of the world 's biggest polluters .",O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN PRP$ VBG NN CC VBG NN IN NNS , NNP VBZ RB VBN CD IN DT NN POS JJS NNS ."
Chinese officials have said they are working to cut greenhouse gas emissions .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN PRP VBP VBG TO VB NN NN NNS .
"The three Chinese companies named by Greenpeace are China Huaneng Group , China Datang Corporation and China Guodian Corporation .",O O B-gpe O O O B-org O B-org I-org I-org O B-geo I-geo I-geo O B-geo I-geo I-geo O,"DT CD JJ NNS VBN IN NNP VBP NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP ."
