Suspected Islamist militants in Pakistan have bombed the mausoleum of a 17th century poet revered in both Pakistan and Afghanistan .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O B-geo O B-geo O,VBN JJ NNS IN NNP VBP VBN DT NN IN DT JJ NN NN VBN IN DT NNP CC NNP .
"People regularly visit the marble shrine on the outskirts of the northwestern city of Peshawar to pay respects to Rehman Baba , a renowned ethnic Pashtun poet .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O,"NNS RB VBP DT NN NN IN DT NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NNP TO VB NNS TO NNP NNP , DT JJ JJ NN NN ."
The blast damaged the structure of the shrine but there were no reports of injuries .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD DT NN IN DT NN CC EX VBD DT NNS IN NNS .
"Days ahead of the attack , hardline Islamic militants had warned women against visiting the shrine .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS RB IN DT NN , JJ NNP NNS VBD VBN NNS IN VBG DT NN ."
Muslim extremists such as the Taliban oppose men and women mingling together unless they are married or close relatives .,B-per O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS JJ IN DT NNP VBP NNS CC NNS VBG RB IN PRP VBP JJ CC JJ NNS .
"In another attack Thursday , one person died and at least 15 others were injured when a grenade was hurled during evening prayers at a mosque in the northwestern town of Dera Ismail Khan .",O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,"IN DT NN NNP , CD NN VBD CC IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN WRB DT NN VBD VBN IN NN NNS IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP NNP ."
"Militant attacks have plagued Pakistan in recent years , especially in the Pashtun-dominated northwest .",O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O,"NN NNS VBP VBN NNP IN JJ NNS , RB IN DT JJ NN ."
