Health officials in Jakarta say local tests show a 39-year old Indonesian man has died from bird flu .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,NNP NNS IN NNP VBP JJ NNS VBP DT JJ JJ JJ NN VBZ VBN IN NN NN .
"Thursday , China 's state media reported a sixth person in the country has been diagnosed with bird flu .",B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP , NNP POS NN NNS VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NN VBZ VBN VBN IN NN NN ."
The Health Ministry identified the latest victim as a 35-year-old man from Suichuan County in the eastern province of Jiangxi .,B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNP NNP VBD DT JJS NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
The ministry gave no further details .,O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD DT JJ NNS .
