"Cuba 's state-run media report that Venezuelan President Hugo Chavez has met with his Cuban counterpart , Raul Castro , and former President Fidel Castro to reaffirm ties between their nations .",B-geo O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ NNS NN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN PRP$ JJ NN , NNP NNP , CC JJ NNP NNP NNP TO VB NNS IN PRP$ NNS ."
The Communist Party newspaper Granma says President Chavez arrived in Cuba from Nicaragua Thursday .,O O O O B-per O B-per I-per O O B-geo O B-geo B-tim O,DT NNP NNP NN NNP VBZ NNP NNP VBD IN NNP IN NNP NNP .
The report says discussions focused on ways to strengthen economic and social ties .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ NNS VBD IN NNS TO VB JJ CC JJ NNS .
It says Mr. Chavez and Raul Castro toured a community construction project in the town of Playa and met with members of the community .,O O B-per I-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ NNP NNP CC NNP NNP VBD DT NN NN NN IN DT NN IN NNP CC VBD IN NNS IN DT NN .
Cuba and Venezuela are close political allies .,B-geo O B-geo O O O O O,NNP CC NNP VBP JJ JJ NNS .
Venezuela is Cuba 's main trading partner .,B-geo O B-geo O O O O O,NNP VBZ NNP POS JJ NN NN .
"In December , the two nations signed cooperation agreements in the areas of health , education , farming and energy worth some $ 3 billion .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , DT CD NNS VBD NN NNS IN DT NNS IN NN , NN , NN CC NN NN DT $ CD CD ."
"Cuba and Venezuela are founding members of ALBA , a leftist bloc of Latin American nations formed in 2004 to counter U.S. influence in the region .",B-geo O B-geo O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O,"NNP CC NNP VBP JJ NNS IN NNP , DT JJ NN IN JJ JJ NNS VBN IN CD TO VB NNP NN IN DT NN ."
