The White House says President George Bush has suspended special trade benefits with Bolivia because of its failure to cooperate in drug-fighting efforts .,O B-org I-org O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN JJ NN NNS IN NNP IN IN PRP$ NN TO VB IN JJ NNS .
White House spokeswoman Dana Perino said Wednesday that Bolivia was suspended as a beneficiary country under the Andean Trade Preference Act ( ATPA ) and the Andean Trade Promotion and Drug Eradication Act ( ATPDEA ) .,B-org I-org O B-per I-per O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NN NNP NNP VBD NNP IN NNP VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP RRB CC DT NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP RRB .
The spokeswoman said the suspension takes effect December 15 .,O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT NN VBD DT NN VBZ NN NNP CD .
"But , Perino said the benefits can be restored if Bolivia were to improve its performance under the criteria of both programs and at the president 's discretion .",O O B-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"CC , NNP VBD DT NNS MD VB VBN IN NNP VBD TO VB PRP$ NN IN DT NNS IN DT NNS CC IN DT NN POS NN ."
The trade preferences lowered tariffs on Andean nations that help the United States fight drugs .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O,DT NN NNS VBD NNS IN JJ NNS WDT VBP DT NNP NNPS VB NNS .
"Three weeks ago , Bolivian President Evo Morales suspended the work of the U.S. Drug Enforcement Administration in his country , accusing agents of spying and supporting anti-government protests .",B-tim O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"CD NNS RB , JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP IN PRP$ NN , VBG NNS IN VBG CC VBG JJ NNS ."
He also gave them three months to leave the country .,O O O O B-tim O O O O O O,PRP RB VBD PRP CD NNS TO VB DT NN .
U.S. officials rejected the accusations .,B-geo O O O O O,NNP NNS VBD DT NNS .
