President Bush 's national security team is meeting in Texas to discuss a new strategy in Iraq .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP POS JJ NN NN VBZ VBG IN NNP TO VB DT JJ NN IN NNP .
"A White House spokesman , Scott Stanzel , called the gathering Thursday at the president 's ranch in Crawford , Texas , an opportunity for Mr. Bush to review options .",O B-org I-org O O B-per I-per O O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O B-per I-per O O O O,"DT NNP NNP NN , NNP NNP , VBD DT NN NNP IN DT NN POS NN IN NNP , NNP , DT NN IN NNP NNP TO VB NNS ."
"Vice President Dick Cheney , Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice , Defense Secretary Robert Gates , national security adviser Stephen Hadley and Chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff Marine General Peter Pace were all present at the meeting .",O B-per I-per I-per O O O B-org B-per I-per O B-org O B-per I-per O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org B-per I-per O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP , NNP IN NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP NNP NNP , JJ NN NN NNP NNP CC NNP IN DT NNP NNPS IN NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT JJ IN DT NN ."
The Bush administration has been debating strategies for reducing the violence in Iraq and whether to send more troops .,O B-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBZ VBN VBG NNS IN VBG DT NN IN NNP CC IN TO VB JJR NNS .
Mr. Bush is expected to announce a new plan next month .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB DT JJ NN JJ NN .
"On Wednesday , the Pentagon said it is sending about 3,500 troops to Kuwait to serve as a standby force for use in Iraq or elsewhere in the region .",O B-tim O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"IN NNP , DT NNP VBD PRP VBZ VBG IN CD NNS TO NNP TO VB IN DT JJ NN IN NN IN NNP CC RB IN DT NN ."
