"President Bush says Iran 's decision to freeze its uranium enrichment programs is a positive step , but "" not the final step . """,B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ NNP POS NN TO VB PRP$ NN NN NNS VBZ DT JJ NN , CC LQU RB DT JJ NN . LQU"
"Speaking at a joint press conference in Canada Tuesday , Mr. Bush said Iran must go further and terminate its nuclear activities .",O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"VBG IN DT JJ NN NN IN NNP NNP , NNP NNP VBD NNP MD VB RBR CC VB PRP$ JJ NNS ."
He also says the world must be able to verify if Tehran will keep its word .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,PRP RB VBZ DT NN MD VB JJ TO VB IN NNP MD VB PRP$ NN .
Iran agreed Monday to suspend its nuclear activities after reaching an agreement with European negotiators .,B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD NNP TO VB PRP$ JJ NNS IN VBG DT NN IN JJ NNS .
"But Iran says it has not abandoned its right to enrich uranium , and says its agreement will end in "" several months . """,O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,"CC NNP VBZ PRP VBZ RB VBN PRP$ NN TO VB NN , CC VBZ PRP$ NN MD VB IN RQU JJ NNS . LQU"
