"Pope Benedict XVI has criticized Western society for what he called its lack of hope , which he said leads many people to seek sexual gratification instead of practicing faith and family values .",B-per I-per I-per O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN JJ NN IN WP PRP VBD PRP$ NN IN NN , WDT PRP VBD VBZ JJ NNS TO VB JJ NN IN IN VBG NN CC NN NNS ."
The pontiff also deplored poverty and other evils burdening families in Rome and elsewhere .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,DT NN RB VBD NN CC JJ NNS VBG NNS IN NNP CC RB .
He made his comments in St. Peter 's Basilica during a homily at the final evening prayer offered there in 2007 .,O O O O O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,PRP VBD PRP$ NNS IN NNP NNP POS NNP IN DT RB IN DT JJ NN NN VBN EX IN CD .
Pope Benedict then expressed hope that efforts by the faithful to deal with such problems will be successful and bear fruit .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP RB VBD NN IN NNS IN DT NN TO VB IN JJ NNS MD VB JJ CC VBP NN .
The pope is to begin the New Year Tuesday with Mass in St. Peter 's Basilica .,O O O O O O B-org I-org B-tim O O O B-geo B-per O B-geo O,DT NN VBZ TO VB DT NNP NNP NNP IN NNP IN NNP NNP POS NNP .
The Roman Catholic Church celebrates January 1 as its World Day of Peace .,O B-per I-per I-per O B-tim I-tim O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNP CD IN PRP$ NNP NNP IN NNP .
