Venezuelan President Hugo Chavez is embarking on a two-week tour that will take him to seven countries .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBG IN DT JJ NN WDT MD VB PRP TO CD NNS .
"Mr. Chavez is expected to first visit Brazil before continuing on to Argentina for a summit Friday of the South American trade bloc , Mercosur .",B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O O B-org I-org O O O B-geo O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO JJ NN NNP IN VBG IN TO NNP IN DT NN NNP IN DT NNP NNP NN NN , NNP ."
"From South America , the Venezuelan president travels to Belarus before visiting Russia .",O B-geo I-geo O O B-gpe O O O B-geo O O B-geo O,"IN NNP NNP , DT JJ NN VBZ TO NNP IN VBG NNP ."
"In Moscow , he is expected to sign a military agreement allowing Caracas to purchase Russian Sukhoi Su-30 fighter planes and small arms .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , PRP VBZ VBN TO VB DT JJ NN VBG NNP TO VB JJ NNP NNP NN NNS CC JJ NNS ."
Mr. Chavez is also seeking rights to build a manufacturing plant for Kalashnikov assault rifles in Venezuela .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP VBZ RB VBG NNS TO VB DT NN NN IN NNP NN NNS IN NNP .
"During the tour , Mr. Chavez will also visit Qatar , Iran and Vietnam .",O O O O B-per I-per O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O,"IN DT NN , NNP NNP MD RB VB NNP , NNP CC NNP ."
"Meanwhile , Venezuelan officials say Foreign Minister Ali Rodriguez has been hospitalized with heart problems , and will not accompany Mr. Chavez on the trip .",O O B-gpe O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O,"RB , JJ NNS VBP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN VBN IN NN NNS , CC MD RB VB NNP NNP IN DT NN ."
