Pilgrims from around the world are flocking into Saint Peter 's Square ahead of Pope Benedict 's first Christmas Eve midnight Mass since he assumed the papacy in April .,O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-geo B-per O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-tim O,NNS IN IN DT NN VBP VBG IN NNP NNP POS NNP RB IN NNP NNP POS JJ NNP NNP NN NNP IN PRP VBD DT NN IN NNP .
"Thousands will crowd into Saint Peter 's Basilica for the service marking the opening of celebrations of the feast of the birth of Jesus Christ , whom Christians call the Prince of Peace .",O O O O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,"NNS MD NN IN NNP NNP POS NNP IN DT NN VBG DT NN IN NNS IN DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP , WP NNPS VBP DT NNP IN NNP ."
Crowds of others will watch the Mass on huge television screens in the square .,O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNS MD VB DT NNP IN JJ NN NNS IN DT NN .
"Ahead of the Mass , the pope appeared at his study window and joined the pilgrims in singing Christmas carols during a prayer service at a life-sized nativity scene in the square .",O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NN IN DT NNP , DT NN VBD IN PRP$ NN NN CC VBD DT NNS IN VBG NNP NNS IN DT NN NN IN DT JJ NN NN IN DT NN ."
"At noon Sunday , Christmas Day , Pope Benedict will deliver his first "" Urbi et Orbi "" ( To the City and the World ) message as well as his blessings and greetings to the faithful of the world from a balcony overlooking Saint Peter 's Square .",O B-tim I-tim O B-tim I-tim O B-geo B-per O O O O O B-art I-art I-art B-per O O O B-geo O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O,"IN NN NNP , NNP NNP , NNP NNP MD VB PRP$ JJ LQU NNP NNP NNP RQU LRB TO DT NN CC DT NNP RRB NN RB RB IN PRP$ NNS CC NNS TO DT NN IN DT NN IN DT NN VBG NNP NNP POS NNP ."
