"Nigeria 's government has taken steps to avoid a confrontation with football 's world governing body ( FIFA ) , by cancelling its recent appointment to the country 's Football Association .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"NNP POS NN VBZ VBN NNS TO VB DT NN IN NN POS NN NN NN LRB NNP RRB , IN VBG PRP$ JJ NN TO DT NN POS NNP NNP ."
"At a news conference Thursday , Nigerian sports minister Musa Mohammed said the government withdrew Segun Odegbami 's appointment as secretary-general of the Nigeria Football Association .",O O O O B-tim O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,"IN DT NN NN NNP , JJ NNS NN NNP NNP VBD DT NN VBD NNP NNP POS NN IN NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP ."
The appointment of Salihu Abubakar as head of the Nigerian Premier League was also cancelled .,O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,DT NN IN NNP NNP IN NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP VBD RB VBN .
"In addition , the government also accepted the resignation of former NFA secretary-general Taiwo Ogunjobi .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-per I-per O,"IN NN , DT NN RB VBD DT NN IN JJ NNP NN NNP NNP ."
No successor has been named .,O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBN VBN .
"The NFA board , not the government , is now expected to name his replacement .",O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NN , RB DT NN , VBZ RB VBN TO VB PRP$ NN ."
"The announcements by the government are expected to prevent sanctions from FIFA , which forbids government interference in member football associations .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS IN DT NN VBP VBN TO VB NNS IN NNP , WDT VBZ NN NN IN NN NN NNS ."
