Georgia is observing two days of mourning following Thursday 's death of Prime Minister Zurab Zhvania .,B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-per O B-per I-per O,NNP VBZ VBG CD NNS IN VBG VBG NNP POS NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP .
"Authorities found the body of the 41-year-old Mr. Zhvania along with that of a friend and fellow politician , Zurab Usupov in the friend 's Tbilisi apartment .",O O O O O O B-org B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O,"NNS VBD DT NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP IN IN DT IN DT NN CC JJ NN , NNP NNP IN DT NN POS NNP NN ."
Officials Friday confirmed that the two men had died of carbon monixide poisoning blamed on a faulty heater .,O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS NNP VBD IN DT CD NNS VBD VBN IN NN NN VBG VBN IN DT JJ NN .
Mr. Zhvzania 's funeral is scheduled for Sunday at Tbilisi 's cathedral .,B-per B-org O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O,NNP NNP POS NN VBZ VBN IN NNP IN NNP POS NN .
"The late prime minister was prominent in the "" Rose Revolution "" that toppled President Eduard Shevardnadze in 2003 .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O,DT JJ JJ NN VBD JJ IN DT LQU NNP NNP RQU WDT VBD NNP NNP NNP IN CD .
"Meanwhile , Georgian officials say a member of the country 's Presidential Commission on Clemency apparently has committed suicide .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-org O O O O O,"RB , JJ NNS VBP DT NN IN DT NN POS NNP NNP IN NNP RB VBZ VBN NN ."
Police say they found Giorgi Khelasvili at his home dead of a gunshot wound .,O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP PRP VBD NNP NNP IN PRP$ NN NN IN DT NN NN .
News agency reports say the victim suffered from depression .,O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NN NNS VBP DT NN VBD IN NN .
Authorities are making no connection between the suicide and the prime minister 's death .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP VBG DT NN IN DT NN CC DT JJ NN POS NN .
