A top United Nations envoy says Syria has promised to remove all its troops and agents from Lebanon by the end of the month .,O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim I-tim O O O,DT JJ NNP NNPS NN VBZ NNP VBZ VBN TO VB DT PRP$ NNS CC NNS IN NNP IN DT NN IN DT NN .
"U.N. special envoy Terje Roed-Larsen announced Syria 's commitment , after meeting Sunday with Syrian President Bashar al-Assad .",B-geo O O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O,"NNP JJ NN NNP NNP VBD NNP POS NN , IN VBG NNP IN JJ NNP NNP NNP ."
"He also said a U.N. team will verify the pullout , if Beirut accepts the offer .",O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"PRP RB VBD DT NNP NN MD VB DT NN , IN NNP VBZ DT NN ."
Opposition leaders have accused Beirut and its Syrian sponsors of complicity in the bombing that killed the billionaire tycoon - a charge both governments deny .,O O O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NN NNS VBP VBN NNP CC PRP$ JJ NNS IN NN IN DT NN WDT VBD DT NN NN IN DT NN DT NNS VBP .
"The Syrian pullout began last month , after days of massive anti-Syrian protests in Beirut .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT JJ NN VBD JJ NN , IN NNS IN JJ JJ NNS IN NNP ."
All Syrian forces have left western Lebanon .,O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O,DT JJ NNS VBP VBN JJ NNP .
"However , some remain deployed on the Lebanese border , awaiting further orders .",O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,"RB , DT VBP VBN IN DT JJ NN , VBG JJ NNS ."
