"Carlos Moya has defeated American Andy Roddick 6-2 , 7-6 , 7-6 in Seville , to clinch the 2004 Davis Cup Tennis Championship for Spain .",B-per I-per O O B-gpe B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim B-eve I-eve I-eve I-eve O B-geo O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBN JJ NNP NNP CD , CD , CD IN NNP , TO VB DT CD NNP NNP NNP NNP IN NNP ."
"The hosts came into Sunday 's final day of play with a 2-1 lead , and the Americans needed to win both reverse singles matches to capture the title .",O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS VBD IN NNP POS JJ NN IN NN IN DT JJ NN , CC DT NNS VBD TO VB DT JJ NN NNS TO VB DT NN ."
Roddick battled hard and had chances in the second and third sets .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD JJ CC VBD NNS IN DT JJ CC JJ NNS .
"But Moya , the former world number-one and French Open champion , took advantage of his clay court expertise to secure Spain 's second-ever Davis Cup title , 3-1 .",O B-per O O O O O O B-eve I-eve O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-eve I-eve O O O O,"CC NNP , DT JJ NN NN CC JJ NNP NN , VBD NN IN PRP$ NN NN NN TO VB NNP POS JJ NNP NNP NN , CD ."
"American Mardy Fish challenges Rafael Nadal in a meaningless "" dead-rubber "" reverse singles match to complete the best-of-five series .",B-gpe B-per I-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP VBZ NNP NNP IN DT JJ LQU NN RQU JJ NN NN TO VB DT JJ NN .
