The African Union says it is running out of money to fund its peace keeping mission in Sudan 's war-ravaged western Darfur region .,B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ VBG IN IN NN TO VB PRP$ NN VBG NN IN NNP POS JJ JJ NNP NN .
"AU Commissioner for Peace and Security Said Djinnit told reporters Friday in Addis Ababa that the mission has only enough money to operate to April , at the latest .",B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-tim O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O,"NNP NNP IN NNP CC NNP NNP NNP VBD NNS NNP IN NNP NNP IN DT NN VBZ RB JJ NN TO VB TO NNP , IN DT JJS ."
"Mr. Djinnit also announced a European Union donation of $ 70 million to the mission , but said it still falls short of what is needed .",B-per B-geo O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP RB VBD DT NNP NNP NN IN $ CD CD TO DT NN , CC VBD PRP RB VBZ JJ IN WP VBZ VBN ."
The United Nations has called Darfur the world 's worst humanitarian crisis .,B-org I-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNP DT NN POS JJS JJ NN .
