Reports from the northern Bosnian city of Banja Luka say a Bosnian Serb suspect who surrendered to authorities there Tuesday is on his way to The Hague for trial before the United Nations war crimes tribunal .,O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo I-geo O O B-gpe I-gpe O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O,NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP NNP VBP DT JJ JJ NN WP VBD TO NNS RB NNP VBZ IN PRP$ NN TO DT NNP IN NN IN DT NNP NNPS NN NNS JJ .
"The suspect , Sredoje Lukic , is accused of some of the most serious war crimes committed in the former Yugoslavia .",O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NN , NNP NNP , VBZ VBN IN DT IN DT RBS JJ NN NNS VBN IN DT JJ NNP ."
"He is said to have been hiding in Russia until his surrender , after what officials called joint action by Serbian and Bosnian Serb authorities .",O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-gpe I-gpe O O,"PRP VBZ VBN TO VB VBN VBG IN NNP IN PRP$ NN , IN WP NNS VBD JJ NN IN JJ CC JJ JJ NNS ."
"The U.N. tribunal indicted Mr. Lukic in 2000 for inhumane acts against non-Serbs , religious persecution and crimes against humanity .",O B-org O O B-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NN VBD NNP NNP IN CD IN JJ NNS IN JJ , JJ NN CC NNS IN NN ."
"Mr. Lukic and his cousin , Milan Lukic , were members of a paramilitary group that murdered , tortured and terrorized Muslims during the conflict of the 1990s in Bosnia-Herzegovina .",B-per I-per O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O,"NNP NNP CC PRP$ NN , NNP NNP , VBD NNS IN DT JJ NN IN VBN , VBN CC VBN NNS IN DT NN IN DT NNS IN NNP ."
Milan Lukic was arrested in Argentina last month and is awaiting extradition .,B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD VBN IN NNP JJ NN CC VBZ VBG NN .
