"The U.S. military says American warplanes have launched air strikes on sites in Iraq near the Syrian border , killing some 40 insurgents .",O B-geo O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NN VBZ NNP NNS VBP VBN NN NNS IN NNS IN NNP IN DT JJ NN , VBG DT CD NNS ."
"In a statement Saturday , U.S. military officials said seven missiles were fired on heavily-armed militants who were stopping and searching cars near the western town of Karabilah .",O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"IN DT NN NNP , NNP JJ NNS VBD CD NNS VBD VBN IN JJ NNS WP VBD VBG CC VBG NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
"Meantime , Iraqi officials said a former member of an elite commando unit , the Wolf Brigade blew himself up inside the unit 's headquarters , killing three people .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , JJ NNS VBD DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN NN , DT NNP NNP VBD PRP RP IN DT NN POS NN , VBG CD NNS ."
"Bayan Jabor Insurgents opened fire on a minibus carrying construction workers in Baghdad , killing at least 11 Iraqis and wounding three others .",B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP VBD NN IN DT NN VBG NN NNS IN NNP , VBG IN JJS CD NNS CC VBG CD NNS ."
"Also today , Interior Minister Bayan Jabor praised a sweeping crackdown on insurgents in the Iraqi capital .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"RB NN , NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN NNS IN DT JJ NN ."
"He says Operation Lightning has led to the arrests of 1,300 terrorists and has sharply cut the number of car bombings in the city .",O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO DT NNS IN CD NNS CC VBZ RB VBN DT NN IN NN NNS IN DT NN .
