An unmanned Russian spacecraft has docked successfully with the International Space Station delivering cargo and supplies for its crew .,O O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O,DT JJ JJ NN VBZ VBN RB IN DT NNP NNP NNP VBG NN CC NNS IN PRP$ NN .
A spokesman for Russian Mission Control Valery Lyndin says the Progress M-67 craft reached the docking module Wednesday .,O O O B-gpe B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O B-tim O,DT NN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT NNP NNP NN VBD DT NN NN NNP .
He said the space station crew guided the freighter to the station 's docking port using manual controls .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT NN NN NN VBD DT NN TO DT NN POS NN NN VBG JJ NNS .
"The craft lifted off Friday from the Baikonur space center in Kazakhstan , carrying two-and-a-half tons of supplies including food , water , fuel and various equipment to the station .",O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD RP NNP IN DT NNP NN NN IN NNP , VBG JJ NNS IN NNS VBG NN , NN , NN CC JJ NN TO DT NN ."
The space station 's permanent crew doubled to six in May .,O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NN NN POS JJ NN VBD TO CD IN NNP .
"It now includes two Russians , two Americans , a Canadian and a Belgian .",O O O O B-gpe O O B-gpe O O B-org O O B-gpe O,"PRP RB VBZ CD NNS , CD NNS , DT NN CC DT NN ."
