"The U.S. Space Agency NASA is planning to launch its space shuttle Atlantis in Cape Canaveral , Florida on Wednesday .",O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O B-tim O,"DT NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBG TO VB PRP$ NN NN NNP IN NNP NNP , NNP IN NNP ."
"A NASA spokesman said the weather forecast is very favorable for the launch , set for 12:29 pm local time - a time of day before Florida 's frequent afternoon thunderstorms .",O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O,"DT NNP NN VBD DT NN NN VBZ RB JJ IN DT NN , VBN IN CD NN JJ NN IN DT NN IN NN IN NNP POS JJ NN NNS ."
Atlantis was originally scheduled to launch August 27 on a mission to resume construction of the International Space Station .,O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O,NNP VBD RB VBN TO VB NNP CD IN DT NN TO VB NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP .
But that launch was delayed after a lightning strike at the launch pad .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NN NN IN DT NN NN .
