The National Football League 's Green Bay Packers fell to a record of no wins and four losses for the season Monday night after falling 32-29 to the host Carolina Panthers .,O B-org I-org I-org O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT NNP NNP NNP POS NNP NNP NNPS VBD TO DT NN IN DT NNS CC CD NNS IN DT NN NNP NN IN VBG CD TO DT NN NNP NNPS .
"Carolina capitalized on two early turnovers by Green Bay to build an early lead , then held on for the victory .",B-geo O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD IN CD JJ NNS IN NNP NNP TO VB DT JJ NN , RB VBN IN IN DT NN ."
The win gives the Panthers an even record of two wins and two losses .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ DT NNPS DT RB NN IN CD NNS CC CD NNS .
"Green Bay rallied from a 19-point deficit , with star quarterback Bret Favre leading the charge , throwing two touchdown passes and two two-point conversions in the fourth quarter .",B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"NNP NNP VBD IN DT JJ NN , IN NN NN NNP NNP VBG DT NN , VBG CD JJ NNS CC CD JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN ."
The future Hall of Fame player moved the Packers into possible scoring The Packers are off to their worst season start in 17 years .,O O B-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,DT JJ NNP IN NNP NN VBD DT NNS IN JJ VBG DT NNS VBP RB TO PRP$ JJS NN NN IN CD NNS .
"The third year expansion team , the Houston Texans , is the only other NFL team without a win so far this season .",O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O B-tim O,"DT JJ NN NN NN , DT NNP NNPS , VBZ DT RB JJ NNP NN IN DT NN RB RB DT NN ."
