"Occupying the northeast corner of the African continent , Egypt is bisected by the highly fertile Nile valley , where most economic activity takes place .",O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"VBG DT NN NN IN DT JJ NN , NNP VBZ VBN IN DT RB JJ NNP NN , WRB RBS JJ NN VBZ NN ."
Egypt 's economy was highly centralized during the rule of former President Gamal Abdel NASSER but opened up considerably under former Presidents Anwar EL-SADAT and Mohamed Hosni MUBARAK .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-per I-per O B-per I-per I-per O,NNP POS NN VBD RB VBN IN DT NN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP CC VBD RP RB IN JJ NNS NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP .
Cairo from 2004 to 2008 aggressively pursued economic reforms to attract foreign investment and facilitate GDP growth .,B-geo B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-art O O,NNP IN CD TO CD RB JJ JJ NNS TO VB JJ NN CC VB NN NN .
The global financial crisis slowed the reform efforts .,O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ JJ NN VBD DT NN NNS .
"The budget deficit climbed to over 8 % of GDP and Egypt 's GDP growth slowed to 4.6 % in 2009 , predominately due to reduced growth in export-oriented sectors , including manufacturing and tourism , and Suez Canal revenues .",O O O O O O O O O B-art O B-org O B-art O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O,"DT NN NN VBD TO IN CD NN IN NN CC NNP POS NN NN VBD TO CD NN IN CD , RB JJ TO JJ NN IN JJ NNS , VBG NN CC NN , CC NNP NNP NNS ."
"In 2010 , the government spent more on infrastructure and public projects , and exports drove GDP growth to more than 5 % , but GDP growth in 2011 is unlikely to bounce back to pre-global financial recession levels , when it stood at 7 % .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN CD , DT NN VBD RBR IN NN CC JJ NNS , CC NNS VBD NN NN TO JJR IN CD NN , CC NN NN IN CD VBZ JJ TO VB RB TO JJ JJ NN NNS , WRB PRP VBD IN CD NN ."
"Despite the relatively high levels of economic growth over the past few years , living conditions for the average Egyptian remain poor .",O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O,"IN DT RB JJ NNS IN JJ NN IN DT JJ JJ NNS , VBG NNS IN DT JJ NN VBP JJ ."
