A seven-nation regional summit scheduled for next month in Dhaka has been postponed following the destruction caused by Sunday 's tsunami in South Asia .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT JJ JJ NN VBN IN JJ NN IN NNP VBZ VBN VBN VBG DT NN VBN IN NNP POS NN IN NNP NNP .
"Bangladeshi Prime Minister Khaleda Zia has issued a statement , saying the decision was made after a request from Sri Lanka .",B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN , VBG DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP ."
The summit of the South Asian Association for Regional Cooperation was to be held from January 9-11 .,O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP IN NNP NNP VBD TO VB VBN IN NNP CD .
"In addition to Sri Lanka and Bangladesh , the forum also includes India , the Maldives , Bhutan , Nepal and Pakistan .",O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O B-geo O B-gpe B-org I-org O,"IN NN TO NNP NNP CC NNP , DT NN RB VBZ NNP , DT NNP , NNP , NNP CC NNP ."
"The statement says a new date for the summit will be set in consultation with the member countries , but no specific time frame has been fixed .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ DT JJ NN IN DT NN MD VB VBN IN NN IN DT NN NNS , CC DT JJ NN NN VBZ VBN VBN ."
"Among this group of countries , India , Sri Lanka and the Maldives were the hardest hit by the tsunami disaster .",O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN IN NNS , NNP , NNP NNP CC DT NNP VBD DT RBS VBN IN DT NN NN ."
Bangladesh escaped the worst of the disaster .,B-geo O O O O O O O,NNP VBD DT JJS IN DT NN .
