The United Nations World Food Program says the first major airlift of emergency food aid for drought-stricken Niger is set to begin on Thursday .,O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-tim O,DT NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ JJ NN IN NN NN NN IN JJ NNP VBZ VBN TO VB IN NNP .
"The agency says an aircraft will take off from Brindisi in southern Italy Thursday morning , to deliver 44 metric tons of high-energy biscuits to Niger 's capital , Niamey .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-org O,"DT NN VBZ DT NN MD VB RP IN NNP IN JJ NNP NNP NN , TO VB CD JJ NNS IN JJ NNS TO NNP POS NN , NNP ."
Country director Giancarlo Cirri says the food can not arrive soon enough for the estimated 2.5 million people facing food shortages as a result of drought and locusts .,O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NN NN NNP NNP VBZ DT NN MD RB VB RB RB IN DT VBN CD CD NNS VBG NN NNS IN DT NN IN NN CC NNS .
He calls the situation some of the worst hunger he has ever witnessed .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ DT NN DT IN DT JJS NN PRP VBZ RB VBN .
"Meanwhile , the British charity Oxfam is calling on the United Nations to create a $ 1 billion emergency relief fund to prevent future food crises .",O O O B-gpe B-org I-org O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , DT JJ NN NNP VBZ VBG IN DT NNP NNPS TO VB DT $ CD CD NN NN NN TO VB JJ NN NNS ."
Aid agencies began warning of severe food shortages in Niger last year - but donors failed to respond until television images of the hungry were broadcast .,O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBD VBG IN JJ NN NNS IN NNP JJ NN : CC NNS VBD TO VB IN NN NNS IN DT NN VBD VBN .
