Russia 's state-run natural gas monopoly Gazprom has reduced gas supplies to Europe in efforts to conserve domestic supplies in the face of bitter cold temperatures at home .,B-geo O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS VBN JJ NN NN NNP VBZ VBN NN NNS TO NNP IN NNS TO VB JJ NNS IN DT NN IN JJ JJ NNS IN NN .
Gazprom officials say the cuts are a temporary measure in response to increased consumption after the cold spell struck western Russia .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNS VBP DT NNS VBP DT JJ NN IN NN TO JJ NN IN DT JJ NN VBD JJ NNP .
"Hungary , Ukraine and Italy have confirmed the reductions .",B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O,"NNP , NNP CC NNP VBP VBN DT NNS ."
Ukrainian Energy Minister Ivan Plachkov says his country agreed with Russia to cut gas transit to Europe by 40 million cubic meters a day .,B-gpe O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP$ NN VBD IN NNP TO VB NN NN TO NNP IN CD CD JJ NNS DT NN .
Much of Russia 's European gas exports reach their destinations via Ukrainian pipelines .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,NN IN NNP POS JJ NN NNS VBP PRP$ NNS IN JJ NNS .
"In Moscow , at least one person froze to death overnight , as temperatures plunged to minus-30 degrees below zero ( Centigrade ) .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , IN JJS CD NN VBD IN NN RB , IN NNS VBD TO CD NNS IN CD LRB NNP RRB ."
Russian news agencies say 22 other people have died from the cold in surrounding regions .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN NNS VBP CD JJ NNS VBP VBN IN DT NN IN VBG NNS .
