"Iraqi Kurdish leaders are meeting in Baghdad with majority Shi'ites , as both sides press for agreement on a new coalition government before parliament meets for the first time Wednesday .",B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"JJ NNP NNS VBP VBG IN NNP IN NN NNS , IN DT NNS VBP IN NN IN DT JJ NN NN IN NN VBZ IN DT JJ NN NNP ."
Top Kurdish envoy Qubad Talabani says Kurdish negotiators want the majority Shi'ites to detail their religious and political agenda for northern Iraq before Kurds agree to form a ruling coalition .,O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NN NNP NNP VBZ NNP NNS VBP DT NN VBZ TO VB PRP$ JJ CC JJ NN IN JJ NNP IN NNPS VBP TO VB DT NN NN .
"Speaking Monday on U.S. television , Mr. Talabani said Kurds want guarantees of a secular government in post-war Iraq .",O B-tim O B-geo O O B-per B-org O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim B-geo O,"VBG NNP IN NNP NN , NNP NNP VBD NNPS VBP NNS IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NNP ."
He also said negotiators seek guarantees that hundreds of thousands of Kurds driven from the oil city of Kirkuk under Saddam Hussein be allowed to return .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O O,PRP RB VBD NNS VBP NNS IN NNS IN NNS IN NNS VBN IN DT NN NN IN NNP IN NNP NNP VB VBN TO VB .
"Earlier Monday , the envoy 's father , Kurdish leader Jalal Talabani , said Kurds also demand that thousands of Kurdish peshmerga fighters continue to provide security in Kurdish-dominated northern provinces .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RBR NNP , DT NN POS NN , NNP NN NNP NNP , VBD NNS RB VBP IN NNS IN NNP NN NNS VBP TO VB NN IN JJ JJ NNS ."
Jalal Talabani is expected to become Iraq 's next president .,B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB NNP POS JJ NN .
