"Former world number one tennis star Martina Hingis has made a successful return to professional tennis , winning her first-round match at the Australian hardcourt championship on the Gold Coast .",O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-org I-org O,"JJ NN NN CD NN NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN TO JJ NN , VBG PRP$ JJ NN IN DT JJ NN NN IN DT NNP NNP ."
"The 25-year old Swiss player beat Maria Vento-Kabchi of Venezuela in straight sets , 6-2 , 6-1 .",O O O B-gpe O O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ JJ JJ NN VBD NNP NNP IN NNP IN JJ NNS , CD , CD ."
It was Hingis ' first competitive match in more than three years .,O O B-per I-per O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O,PRP VBD NNP POS JJ JJ NN IN JJR IN CD NNS .
"She retired in October 2002 , after suffering chronic foot and ankle injuries .",O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD IN NNP CD , IN VBG JJ NN CC NN NNS ."
"The five-time Grand Slam singles champion made a tense start against Vento-Kabchi , ranked 62nd in the world .",O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O O O,"DT JJ NNP NNP VBZ NN VBD DT JJ NN IN NNP , VBD CD IN DT NN ."
"Hingis dropped her serve in the opening game , but quickly broke back , and dominated the rest of the match .",B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD PRP VB IN DT NN NN , CC RB VBD RB , CC VBD DT NN IN DT NN ."
She will face Klara Koukalova of the Czech Republic in the second round .,O O O B-per I-per O O B-gpe B-geo O O O O O,PRP MD VB NNP NNP IN DT JJ NNP IN DT JJ NN .
"Hingis is using the event as a warm-up for this month 's Australian Open , which she has won three times .",B-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-org O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBG DT NN IN DT NN IN DT NN POS JJ NNP , WDT PRP VBZ VBN CD NNS ."
