An independent U.S. government report says the Army has enough money available to fund its military operations in Iraq through July .,O O B-geo O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim I-tim O,DT JJ NNP NN NN VBZ DT NNP VBZ JJ NN JJ TO VB PRP$ JJ NNS IN NNP IN NNP .
The Congressional Research Service - the nonpartisan research agency of U.S. Congress - issued a report this week saying the Army could pay for both its regular and combat operations through May .,O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT NNP NNP NNP IN DT JJ NN NN IN NNP NNP : VBD DT NN DT NN VBG DT NNP MD VB IN DT PRP$ JJ CC NN NNS IN NNP .
"After that , it can shift money from different accounts dedicated to non-combat functions .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT , PRP MD VB NN IN JJ NNS VBN TO JJ NNS ."
The report is in contrast to assertions by President Bush and military leaders that the Army would start running out of money in April if lawmakers did not approve an emergency spending bill .,O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ IN NN TO NNS IN NNP NNP CC JJ NNS IN DT NNP MD VB VBG IN IN NN IN NNP IN NNS VBD RB VB DT NN NN NN .
Congress has approved the money in proposed bills .,B-org O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN JJ NNS .
But the proposals backed mainly by Democratic Party members in both the Senate and House of Representatives impose deadlines to withdraw the troops from Iraq .,O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O B-geo O,CC DT NNS VBN RB IN NNP NNP NNS IN DT DT NNP CC NNP IN NNPS VB NNS TO VB DT NNS IN NNP .
Mr. Bush has threatened to veto any bill that includes such timetables .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB DT NN WDT VBZ JJ NNS .
