Iran 's outgoing President Mohammed Khatami says his government will resume some key nuclear work regardless of what European diplomats propose next month to defuse a dispute over Tehran 's nuclear program .,B-geo O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,NNP POS JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP$ NN MD VB DT JJ JJ NN RB IN WP JJ NNS VB JJ NN TO VB DT NN IN NNP POS JJ NN .
"Mr. Khatami told reporters Wednesday , that Tehran will resume low-level uranium enrichment for use in power stations .",B-per I-per O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD NNS NNP , DT NNP MD VB JJ NN NN IN NN IN NN NNS ."
Washington has accused Iran of trying to boost its enrichment process to create weapons grade material for use in warheads .,B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN NNP IN VBG TO VB PRP$ NN NN TO VB NNS NN NN IN NN IN NNS .
Tehran denies the charges .,B-geo O O O O,NNP VBZ DT NNS .
"Mr. Khatami gave no date for the restarting of enrichment activities , which were suspended late last year under pressure from the European Union and the United Nations .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-org I-org O,"NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN DT NN IN NN NNS , WDT VBD VBN RB JJ NN IN NN IN DT NNP NNP CC DT NNP NNPS ."
"Britain , France and Germany want Tehran to freeze its enrichment program permanently in exchange for economic incentives .",B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP , NNP CC NNP VBP NNP TO VB PRP$ NN NN RB IN NN IN JJ NNS ."
The two sides are to meet again in early August .,O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT CD NNS VBP TO VB RB IN JJ NNP .
