Colombia is launching an operation aimed at eradicating illegal drug production from its largest nature park .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBG DT NN VBN IN VBG JJ NN NN IN PRP$ JJS NN NN .
"Colombian police announced Wednesday they are starting to uproot coca plants in the Macarena National Park in Meta department , where rebel groups are known to produce cocaine to help fund their fight against the government .",B-gpe O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN VBD NNP PRP VBP VBG TO VB NN NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP IN NNP NN , WRB NN NNS VBP VBN TO VB NN TO VB VB PRP$ NN IN DT NN ."
"Some 900 workers are clearing some 4,600 hectares of coca plants by hand over the next several months , under heavy security to guard against rebel attacks .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT CD NNS VBP VBG DT CD NNS IN NN NNS IN NN IN DT JJ JJ NNS , IN JJ NN TO VB IN JJ NNS ."
The Associated Press reports the workers will also destroy clandestine roads and bridges used by the rebels to transport their drugs through the area .,B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ DT NNS MD RB VB JJ NNS CC NNS VBN IN DT NNS TO VB PRP$ NNS IN DT NN .
"The United States helps fund a crop-dusting program in Colombia to destroy coca plants on private land , but stays away from park areas to preserve the vegetation .",B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNPS VBZ VB DT JJ NN IN NNP TO VB NN NNS IN JJ NN , CC VBZ RB IN NN NNS TO VB DT NN ."
