"A Muslim chaplain has delivered the opening prayer for the U.S. House of Representatives , an honor few Muslim clergy get .",O B-org O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O B-org O O O,"DT NNP NN VBZ VBN DT NN NN IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP , DT NN JJ NNP NNS VBP ."
"Abdullah Antepli of Duke University in North Carolina served as a guest chaplain Wednesday , at the invitation of Representative David Price , a North Carolina Democrat .",B-per I-per B-org I-org I-org O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-per I-per O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O,"NNP NNP IN NNP NNP IN NNP NNP VBD IN DT NN NN NNP , IN DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP , DT NNP NNP NNP ."
"He prayed for God to guide members of Congress and enable them to serve citizens of the country and all humanity , regardless of gender , ethnicity or religion .",O O O B-geo O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD IN NNP TO VB NNS IN NNP CC VB PRP TO VB NNS IN DT NN CC DT NN , RB IN NN , NN CC NN ."
"Duke University says Antepli , who was born in Turkey , is only one of a few full-time Muslim chaplains at U.S. colleges and universities .",B-org I-org O B-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ NNP , WP VBD VBN IN NNP , VBZ RB CD IN DT JJ JJ NN NNS IN NNP NNS CC NNS ."
"It says his work focuses on religious leadership for Duke 's Muslim community , pastoral care and counseling for people of any faith or belief , and intra- and interfaith work .",O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBZ PRP$ NN VBZ IN JJ NN IN NNP POS NNP NN , JJ NN CC NN IN NNS IN DT NN CC NN , CC JJ CC JJ NN ."
