"The U.S. military Friday released the details of five incidents in which guards mishandled the Koran at the detention facility at Guantanamo Bay , Cuba .",O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O,"DT NNP JJ NNP VBD DT NNS IN CD NNS IN WDT NNS VBD DT NN IN DT NN NN IN NNP NNP , NNP ."
"An investigation by the base commander , Brigadier General Jay Hood , said the incidents included a prison guard splashing a Koran inadvertently with urine , an interrogator stepping on the holy book , and an obscenity written on the inside cover of a Koran .",O O O O O O O B-org I-org B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN DT NN NN , NNP NNP NNP NNP , VBD DT NNS VBD DT NN NN VBG DT NNP RB IN NN , DT NN VBG IN DT JJ NN , CC DT NN VBN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP ."
"The U.S. military noted that more than 1,600 Korans have been given to detainees , and guards are told to avoid touching the holy books if possible .",O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NN VBD IN JJR IN CD NNS VBP VBN VBN TO NNS , CC NNS VBP VBN TO VB VBG DT JJ NNS IN JJ ."
"General Hood says the investigation found that mishandling the Koran was rare , and never condoned .",B-org B-per O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ DT NN VBD IN VBG DT NNP VBD JJ , CC RB VBN ."
"The military said again Friday that there is no evidence that U.S. guards or interrogators ever flushed a Koran down the toilet , as Newsweek reported in a story that the magazine has since retracted .",O O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD RB NNP IN EX VBZ DT NN IN NNP NNS CC NNS RB VBD DT NNP IN DT NN , IN NNP VBD IN DT NN IN DT NN VBZ IN VBN ."
The report sparked ant-American protests in several Islamic countries .,O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD JJ NNS IN JJ JJ NNS .
