Brazil has rejected a U.S. State Department human rights report accusing its police and prison guards of serious abuses .,B-geo O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN DT NNP NNP NNP JJ NNS NN VBG PRP$ NN CC NN NNS IN JJ NNS .
"Brazil 's Foreign Ministry said in a statement Wednesday that Brazil does not recognize reports by individual countries , because they tend to use their own domestic criteria .",B-geo B-org I-org I-org O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NNP NNP VBD IN DT NN NNP IN NNP VBZ RB VB NNS IN JJ NNS , IN PRP VBP TO VB PRP$ JJ JJ NNS ."
It said Brazil is open to dialogue with all international and regional forums on human rights .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD NNP VBZ JJ TO NN IN DT JJ CC JJ NNS IN JJ NNS .
The 2006 U.S. State Department report released Tuesday said Brazil 's government generally respects its citizens ' human rights .,O B-tim B-org I-org I-org O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,DT CD NNP NNP NNP NN VBN NNP VBD NNP POS NN RB VBZ PRP$ NNS POS JJ NNS .
"But the report said serious abuses , such as beatings and torture , were found among Brazil 's police and security forces .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"CC DT NN VBD JJ NNS , JJ IN NNS CC NN , VBD VBN IN NNP POS NN CC NN NNS ."
It said in most cases abusers were not punished .,O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD IN JJS NNS NNS VBD RB VBN .
