Thousands of Iraqi police and troops are on high alert in the Shi'ite holy city of Karbala as hundreds of thousands of pilgrims gathered for a Shi'ite religious festival .,O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN JJ NNS CC NNS VBP IN JJ NN IN DT NNP JJ NN IN NNP IN NNS IN NNS IN NNS VBN IN DT NNP JJ NN .
Officials closed the city to cars Friday to prevent car bomb attacks .,O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O,NNS VBD DT NN TO NNS NNP TO VB NN NN NNS .
"North of Karbala , two car bombers killed eight people , including seven police officers , on a road linking the city to Baghdad .",B-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP IN NNP , CD NN NNS VBD CD NNS , VBG CD NN NNS , IN DT NN VBG DT NN TO NNP ."
"Celebrations begin Monday marking the birthday more than 11 centuries ago of a revered Shi'ite leader , Imam Mehdi .",O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O,"NNS VBP NNP VBG DT NN JJR IN CD NNS IN IN DT JJ NNP NN , NNP NNP ."
Pilgrims are pouring in even though al-Qaida in Iraq leader Abu Musab al-Zarqawi declared war on Shi'ites last week .,O O O O O O B-org O B-geo O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O,NNS VBP VBG IN RB IN NNP IN NNP NN NNP NNP NNP VBD NN IN NNS JJ NN .
"Further south , two Iraqis were killed in violence that erupted after Iraqi authorities detained two British soldiers in Basra .",O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O,"JJ NN , CD NNS VBD VBN IN NN WDT VBD IN JJ NNS VBD CD JJ NNS IN NNP ."
"In a separate development , one of Saddam Hussein 's nephews was sentenced to life in prison for bomb-making and funding the country 's insurgency .",O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN , CD IN NNP NNP POS NNS VBD VBN TO NN IN NN IN NN CC VBG DT NN POS NN ."
