The UAE has an open economy with a high per capita income and a sizable annual trade surplus .,O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN DT JJ IN NN NN CC DT JJ JJ NN NN .
Successful efforts at economic diversification have reduced the portion of GDP based on oil and gas output to 25 % .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS IN JJ NN VBP VBN DT NN IN NN VBN IN NN CC NN NN TO CD NN .
"Since the discovery of oil in the UAE more than 30 years ago , the UAE has undergone a profound transformation from an impoverished region of small desert principalities to a modern state with a high standard of living .",O O O O O O O B-org O O B-tim O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN IN NN IN DT NNP JJR IN CD NNS RB , DT NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NN NNS TO DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN IN NN ."
The government has increased spending on job creation and infrastructure expansion and is opening up utilities to greater private sector involvement .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBN NN IN NN NN CC NN NN CC VBZ VBG RP NNS TO JJR JJ NN NN .
"In April 2004 , the UAE signed a Trade and Investment Framework Agreement with Washington and in November 2004 agreed to undertake negotiations toward a Free Trade Agreement with the US , however , those talks have not moved forward .",O B-tim I-tim O O B-org O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-geo O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP CD , DT NNP VBD DT NNP CC NNP NNP NNP IN NNP CC IN NNP CD VBD TO VB NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP IN DT NNP , RB , DT NNS VBP RB VBN RB ."
The country 's Free Trade Zones - offering 100 % foreign ownership and zero taxes - are helping to attract foreign investors .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN POS NNP NNP NNP IN VBG CD NN JJ NN CC NN NNS : VBP VBG TO VB JJ NNS .
"The global financial crisis , tight international credit , and deflated asset prices constricted the economy in 2009 and 2010 .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,"DT JJ JJ NN , JJ JJ NN , CC VBN NN NNS VBD DT NN IN CD CC CD ."
UAE authorities tried to blunt the crisis by increasing spending and boosting liquidity in the banking sector .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBD TO VB DT NN IN VBG NN CC VBG NN IN DT NN NN .
"The crisis hit Dubai hardest , as it was heavily exposed to depressed real estate prices .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD NNP JJS , IN PRP VBD RB VBN TO JJ JJ NN NNS ."
"Dubai lacked sufficient cash to meet its debt obligations , prompting global concern about its solvency .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD JJ NN TO VB PRP$ NN NNS , VBG JJ NN IN PRP$ NN ."
The UAE Central Bank and Abu Dhabi-based banks bought the largest shares .,O B-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP CC NNP JJ NNS VBD DT JJS NNS .
In December 2009 Dubai received an additional $ 10 billion loan from the emirate of Abu Dhabi .,O B-tim I-tim B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,IN NNP CD NNP VBD DT JJ $ CD CD NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP .
The economy is expected to continue a slow rebound .,O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBN TO VB DT JJ NN .
"Dependence on oil , a large expatriate workforce , and growing inflation pressures are significant long-term challenges .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NN IN NN , DT JJ JJ NN , CC VBG NN NNS VBP JJ JJ NNS ."
The UAE 's strategic plan for the next few years focuses on diversification and creating more opportunities for nationals through improved education and increased private sector employment .,O B-org O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP POS JJ NN IN DT JJ JJ NNS VBZ IN NN CC VBG JJR NNS IN NNS IN VBN NN CC JJ JJ NN NN .
