Associates of one of Tibet 's richest businessmen say Dorje Tashi has been sentenced to life in prison on charges of helping Tibetan exile groups .,B-org O O O B-geo O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O,NNP IN CD IN NNP POS JJS NNS VBP NNP NNP VBZ VBN VBN TO NN IN NN IN NNS IN VBG JJ NN NNS .
People close to the prominent hotel owner 's family told VOA 's Tibetan service the sentence was delivered on June 26 but has not been made public by the Chinese government .,O O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,NNS RB TO DT JJ NN NN POS NN VBD NNP POS JJ NN DT NN VBD VBN IN NNP CD CC VBZ RB VBN VBN JJ IN DT JJ NN .
The sentence is also reported by the Tibetan Center for Human Rights and Democracy .,O O O O O O O B-gpe B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,DT NN VBZ RB VBN IN DT JJ NNP IN NNP NNP CC NNP .
"The Associated Press quoted that India-based group saying Dorje Tashi , owner of the famed Yak Hotel , was accused of "" funding some outside Tibetan groups . """,B-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O,"DT NNP NNP VBD IN JJ NN VBG NNP NNP , NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP , VBD VBN IN LQU VBG DT JJ JJ NNS . LQU"
No further details of the charges were available .,O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNS IN DT NNS VBD JJ .
China has cracked down on dissent in Tibet since riots in 2008 left at least 22 people dead .,B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN RP IN NN IN NNP IN NNS IN CD VBD IN JJS CD NNS JJ .
"But observers were surprised at the harshness of the sentence given to Dorje Tashi , who is reported to have joined the Communist Party and worked closely with authorities .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O,"CC NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN IN DT NN VBN TO NNP NNP , WP VBZ VBN TO VB VBN DT NNP NNP CC VBD RB IN NNS ."
