"Israel has released Palestinian Deputy Prime Minister Nasser Shaer , a top Hamas official , who was detained by the military more than a month ago .",B-geo O O B-gpe O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBN JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP , DT JJ NNP NN , WP VBD VBN IN DT JJ JJR IN DT NN RB ."
A military judge ordered Shaer to be released citing a lack of evidence .,O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBD NNP TO VB VBN VBG DT NN IN NN .
Israeli officials had never brought charges against the most senior Hamas official in Israeli custody .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-gpe O O,JJ NNS VBD RB VBN NNS IN DT RBS JJ NNP NN IN JJ NN .
The deputy prime minister later returned to his home in the West Bank city of Nablus where he was greeted by dozens of supporters .,O O B-per O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ JJ NN RB VBD TO PRP$ NN IN DT NNP NNP NN IN NNP WRB PRP VBD VBN IN NNS IN NNS .
Israeli forces seized Shaer at his home on August 19 as they rounded up dozens of Hamas officials after Palestinian militants captured an Israeli soldier in the Gaza Strip in June .,B-gpe O O B-per O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O B-org O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org O B-tim O,JJ NNS VBD NNP IN PRP$ NN IN NNP CD IN PRP VBD RP NNS IN NNP NNS IN JJ NNS VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP .
About 30 Hamas lawmakers and cabinet members are still in Israeli custody .,O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,IN CD NNP NNS CC NN NNS VBP RB IN JJ NN .
