"U.S. Secretary of State Hillary Clinton flies Sunday to Latin America , where she is expected to focus on Chile 's deadly earthquake and Brazil 's relations with Iran .",B-org O O B-org B-per I-per O B-tim O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O,"NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNP TO NNP NNP , WRB PRP VBZ VBN TO VB IN NNP POS JJ NN CC NNP POS NNS IN NNP ."
"Clinton begins her five-day tour in Uruguay , where she will attend the inauguration of President-elect Jose Mujica .",B-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O,"NNP VBZ PRP$ JJ NN IN NNP , WRB PRP MD VB DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP ."
"She is due next in Chile , unless the 8.8-magnitude earthquake that struck Saturday disrupts her plans .",O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O,"PRP VBZ JJ JJ IN NNP , IN DT JJ NN WDT VBD NNP VBZ PRP$ NNS ."
Wednesday 's visit to Brazil will be the centerpiece of Clinton 's diplomatic efforts .,B-tim O O O B-geo O O O O O B-per O O O O,NNP POS NN TO NNP MD VB DT NN IN NNP POS JJ NNS .
She plans to lobby Brazilian President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva to support new sanctions against Iran .,O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O,PRP VBZ TO VB JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP TO VB JJ NNS IN NNP .
"Brazil is a voting member of the U.N. Security Council , but has warm relations with Iran and has been reluctant to further punish Tehran for its nuclear enrichment program .",B-geo O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ DT NN NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP , CC VBZ JJ NNS IN NNP CC VBZ VBN JJ TO RB VB NNP IN PRP$ JJ NN NN ."
"Clinton ends her tour in Costa Rica and Guatemala , where she will also meet the leaders of the Dominican Republic and El Salvador .",B-per O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo I-geo O,"NNP VBZ PRP$ NN IN NNP NNP CC NNP , WRB PRP MD RB VB DT NNS IN DT NNP NNP CC NNP NNP ."
