"Landslides in northwestern China have buried a mountain village , leaving at least 20 people missing Monday .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"NNS IN JJ NNP VBP VBN DT NN NN , VBG IN JJS CD NNS VBG NNP ."
The official Xinhua news agency said landslides and mud-rock flows struck several villages in Langao County Sunday evening after days of continuous rain .,O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo B-tim O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNP NN NN VBD NNS CC JJ NNS VBD JJ NNS IN NNP NNP NNP NN IN NNS IN JJ NN .
The report said nine homes were flattened and 20 people are missing in Muzhu village in the city of Ankang in Shaanxi province .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O,DT NN VBD CD NNS VBD VBN CC CD NNS VBP VBG IN NNP NN IN DT NN IN NNP IN NNP NN .
"Chinese media also said rising river waters are putting to the test the massive Three Gorges Dam , which is expected this week to see its highest water level since it was completed in 2006 .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"JJ NNS RB VBD VBG NN NNS VBP VBG TO DT NN DT JJ CD NNP NNP , WDT VBZ VBN DT NN TO VB PRP$ JJS NN NN IN PRP VBD VBN IN CD ."
China 's civil affairs ministry says heavy rainfall has caused water levels in lakes and rivers to exceed danger levels .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS JJ NNS NN VBZ JJ NN VBZ VBN NN NNS IN NNS CC NNS TO VB NN NNS .
