"THE NORTH WIND and the Sun disputed as to which was the most powerful , and agreed that he should be declared the victor who could first strip a wayfaring man of his clothes .",O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN NN CC DT NN VBD IN TO WDT VBD DT RBS JJ , CC VBD IN PRP MD VB VBN DT NN WP MD RB VB DT JJ NN IN PRP$ NNS ."
"The North Wind first tried his power and blew with all his might , but the keener his blasts , the closer the Traveler wrapped his cloak around him , until at last , resigning all hope of victory , the Wind called upon the Sun to see what he could do .",O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"DT NN NN RB VBD PRP$ NN CC VBD IN DT PRP$ NN , CC DT JJR PRP$ NNS , DT JJR DT NN VBD PRP$ NN IN PRP , IN IN JJ , VBG DT NN IN NN , DT NNP VBD IN DT NNP TO VB WP PRP MD VB ."
The Sun suddenly shone out with all his warmth .,O B-geo O O O O O O O O,DT NN RB VBD RP IN DT PRP$ NN .
"The Traveler no sooner felt his genial rays than he took off one garment after another , and at last , fairly overcome with heat , undressed and bathed in a stream that lay in his path .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN DT RBR VBD PRP$ JJ NNS IN PRP VBD RP CD NN IN DT , CC IN JJ , RB VBN IN NN , VBD CC VBD IN DT NN WDT VBD IN PRP$ NN ."
Persuasion is better than Force .,O O O O B-geo O,NN VBZ JJR IN NN .
