"Uzbek residents of Korasuv , hold a banner , reading "" We are against terrorism "" as they gather to protest arrest of Bakhtiyor Rakhimov Hundreds of people have taken to the streets in Uzbekistan , calling for the release of a self-proclaimed Islamic leader .",B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS IN NNP , VBP DT NN , VBG LQU PRP VBP IN NN RQU IN PRP VBP TO VB NN IN NNP NNP NNS IN NNS VBP VBN TO DT NNS IN NNP , VBG IN DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NN ."
Bakhtiyor Rakhimov was arrested near the border with Kyrgystan after his followers briefly seized the town of Korasuv in a failed Islamic rebellion last week .,B-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD VBN IN DT NN IN NNP IN PRP$ NNS RB VBD DT NN IN NNP IN DT JJ JJ NN JJ NN .
"Meanwhile , western diplomats , led by the European Union and the United Nations , have increased pressure on Uzbek President Islam Karimov to allow an independent probe of recent clashes in Andijan , which left scores of people dead .",O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-org I-org O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"RB , JJ NNS , VBN IN DT NNP NNP CC DT NNP NNPS , VBP VBN NN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP TO VB DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS IN NNP , WDT VBD NNS IN NNS JJ ."
The Organization for Security and Cooperation in Europe Saturday expressed deep concern over Tashkent 's rejection of a U.N.-led investigation .,B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-geo B-tim O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,DT NNP IN NNP CC NNP IN NNP NNP VBD JJ NN IN NNP POS NN IN DT JJ NN .
