Japan 's defense agency says it is concerned about China 's expansion of its military forces .,B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,NNP POS NN NN VBZ PRP VBZ JJ IN NNP POS NN IN PRP$ JJ NNS .
"An annual report issued Tuesday also noted Beijing 's increasing use of its maritime military forces , citing an incident last November , when a Chinese submarine violated Japanese territorial waters .",O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-gpe O O B-gpe O O O,"DT JJ NN VBN NNP RB VBD NNP POS VBG NN IN PRP$ JJ JJ NNS , VBG DT NN JJ NNP , WRB DT JJ NN VBD JJ JJ NNS ."
The report says Tokyo will keep a close watch on China 's current modernization efforts to determine if they go beyond Beijing 's self-defense needs .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,DT NN VBZ NNP MD VB DT JJ NN IN NNP POS JJ NN NNS TO VB IN PRP VBP IN NNP POS JJ NNS .
"The head of Japan Defense Agency , Yoshinori Ono , says he wants China to become more "" transparent "" about its military plans .",O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP , VBZ PRP VBZ NNP TO VB RBR RQU JJ LQU IN PRP$ JJ NNS ."
"Relations between Japan and China are at their lowest in several decades , in part because of a feud over gas drilling in the East China Sea .",O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O,"NNP IN NNP CC NNP VBP IN PRP$ JJS IN JJ NNS , IN NN IN IN DT NN IN NN NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP ."
