Mick was showing an American some Irish marrows and the American said that they had gherkins as big as marrows .,B-per O O O B-gpe O B-gpe O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD VBG DT JJ DT JJ NNS CC DT NNP VBD IN PRP VBD NNS RB JJ IN NNS .
"Then Mick showed him some cabbages , the American said that in the States they had brussel sprouts as big as them and that American cabbages are about 3 feet in diameter .",O B-per O O O O O O B-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,"RB NNP VBD PRP DT NNS , DT NNP VBD IN IN DT NNS PRP VBD NN NNS RB JJ IN PRP CC IN JJ NNS VBP IN CD NNS IN NN ."
Eventually the American pointed to some old gasometers and asked what they were .,O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O,RB DT NNP VBD TO DT JJ NNS CC VBD WP PRP VBD .
Mick replied they are saucepans for cooking American cabbages .,B-per O O O O O O B-gpe O O,NNP VBD PRP VBP NNS IN JJ JJ NNS .
