"South Africa occupied the German colony of South-West Africa during World War I and administered it as a mandate until after World War II , when it annexed the territory .",B-geo I-geo O O B-gpe O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-eve O O O O O O O O O O B-eve O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP CC VBD PRP IN DT NN IN IN NNP NNP NNP , WRB PRP VBD DT NN ."
"In 1966 the Marxist South-West Africa People 's Organization ( SWAPO ) guerrilla group launched a war of independence for the area that became Namibia , but it was not until 1988 that South Africa agreed to end its administration in accordance with a UN peace plan for the entire region .",O B-tim O B-tim B-geo I-geo O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,"IN CD DT JJ NNP NNP NNP POS NNP LRB NNP RRB NN NN VBD DT NN IN NN IN DT NN WDT VBD NNP , CC PRP VBD RB IN CD IN NNP NNP VBD TO VB PRP$ NN IN NN IN DT NNP NN NN IN DT JJ NN ."
Namibia has been governed by SWAPO since the country won independence in 1990 .,B-geo O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP VBZ VBN VBN IN NNP IN DT NN VBD NN IN CD .
Hifikepunye POHAMBA was elected president in November 2004 in a landslide victory replacing Sam NUJOMA who led the country during its first 14 years of self rule .,B-per I-per O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD VBN NN IN NNP CD IN DT NN NN VBG NNP NNP WP VBD DT NN IN PRP$ JJ CD NNS IN NN NN .
POHAMBA was reelected in November 2009 .,B-per O O O B-tim I-tim O,NNP VBD VBN IN NNP CD .
