Russia has dropped plans to supply Iran with S-300 air defense missiles .,B-org O O O O O B-geo O B-art O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN NNS TO VB NNP IN NNP NN NN NNS .
"The chief of Russia 's armed forces , General Nikolai Makarov , said the delivery of the missiles would violate U.N. sanctions .",O O O B-geo O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"DT NN IN NNP POS JJ NNS , NNP NNP NNP , VBD DT NN IN DT NNS MD VB NNP NNS ."
"The S-300 is a mobile , long-range air defense system that can detect , track and destroy ballistic missiles , cruise missiles and low-flying aircraft .",O B-art O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP VBZ DT JJ , JJ NN NN NN WDT MD VB , VB CC VB JJ NNS , NN NNS CC JJ NN ."
"Western nations have opposed the sale , saying it would give Iran the means to withstand air strikes against its nuclear sites .",B-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP VBN DT NN , VBG PRP MD VB NNP DT NNS TO VB NN NNS IN PRP$ JJ NNS ."
The U.N. imposed a fourth set of sanctions on Iran in June for refusing to stop enriching uranium .,O B-org O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O,DT NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN NNS IN NNP IN NNP IN VBG TO VB VBG NN .
