Parties loyal to Pakistani military ruler have routed hard-line Islamic groups in the last phase of nationwide elections for local mayors .,O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS JJ TO JJ JJ NN VBP VBN JJ JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS IN JJ NNS .
"The result is a setback for the country 's main alliance of religion-based parties , the Muttahida Majlis-e-Amal .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"DT NN VBZ DT NN IN DT NN POS JJ NN IN JJ NNS , DT NNP NNP ."
"The polls are being seen as a test of General Musharraf 's efforts to sideline Islamic groups and increase his own popularity ahead of national polls due in October , 2007 .",O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,"DT NNS VBP VBG VBN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP POS NNS TO NN JJ NNS CC VB PRP$ JJ NN RB IN JJ NNS JJ IN NNP , CD ."
"In Karachi , Pakistan 's biggest city , the ethnic-based pro-Musharraf Muttahida Qaumi Movement took all 18 districts , wiping out Islamic parties who formerly dominated the area .",O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , NNP POS JJS NN , DT JJ JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD DT CD NNS , VBG RP JJ NNS WP RB VBD DT NN ."
"In North West Frontier Province , religious parties won only six mayoral seats out of 24 .",O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"IN NNP NNP NNP NNP , JJ NNS VBD RB CD JJ NNS IN IN CD ."
"Most were won by the Pakistan Muslim League , who also took most seats in central Punjab province .",O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"JJS VBD VBN IN DT NNP NNP NNP , WP RB VBD JJS NNS IN JJ NNP NN ."
"Opposition parties allege there was vote-rigging , but the Election Commission says there were no official complaints .",O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O,"NN NNS VBP EX VBD NN , CC DT NNP NNP VBZ EX VBD DT JJ NNS ."
