"Japanese transport trucks lugging military vehicles and equipment have left Iraq , marking the start of Japan 's withdrawal from the war-torn country .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"JJ NN NNS VBG JJ NNS CC NN VBP VBN NNP , VBG DT NN IN NNP POS NN IN DT JJ NN ."
The military contingent was seen crossing into Kuwait Sunday after leaving the base at Samawa in the southern Iraqi province of Muthanna .,O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O,DT JJ JJ VBD VBN VBG IN NNP NNP IN VBG DT NN IN NNP IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP .
Iraqi forces are scheduled to take over security from coalition forces in the province next month .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN TO VB RP NN IN NN NNS IN DT NN JJ NN .
Japanese Prime Minister Junichiro Koizumi said Tuesday that Japan 's 600 non-combat troops had fulfilled their humanitarian assignment and would leave Iraq .,B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP IN NNP POS CD JJ NNS VBD VBN PRP$ JJ NN CC MD VB NNP .
"Mr. Koizumi has supported the U.S. policy in Iraq , although a vast majority of Japanese opposed the deployment of their troops .",B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NNP NN IN NNP , IN DT JJ NN IN NNS VBD DT NN IN PRP$ NNS ."
"Japan 's air force will remain active in Iraq , transporting goods and personnel for the U.S.-led coalition .",B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NN NN MD VB JJ IN NNP , VBG NNS CC NNS IN DT JJ NN ."
"No Japanese troops have been hurt in Iraq , but insurgents have killed six Japanese citizens , including two diplomats .",O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNS VBP VBN VBN IN NNP , CC NNS VBP VBN CD JJ NNS , VBG CD NNS ."
