"French President Nicolas Sarkozy will begin a three-day trip to the Middle East on Sunday , meeting with a group of leaders in an effort to build diplomatic relationships in the region .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O B-geo I-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP MD VB DT JJ NN TO DT NNP NNP IN NNP , NN IN DT NN IN NNS IN DT NN TO VB JJ NNS IN DT NN ."
"Mr. Sarkozy will visit Saudi Arabia , Qatar and the United Arab Emirates .",B-per I-per O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O B-org I-org I-org O,"NNP NNP MD VB NNP NNP , NNP CC DT NNP NNP NNPS ."
"He will arrive in the Middle East at the same time U.S. President George Bush is there , although they are not expected to cross paths .",O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-geo B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP MD VB IN DT NNP NNP IN DT JJ NN NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ RB , IN PRP VBP RB VBN TO VB NNS ."
A report on Saudi government-run television says an agreement is expected with France to sell military equipment to the kingdom .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN JJ JJ NN VBZ DT NN VBZ VBN IN NNP TO VB JJ NN TO DT NN .
"During his visit to the United Arab Emirates , Mr. Sarkozy is expected to sign a nearly $ 6 billion agreement for nuclear power generation .",O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN PRP$ NN TO DT NNP NNP NNPS , NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB DT RB $ CD CD NN IN JJ NN NN ."
France already has signed similar agreements with Algeria and Libya .,B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,NNP RB VBZ VBN JJ NNS IN NNP CC NNP .
