"U.S. Defense Secretary Robert Gates says Washington will remain committed to Asia , no matter who is in the White House .",B-org I-org B-per I-per I-per O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNP MD VB JJ TO NNP , DT NN WP VBZ IN DT NNP NNP ."
"Gates told a high-level security forum , the Shangri-La Dialogue , in Singapore Saturday that the United States would be even further engaged in Asia in the future .",B-per O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-org B-tim O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"NNP VBD DT JJ NN NN , DT NNP NNP , IN NNP NNP IN DT NNP NNPS MD VB RB RBR VBN IN NNP IN DT NN ."
"Some Asian allies have raised doubts over U.S. leadership in the region , which comes as China continues its military build-up .",O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,"DT JJ NNS VBP VBN NNS IN NNP NN IN DT NN , WDT VBZ IN NNP VBZ PRP$ JJ NN ."
"Gates said dismissed concerns that Iraq and Afghanistan have distracted the U.S from Asia , saying Washington has never been engaged with more Asian countries .",B-per O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O B-org O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD VBN NNS IN NNP CC NNP VBP VBN DT NNP IN NNP , VBG NNP VBZ RB VBN VBN IN JJR JJ NNS ."
Gates said any future U.S. administration 's Asia policies will be grounded in the fact that the United States remains a nation with strong and enduring interests in the region .,B-per O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD DT JJ NNP NN POS NNP NNS MD VB VBN IN DT NN IN DT NNP NNPS VBZ DT NN IN JJ CC JJ NNS IN DT NN .
