"A United Nations food agency is appealing for $ 40 million to help Sudanese farmers , fishermen and cattle producers .",O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNPS NN NN VBZ VBG IN $ CD CD TO VB JJ NNS , NNS CC NN NNS ."
The U.N. Food and Agriculture Organization says support for Sudan 's agricultural sector is crucial for ensuring lasting peace in the war-torn African nation .,O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT NNP NNP CC NNP NNP VBZ NN IN NNP POS JJ NN VBZ JJ IN VBG JJ NN IN DT JJ JJ NN .
"It says the country 's humanitarian needs "" remain immense "" despite last year 's peace accord that ended more than 20 years of civil war in southern Sudan .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,PRP VBZ DT NN POS JJ NNS LQU VBP JJ LQU IN JJ NN POS NN NN WDT VBD JJR IN CD NNS IN JJ NN IN JJ NNP .
"The FAO says conflict in the Darfur region , the risk of a poor harvest and the return of 680,000 displaced Sudanese make international relief a necessity .",O B-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,"DT NNP VBZ NN IN DT NNP NN , DT NN IN DT JJ NN CC DT NN IN CD JJ NNS VBP JJ NN DT NN ."
"The agency plans to use the funds raised to provide seeds and tools , fishing equipment and livestock medicine .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ TO VB DT NNS VBN TO VB NNS CC NNS , NN NN CC NN NN ."
It says some 87 percent of the people of Sudan depend on agriculture for their food security and livelihoods .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ DT CD NN IN DT NNS IN NNP VBP IN NN IN PRP$ NN NN CC NNS .
