"Business and political leaders from around the world have opened their annual meeting in Davos , Switzerland , with the growing power of China and India high on the agenda .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O,"NN CC JJ NNS IN IN DT NN VBP VBN PRP$ JJ NN IN NNP , NNP , IN DT VBG NN IN NNP CC NNP JJ IN DT NN ."
"Organizers of the World Economic Forum say more than 2,300 participants from 89 countries will attend the five-day event .",O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP VBP JJR IN CD NNS IN CD NNS MD VB DT JJ NN .
One of the top themes will be the emergence of China and India as economic heavyweights .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O,CD IN DT JJ NNS MD VB DT NN IN NNP CC NNP IN JJ NNS .
"Attendees will also discuss high energy prices , Iran 's nuclear program , and terrorism .",O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"NNS MD RB VB JJ NN NNS , NNP POS JJ NN , CC NN ."
"Among the political leaders attending will be Chinese Vice Premier Zeng Peiyan , German Chancellor Angela Merkel , Pakistani President Pervez Musharraf and U.N. Secretary-General Kofi Annan .",O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O B-org I-org B-per I-per O,"IN DT JJ NNS VBG MD VB JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP , JJ NNP NNP NNP , JJ NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
"Several entertainment figures will address the forum including actress Angelina Jolie , who is a goodwill ambassador for the U.N , and anti-poverty campaigner Bono of the rock group U-2 .",O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O B-per O O O O O O,"JJ NN NNS MD VB DT NN VBG NN NNP NNP , WP VBZ DT NN NN IN DT NNP , CC JJ NN NNP IN DT NN NN NN ."
