A U.S. Defense Department analyst has been arrested on charges that he illegally disclosed classified information about potential attacks on U.S. forces in Iraq .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O,DT NNP NNP NNP NN VBZ VBN VBN IN NNS IN PRP RB VBD JJ NN IN JJ NNS IN NNP NNS IN NNP .
"Fifty-eight-year-old Larry Franklin surrendered to the FBI Wednesday , and is expected to appear in a U.S. district court later in the day .",B-per I-per I-per O O O B-org B-tim O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O,"NNP NNP NNP VBD TO DT NNP NNP , CC VBZ VBN TO VB IN DT NNP NN NN RB IN DT NN ."
A criminal complaint filed against Mr. Franklin says he passed the information to two individuals at a lunch outside Washington in June 2003 .,O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim I-tim O,DT JJ NN VBN IN NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBD DT NN TO CD NNS IN DT NN IN NNP IN NNP CD .
"The individuals were not named in the court documents , but law enforcement officials say the two were employees of AIPAC , an American pro-Israel group .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-gpe O O O,"DT NNS VBD RB VBN IN DT NN NNS , CC NN NN NNS VBP DT CD VBD NNS IN NNP , DT JJ JJ NN ."
AIPAC later fired the two men .,B-org O O O O O O,NNP RB VBD DT CD NNS .
"At the time of the lunch , Mr. Franklin was working as a Pentagon specialist on Iran and Middle Eastern affairs .",O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-org O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O,"IN DT NN IN DT NN , NNP NNP VBD VBG IN DT NNP NN IN NNP CC NNP NNP NNS ."
