Reports say Syrian troops have completely withdrawn from northern Lebanon .,O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O,NNS VBP JJ NNS VBP RB VBN IN JJ NNP .
Lebanese security sources say thousands of soldiers evacuated their northern posts for the first time since Syrian forces entered Lebanon in 1976 .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O B-tim O,JJ NN NNS VBP NNS IN NNS VBD PRP$ JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS VBD NNP IN CD .
"However , Syrian intelligence agents remain in the north , and Syrian soldiers remain elsewhere in the country .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,"RB , JJ NN NNS VBP IN DT NN , CC JJ NNS VBP RB IN DT NN ."
The news comes as a top United Nations envoy prepares to visit Damascus to discuss evacuating all of Syria 's military forces from Lebanon .,O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O,DT NN VBZ IN DT JJ NNP NNPS NN VBZ TO VB NNP TO VB VBG DT IN NNP POS JJ NNS IN NNP .
Terje Roed-Larsen says he expects to receive a firm timetable on troop withdrawals from Syrian President Bashar al-Assad .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O,NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ TO VB DT NN NN IN NN NNS IN JJ NNP NNP NNP .
"Friday , the Washington Post newspaper reported that the envoy plans to tell Syria it faces political and economic isolation if it does not quickly withdraw all of its troops .",B-tim O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP , DT NNP NNP NN VBD IN DT NN VBZ TO VB NNP PRP VBZ JJ CC JJ NN IN PRP VBZ RB RB VB DT IN PRP$ NNS ."
