A U.S. newspaper says the American military in Iraq is secretly paying Iraqi newspapers to print stories highlighting the work of U.S. and Iraqi troops and denouncing insurgents .,O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-gpe O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBZ DT JJ NN IN NNP VBZ RB VBG JJ NNS TO NN NNS VBG DT NN IN NNP CC JJ NNS CC VBG NNS .
The Los Angeles Times reports Wednesday that the articles are written by American soldiers but are presented to Iraqi media as unbiased accounts from independent journalists .,O B-org I-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNP IN DT NNS VBP VBN IN JJ NNS CC VBP VBN TO JJ NNS IN JJ NNS IN JJ NNS .
"The Times says the stories are translated and placed in Iraqi newspapers with the help of an American defense contractor , the Lincoln Group .",O B-org O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-org I-org O,"DT NNP VBZ DT NNS VBP VBN CC VBN IN JJ NNS IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN NN , DT NNP NNP ."
"Pentagon spokesman Bryan Whitman says the allegations are being investigated , and if they are true , some of them are troubling and could violate Pentagon policy .",B-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O,"NNP NN NNP NNP VBZ DT NNS VBP VBG VBN , CC IN PRP VBP JJ , DT IN PRP VBP JJ CC MD VB NNP NN ."
Iraqi editors and journalists interviewed for the Times article reacted with a mixture of surprise and indifference when told about the alleged origin of the stories .,B-gpe O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS CC NNS VBN IN DT NNP NN VBD IN DT NN IN NN CC NN WRB VBN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNS .
