"Former U.N. Secretary General Kofi Annan says he is "" seriously concerned "" Kenyan leaders have yet to fulfill an agreement to form a power-sharing coalition government .",O B-org O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ LQU RB JJ RQU JJ NNS VBP RB TO VB DT NN TO VB DT JJ NN NN .
"In a statement Wednesday , the former U.N. chief urged Kenyan President Mwai Kibaki and prime minister-designate Raila Odinga to respect the power-sharing pact and promptly resolve their differences for the good of the nation .",O O O B-tim O O O B-org O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN NNP , DT JJ NNP NN VBD JJ NNP NNP NNP CC JJ JJ NNP NNP TO VB DT JJ NN CC RB VB PRP$ NNS IN DT NN IN DT NN ."
The two Kenyan rivals agreed to form a coalition government under a deal brokered by Mr. Annan in February .,O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O B-tim O,DT CD JJ NNS VBD TO VB DT NN NN IN DT NN VBN IN NNP NNP IN NNP .
The cabinet would be divided between Mr. Kibaki 's Party of National Unity and Mr. Odinga 's Orange Democratic Movement .,O O O O O O B-per B-geo O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org B-per B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,DT NN MD VB VBN IN NNP NNP POS NNP IN NNP NNP CC NNP NNP POS NNP NNP NNP .
"The pact brought calm to Kenya after a disputed presidential election in December led to weeks of riots and ethnic violence that killed more than 1,000 people .",O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD NN TO NNP IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP VBD TO NNS IN NNS CC JJ NN WDT VBD JJR IN CD NNS .
"Last week , Mr. Kibaki and Mr. Odinga suspended power-sharing negotiations after failing to agree on the size and distribution of the cabinet .",O O O B-per B-geo O B-per B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN , NNP NNP CC NNP NNP VBD JJ NNS IN VBG TO VB IN DT NN CC NN IN DT NN ."
