Brazilian officials are in Geneva Wednesday to defend their country 's record before the U.N. Human Rights Commission .,B-gpe O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,JJ NNS VBP IN NNP NNP TO VB PRP$ NN POS NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP .
The officials are expected to report to the commission during a two-day meeting .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,DT NNS VBP VBN TO VB TO DT NN IN DT JJ NN .
"The commission has said it will ask the officials to explain measures Brazil is taking to stop corruption , which the United Nations says contributes to impunity for violators of human rights .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ VBN PRP MD VB DT NNS TO VB NNS NNP VBZ VBG TO VB NN , WDT DT NNP NNP VBZ NNS TO NN IN NNS IN JJ NNS ."
The commission says it has information extrajudicial executions are being committed by the police and disguised as lawful actions .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ PRP VBZ NN JJ NNS VBP VBG VBN IN DT NN CC VBN IN JJ NNS .
It has also asked Brazil to explain the increase in the number of deaths caused by police actions .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ RB VBN NNP TO VB DT NN IN DT NN IN NNS VBN IN NN NNS .
The review comes one day after the human rights group Amnesty International reported that Brazil has scarcely improved its human rights record over the past decade .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT NN VBZ CD NN IN DT JJ NNS NN NNP NNP VBD IN NNP VBZ RB VBN PRP$ JJ NNS NN IN DT JJ NN .
