"The United States women 's football ( soccer ) team has defeated host Norway , 4-0 , in a friendly warm-up in Fredrikstad for the Olympic tournament in China .",O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NNP NNPS NNS POS NN LRB NN RRB NN VBZ VBN NN NNP , CD , IN DT JJ NN IN NNP IN DT NNP NN IN NNP ."
"Midfielder Lindsay Tarpley scored first Wednesday before Carli Lloyd , Angela Hucles and Abby Wambach added goals for the Americans .",O B-per I-per O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O B-per I-per O B-per I-per O O O O B-gpe O,"NN NNP NNP VBD JJ NNP IN NNP NNP , NNP NNP CC NNP NNP VBD NNS IN DT NNS ."
"The United States improved to 19-0 this year , including a penalty-kicks victory over Canada .",O B-geo I-geo O O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NNP NNPS VBD TO CD DT NN , VBG DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
"The U.S. women are a strong favorite to medal at the Olympics as are Norway , Brazil and Germany .",O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O,"DT NNP NNS VBP DT JJ NN TO VB IN DT NNS IN VBP NNP , NNP CC NNP ."
The Americans head to Sweden for another exhibition on Saturday .,O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O B-tim O,DT NNS VBP TO NNP IN DT NN IN NNP .
The United States then hosts Brazil on July 13 in Colorado and again on July 16 in San Diego .,O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo O B-tim I-tim O B-geo O O O B-tim I-tim O B-geo I-geo O,DT NNP NNPS RB VBZ NNP IN NNP CD IN NNP CC RB IN NNP CD IN NNP NNP .
"Two weeks ago , the Americans won the Peace Queen Cup in South Korea for their fourth tournament victory of the year .",B-tim O O O O B-gpe O O B-org I-org I-org O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O,"CD NNS RB , DT NNS VBD DT NNP NNP NNP IN NNP NNP IN PRP$ JJ NN NN IN DT NN ."
