Palestinian police officers set up a post at the entrance of the West Bank town of Tulkarem Israel has frozen the planned handover of more West Bank towns to Palestinian security forces because it says Palestinian forces have failed to disarm militants .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-gpe O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,JJ NN NNS VBD RP DT NN IN DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NN IN NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN JJR NNP NNP NNS TO JJ NN NNS IN PRP VBZ JJ NNS VBP VBN TO VB NNS .
The Israeli security cabinet made the decision Wednesday .,O B-gpe O O O O O B-tim O,DT JJ NN NN VBD DT NN NNP .
Israel had recently pledged to transfer control of five West Bank towns after Palestinians agreed to end attacks on Israeli targets .,B-geo O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-gpe O O O O O B-gpe O O,NNP VBD RB VBN TO VB NN IN CD NNP NNP NNS IN NNS VBD TO VB NNS IN JJ NNS .
But Israel has so far only handed over control of Jericho and Tulkarem .,O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,CC NNP VBZ RB RB RB VBN IN NN IN NNP CC NNP .
"In other developments , Israeli troops shot and killed two Palestinian teenagers who were among stone-throwers protesting Israel 's separation barrier near the West Bank village of Beit Lakia .",O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo I-geo O,"IN JJ NNS , JJ NNS VBD CC VBD CD JJ NNS WP VBD IN NNS VBG NNP POS NN NN IN DT NNP NNP NN IN NNP NNP ."
