Iraq has urged its neighbors to open diplomatic missions in Baghdad despite a warning from al-Qaida in Iraq that it will kill Arab diplomats in the country .,B-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-org O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN PRP$ NNS TO VB JJ NNS IN NNP IN DT NN IN NNP IN NNP IN PRP MD VB JJ NNS IN DT NN .
An Iraqi foreign ministry statement released Friday said the apparent assassination of an Egyptian Ambassador Ihab al-Sherif Thursday by al-Qaida militants was intended to scare Arab and Muslim countries from deepening ties with Iraq .,O B-gpe O O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-gpe B-org I-org I-org B-tim O B-org O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT JJ JJ NN NN VBN NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN NNP NNP NNP IN NNP NNS VBD VBN TO VB JJ CC JJ NNS IN VBG NNS IN NNP .
"The government urged Western and Arab nations to help Iraq fight terrorists in the country , saying the international community would be subject to blackmail if easily intimidated .",O O O B-per O B-gpe O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD JJ CC JJ NNS TO VB NNP VB NNS IN DT NN , VBG DT JJ NN MD VB NN TO VB IN RB VBN ."
Al-Qaida in Iraq claimed in a web posting that it killed the Egyptian ambassador and would go after as many ambassadors as it could to punish countries supporting Iraq 's U.S.-backed government .,B-org O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,NNP IN NNP VBD IN DT NN VBG IN PRP VBD DT JJ NN CC MD VB IN IN JJ NNS IN PRP MD TO VB NNS VBG NNP POS JJ NN .
Egyptian President Hosni Mubarak later confirmed the death of the ambassador .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP RB VBD DT NN IN DT NN .
