Turkey says it is suspending its role as mediator for peace talks between Israel and Syria due to the recent Israeli attacks on Hamas targets in the Gaza Strip .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O B-org O O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP VBZ PRP VBZ VBG PRP$ NN IN NN IN NN NNS IN NNP CC NNP JJ TO DT JJ JJ NNS IN NNP NNS IN DT NNP NNP .
Turkish Foreign Minister Ali Babacan Monday said that Israel can not speak of peace with Syria while engaging in war with Gaza .,O O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD IN NNP MD RB VB IN NN IN NNP IN VBG IN NN IN NNP .
Syria announced Sunday that it was putting peace talks with Israel on hold because of the attacks on Gaza that have killed more than 300 Palestinians .,B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O,NNP VBD NNP IN PRP VBD VBG NN NNS IN NNP IN NN IN IN DT NNS IN NNP WDT VBP VBN JJR IN CD NNS .
"Earlier today , Babacan and Egypt 's foreign minister , Ahmed Abul Gheit , met in Ankara in an attempt to find a solution to the fighting in Gaza .",O B-tim I-tim I-tim O B-geo O O O O B-per B-org I-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"RBR NN , NNP CC NNP POS JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP , VBD IN NNP IN DT NN TO VB DT NN TO DT NN IN NNP ."
"They urged Israel to stop its deadly offensive on the Gaza Strip , warning of increased tensions in the Middle East .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"PRP VBD NNP TO VB PRP$ JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP , NN IN VBN NNS IN DT NNP NNP ."
"Gheit says Egypt is trying to broker a cease-fire between the two sides , to be followed by a truce .",B-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ NNP VBZ VBG TO NN DT NN IN DT CD NNS , TO VB VBN IN DT NN ."
