"The Bulgars , a Central Asian Turkic tribe , merged with the local Slavic inhabitants in the late 7th century to form the first Bulgarian state .",O O O O B-org I-org B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O B-gpe O O,"DT NNS , DT NNP NNP JJ NN , VBN IN DT JJ NNP NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN TO VB DT JJ JJ NN ."
"In succeeding centuries , Bulgaria struggled with the Byzantine Empire to assert its place in the Balkans , but by the end of the 14th century the country was overrun by the Ottoman Turks .",O O O O B-per O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O B-org B-gpe O,"IN VBG NNS , NNP VBD IN DT NNP NNP TO VB PRP$ NN IN DT NNPS , CC IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NNP NNS ."
Northern Bulgaria attained autonomy in 1878 and all of Bulgaria became independent from the Ottoman Empire in 1908 .,B-geo B-per O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O O B-org I-org O B-tim O,NNP NNP VBD NN IN CD CC DT IN NNP VBD JJ IN DT NNP NNP IN CD .
"Having fought on the losing side in both World Wars , Bulgaria fell within the Soviet sphere of influence and became a People 's Republic in 1946 .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O,"VBG VBN IN DT VBG NN IN DT NNP NNP , NNP VBD IN DT JJ NN IN NN CC VBD DT NNP POS NNP IN CD ."
"Communist domination ended in 1990 , when Bulgaria held its first multiparty election since World War II and began the contentious process of moving toward political democracy and a market economy while combating inflation , unemployment , corruption , and crime .",O O O O B-tim O O B-per O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim B-eve O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NN VBD IN CD , WRB NNP VBD PRP$ JJ JJ NN IN NNP NNP NNP CC VBD DT JJ NN IN VBG IN JJ NN CC DT NN NN IN VBG NN , NN , NN , CC NN ."
The country joined NATO in 2004 and the EU in 2007 .,O O O B-org O B-tim O O B-org O B-tim O,DT NN VBD NNP IN CD CC DT NNP IN CD .
