Iraqi officials say at least four people were wounded in a car bomb explosion in northern Baghdad early Tuesday .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O,JJ NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN NN NN IN JJ NNP JJ NNP .
Officials say the blast occurred in the parking lot of a medical compound in a predominantly Sunni Muslim area of the city .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O,NNS VBP DT NN VBD IN DT NN NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT RB NNP NNP NN IN DT NN .
"Separately , one U.S. Marine was killed Monday , while conducting security operations in the restive Al Anbar province west of Baghdad .",O O O B-org I-org O O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O B-geo O,"RB , CD NNP NN VBD VBN NNP , IN VBG NN NNS IN DT JJ NNP NNP NN NN IN NNP ."
"On the political front , Iraqi Kurdish and Shi'ite leaders are still trying to agree on a new coalition government before the country 's parliament meets for the first time Wednesday .",O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"IN DT JJ NN , JJ NNP CC NNP NNS VBP RB VBG TO VB IN DT JJ NN NN IN DT NN POS NN VBZ IN DT JJ NN NNP ."
"The two sides held another round of talks Monday , but did not say how much progress was made .",O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT CD NNS VBD DT NN IN NNS NNP , CC VBD RB VB WRB JJ NN VBD VBN ."
"Kurds are seeking guarantees of a secular government , as well as guarantees that hundreds of thousands of Kurds driven from Kirkuk under Saddam Hussein will be allowed to return .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O,"NNS VBP VBG NNS IN DT JJ NN , RB RB IN NNS IN NNS IN NNS IN NNS VBN IN NNP IN NNP NNP MD VB VBN TO VB ."
