Ukraine is observing a national day of mourning for 89 people killed in the worst mining catastrophe in the country 's post-Soviet history .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBG DT JJ NN IN VBG IN CD NNS VBN IN DT JJS NN NN IN DT NN POS JJ NN .
"Flags decorated with black ribbons flew at half-staff Tuesday , as families of the coal miners gathered to bury the dead in and near the eastern industrial city of Donetsk .",O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNS VBN IN JJ NNS VBD IN NN NNP , IN NNS IN DT NN NNS VBD TO VB DT NN IN CC IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP ."
Rescue workers have pulled more than 350 people to safety following the coal mine explosion Sunday .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NN NNS VBP VBN JJR IN CD NNS TO VB VBG DT NN NN NN NNP .
Authorities say at least 11 miners are still missing from the Zasyadko mine .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBP RB VBG IN DT NNP NN .
"The methane gas explosion occurred 1,000 meters underground .",O O O O O O O O O,DT NN NN NN VBD CD NNS RB .
A subsequent fire hampered rescue efforts .,O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBN NN NNS .
Ukrainian President Viktor Yushchenko visited the area Monday and called on the mining ministry to develop new safety plans for 2008 .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN NNP CC VBN IN DT NN NN TO VB JJ NN NNS IN CD .
Prime Minister Viktor Yanukovych visited the mine in his native Russian-speaking region on Sunday .,B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN PRP$ JJ JJ NN IN NNP .
Russian President Vladimir Putin has sent his condolences to the victims ' families .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP$ NNS TO DT NNS POS NNS .
