The Italian Parliament has given final approval to a set of tougher anti-terrorism measures announced by the government in the wake of deadly terrorist attacks in England earlier this month .,O B-gpe B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,DT JJ NNP VBZ VBN JJ NN TO DT NN IN JJR NN NNS VBN IN DT NN IN DT NN IN JJ JJ NNS IN NNP RBR DT NN .
"The measures passed the House of Deputies on Saturday , some 24 hours after gaining approval by the Senate , the upper house of Parliament .",O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-org O,"DT NNS VBD DT NNP IN NNPS IN NNP , DT CD NNS IN VBG NN IN DT NNP , DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
"The measures would , among other things , make it illegal to train people to use explosives that are used in terrorist attacks .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS MD , IN JJ NNS , VB PRP JJ TO VB NNS TO VB NNS WDT VBP VBN IN JJ NNS ."
They also extend the time during which police may hold detainees to verify their identity from 12 to 24 hours .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O,PRP RB VBP DT NN IN WDT NNS MD VB NNS TO VB PRP$ NN IN CD TO CD NNS .
The coalition government of Prime Minister Silvio Berlusconi approved the measures last week before submitting them to Parliament .,O O O O B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-org O,DT NN NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NNS JJ NN IN VBG PRP TO NNP .
"Some Italians say their country , which has troops serving in Iraq , could become a terrorist target - citing threats posted on Islamist web sites .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS VBP PRP$ NN , WDT VBZ NNS VBG IN NNP , MD VB DT JJ NN : VBG NNS VBN IN JJ NN NNS ."
