More than 1.7 million Iraqi Kurds have signed a petition calling for a referendum on whether northern Iraq should become an independent Kurdish state .,O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,JJR IN CD CD JJ NNPS VBP VBN DT NN VBG IN DT NN IN IN JJ NNP MD VB DT JJ JJ NN .
A spokesman for the Referendum Movement of Kurdistan says the petition has been presented to the United Nations and the Iraqi government .,O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-gpe O O,DT NN IN DT NNP NN IN NNP VBZ DT NN VBZ VBN VBN TO DT NNP NNPS CC DT JJ NN .
"Baghdad has ruled out a separate Kurdish state , and has not commented on the petition .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBN RP DT JJ NNP NN , CC VBZ RB VBN IN DT NN ."
"Neighboring Turkey also has a large Kurdish minority , and is strongly opposed to independence moves by Iraqi Kurds for fear it could encourage unrest inside Turkey .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP NNP RB VBZ DT JJ JJ NN , CC VBZ RB VBN TO NN NNS IN JJ NNPS IN NN PRP MD VB NN IN NNP ."
"Ankara has warned repeatedly it is prepared to act militarily , if necessary , to prevent the formation of a separate Kurdish state .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBN RB PRP VBZ VBN TO VB RB , IN JJ , TO VB DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NN ."
