"In recent months , riots over high food prices have broken out around the world , amid concerns that food supply might not meet growing demand .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN JJ NNS , NNS IN JJ NN NNS VBP VBN RP IN DT NN , IN NNS IN NN NN MD RB VB VBG NN ."
"As leaders of developed nations and development banks discuss solutions , a research facility in the western U.S. is helping to improve world grain yields and fight crop diseases .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNS IN JJ NNS CC NN NNS VBP NNS , DT NN NN IN DT JJ NNP VBZ VBG TO VB NN NN NNS CC VB NN NNS ."
VOA 's Jeff Swicord takes a look at the role of technology and agricultural science at the U.S. Agricultural Research Service 's Small Grains Collection in the western state of Idaho .,B-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-geo O,NNP POS NNP NNP VBZ DT NN IN DT NN IN NN CC JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP POS JJ NNS NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
