"Norwegian authorities said the captain of a Russian trawler is dead , but 18 other members of his crew were rescued when the vessel sank in the Barents Sea .",B-gpe O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"JJ NNS VBD DT NN IN DT JJ NN VBZ JJ , CC CD JJ NNS IN PRP$ NN VBD VBN WRB DT NN VBD IN DT NNP NNP ."
"Officials at Norway 's Rescue Coordination Center said other Russian vessels picked up the 18 crew members from lifeboats after the trawler , the Topaz A , began to sink Tuesday off Bear Island in Norway 's Svalbard archipelago .",O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-tim O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O,"NNS IN NNP POS NNP NNP NNP VBD JJ JJ NNS VBD RP DT CD NN NNS IN NNS IN DT NN , DT NNP NNP , VBD TO VB NNP IN NNP NNP IN NNP POS NNP NN ."
Helicopters took two of those rescued to a hospital on the island of Spitsbergen .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNS VBD CD IN DT VBN TO DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP .
Russian vessels are taking the others to the Norwegian mainland .,B-gpe O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,JJ NNS VBP VBG DT NNS TO DT JJ NN .
There is no information on the cause of the sinking or what caused the captain 's death .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,EX VBZ DT NN IN DT NN IN DT NN CC WP VBD DT NN POS NN .
