"The United Nations says two unarmed U.N. military observers in Ivory Coast have been attacked by supporters of President Laurent Gbagbo , the second such incident in recent days .",O B-org I-org O O O B-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP VBZ CD JJ NNP JJ NNS IN NNP NNP VBP VBN VBN IN NNS IN NNP NNP NNP , DT JJ JJ NN IN JJ NNS ."
A U.N. spokesman says dozens of young people wrecked the observers ' vehicle Thursday in the southwestern town of Gagnoa and forced them to flee .,O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBZ NNS IN JJ NNS VBD DT NNS POS NN NNP IN DT JJ NN IN NNP CC VBD PRP TO VB .
The spokesman says the observers were later evacuated by U.N. peacekeeping troops .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,DT NN VBZ DT NNS VBD RB VBN IN NNP VBG NNS .
The U.N. observers were in Gagnoa to investigate a similar attack on two unarmed U.N. personnel from the day before .,O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O B-tim I-tim O,DT NNP NNS VBD IN NNP TO VB DT JJ NN IN CD JJ NNP NNS IN DT NN RB .
"U.N. peacekeepers are in Ivory Coast to monitor a cease-fire between the government and rebels , as they engage in a peace process to resolve the country 's civil war .",B-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNS VBP IN NNP NNP TO VB DT NN IN DT NN CC NNS , IN PRP VBP IN DT NN NN TO VB DT NN POS JJ NN ."
