Iran is insisting that European negotiators meeting in Vienna acknowledge Tehran 's right to develop a full nuclear fuel cycle .,B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBG IN JJ NNS NN IN NNP VBP NNP POS NN TO VB DT JJ JJ NN NN .
"The comment from Iranian Foreign Minister Manouchehr Motakki was made Wednesday in Tehran , as European envoys met with their Iranian counterparts to explore the possibility of a new round of nuclear talks in January .",O O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"DT NN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD VBN NNP IN NNP , IN JJ NNS VBD IN PRP$ JJ NNS TO VB DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS IN NNP ."
"Diplomats from Britain , France and Germany are seeking guarantees that Iran will continue its suspension of its suspect uranium enrichment program .",O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN NNP , NNP CC NNP VBP VBG NNS IN NNP MD VB PRP$ NN IN PRP$ JJ NN NN NN ."
"For its part , Tehran says Wednesday 's talks should lead to the establishment of a timetable for the full resumption of nuclear fuel cycle work .",O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN PRP$ NN , NNP VBZ NNP POS NNS MD VB TO DT NN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NN NN NN ."
Wednesday 's talks are the first contact between the two sides since August .,B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,NNP POS NNS VBP DT JJ NN IN DT CD NNS IN NNP .
The United States alleges Iran 's nuclear work is a cover for secret efforts to develop an atomic bomb .,O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNPS VBZ NNP POS JJ NN VBZ DT NN IN JJ NNS TO VB DT JJ NN .
Tehran says its research is aimed at developing sources of electricity .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ PRP$ NN VBZ VBN IN VBG NNS IN NN .
