"The offices of Turkey 's ruling Justice and Development Party were bombed Wednesday in Istanbul , wounding two people .",O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O,"DT NNS IN NNP POS NN NNP CC NNP NNP VBD VBN NNP IN NNP , VBG CD NNS ."
"Separately , in southeastern Turkey , reports say Kurdish rebels have killed at least three soldiers during a government military operation .",O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , IN JJ NNP , NNS VBP NNP NNS VBP VBN IN JJS CD NNS IN DT NN JJ NN ."
At least four other soldiers were reported wounded in the ambush in Sirnak province near Iraq .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O,IN JJS CD JJ NNS VBD VBN VBN IN DT NN IN NNP NN IN NNP .
"Earlier , a Turkish policeman died after Kurdish rebels attacked a police station in Bingol province .",O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"RB , DT JJ NN VBD IN NNP NNS VBD DT NN NN IN NNP NN ."
The attacks follow a week of daily clashes between Kurdish protesters and security forces in mainly Kurdish parts of the country .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP DT NN IN JJ NNS IN NNP NNS CC NN NNS IN RB JJ NNS IN DT NN .
"At least 16 people have been killed in the unrest , which began after a funeral for 14 rebels of the Kurdistan Workers Party killed by the security forces .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O,"IN JJS CD NNS VBP VBN VBN IN DT NN , WDT VBD IN DT NN IN CD NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP VBN IN DT NN NNS ."
"Turkey 's prime minister , Recep Tayyip Erdogan , Tuesday appealed for calm and national unity .",B-org O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP , NNP VBD IN NN CC JJ NN ."
