A group of Burmese exiles is in New Zealand to ask government and labor leaders to pressure Rangoon 's military leaders to implement democratic reforms .,O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN JJ NNS VBZ IN NNP NNP TO VB NN CC NN NNS TO VB NNP POS JJ NNS TO VB JJ NNS .
The group is expected to urge officials to support growing calls to deny Rangoon the chair of the Association of Southeast Asian Nations ( ASEAN ) in 2006 if it fails to carry out democratic reforms .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-org O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBN TO VB NNS TO VB VBG NNS TO VB NNP DT NN IN DT NNP IN NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP RRB IN CD IN PRP VBZ TO VB RP JJ NNS .
"New Zealand currently exports nearly $ 5 million in goods annually to Burma , mainly in dairy products .",B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"NNP NNP RB VBZ RB $ CD CD IN NNS RB TO NNP , RB IN NN NNS ."
"Trade unions president Ross Wilson is calling on Wellington to join the international campaign against Burma , calling it "" the forgotten country . """,O O O B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNS NN NNP NNP VBZ VBG IN NNP TO VB DT JJ NN IN NNP , VBG PRP LQU DT VBN NN . LQU"
New Zealand 's Foreign Minister Phil Goff says his government has consistently expressed its concerns directly to Burma 's military rulers about its human rights record .,B-geo I-geo O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP POS NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP$ NN VBZ RB VBN PRP$ NNS RB TO NNP POS JJ NNS IN PRP$ JJ NNS NN .
But he says broad economic sanctions will only cause suffering to Burma 's children .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,CC PRP VBZ JJ JJ NNS MD RB VB NN TO NNP POS NNS .
