"Iran 's president says other countries besides Britain , France and Germany have offered to enter talks on Iran 's nuclear activities , and Tehran is considering their offers .",B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-org O O O O O,"NNP POS NN VBZ JJ NNS IN NNP , NNP CC NNP VBP VBN TO VB NNS IN NNP POS JJ NNS , CC NNP VBZ VBG PRP$ NNS ."
"Without giving further details , Mahmoud Ahmadinejad told Iranian media that the door is open for other states to enter the talks .",O O O O O B-per I-per O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN VBG JJ NNS , NNP NNP VBD JJ NNS IN DT NN VBZ JJ IN JJ NNS TO VB DT NNS ."
But he cautioned that Iran will never accept any negotiations that challenge its right to peaceful nuclear energy .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC PRP VBD IN NNP MD RB VB DT NNS WDT VBP PRP$ NN TO JJ JJ NN .
"In Moscow , Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov dismissed speculation that his country might enter the talks .",O B-geo O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NN IN PRP$ NN MD VB DT NNS ."
He said Russia intends to move along a parallel path to achieve a result in everyone 's interest .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD NNP VBZ TO VB IN DT JJ NN TO VB DT NN IN DT POS NN .
"On Wednesday , Mr. ElBaradei expressed optimism that talks between European negotiators and Iran would resume soon .",O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"IN NNP , NNP NNP VBD NN IN NNS IN JJ NNS CC NNP MD VB RB ."
Iran denies charges that it is secretly trying to build nuclear weapons .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ NNS IN PRP VBZ RB VBG TO VB JJ NNS .
