"U.S. Defense Secretary Donald Rumsfeld says the Pentagon hopes to bring home some 20,000 troops from Iraq after next week 's parliamentary elections there .",B-org I-org O B-per I-per O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT NNP VBZ TO VB NN DT CD NNS IN NNP IN JJ NN POS JJ NNS RB .
Mr. Rumsfeld said Thursday the move would reverse a troop build-up aimed at preventing attacks ahead of the Iraqi vote .,B-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,NNP NNP VBD NNP DT NN MD VB DT NN NN VBN IN VBG NNS RB IN DT JJ NN .
"Separately , military officials said they may cancel the deployment of two brigades to Iraq in coming weeks .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"RB , JJ NNS VBD PRP MD VB DT NN IN CD NNS TO NNP IN VBG NNS ."
"Meanwhile , Iraqi militants in an Internet statement claimed to have killed an American security consultant , Ronald Schulz , taken hostage this week .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O,"RB , JJ NNS IN DT NNP NN VBD TO VB VBN DT JJ NN NN , NNP NNP , VBN NN DT NN ."
The White House said it could not confirm the claim .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBD PRP MD RB VB DT NN .
"Four Western peace activists are also being held by militants , who have threatened to kill them Saturday , unless Iraqi prisoners are released .",O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-gpe O O O O,"CD JJ NN NNS VBP RB VBG VBN IN NNS , WP VBP VBN TO VB PRP NNP , IN JJ NNS VBP VBN ."
"Also Thursday , a suicide bomber blew himself up on a Baghdad bus , killing at least 30 people .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"RB NNP , DT NN NN VBD PRP RP IN DT NNP NN , VBG IN JJS CD NNS ."
