"President Bush is celebrating the Thanksgiving holiday at his ranch in Crawford , Texas , as protesters demonstrate nearby despite new ordinances against parking cars or camping in the area .",B-per I-per O O O B-org O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBG DT NNP NN IN PRP$ NN IN NNP , NNP , IN NNS VBP JJ IN JJ NNS IN NN NNS CC NN IN DT NN ."
"Before having dinner with his family , Mr. Bush made phone calls to members of the U.S. Armed Forces , including personnel in Afghanistan , Iraq , and at sea .",O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O,"IN VBG NN IN PRP$ NN , NNP NNP VBD NN NNS TO NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNS , VBG NNS IN NNP , NNP , CC IN NN ."
A presidential spokeswoman said he wished them a happy holiday and thanked them for their service on behalf of the American people .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT JJ NN VBD PRP VBD PRP DT JJ NN CC VBD PRP IN PRP$ NN IN NN IN DT JJ NNS .
"Meanwhile , a small group of anti-war protesters a few kilometers from the ranch ate an Iraqi-style meal for Thanksgiving .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,"RB , DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS DT JJ NNS IN DT NN VBD DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
"On Wednesday , about a dozen were arrested near the ranch for criminal trespassing and obstructing a highway passageway .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , IN DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NN IN JJ NN CC VBG DT NN NN ."
"Among them was Daniel Ellsberg , a former defense official turned anti-war protester , who released secret documents about the Vietnam War to the press in 1971 .",O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-tim O,"IN PRP VBD NNP NNP , DT JJ NN NN VBD JJ NN , WP VBD JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNP TO DT NN IN CD ."
