Michael Jackson is considering legal action to oppose an upcoming auction of Jackson family memorabilia .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBG JJ NN TO VB DT JJ NN IN NNP NN NNS .
"Scheduled to take place May 30 and 31 in Las Vegas , Nevada , the auction will feature more than 1,100 items .",O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"VBN TO VB NN NNP CD CC CD IN NNP NNP , NNP , DT NN MD VB JJR IN CD NNS ."
"Included are Michael 's gold record for his Thriller album , handwritten lyrics for the Jackson Five 's hit single "" ABC , "" and an autographed program for the Jacksons ' "" Victory "" tour .",O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per B-tim O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-eve O O O,"VBN VBP NNP POS NN NN IN PRP$ NN NN , JJ NNS IN DT NNP CD POS NN JJ LQU NNP , LQU CC DT JJ NN IN DT NNPS POS LQU NNP LQU NN ."
"Michael Jackson 's spokesperson Raymone K. Bain says the singer was unaware of the auction , and is upset that his memorabilia is included among the items .",B-per I-per O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP POS NN NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT NN VBD JJ IN DT NN , CC VBZ VBN IN PRP$ NN VBZ VBN IN DT NNS ."
"Arlan Ettinger , founder and president of Guernsey 's Auction House , says a Florida-based luggage transportation company owns the items .",B-per I-per O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP , NN CC NN IN NNP POS NNP NNP , VBZ DT JJ NN NN NN VBZ DT NNS ."
Michael Jackson has been living in Las Vegas while he evaluates proposals for a professional comeback .,B-per I-per O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN VBG IN NNP NNP IN PRP VBZ NNS IN DT JJ NN .
