Russian President Dmitri Medvedev reiterated Saturday that he may seek re-election when his term is up in 2012 .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP IN PRP MD VB NN WRB PRP$ NN VBZ RB IN CD .
"Mr. Medvedev told a Norwegian newspaper , Aftenposten , he would consider a bid to stay in power if it were necessary to continue the political course that began with Prime Minister Vladimir Putin 's administration .",B-per I-per O O B-gpe O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O,"NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN , NNP , PRP MD VB DT NN TO VB IN NN IN PRP VBD JJ TO VB DT JJ NN WDT VBD IN NNP NNP NNP NNP POS NN ."
He also said his work would have to be acceptable to Russian citizens and poised to achieve results in a new term .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP RB VBD PRP$ NN MD VB TO VB JJ TO JJ NNS CC VBN TO VB NNS IN DT JJ NN .
"Late last year Mr. Medvedev said he will review the situation with Mr. Putin , and the longtime allies will decide together on a potential presidential run .",O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB JJ NN NNP NNP VBD PRP MD VB DT NN IN NNP NNP , CC DT JJ NNS MD VB RB IN DT JJ JJ NN ."
"Mr. Putin served as president from 2000 to 2008 , leaving office after serving the two consecutive terms allowed by Russia 's constitution .",B-per I-per O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,"NNP NNP VBD IN NN IN CD TO CD , VBG NN IN VBG DT CD JJ NNS VBN IN NNP POS NN ."
He would be eligible to run again in 2012 .,O O O O O O O O B-tim O,PRP MD VB JJ TO VB RB IN CD .
Candidates running for president in 2012 will be seeking a new six-year term approved by Russian lawmakers in 2009 .,O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-tim O,NNS VBG IN NN IN CD MD VB VBG DT JJ JJ NN VBN IN JJ NNS IN CD .
