U.S.-led coalition forces have bombed suspected Taleban positions in southern Afghanistan after two British soldiers and their Afghan interpreter were killed in an attack by insurgents .,O O O O O O B-org O O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN NNS VBP VBN JJ NNP NNS IN JJ NNP IN CD JJ NNS CC PRP$ JJ NN VBD VBN IN DT NN IN NNS .
Four coalition troops were also wounded in the battle Saturday night on a base in the Sangin district of Helmand province .,O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O,CD NN NNS VBD RB VBN IN DT NN NNP NN IN DT NN IN DT NNP NN IN NNP NN .
Provincial officials say Afghan forces killed 12 Taleban fighters in the same district Saturday .,O O O B-gpe O O O B-org O O O O O B-tim O,JJ NNS VBP JJ NNS VBN CD NNP NNS IN DT JJ NN NNP .
It is not clear if the rebels were involved in the attack on the British base .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,PRP VBZ RB JJ IN DT NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN .
Britain has more than 3000 troops in southern Afghanistan taking part in a U.S.-led offensive ( dubbed Operation Mountain Thrust ) against Taleban insurgents .,B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-org O O,NNP VBZ JJR IN CD NNS IN JJ NNP VBG NN IN DT JJ NN LRB VBD NNP NNP NNP RRB IN NNP NNS .
It is the largest anti-Taleban offensive in Afghanistan since the Taleban regime was ousted from power in 2001 .,O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org O O O O O O B-tim O,PRP VBZ DT JJS JJ NN IN NNP IN DT NNP NN VBD VBN IN NN IN CD .
"More than 10,000 coalition and Afghan troops are taking part in the offensive that began in May .",O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,JJR IN CD NN CC JJ NNS VBP VBG NN IN DT NN WDT VBD IN NNP .
