"Two suspected terrorists being held at the U.S. naval base in Guantanamo Bay , Cuba will appear before a military tribunal this week .",O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"CD JJ NNS VBG VBN IN DT NNP JJ NN IN NNP NNP , NNP MD VB IN DT JJ NN DT NN ."
Preliminary hearings will be held Wednesday in the cases of Canadian-born Omar Ahmed Khadr and Yemeni national Ali Hamza Ahmad al-Bahlul .,O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O B-gpe O B-per I-per I-per I-per O,JJ NNS MD VB VBN NNP IN DT NNS IN JJ NNP NNP NNP CC JJ NN NNP NNP NNP NNP .
Khadr was just 15 when he was captured in Afghanistan for allegedly killing a U.S. serviceman while fighting with al Qaida militants .,B-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O B-org I-org O O,NNP VBD RB CD WRB PRP VBD VBN IN NNP IN RB VBG DT NNP NN IN VBG IN NNP NNP NNS .
Officials say al-Bahlul was commissioned by al Qaida leader Osama bin Laden to produce propaganda video .,O O B-per O O O B-org I-org O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O,NNS VBP NNP VBD VBN IN NNP NNP NN NNP NNP NNP TO VB NN NN .
"During a hearing last August , he claimed membership in al Qaida and asked to represent himself .",O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O,"IN DT NN JJ NNP , PRP VBD NN IN NNP NNP CC VBD TO VB PRP ."
Critics have argued the hearings should be postponed until the U.S. Supreme Court rules on the constitutionality of the military tribunals in a related case later this year .,O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,NNS VBP VBN DT NNS MD VB VBN IN DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ IN DT NN IN DT JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN RB DT NN .
