The race for Iraq 's new prime minister has tightened after one of two top Shi'ite candidates dropped out of the contest .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN NNP POS JJ JJ NN VBZ VBN IN CD IN CD JJ NNP NNS VBD IN IN DT NN .
The party representing Interim Finance Minister Adel Abdul-Mahdi says it withdrew his name Tuesday to preserve unity in the United Iraqi Alliance .,O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-org B-gpe B-org O,DT NN VBG NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBD PRP$ NN NNP TO VB NN IN DT NNP JJ NNP .
The Shi'ite group won 48 percent of the vote in last month 's election for a national assembly .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBD CD NN IN DT NN IN JJ NN POS NN IN DT JJ NN .
"This leaves Ibrahim al-Jaafari , a former London-based opposition figure , as the likely new front-runner .",O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT VBZ NNP NNP , DT JJ JJ NN NN , IN DT JJ JJ NN ."
"Mr. al-Jaafari told the Associated Press Tuesday that if he becomes the new prime minister , he would not push for a U.S. withdrawal from Iraq any time soon .",B-per I-per O O B-org I-org B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD DT NNP NNP NNP IN IN PRP VBZ DT JJ JJ NN , PRP MD RB VB IN DT NNP NN IN NNP DT NN RB ."
"Meanwhile , the U.S. military says an American soldier was killed in action Tuesday in the restive Anbar province , west of Baghdad .",O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O,"RB , DT NNP NN VBZ DT JJ NN VBD VBN IN NN NNP IN DT JJ NNP NN , NN IN NNP ."
