"President Hamid Karzai 's spokesman says the Afghan leader respects U.S. President Barack Obama 's decision to replace the U.S. and NATO commander in Afghanistan , General Stanley McChrystal .",B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O B-org O O B-geo O B-org I-org I-org O,"NNP NNP NNP POS NN VBZ DT JJ NN VBZ NNP NNP NNP NNP POS NN TO VB DT NNP CC NNP NN IN NNP , NNP NNP NNP ."
"Waheed Omar told reporters Wednesday that President Karzai looks forward to working with McChrystal 's replacement , General David Petraeus , who has been the head of U.S. Central Command .",B-per I-per O O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O B-org O O O B-org B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,"NNP NNP VBD NNS NNP IN NNP NNP VBZ RB TO VBG IN NNP POS NN , NNP NNP NNP , WP VBZ VBN DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP ."
President Obama announced McChrystal 's resignation Wednesday after the U.S. general was summoned to the White House to explain disparaging comments he made about the president and other top administration officials in an article published in Rolling Stone magazine .,B-per I-per O B-org O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O,NNP NNP VBD NNP POS NN NNP IN DT NNP NN VBD VBN TO DT NNP NNP TO VB VBG NNS PRP VBD IN DT NN CC JJ JJ NN NNS IN DT NN VBN IN NNP NNP NN .
"Earlier in the day , President Karzai and other Afghan officials pledged support for McChrystal , warning that his removal would hurt counter-insurgency efforts .",O O O B-tim O B-per I-per O O B-gpe O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,"RBR IN DT NN , NNP NNP CC JJ JJ NNS VBD NN IN NNP , VBG IN PRP$ NN MD VB NN NNS ."
"Afghan Defense Ministry spokesman General Mohammad Zahir Azimi said there have been many positive changes since McChrystal took command , including a decrease in civilian casualties .",B-gpe B-org I-org O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NN NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD EX VBP VBN JJ JJ NNS IN NNP VBD NN , VBG DT NN IN JJ NNS ."
