Pakistani warplanes have bombed suspected Taliban positions in the country 's northwest .,B-gpe O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN JJ NNP NNS IN DT NN POS NN .
Government officials say at least 19 militants were killed .,O O O O O O O O O O,NN NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN .
The officials say the air strikes Sunday targeted insurgent hideouts in the Orakzai tribal region near the Afghan border .,O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O,DT NNS VBP DT NN NNS NNP VBD JJ NNS IN DT NNP JJ NN IN DT JJ NN .
Independent confirmation of the casualties is impossible because media access to the region is restricted .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN IN DT NNS VBZ JJ IN NNS NN TO DT NN VBZ VBN .
"Since March , Pakistani forces have been carrying out an anti-Taliban offensive in Orakzai to target militants believed to have fled an earlier offensive in South Waziristan .",B-tim I-tim O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"IN NNP , JJ NNS VBP VBN VBG RP DT JJ NN IN NNP TO VB NNS VBN TO VB VBN DT JJR NN IN NNP NNP ."
