"Paul Wolfowitz , the United States nominee to lead the World Bank , says he will not pursue a strictly American agenda as president of the global organization .",B-per I-per O O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP , DT NNP NNPS NN TO VB DT NNP NNP , VBZ PRP MD RB VB DT RB JJ NN IN NN IN DT JJ NN ."
"In an interview published in Sunday 's Washington Post , Mr. Wolfowitz said Washington has an important voice in the 184-nation body , but he would be responsive to the entire membership .",O O O O O B-tim O B-org I-org O B-per B-org O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN VBN IN NNP POS NNP NNP , NNP NNP VBD NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN , CC PRP MD VB JJ TO DT JJ NN ."
Mr. Wolfowitz said he understood European concerns that senior management of the Bank adequately represent the diverse organization and the importance of the Bank 's work in Africa .,B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP VBD PRP VBD JJ NNS WDT JJ NN IN DT NNP RB VBP DT JJ NN CC DT NN IN DT NNP POS NN IN NNP .
He said the World Bank 's mission of reducing poverty and promoting economic development helps advance freedom and democracy throughout the world .,O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT NNP NNP POS NN IN VBG NN CC VBG JJ NN VBZ NN NN CC NN IN DT NN .
Critics say Mr. Wolfowitz does not have a background in poverty reduction and economic development and they question his role as a leading architect of the U.S.-led war in Iraq .,O O B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNS VBP NNP NNP VBZ RB VB DT NN IN NN NN CC JJ NN CC PRP VBP PRP$ NN IN DT VBG NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
World Bank directors are expected to vote on his nomination later this week .,B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,NNP NNP NNS VBP VBN TO VB IN PRP$ NN RB DT NN .
