Officials in Haiti said Sunday that heavy flooding caused by Hurricane Ike has killed at least 47 people .,O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNP VBD NNP IN JJ NN VBN IN NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN JJS CD NNS .
Those deaths add to an estimated toll of 500 people killed during the past week by a series of storms .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP TO DT JJ NN IN CD NNS VBN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN NNS .
"Officials also said a key bridge collapsed , cutting off the central city of Gonaives from desperately needed aid supplies .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS RB VBD DT JJ NN VBD , VBG RP DT JJ NN IN NNS IN RB VBN NN NNS ."
"In the neighboring Dominican Republic , officials said a man was killed Sunday by a falling tree .",O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NNP NNP , NNS VBD DT NN VBD VBN NNP IN DT VBG NN ."
International aid efforts are under way to help thousands of Haitians who have been without food and clean water for days as a result of heavy flooding caused by the severe weather .,O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN NNS VBP IN NN TO VB NNS IN NNS WP VBP VBN IN NN CC JJ NN IN NNS IN DT NN IN JJ NN VBN IN DT JJ NN .
The European Union has announced it is giving the impoverished country $ 2.8 million to help the storm victims .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP VBZ VBG DT JJ NN $ CD CD TO VB DT NN NNS .
"Haitian President René Preval has appealed for international help , saying the situation in his country is catastrophic .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN JJ NN , VBG DT NN IN PRP$ NN VBZ JJ ."
Haiti is the Western Hemisphere 's poorest country .,B-geo O O B-org I-org O O O O,NNP VBZ DT NNP NNP POS JJS NN .
