"American skier Bode Miller will not bring home any medals from the Turin Olympics after he straddled a gate in his last race , the men 's slalom Saturday in Sestriere .",B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O,"JJ NN NNP NNP MD RB VB NN DT NNS IN DT NNP NNPS IN PRP VBD DT NN IN PRP$ JJ NN , DT NNS POS NN NNP IN NNP ."
"Miller , last year 's overall World Cup Alpine ski champion , had hoped to win as many as five medals at the Winter Games .",B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP , JJ NN POS JJ NNP NNP NNP NN NN , VBD VBN TO VB RB JJ IN CD NNS IN DT NNP NNPS ."
"However , he finished fifth in the downhill , did not finish the men 's combined event or super-giant slalom , and finished seventh in the giant slalom .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , PRP VBD RB IN DT NN , VBD RB VB DT NNS POS VBN NN CC JJ NN , CC VBD JJ IN DT JJ NN ."
"Miller 's teammate , Combined gold medalist Ted Ligety , was also disqualified in the slalom along with Italian fan favorite Giorgio Rocca and several other skiers .",B-per O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O,"NNP POS NN , JJ NN NN NNP NNP , VBD RB VBN IN DT NN IN IN JJ NN JJ NNP NNP CC JJ JJ NNS ."
