Pakistani President Pervez Musharraf says he will discuss the contentious issue of Kashmir with Indian leaders during his visit to India next week .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP MD VB DT JJ NN IN NNP IN JJ NNS IN PRP$ NN TO NNP JJ NN .
"Speaking to a gathering of students in Islamabad Saturday , Mr. Musharraf said talks on Kashmir will be more important than cricket during his visit .",O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"VBG TO DT NN IN NNS IN NNP NNP , NNP NNP VBD NNS IN NNP MD VB RBR JJ IN NN IN PRP$ NN ."
"The Pakistani leader is visiting India to watch his nation 's cricket team , which has been on a tour of India .",O B-gpe O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT JJ NN VBZ VBG NNP TO VB PRP$ NN POS NN NN , WDT VBZ VBN IN DT NN IN NNP ."
Relations between the two South Asian nuclear rivals have improved since they launched a peace process last year .,O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP IN DT CD NNP NNP JJ NNS VBP VBN IN PRP VBD DT NN NN JJ NN .
"Mr. Musharraf said a bus service between Indian- and Pakistani-controlled Kashmir , inaugurated Thursday , is a step toward reducing tension .",B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O B-tim O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD DT NN NN IN NNP CC JJ NNP , JJ NNP , VBZ DT NN IN VBG NN ."
