Public opinion polls indicate Americans are split in their views of local and federal government response to Hurricane Katrina .,O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN NNS VBP NNS VBP VBN IN PRP$ NNS IN JJ CC JJ NN NN TO NNP NNP .
"A recent Gallup survey reports 42 percent of Americans say President Bush did a "" bad "" or "" terrible "" job responding to the disaster .",O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNP NN VBZ CD NN IN NNS VBP NNP NNP VBD DT LQU JJ RQU CC LQU JJ LQU NN VBG TO DT NN .
"But 35 percent called his performance "" good "" or "" great . """,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC CD NN VBD PRP$ NN LQU JJ LQU CC LQU JJ . LQU
"Public opinion of local officials ' handling of the crises were more closely split , with 35 percent of people voicing a negative opinion , and 37 percent a positive view .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN IN JJ NNS POS NN IN DT NNS VBD RBR RB VBN , IN CD NN IN NNS VBG DT JJ NN , CC CD NN DT JJ NN ."
U.S. news media continue to focus on why mass evacuations and food drops in devastated areas were delayed .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NN NNS VBP TO VB IN WRB NN NNS CC NN NNS IN JJ NNS VBD VBN .
President Bush and members of Congress have pledged to investigate what went wrong in the response to the disaster .,B-per I-per O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP CC NNS IN NNP VBP VBN TO VB WP VBD JJ IN DT NN TO DT NN .
Some lawmakers have called the incident a failure of the new national emergency preparedness systems created after the September 2001 terrorist attacks .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O,DT NNS VBP VBN DT NN DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NN NN NNS VBN IN DT NNP CD JJ NNS .
