Chinese President Hu Jintao has arrived in Macau for the fifth anniversary of the former Portuguese enclave 's return to China .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NNP IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ JJ NN POS NN TO NNP .
"During a two-day visit , Mr. Hu will participate in anniversary celebrations and oversee the inauguration of Edmund Ho for a second term as Macau 's chief executive on Monday .",O O B-tim O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim O,"IN DT JJ NN , NNP NNP MD VB IN NN NNS CC VB DT NN IN NNP NNP IN DT JJ NN IN NNP POS JJ NN IN NNP ."
The Chinese president also will open a new bridge Sunday .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT JJ NN RB MD VB DT JJ NN NNP .
Macau 's once-fading economy is booming with rising tourist numbers and casino profits since the government allowed more foreign investors to run casinos .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS JJ NN VBZ VBG IN VBG NN NNS CC NN NNS IN DT NN VBD RBR JJ NNS TO VB NNS .
"There has also been a significant drop in crime since Beijing 's choice to lead the territory , Edmund Ho , put law and order at the top of his agenda .",O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"EX VBZ RB VBN DT JJ NN IN NN IN NNP POS NN TO VB DT NN , NNP NNP , VBD NN CC NN IN DT NN IN PRP$ NN ."
