"The Afghan Defense Ministry says Afghan and NATO forces have killed , wounded or detained hundreds of Taliban insurgents during this week 's battle to push the rebels out from the southern town of Musa Qala .",O B-gpe B-org I-org O B-gpe O B-org O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"DT JJ NNP NNP VBZ JJ CC NNP NNS VBP VBN , VBN CC VBN NNS IN NNP NNS IN DT NN POS NN TO VB DT NNS RP IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP ."
A spokesman told reporters Thursday that several rebel commanders and foreign fighters were among those killed during the successful operation .,O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD NNS NNP IN JJ NN NNS CC JJ NNS VBD IN DT VBN IN DT JJ NN .
The spokesman said he could not provide exact casualty figures because bodies are still being collected .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD PRP MD RB VB JJ NN NNS IN NNS VBP RB VBG VBN .
He said Afghan and NATO forces also bombed a Taliban meeting in the mountains of Sangin and Musa Qala district that led to high casualties .,O O B-gpe O B-org O O O O B-org O O O O O B-org O B-org I-org O O O O O O O,PRP VBD JJ CC NNP NNS RB VBD DT NNP NN IN DT NNS IN NNP CC NNP NNP NN WDT VBD TO JJ NNS .
"The Taliban took control of Musa Qala , in Helmand province , about eight months ago .",O B-org O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O O O B-tim O O O,"DT NNP VBD NN IN NNP NNP , IN NNP NN , IN CD NNS RB ."
"In other violence , Afghan Interior Ministry said a landmine blast killed six civilians and wounded six others in neighboring Uruzgan province Thursday .",O O O O B-gpe B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O,"IN JJ NN , JJ NNP NNP VBD DT NN NN VBD CD NNS CC VBD CD NNS IN JJ NNP NN NNP ."
