Iraqi officials say a series of car bombs north of Baghdad has killed 60 people and injured dozens of others .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP DT NN IN NN NNS RB IN NNP VBZ VBN CD NNS CC JJ NNS IN NNS .
"Officials say the police chief in the town of Balad was among those wounded in the blasts targeting a bank , a market and a third location .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP DT NN NN IN DT NN IN NNP VBD IN DT VBN IN DT NNS VBG DT NN , DT NN CC DT JJ NN ."
"Earlier , U.S. forces conducted a pre-dawn raid on the Baghdad home of influential Sunni Arab politician Adnan al-Dulaimi .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per I-per O,"RB , NNP NNS VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NN IN JJ NNP NNP NN NNP NNP ."
A military spokeswoman told VOA that four men were detained and a large cache of weapons and ammunition was confiscated .,O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBD NNP IN CD NNS VBD VBN CC DT JJ NN IN NNS CC NN VBD VBN .
"Mr. al-Dulaimi , who heads a leading Sunni Arab political organization ( the Conference for Iraq 's People ) , said he was shocked by the raid .",B-per I-per O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP , WP VBZ DT VBG NNP NNP JJ NN LRB DT NN IN NNP POS NNS RRB , VBD PRP VBD VBN IN DT NN ."
"Elsewhere , the U.S. military reported five American soldiers were killed Wednesday in a roadside bomb blast in the western town of Ramadi .",O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"RB , DT NNP NN VBD CD JJ NNS VBD VBN NNP IN DT NN NN NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
