An Iranian news report says Iran has formally asked the European Union to reopen stalled talks on its nuclear program .,O B-gpe O O O B-geo O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN NN VBZ NNP VBZ RB VBN DT NNP NNP TO VB VBN NNS IN PRP$ JJ NN .
"The Fars news agency said a letter from top Iranian nuclear negotiator Ali Larijani has been delivered to Britain , France and Germany , welcoming the resumption of "" rational and constructive "" talks .",O B-org O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NN NN VBD DT NN IN JJ JJ JJ NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN VBN TO NNP , NNP CC NNP , VBG DT NN IN LQU JJ CC JJ LQU NNS ."
The EU has not publicly responded to the offer .,O B-org O O O O O O O O,DT NNP VBZ RB RB VBD TO DT NN .
"Talks between the two sides broke down in August , when Tehran rejected a European offer of economic and political incentives in return for scrapping its nuclear fuel program .",O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-org O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN DT CD NNS VBD RP IN NNP , WRB NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN JJ CC JJ NNS IN NN IN VBG PRP$ JJ NN NN ."
"Instead , Tehran resumed uranium conversion activities , and the International Atomic Energy Agency declared Tehran was not cooperating with nuclear inspectors as required under international treaty .",O O B-org O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , NNP VBD NN NN NNS , CC DT NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP VBD RB VBG IN JJ NNS IN VBN IN JJ NN ."
"The Iranian Foreign Ministry said Sunday that Tehran allowed IAEA inspectors access to a high-security military site last week , to counter U.S. suspicions it is trying to develop nuclear weapons .",O B-gpe B-org I-org O B-tim O B-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNP NNP VBD NNP IN NNP VBD NNP NNS NN TO DT JJ JJ NN JJ NN , TO VB NNP NNS PRP VBZ VBG TO VB JJ NNS ."
