"The United Nations War Crimes Tribunal in The Hague has released indictments against two Bosnian Serb generals , as news agencies report that one of them is about to surrender to the court .",O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-org I-org O O O O O B-gpe I-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP IN DT NNP VBZ VBN NNS IN CD JJ JJ NNS , IN NN NNS VBP IN CD IN PRP VBZ IN TO VB TO DT NN ."
"The indictment , made public Thursday , charges Milan Gvero and Radivoje Miletic with the murder , persecution and deportation of Muslim civilians in Bosnia-Herzegovina .",O O O O O B-tim O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O,"DT NN , VBN JJ NNP , VBZ NNP NNP CC NNP NNP IN DT NN , NN CC NN IN NNP NNS IN NNP ."
"The indictment centers on events that occurred in the Muslim enclave of Srebrenica , where Bosnian Serb forces killed more than 7,000 men and boys in 1995 .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O B-gpe I-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"DT NN VBZ IN NNS WDT VBD IN DT NNP NN IN NNP , WRB JJ JJ NNS VBD JJR IN CD NNS CC NNS IN CD ."
News agencies reported that General Gvero flew to The Hague Thursday to surrender .,O O O O B-org I-org O O O B-org B-tim O O O,NN NNS VBD IN NNP NNP VBD TO DT NNP NNP TO VB .
"The tribunal has not confirmed the reports , nor has it given any information on General Miletic 's intentions .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O,"DT NN VBZ RB VBN DT NNS , CC VBZ PRP VBN DT NN IN NNP NNP POS NNS ."
