U.S. Hispanic advocates are expessing concern that illegal immigrants affected by Hurricane Katrina could be at risk of deportation if they seek aid from the federal government .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP JJ NNS VBP VBG NN IN JJ NNS VBN IN NNP NNP MD VB IN NN IN NN IN PRP VBP NN IN DT JJ NN .
They cite a recent case of two immigrants from Central America who were part of a group of evacuees transported to the U.S. eastern state of West Virginia earlier this month .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O,PRP VBP DT JJ NN IN CD NNS IN NNP NNP WP VBD NN IN DT NN IN NNS VBN TO DT NNP JJ NN IN NNP NNP RBR DT NN .
The two men were taken into custody by immigration agents after authorities received a complaint that one of them had sexually assaulted a female passenger .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT CD NNS VBD VBN IN NN IN NN NNS IN NNS VBD DT NN IN CD IN PRP VBD RB VBN DT JJ NN .
The Department of Homeland Security has encouraged illegal immigrants displaced by the hurricane to come forward and seek federal aid .,O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP IN NNP NNP VBZ VBN JJ NNS VBN IN DT NN TO VB RB CC VB JJ NN .
Some Democratic lawmakers say the department should promise immigrants they will not share their information with law enforcement agencies .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNS VBP DT NN MD VB NNS PRP MD RB VB PRP$ NN IN NN NN NNS .
