"Yasser Arafat returned to Ramallah on Friday , where he was laid to rest as tens-of-thousands of Palestinians came to say their final farewell .",B-per I-per O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD TO VB IN NNP , WRB PRP VBD VBN TO VB IN NNS IN NNS VBD TO VB PRP$ JJ NN ."
Yasser Arafat was coming home Friday to his Muqata compound in Ramallah .,B-per I-per O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O B-geo O,NNP NNP VBD VBG NN NNP TO PRP$ NNP NN IN NNP .
"Tens-of-thousands of Palestinians , mostly young men , but also women , and entire families gathered at the Muqata hours before his body arrived for burial .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN NNS , RB JJ NNS , CC RB NNS , CC JJ NNS VBD IN DT NNP NNS IN PRP$ NN VBD IN NN ."
"Even before the helicopter carrying his remains touched down , the Muqata had become a sea of bodies .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"RB IN DT NN VBG PRP$ NNS VBD RB , DT NNP VBD VBN DT NN IN NNS ."
Palestinians expressed a combination of grief at the loss of Palestinian leader Yasser Arafat and pride for him as a leader .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O,NNS VBD DT NN IN NN IN DT NN IN JJ NN NNP NNP CC NN IN PRP IN DT NN .
Young men with black-and-white-checked kaffyieh scarves wrapped around their heads and necks joined in spontaneous chants in praise of Yasser Arafat .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O,JJ NNS IN JJ NN VBZ VBN IN PRP$ NNS CC NNS VBD IN JJ NNS IN NN IN NNP NNP .
"Unlike the stately ceremony provided for the the Palestinian leader in France , or the military funeral in Cairo , this was the people 's farewell .",O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN VBN IN DT DT JJ NN IN NNP , CC DT JJ NN IN NNP , DT VBD DT NNS POS NN ."
