Arabic-language media report that Iraq 's government has accused Iran of siphoning Iraqi oil from wells near their shared border .,O O O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS NN IN NNP POS NN VBZ VBN NNP IN VBG JJ NN IN NNS IN PRP$ JJ NN .
The news reports say the Iraqi government has sent a letter to the Iranian embassy in Baghdad demanding that Tehran stop encroaching on the oil fields .,O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O,DT NN NNS VBP DT JJ NN VBZ VBN DT NN TO DT JJ NN IN NNP VBG IN NNP VB VBG IN DT NN NNS .
"A London-based Arabic newspaper , Al-Hayat , quotes an Iraqi foreign ministry official , Muhammad Mahmud al-Hajj , as saying Baghdad will soon send a delegation to Iran to discuss the issue .",O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,"DT JJ NNP NN , NNP , VBZ DT JJ JJ NN NN , NNP NNP NNP , IN VBG NNP MD RB VB DT NN TO NNP TO VB DT NN ."
The Iraqi official says Baghdad wants to negotiate a solution to its border dispute with Tehran and to reach an agreement for developing joint oil wells in the border region .,O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBZ NNP VBZ TO VB DT NN TO PRP$ NN NN IN NNP CC TO VB DT NN IN VBG JJ NN NNS IN DT NN NN .
"Iraq and Iran have for decades claimed sovereignty over the mouth of the Shatt al-Arab waterway , which forms the southern-most section of their common border .",B-gpe O B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP CC NNP VBP IN NNS VBN NN IN DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NN , WDT VBZ DT JJ NN IN PRP$ JJ NN ."
