The lead lawyer for former Iraqi dictator Saddam Hussein and his seven co-defendants says the defense team will not appear for the next court session because of security concerns .,O O O O O B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN NN IN JJ JJ NN NNP NNP CC PRP$ CD NNS VBZ DT NN NN MD RB VB IN DT JJ NN NN IN IN NN NNS .
"Khalil al-Dulaimi said Wednesday that he and his colleagues will not attend a hearing November 28 , unless they have international guarantees for their personal security .",B-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD NNP IN PRP CC PRP$ NNS MD RB VB DT NN NNP CD , IN PRP VBP JJ NNS IN PRP$ JJ NN ."
Their decision comes a day after a second member of their team was murdered in less than three weeks .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,PRP$ NN VBZ DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN PRP$ NN VBD VBN IN JJR IN CD NNS .
"Meanwhile , Iraqi police say the brother of parliament speaker Hajim al-Hassani was kidnapped late Tuesday near Kirkuk .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O B-tim O B-geo O,"RB , JJ NNS VBP DT NN IN NN NN NNP NNP VBD VBN RB NNP IN NNP ."
"Elsewhere , attacks in Baquba and Baghdad killed at least seven people .",O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O,"RB , NNS IN NNP CC NNP VBD IN JJS CD NNS ."
