French Foreign Minister Bernard Kouchner says Europe must play a bigger role in Iraq because the United States can not solve the country 's problems alone .,B-gpe O O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNP MD VB DT JJR NN IN NNP IN DT NNP NNPS MD RB VB DT NN POS NNS RB .
"Kouchner was speaking to French radio Tuesday from Baghdad , where he held three days of meetings with Iraqi leaders .",B-per O O O B-gpe O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O B-tim O O O O B-gpe O O,"NNP VBD VBG TO JJ NN NNP IN NNP , WRB PRP VBD CD NNS IN NNS IN JJ NNS ."
He is the first senior French official to visit Iraq since the U.S.-led invasion in 2003 .,O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O,PRP VBZ DT JJ JJ JJ NN TO VB NNP IN DT JJ NN IN CD .
"Kouchner called on other European foreign ministers to visit Iraq and said Sweden 's top diplomat , Karl Bildt , will make the trip soon .",B-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-per O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD IN JJ JJ JJ NNS TO VB NNP CC VBD NNP POS JJ NN , NNP NNP , MD VB DT NN RB ."
"Kouchner says that if Iraq asks for more United Nations assistance , France is ready to help .",B-per O O O B-geo O O O B-org I-org O O B-org O O O O O,"NNP VBZ IN IN NNP VBZ IN JJR NNP NNPS NN , NNP VBZ JJ TO VB ."
Former French president Jacques Chirac strongly opposed Washington 's military intervention in Iraq and limited France 's role in the country .,O B-gpe O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O B-org O O O O O O,JJ JJ NN NNP NNP RB VBD NNP POS JJ NN IN NNP CC JJ NNP POS NN IN DT NN .
"His successor , Nicholas Sarkozy , has said he wants to repair relations with the U.S. that were strained by the Iraq war .",O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O,"PRP$ NN , NNP NNP , VBZ VBN PRP VBZ TO VB NNS IN DT NNP WDT VBD VBN IN DT NNP NN ."
