"The foreign minister of France , which currently holds the presidency of the European Union , says Europe is strongly urging Russia to withdraw its troops from Georgia .",O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O,"DT JJ NN IN NNP , WDT RB VBZ DT NN IN DT NNP NNP , VBZ NNP VBZ RB VBG NNP TO VB PRP$ NNS IN NNP ."
"Lisa Bryant reports from Paris , the comment comes on the eve of an emergency NATO meeting on the crisis .",B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ IN NNP , DT NN VBZ IN DT NN IN DT NN NNP NN IN DT NN ."
"At a news conference Monday , French Foreign Minister Bernard Kouchner expressed frustration at what is seen as Russia 's slow-paced withdrawal of its forces from Georgia , despite Moscow 's claims it has begun to do so .",O O O O B-tim O B-org I-org B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN NN NNP , NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NN IN WP VBZ VBN IN NNP POS JJ NN IN PRP$ NNS IN NNP , IN NNP POS NNS PRP VBZ VBN TO VB RB ."
"Kouchner said every time France phones Russia , the answer is that the troop withdrawal will begin .",B-per O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD DT NN NNP NNS NNP , DT NN VBZ IN DT NN NN MD VB ."
But he said Paris wants it to begin today .,O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim O,CC PRP VBD NNP VBZ PRP TO VB NN .
"He noted that Moscow has signed onto a newly-brokered cease-fire with Georgia , and he said he hoped Russia understood that its signature must be respected .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD IN NNP VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , CC PRP VBD PRP VBD NNP VBD IN PRP$ NN MD VB VBN ."
"An emergency NATO meeting begins in Brussels , Tuesday .",O O B-org O O O B-geo O B-tim O,"DT NN NNP NN VBZ IN NNP , NNP ."
Foreign ministers there are expected to pledge support for Georgia 's sovereignty and territorial integrity .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,JJ NNS EX VBP VBN TO VB NN IN NNP POS NN CC JJ NN .
They are also expected to urge both sides to abide by a ceasefire agreement brokered by France last week .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,PRP VBP RB VBN TO VB DT NNS TO VB IN DT JJ NN VBN IN NNP JJ NN .
"But they are divided on what tack to take with Russia , which sent troops into swathes of Georgian territory after clashes in the breakaway region of South Ossetia earlier this month .",O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O,"CC PRP VBP VBN IN WP NN TO VB IN NNP , WDT VBD NNS IN NNS IN JJ NN IN NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP RBR DT NN ."
Russian President Dmitri Medvedev said Russian military forces would begin pulling out by midday Monday .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD JJ JJ NNS MD VB VBG RP IN NN NNP .
But Georgia at the time said it had seen no sign of troop movement .,O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC NNP IN DT NN VBD PRP VBD VBN DT NN IN NN NN .
"French President Nicolas Sarkozy said Sunday that in a telephone call to his Russian counterpart , he had warned of "" serious consequences , "" should Russia fail to implement the ceasefire deal .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP IN IN DT NN NN TO PRP$ JJ NN , PRP VBD VBN IN LQU JJ NNS , LQU MD NNP VB TO VB DT JJ NN ."
It is unclear just what those consequences may be .,O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ JJ RB WP DT NNS MD VB .
Mr. Kouchner said the French president may call for an emergency EU meeting on the Georgian crisis in the coming days .,B-per I-per O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-org O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN MD VB IN DT NN NNP NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NNS .
