Police in Afghanistan say 12 civilians were killed in two roadside bombings in two days .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,NNS IN NNP VBP CD NNS VBD VBN IN CD NN NNS IN CD NNS .
"Seven civilians , including two young children , were killed Wednesday when their car struck a bomb in southern Kandahar province .",O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"CD NNS , VBG CD JJ NNS , VBD VBN NNP WRB PRP$ NN VBD DT NN IN JJ NNP NN ."
Another roadside bombing killed five people in Farah province on Tuesday .,O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O,DT NN NN VBD CD NNS IN NNP NN IN NNP .
"In other violence , officials say 21 Taliban fighters were killed in an air strike by international forces in a remote area of southwestern Nimroz province .",O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"IN JJ NN , NNS VBP CD NNP NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN NN IN JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NNP NN ."
Provincial Governor Ghulam Dagastir Azad says the bombings targeted three militant vehicles that were reported to be traveling toward Afghan security posts along the border with Pakistan .,O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT NNS VBD CD JJ NNS WDT VBD VBN TO VB VBG IN JJ NN NNS IN DT NN IN NNP .
He says that there were no civilian casualties .,O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ IN EX VBD DT JJ NNS .
