"Michael King , a member of American Border Patrol , a citizen watchdog group , rides along US-Mexico border",B-per I-per O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP , DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP , DT NN NN NN , VBZ IN JJ NN"
A citizen group is wrapping up a month-long effort to monitor illegal immigrants crossing one section of the U.S.-Mexico border .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN NN VBZ VBG RP DT JJ NN TO VB JJ NNS VBG CD NN IN DT JJ NN .
"The Minuteman Project plans to stop monitoring illegal immigrant activity in southern Arizona by Sunday , but says it will soon expand its program to other parts of the U.S. border .",O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"DT NNP NNP VBZ TO VB VBG JJ JJ NN IN JJ NNP IN NNP , CC VBZ PRP MD RB VB PRP$ NN TO JJ NNS IN DT NNP NN ."
The volunteers say they have prevented illegal immigrants from entering the United States by reporting their location to authorities .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP PRP VBP VBN JJ NNS IN VBG DT NNP NNPS IN VBG PRP$ NN TO NNS .
Their efforts have drawn protests from human rights groups and Mexico 's government .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,PRP$ NNS VBP VBN NNS IN JJ NNS NNS CC NNP POS NN .
