A survey released Monday says a majority of Afghans believe corruption is at its worst in more than 20 years .,O O O B-tim O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,DT NN VBN NNP VBZ DT NN IN NNS VBP NN VBZ IN PRP$ JJS IN JJR IN CD NNS .
"About 60 percent of those polled said the administration of President Hamid Karzai is more corrupt than any government since the 1980s , including the Taleban and Soviet-backed communist governments .",O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-org O O O O O,"IN CD NN IN DT VBN VBD DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP VBZ RBR JJ IN DT NN IN DT NNS , VBG DT NNP CC JJ NN NNS ."
Almost all of those surveyed ( 93 percent ) said they believe paying bribes are necessary for basic public services .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,RB DT IN DT VBN LRB CD NN RRB VBD PRP VBP VBG NNS VBP JJ IN JJ JJ NNS .
About half of those survey said they had actually paid a bribe .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,IN NN IN DT NN VBD PRP VBD RB VBN DT NN .
"The organization that conducted the survey , Integrity Watch Afghanistan ( IWA ) , said the perception of corruption is so bad that it undermines the legitimacy of the government .",O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN WDT VBD DT NN , NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP RRB , VBD DT NN IN NN VBZ RB JJ IN PRP VBZ DT NN IN DT NN ."
The group also said corruption has directly affected national security .,O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN RB VBD NN VBZ RB VBN JJ NN .
The watchdog group said the growing unrest in southern Afghanistan is in part related to the inability of the government to deal with corruption .,O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN NN VBD DT VBG NN IN JJ NNP VBZ IN NN VBN TO DT NN IN DT NN TO VB IN NN .
"About 1,250 Afghans were questioned for the survey .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O,IN CD NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN .
