Lawmakers from throughout Europe have overwhelmingly approved an investigator 's report about the existence of secret U.S. prisons on the continent .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,NNS IN IN NNP VBP RB VBN DT NN POS NN IN DT NN IN JJ NNP NNS IN DT NN .
The Parliamentary Assembly of the Council of Europe Wednesday approved the report presented earlier this month by Swiss Senator Dick Marty .,O O O O O B-org O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-per I-per O,DT JJ NN IN DT NNP IN NNP NNP VBD DT NN VBN RBR DT NN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP .
"Prior to the vote , Marty said some European countries had built a wall of silence about the prisons and the human rights abuses that may have occurred there .",O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB TO DT NN , NNP VBD DT JJ NNS VBD VBN DT NN IN NN IN DT NNS CC DT JJ NNS NNS WDT MD VB VBN RB ."
"The report says there were secret U.S. prisons in Romania and Poland , but representatives of both countries denied the claim during the assembly debate .",O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ EX VBD JJ NNP NNS IN NNP CC NNP , CC NNS IN DT NNS VBD DT NN IN DT NN NN ."
Marty said his report is based on many conversations with unnamed U.S. and other intelligence sources .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,NNP VBD PRP$ NN VBZ VBN IN JJ NNS IN JJ NNP CC JJ NN NNS .
U.S. President George Bush last September acknowledged the existence of the overseas detention centers .,B-geo B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP JJ NNP VBD DT NN IN DT JJ NN NNS .
"He did not say where they were located , but he said they were by then empty .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD RB VB WRB PRP VBD VBN , CC PRP VBD PRP VBD IN RB JJ ."
