India has beaten host Australia by 72 runs and snapped the Aussies ' winning streak at 16 matches on the fourth day of their third test match in Perth .,B-org O O O B-org O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP VBZ VBN NN NNP IN CD NNS CC VBN DT NNS POS NN NN IN CD NNS IN DT JJ NN IN PRP$ JJ NN NN IN NNP .
"Resuming its second innings at 65-2 and needing 413 runs to win , Australia was all out for 340 at the WACA Cricket Ground .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,"VBG PRP$ JJ NN IN CD CC VBG CD NNS TO VB , NNP VBD DT RP IN CD IN DT NNP NNP NNP ."
"Indian bowler Irfan Pathan took three wickets while Anil Kumble , R.P. Singh and Virender Sehwag took two each for India .",B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O O B-org I-org O B-org B-per B-org I-org I-org O O O O B-geo O,"JJ NN NNP NNP VBD CD NNS IN NNP NNP , NNP NNP CC NNP NNP VBD CD DT IN NNP ."
"Australia 's Michael Clarke was the top scorer for the home side , with 81 runs before he was out .",B-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NN NN , IN CD NNS IN PRP VBD RB ."
Mitchell Johnson added another 50 runs for the home side .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD DT CD NNS IN DT NN NN .
The Australians were trying to win an unprecedented 17th straight test match .,O B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim O O O O,DT NNS VBD VBG TO VB DT JJ JJ JJ NN NN .
"The home side leads the four-match series , 2-1 .",O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN NN VBZ DT JJ NN , CD ."
The fourth test starts in Adelaide January 24th .,O O O O O B-geo B-tim I-tim O,DT JJ NN VBZ IN NNP NNP NN .
