"Iraqi authorities say at least two people were killed and six others wounded when two bombs planted on vehicles exploded Monday in the capital , Baghdad .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-geo O,"JJ NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN CC CD NNS VBD WRB CD NNS VBN IN NNS VBD NNP IN DT NN , NNP ."
Officials say one bomb was attached to a bus and a second was inside another vehicle in the mainly Shi'ite district of Shaab .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNS VBP CD NN VBD VBN TO DT NN CC DT NN VBD IN DT NN IN DT RB JJ NN IN NNP .
"Overall violence has declined in recent months in Iraq , but sectarian strife has been evident in the capital in recent days .",O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN VBZ VBN IN JJ NNS IN NNP , CC JJ NN VBZ VBN JJ IN DT NN IN JJ NNS ."
"On Friday , the leader of the main Sunni bloc in Iraq 's parliament ( Harith al-Obeidi of the National Accordance Front ) and four other people were shot dead after Friday prayers in the Yarmouk area of Baghdad .",O B-tim O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O B-per I-per O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O B-geo O,"IN NNP , DT NN IN DT JJ NNP NN IN NNP POS NN LRB NNP NNP IN DT NNP NNP NNP RRB CC CD JJ NNS VBD VBN RB IN NNP NNS IN DT NNP NN IN NNP ."
"Iraqi Prime Minster Nouri al-Maliki has ordered an investigation into that attack , which he called "" a futile attempt to incite sectarian strife . """,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN DT NN , WDT PRP VBD LQU DT JJ NN TO VB JJ NN . LQU"
