"Italy 's interior minister says almost $ 110 million has been spent on security for the Turin Winter Olympics , and that amount is expected to grow in the next few weeks .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"NNP POS JJ NN VBZ RB $ CD CD VBZ VBN VBN IN NN IN DT NNP NNP NNPS , CC DT NN VBZ VBN TO VB IN DT JJ JJ NNS ."
"Interior Minister Giuseppe Pisanu gave the first official figures for security spending Monday , and said security arrangements are on schedule .",O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT JJ JJ NNS IN NN NN NNP , CC VBD NN NNS VBP IN NN ."
"Pisanu said Italian officials are "" reasonably optimistic "" they will be able to foil any terrorist threats , although there have been no specific threats against the Olympics or Italy .",B-per O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-geo O,"NNP VBD JJ NNS VBP LQU RB JJ LQU PRP MD VB JJ TO VB DT JJ NNS , IN EX VBP VBN DT JJ NNS IN DT NNP CC NNP ."
"More than 9,000 extra officers will help protect the Games , while a center coordinating the intelligence from national and international security forces will provide surveillance .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJR IN CD JJ NNS MD VB VB DT NNPS , IN DT NN VBG DT NN IN JJ CC JJ NN NNS MD VB NN ."
"Pisanu said that Italian security will be in charge during the Olympics , though foreign security agencies will be included in the information center .",B-per O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD IN JJ NN MD VB IN NN IN DT NNS , IN JJ NN NNS MD VB VBN IN DT NN NN ."
"The Italians are drawing on their experience handling previous major events , including the funeral of Pope John Paul II at the Vatican .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O B-geo O,"DT NNS VBP VBG IN PRP$ NN VBG JJ JJ NNS , VBG DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP IN DT NNP ."
