Salvadoran President Elias Antonio Saca says his country is ending its military presence in Iraq at the end of this month .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim I-tim O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP$ NN VBZ VBG PRP$ JJ NN IN NNP IN DT NN IN DT NN .
"President Saca said Tuesday that El Salvador has fulfilled its mission in Iraq , and that the troops will leave sometime after December 31 , when the United Nations resolution that authorized the international coalition there expires .",B-per I-per O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD NNP IN NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP$ NN IN NNP , CC IN DT NNS MD VB RB IN NNP CD , WRB DT NNP NNP NN WDT VBD DT JJ NN RB VBZ ."
"El Salvador has had troops in Iraq since 2003 , as part of the coalition led by the United States .",B-per I-per O O O O B-geo B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNS IN NNP IN CD , IN NN IN DT NN VBN IN DT NNP NNPS ."
El Salvador is the only Latin American nation that still has military forces in Iraq .,B-per I-per O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP VBZ DT RB JJ JJ NN IN RB VBZ JJ NNS IN NNP .
Fighting in Iraq has killed five Salvadoran soldiers and wounded 20 others since 2003 .,O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,VBG IN NNP VBZ VBN CD JJ NNS CC VBD CD NNS IN CD .
Some 200 Salvadoran troops are stationed in Iraq .,O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O,DT CD JJ NNS VBP VBN IN NNP .
