An author of the Iraq Study Group report says a continued rise in violence in Iraq could lead to a catastrophe in the Middle East .,O O O B-geo I-geo B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NN VBZ DT JJ NN IN NN IN NNP MD VB TO DT NN IN DT NNP NNP .
"Former U.S. Senator Charles Robb of Virginia made that assessment while he and another author of the report , former U.S. Supreme Court Justice Sandra Day O'Connor , spoke Thursday to VOA .",O B-org B-per I-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org B-tim I-tim O O B-tim O B-org O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP IN NNP VBD DT NN IN PRP CC DT NN IN DT NN , JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP , VBD NNP TO NNP ."
Robb said the rising violence may lead to a failed state and that might prompt Iran and Turkey to send forces into the country .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O,NNP VBD DT VBG NN MD VB TO DT JJ NN CC DT MD VB NNP CC NNP TO VB NNS IN DT NN .
He also said there would be a huge humanitarian problem with respect to refugees .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP RB VBD EX MD VB DT JJ JJ NN IN NN TO NNS .
O'Connor said Iran has been a source of trouble in Iraq .,B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP VBD NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN NN IN NNP .
But she called for U.S. officials to hold talks with Tehran just like the United States did with the Soviet Union during the Cold War .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-org O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O,CC PRP VBD IN NNP NNS TO VB NNS IN NNP RB IN DT NNP NNPS VBD IN DT NNP NNP IN DT NNP NNP .
