A woman who has served in the U.S. Army for 33 years has become the first female to rise to the rank of four-star general in the history of the U.S. military .,O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,DT NN WP VBZ VBN IN DT NNP NNP IN CD NNS VBZ VBN DT JJ NN TO VB TO DT NN IN JJ NN IN DT NN IN DT NNP NN .
General Ann Dunwoody received the promotion Friday during a ceremony at Department of Defense headquarters [ the Pentagon ] outside Washington .,B-per I-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O B-org O O B-geo O,NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN NNP IN DT NN IN NNP IN NNP NN LRB DT NNP RRB IN NNP .
"She said that although she is the first woman to reach the rank , she knows she will not be the last .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD IN IN PRP VBZ DT JJ NN TO VB DT NN , PRP VBZ PRP MD RB VB DT JJ ."
"Defense Secretary Robert Gates , who presided over the ceremony , called Dunwoody a "" proven leader . """,B-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP , WP VBD IN DT NN , VBD NNP DT LQU VBN NN . RQU"
"U.S. President George Bush nominated Dunwoody for the post in June , and the decision was approved by the U.S. Senate .",B-org B-per I-per I-per O B-per O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP IN DT NN IN NNP , CC DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NNP NNP ."
"In her new role , General Dunwoody will take charge of the Army 's Materiel Command , which is responsible for providing arms , equipment and other logistical support for soldiers .",O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN PRP$ JJ NN , NNP NNP MD VB NN IN DT NNP POS NNP NNP , WDT VBZ JJ IN VBG NNS , NN CC JJ JJ NN IN NNS ."
