"The Chinese government has declassified almost 26,000 diplomatic files from between 1956 and 1960 and made them available for public viewing .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBZ VBN RB CD JJ NNS IN IN CD CC CD CC VBD PRP JJ IN JJ NN .
"The official Xinhua news agency reports the files contain documents , recorded conversations and telegrams from major diplomatic events during the period .",O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNP NN NN VBZ DT NNS VBP NNS , VBN NNS CC NNS IN JJ JJ NNS IN DT NN ."
"The files include documents signed by Chinese leaders Mao Zedong and Zhou Enlai and records of diplomatic efforts between China and 14 Asian , African and Latin American countries .",O O O O O O B-gpe O B-per I-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O B-gpe O O,"DT NNS VBP NNS VBN IN JJ NNS NNP NNP CC NNP NNP CC NNS IN JJ NNS IN NNP CC CD JJ , JJ CC JJ JJ NNS ."
They also include diplomatic discussions between China and both the Soviet Union and the United States .,O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo I-geo O,PRP RB VBP JJ NNS IN NNP CC DT DT NNP NNP CC DT NNP NNPS .
Xinhua reports China first declassified diplomatic files in January of 2004 and officials say they expect to declassify more in the future .,B-org O B-geo O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ NNP RB VBD JJ NNS IN NNP IN CD CC NNS VBP PRP VBP TO VB RBR IN DT NN .
The files are available to the public at the Archives Bureau in Beijing .,O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-geo O,DT NNS VBP JJ TO DT NN IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP .
