"The head of Merrill Lynch , the world 's largest brokerage firm , is "" retiring "" just a week after reporting the largest quarterly loss in the company 's 93-year history .",O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN NNP NNP , DT NN POS JJS NN NN , VBZ LQU VBG LQU RB DT NN IN VBG DT JJS JJ NN IN DT NN POS JJ NN ."
"Stan O'Neal was chief executive of Merrill Lynch for five years , and got into trouble when large investments in sub-prime mortgages went sour .",B-per I-per O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD JJ NN IN NNP NNP IN CD NNS , CC VBD IN NN WRB JJ NNS IN JJ NNS VBD JJ ."
The firm lost more than $ 2 billion in the third quarter .,O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT NN VBD JJR IN $ CD CD IN DT JJ NN .
"Meanwhile , Europe 's largest bank , UBS , says it also was hit by sub-prime problems , losing more than $ 700 million for the quarter .",O O B-geo O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"RB , NNP POS JJS NN , NNP , VBZ PRP RB VBD VBN IN JJ NNS , VBG JJR IN $ CD CD IN DT NN ."
"Banks that loaned money to home buyers with poor credit and investors who bought up securities backed by the shaky mortgages , have lost tens of billions of dollars in recent months as rising interest rates and falling home prices sparked a wave of defaults .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS WDT VBD NN TO NN NNS IN JJ NN CC NNS WP VBD RP NNS VBN IN DT JJ NNS , VBP VBN NNS IN NNS IN NNS IN JJ NNS IN VBG NN NNS CC VBG NN NNS VBD DT NN IN NNS ."
