"About 1,100 lawyers have withdrawn from the defense team of ousted Iraqi leader Saddam Hussein , following the slayings of two colleagues in the past month .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"IN CD NNS VBP VBN IN DT NN NN IN JJ JJ NN NNP NNP , VBG DT NNS IN CD NNS IN DT JJ NN ."
The lawyers say they decided to quit because neither the Iraqi government nor U.S. forces responded to their demands for protection .,O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP PRP VBD TO VB IN DT DT JJ NN CC NNP NNS VBD TO PRP$ NNS IN NN .
The lawyers say they will not be present when the trial resumes November 28 .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT NNS VBP PRP MD RB VB JJ WRB DT NN VBZ NNP CD .
The mass resignations come less than a week after a defense lawyer was gunned down in Baghdad .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NN NNS VBP JJR IN DT NN IN DT NN NN VBD VBN RP IN NNP .
The bullet-riddled body of another attorney was found in the capital in October .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT JJ NN IN DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NN IN NNP .
"Meanwhile , the U.S. military says a roadside bomb killed two U.S. Marines during combat operations on Saturday in al-Amiriyah , west of Baghdad .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O B-geo O,"RB , DT NNP NN VBZ DT NN NN VBD CD NNP NNS IN NN NNS IN NNP IN NNP , NN IN NNP ."
