"There is new flooding in a section of the southern U.S. city of New Orleans , which was already devastated by massive flooding several weeks ago .",O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,"EX VBZ JJ NN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NNP NN IN NNP NNP , WDT VBD RB VBN IN JJ NN JJ NNS RB ."
"The Army Corp of Engineers says water is overrunning one of the city 's levees , sending water into the low-lying Ninth Ward neighborhood .",O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O,"DT NNP NNP IN NNP VBZ NN VBZ VBG CD IN DT NN POS NNS , VBG NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP NN ."
The area is said to be vacated .,O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBN TO VB VBN .
Officials say water is pouring over at least three sections of the levee and that the water has risen higher and faster than anticipated as a result of Hurricane Rita .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-nat I-nat O,NNS VBP NN VBZ VBG RP IN JJS CD NNS IN DT NN CC IN DT NN VBZ VBN JJR CC JJR IN VBN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP .
Engineers have been draining New Orleans and working to repair damaged levees since Hurricane Katrina blew through the city three weeks ago .,O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-nat O O O O B-tim O O O,NNS VBP VBN VBG NNP NNP CC VBG TO VB JJ NNS IN NNP NNP VBD IN DT NN CD NNS RB .
"Poor weather conditions , particularly the strong winds caused by the outer bands of Hurricane Rita , makes helicopter entry into the Ninth Ward area too dangerous .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-nat I-nat O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O,"JJ NN NNS , RB DT JJ NNS VBN IN DT JJ NNS IN NNP NNP , VBZ NN NN IN DT NNP NNP NN RB JJ ."
Military leaders are giving some consideration to using boats to get into the area to assess the situation .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBG DT NN TO VBG NNS TO VB IN DT NN TO VB DT NN .
