The British charity Oxfam says the humanitarian crisis in Sudan 's Darfur region could leave more than two million people completely dependent on international aid until late 2006 .,O B-gpe O B-org O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT JJ NN NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN NNP POS NNP NN MD VB JJR IN CD CD NNS RB JJ IN JJ NN IN JJ CD .
Oxfam regional director Paul Smith-Lomas says most Darfur refugees do not feel safe enough to return to their villages .,B-org O O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP JJ NN NNP NNP VBZ RBS NNP NNS VBP RB VB JJ NN TO VB TO PRP$ NNS .
"With this year 's planting season likely to be missed , he says the region 's next harvest will not take place until October of next year .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O,"IN DT NN POS NN NN JJ TO VB VBN , PRP VBZ DT NN POS JJ NN MD RB VB NN IN NNP IN JJ NN ."
Peace talks between the Sudanese government and rebel leaders have so far failed .,O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O,NN NNS IN DT JJ NN CC NN NNS VBP RB RB VBN .
"Meanwhile , an African Union peacekeeping operation in Darfur has not stopped the violence .",O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"RB , DT NNP NNP VBG NN IN NNP VBZ RB VBN DT NN ."
"But the pan-African body has announced plans to double its troop strength to more than 7,000 personnel .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC DT JJ NN VBZ VBN NNS TO VB PRP$ NN NN TO JJR IN CD NNS .
"Oxfam estimates that about 300,000 people have died since the conflict erupted in 2003 - while the United Nation 's puts the death toll at around 180,000 .",B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP VBZ IN IN CD NNS VBP VBN IN DT NN VBD IN CD : IN DT NNP NNP POS VBZ DT NN NN IN IN CD .
