Police in Montenegro again have searched the home of the brother of fugitive war crimes suspect Radovan Karadzic .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,NNS IN NNP RB VBP VBN DT NN IN DT NN IN JJ NN NNS VBP NNP NNP .
Family members say authorities confiscated a mobile telephone and mobile phone cards during Friday 's search of the home of Luka Karadzic in the Montenegrin town of Niksic .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-gpe O O B-geo O,NN NNS VBP NNS VBD DT JJ NN CC JJ NN NNS IN NNP POS NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
"In the past , police have searched the Niksic home as well as other residences of family members of the former Bosnian Serb leader .",O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe I-gpe O O,"IN DT NN , NNS VBP VBN DT NNP NN RB RB IN JJ NNS IN NN NNS IN DT JJ JJ JJ NN ."
"The United Nations war crimes tribunal indicted Mr. Karadzic and his top military commander , General Ratko Mladic , 10 years ago on charges of a role in attacks on civilians during the conflict in Bosnia-Herzegovina .",O B-org I-org O O O O B-per B-geo O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NNP NNPS NN NNS JJ VBD NNP NNP CC PRP$ JJ JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP , CD NNS RB IN NNS IN DT NN IN NNS IN NNS IN DT NN IN NNP ."
