Italy 's coalition government is on the brink of unraveling one week after it was badly beaten in regional elections .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NN NN VBZ IN DT NN IN VBG CD NN IN PRP VBD RB VBN IN JJ NNS .
Prime Minister Silvio Berlusconi held a crisis meeting Thursday .,B-per O B-per I-per O O O O B-tim O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN NN NNP .
"At the meeting , Foreign Minister Gianfranco Fini pushed for a no-confidence vote and another partner , the Christian Democrats , threatened to withdraw from the coalition .",O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN , NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD IN DT JJ NN CC DT NN , DT NNP NNPS , VBD TO VB IN DT NN ."
"The prime minister 's political allies are concerned about a dismal economy , unhappy about election results and unsure that he has a plan that can reverse Italy 's fortunes .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,"DT JJ NN POS JJ NNS VBP VBN IN DT JJ NN , JJ IN NN NNS CC JJ IN PRP VBZ DT NN WDT MD VB NNP POS NNS ."
Italy 's involvement in the Iraq war has also been unpopular .,B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,NNP POS NN IN DT NNP NN VBZ RB VBN JJ .
"Mr. Berlusconi is resisting calls for early elections following losses in 11 of 13 regional races last week and has offered , instead , to reshuffle his cabinet and present a new program to parliament .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBG NNS IN JJ NNS VBG NNS IN CD IN CD JJ NNS JJ NN CC VBZ VBN , RB , TO VB PRP$ NN CC VB DT JJ NN TO NN ."
He is Italy 's longest-serving post-World War II prime minister .,O O B-geo O O O O B-eve O O O,PRP VBZ NNP POS JJ NNP NNP NNP JJ NN .
