The European Union is preparing to release substantial aid to the Palestinians facing a financial crisis after Israel stopped its monthly transfer of Palestinian tax revenues .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ VBG TO VB JJ NN TO DT NNS VBG DT JJ NN IN NNP VBD PRP$ JJ NN IN JJ NN NNS .
"The EU 's External Relations Commissioner , Benita Ferrero-Waldner , told reporters in Brussels Monday that she would announce a package of about $ 142 million to meet the basic needs of the Palestinians .",O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O,"DT NNP POS NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP , VBD NNS IN NNP NNP IN PRP MD VB DT NN IN IN $ CD CD TO VB DT JJ NNS IN DT NNS ."
She said the package would include direct payment to Israel of the Palestinian Authority 's energy bill as well as aid through United Nations relief agencies .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O,PRP VBD DT NN MD VB JJ NN TO NNP IN DT JJ NNP POS NN NN RB RB IN NN IN NNP NNPS NN NNS .
The EU - the largest donor to the Palestinian Authority - also joins the United States in demanding that Hamas renounce violence and accept Israel 's right to exist as Hamas forms the next Palestinian government .,O B-org O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-org O O O B-gpe O O,DT NNP IN DT JJS NN TO DT JJ NNP : RB VBZ DT NNP NNPS IN VBG IN NNP NN NN CC VB NNP POS NN TO VB IN NNP VBZ DT JJ JJ NN .
EU foreign ministers are to meet in Brussels Monday to discuss the situation .,B-org O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O,NNP JJ NNS VBP TO VB IN NNP NNP TO VB DT NN .
