Iraqi police say insurgents have kidnapped a driver for the Jordanian Embassy in Baghdad .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-geo O,JJ NNS VBP NNS VBP VBN DT NN IN DT JJ NNP IN NNP .
"They say the abductors , riding in three separate vehicles , stopped the Jordanian man 's car as he was driving from home to work this Tuesday morning .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"PRP VBP DT NNS , VBG IN CD JJ NNS , VBD DT JJ NN POS NN IN PRP VBD VBG IN NN TO VB DT NNP NN ."
"Jordanian officials in Amman say the man , Mahmoud Ziyadat , has worked at the Baghdad embassy for four years .",O O O B-geo O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O,"JJ NNS IN NNP VBP DT NN , NNP NNP , VBZ VBN IN DT NNP NN IN CD NNS ."
Tuesday 's kidnappings is the latest in a series of attacks aimed against Jordanians in Iraq .,B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-geo O,NNP POS NNS VBZ DT JJS IN DT NN IN NNS VBN IN NNS IN NNP .
"The terrorist group al-Qaida in Iraq , led by Jordanian-born Abu Musab al-Zarqawi , has claimed responsibility for most of the attacks , including a suicide bomb blast at Jordan 's embassy in the Iraqi capital two years ago .",O O O B-org O B-geo O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-gpe O B-tim O O O,"DT JJ NN NNP IN NNP , VBN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP , VBZ VBN NN IN JJS IN DT NNS , VBG DT NN NN NN IN NNP POS NN IN DT JJ NN CD NNS RB ."
The Zarqawi group also claimed responsibility for last month 's suicide attacks in Amman - bomb blasts at three hotels in the Jordanian capital that killed more than 60 people .,O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN RB VBD NN IN JJ NN POS NN NNS IN NNP IN NN NNS IN CD NNS IN DT JJ NN WDT VBD JJR IN CD NNS .
