Negotiations for territorial status began in 1972 .,O O O O O O B-tim O,NNS IN JJ NN VBD IN CD .
"A covenant to establish a commonwealth in political union with the US was approved in 1975 , and came into force on 24 March 1976 .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,"DT NN TO VB DT NN IN JJ NN IN DT NNP VBD VBN IN CD , CC VBD IN NN IN CD NNP CD ."
A new government and constitution went into effect in 1978 .,O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT JJ NN CC NN VBD IN NN IN CD .
