U.S. officials say they hope North Korea comes to the upcoming round of six-party nuclear talks ready to follow through on commitments made in the last round of discussions .,B-geo O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBP PRP VBP NNP NNP VBZ TO DT JJ NN IN JJ JJ NNS JJ TO VB IN IN NNS VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NNS .
U.S. State Department spokesman Sean McCormack says the new round of talks will require tough negotiating to move forward .,B-org I-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NN NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN NNS MD VB JJ NN TO VB RB .
"On Thursday , China confirmed the next round of talks will begin November 9 in Beijing .",O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-geo O,"IN NNP , NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN NNS MD VB NNP CD IN NNP ."
U.S. officials say the demand is unacceptable .,B-geo O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBP DT NN VBZ JJ .
