Two bomb disposal policemen were killed in Thailand Saturday when a suspected explosive they were trying to defuse was detonated by a mobile phone .,O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CD NN NN NNS VBD VBN IN NNP NNP WRB DT JJ JJ PRP VBD VBG TO VB VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN .
"Authorities said that at least eight people , including four other officers , were wounded in the blast at an open market in Thailand 's violence-wracked southern province of Narathiwat .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O,"NNS VBD IN IN JJS CD NNS , VBG CD JJ NNS , VBD VBN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP POS JJ JJ NN IN NNP ."
Police said the owner of a vegetable stall alerted authorities about a suspicious motorcycle that two teenagers parked nearby .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBD DT NN IN DT JJ NN VBD NNS IN DT JJ NN IN CD NNS VBN RB .
"Police cleared most people from the area , but a bomb hidden in the motorcycle exploded as police tried to disarm it .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD JJS NNS IN DT NN , CC DT NN VBN IN DT NN VBD IN NN VBD TO VB PRP ."
Officials said Islamic insurgents had threatened New Year 's violence as part of a years-long campaign against Thai authorities .,O O B-per O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O B-tim O O B-gpe O O,NNS VBD NNP NNS VBD VBN NNP NNP POS NN IN NN IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS .
"Majority-Muslim southern Thailand has been the scene of persistent violence since early 2004 , when Muslim militants raided a weapons depot and escaped with 300 rifles .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ JJ NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN JJ NN IN JJ CD , WRB NNP VBZ VBD DT NNS NN CC VBD IN CD NNS ."
"More than 4,000 people have been killed since then , both Muslims and Buddhists .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,"JJR IN CD NNS VBP VBN VBN IN RB , DT NNPS CC NNPS ."
