Palestinian sources identified the men killed Thursday as members of the Islamic militant group Hamas .,B-gpe O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,JJ NNS VBN DT NNS VBN NNP IN NNS IN DT NNP JJ NN NNP .
The house from which the men fired had been destroyed earlier in the day by the Israeli troops .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT NN IN WDT DT NNS VBD VBD VBN VBN RBR IN DT NN IN DT JJ NNS .
"In Gaza , a resident of the Rafah refugee camp died after an Israeli tank fired at him .",O B-geo O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,"IN NNP , DT NN IN DT NNP NN NN VBD IN DT JJ NN VBN IN PRP ."
