"A rights group has called on Thailand to investigate the use of lethal force by Thai soldiers against Burmese migrants , allegedly resulting in the deaths of three children .",O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS NN VBZ VBN IN NNP TO VB DT NN IN JJ NN IN JJ NNS IN JJ NNS , RB VBG IN DT NNS IN CD NNS ."
New York-based Human Rights Watch said in a press release Friday that Thai soldiers fired on a truck carrying 13 undocumented migrant workers from Burma on February 25 after the driver failed to stop for inspection .,O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O,NNP JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD IN DT NN NN NNP IN JJ NNS VBD IN DT NN VBG CD JJ NN NNS IN NNP IN NNP CD IN DT NN VBD TO VB IN NN .
The rights group said it had obtained photos showing the truck riddled with bullet holes .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS NN VBD PRP VBD VBN NNS VBG DT NN VBD IN NN NNS .
"Brad Adams , Asia director at HRW , said the soldiers who fired into the truck , apparently without concern for who could be killed or wounded , need to face the consequences .",B-per I-per O B-geo O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP , NNP NN IN NNP , VBD DT NNS WP VBD IN DT NN , RB IN NN IN WP MD VB VBN CC VBN , VBP TO VB DT NNS ."
HRW also called on the Thai government to provide access for investigators and to ensure none of the survivors are deported to Burma while investigations are conducted .,B-org O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,NNP RB VBD IN DT JJ NN TO VB NN IN NNS CC TO VB NN IN DT NNS VBP VBN TO NNP IN NNS VBP VBN .
