Both peacekeepers and insurgents say fighting in Somalia is set to increase during the Muslim holy month of Ramadan .,O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim I-tim O,DT NNS CC NNS VBP VBG IN NNP VBZ VBN TO VB IN DT NNP JJ NN IN NNP .
"A spokesman for the African Union peacekeeping force in Mogadishu , Major Ba-Hoku Barigye , says troops are preparing for a surge in attacks from militants over the next thirty days .",O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"DT NN IN DT NNP NNP VBG NN IN NNP , NNP NNP NNP , VBZ NNS VBP VBG IN DT NN IN NNS IN NNS IN DT JJ CD NNS ."
The prediction comes as authorities in Kenya say they have arrested dozens of non-Somalis over the last two months suspected of attempting to cross the border to join insurgent fighters .,O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ IN NNS IN NNP VBP PRP VBP VBN NNS IN JJ IN DT JJ CD NNS VBN IN VBG TO VB DT NN TO VB JJ NNS .
"Hizbul Islam , one of the groups fighting AU forces and soldiers from the Somali transitional government , has vowed to step up its assaults during the holy month .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"NNP NNP , CD IN DT NNS VBG NNP NNS CC NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN , VBZ VBN TO VB RP PRP$ NNS IN DT JJ NN ."
"A militia group fighting the insurgents , Ahlu-Summa Wal-Jama , says it will increase its own attacks .",O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN NN VBG DT NNS , NNP NNP , VBZ PRP MD VB PRP$ JJ NNS ."
Ramadan begins Wednesday for Somalia 's mostly Sunni Muslims .,B-eve O B-tim O B-geo O O B-per I-per O,NNP VBZ NNP IN NNP POS RB NNP NNPS .
"Observers refrain from eating , drinking and sexual relations between daybreak and sunset .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP IN NN , NN CC JJ NNS IN NN CC NN ."
