The United States is urging Iran to grant consular access to jailed Iranian-American journalist Roxana Saberi .,O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O,DT NNP NNPS VBZ VBG NNP TO VB JJ NN TO JJ JJ NN NNP NNP .
"A U.S. State Department spokesman , Gordon Duguid , told reporters on Wednesday that the U.S. is pushing for the access through Swiss diplomats who represent U.S. interests in Tehran .",O B-org I-org I-org O O B-per I-per O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo O O B-geo O,"DT NNP NNP NNP NN , NNP NNP , VBD NNS IN NNP IN DT NNP VBZ VBG IN DT NN IN JJ NNS WP VBP NNP NNS IN NNP ."
"Iranian authorities arrested Saberi in January , accusing her of working illegally in the country after her press credentials were revoked .",B-gpe O O B-per O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBN NNP IN NNP , VBG PRP IN VBG RB IN DT NN IN PRP$ NN NNS VBD VBN ."
She is being held in Tehran 's Evin prison .,O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O,PRP VBZ VBG VBN IN NNP POS NNP NN .
The journalist met with a lawyer in Tehran earlier this month .,O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,DT NN VBD IN DT NN IN NNP RBR DT NN .
"The spokesman says State Department officials spoke with Saberi 's father on Wednesday and that he and U.S. Secretary of State Hillary Clinton are very concerned about Saberi 's well-being , The Committee to Protect Journalists said Wednesday it was alarmed by a news report in which Saberi was quoted as saying she might remain in prison for "" months or even years . """,O O O B-org I-org O O O B-per O O O B-tim O O O O B-org O O B-org B-per I-per O O O O B-per O O O B-org I-org O B-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ NNP NNP NNS VBD IN NNP POS NN IN NNP CC IN PRP CC NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBP RB JJ IN NNP POS NN , DT NNP TO VB NNS VBD NNP PRP VBD VBN IN DT NN NN IN WDT NNP VBD VBN IN VBG PRP MD VB IN NN IN LQU NNS CC RB NNS . LQU"
