"The Israeli army says Palestinian militants fired two homemade rockets into an army base near the Gaza border Wednesday , wounding 12 people , many of them soldiers .",O B-gpe O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBZ JJ NNS VBD CD JJ NNS IN DT NN NN IN DT NNP NN NNP , VBG CD NNS , NN IN PRP NNS ."
"The army said two other rockets landed earlier near the southern Israeli town of Sderot , but did not cause any casualties .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD CD JJ NNS VBD RBR IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP , CC VBD RB VB DT NNS ."
"Palestinian militants in northern Gaza have stepped up rocket fire in recent weeks , prompting the Israeli army to launch new operations in the area to halt such attacks .",B-gpe O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS IN JJ NNP VBP VBN RP NN NN IN JJ NNS , VBG DT JJ NN TO VB JJ NNS IN DT NN TO VB JJ NNS ."
