Officials in India Monday say a top U.S. diplomat will visit New Delhi this week to help resolve disputes about a U.S.-India nuclear agreement .,O O B-geo B-tim O O O B-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNP NNP VBP DT JJ NNP NN MD VB NNP NNP DT NN TO VB VB NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN .
They say U.S. Undersecretary of State Nicholas Burns will arrive in New Delhi on May 31 for two days of talks .,O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O B-geo I-geo O B-tim I-tim O B-tim O O O O,PRP VBP NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP MD VB IN NNP NNP IN NNP CD IN CD NNS IN NNS .
Critics of the deal in both countries say that their own governments are giving away too much .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN DT NN IN DT NNS VBP IN PRP$ JJ NNS VBP VBG RB RB RB .
The disputes threaten to undermine an agreement that would allow the U.S. to provide civilian nuclear technology to India .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNS VBP TO VB DT NN WDT MD VB DT NNP TO VB JJ JJ NN TO NNP .
"If finalized , the deal would end three decades of sanctions on U.S. nuclear trade with India .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O,"IN VBN , DT NN MD VB CD NNS IN NNS IN NNP JJ NN IN NNP ."
India wants assurances that the U.S. would continue supplying fuel for its nuclear plants even if India conducts another nuclear weapons test .,B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,NNP VBZ NNS IN DT NNP MD VB VBG NN IN PRP$ JJ NNS RB IN NNP VBZ DT JJ NNS NN .
