The White House says President Bush sustained scrapes on his hands and arms after he collided with a local police officer during a bicycle ride at the site of the G-8 summit in Scotland .,O B-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-geo O,DT NNP NNP VBZ NNP NNP VBD NNS IN PRP$ NNS CC NNS IN PRP VBD IN DT JJ NN NN IN DT NN NN IN DT NN IN DT NNP NN IN NNP .
White House spokesman Scott McClellan told reporters that Mr. Bush slid on a paved surface while cycling at a high speed at the Gleneagles resort on Wednesday .,B-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O,NNP NNP NN NNP NNP VBD NNS IN NNP NNP VBD IN DT JJ NN IN VBG IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NN IN NNP .
"He said the president required bandaging by his White House physician , but added that the incident did not affect Mr. Bush 's attendance at the official dinner marking the summit 's formal opening .",O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD DT NN VBN NN IN PRP$ NNP NNP NN , CC VBD IN DT NN VBD RB VB NNP NNP POS NN IN DT JJ NN VBG DT NN POS JJ NN ."
Mr. McClellan said the police officer was taken to a local hospital for treatment of what the spokesman said might be an ankle injury .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD DT NN NN VBD VBN TO DT JJ NN IN NN IN WP DT NN VBD MD VB DT JJ NN .
He said President Bush would call the officer to inquire about his condition .,O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD NNP NNP MD VB DT NN TO VB IN PRP$ NN .
