The uninhabited islands were discovered and colonized by the Portuguese in the 15th century ; Cape Verde subsequently became a trading center for African slaves and later an important coaling and resupply stop for whaling and transatlantic shipping .,O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-tim I-tim O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNS VBD VBN CC VBN IN DT NNS IN DT JJ NN ; NNP NNP RB VBD DT NN NN IN JJ NNS CC RB DT JJ NN CC NN NN IN NN CC JJ NN .
"Following independence in 1975 , and a tentative interest in unification with Guinea-Bissau , a one-party system was established and maintained until multi-party elections were held in 1990 .",O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-tim O,"VBG NN IN CD , CC DT JJ NN IN NN IN NNP , DT JJ NN VBD VBN CC VBN IN JJ NNS VBD VBN IN CD ."
Cape Verde continues to exhibit one of Africa 's most stable democratic governments .,B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ TO VB CD IN NNP POS JJS JJ JJ NNS .
Repeated droughts during the second half of the 20th century caused significant hardship and prompted heavy emigration .,O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O,VBN NNS IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN VBD JJ NN CC VBD JJ NN .
"As a result , Cape Verde 's expatriate population is greater than its domestic one .",O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN , NNP NNP POS JJ NN VBZ JJR IN PRP$ JJ NN ."
Most Cape Verdeans have both African and Portuguese antecedents .,O B-gpe I-gpe O O B-gpe O B-gpe O O,JJS NNP NNS VBP DT JJ CC JJ NNS .
