Diplomatic sources say that pirates have seized a South Korean cargo ship off the coast of Somalia .,O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNS VBP IN NNS VBP VBN DT JJ JJ NN NN IN DT NN IN NNP .
The sources say the ship was carrying at least eight South Korean crew members and a number of foreigners when pirates seized it Wednesday .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NNS VBP DT NN VBD VBG IN JJS CD JJ JJ NN NNS CC DT NN IN NNS WRB NNS VBD PRP NNP .
Somali pirates have attacked dozens of ships this year and are now believed to be holding 11 ships and their crews hostage .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN NNS IN NNS DT NN CC VBP RB VBN TO VB VBG CD NNS CC PRP$ NNS NN .
Somali officials say the large ransoms being paid by ship owners are fueling the piracy .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP DT JJ NNS VBG VBN IN NN NNS VBP VBG DT NN .
The International Maritime Bureau advises ships traveling near Somalia to keep more than 200 nautical miles offshore and report any boats that look suspicious .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNS VBG IN NNP TO VB JJR IN CD JJ NNS RB CC VB DT NNS WDT VBP JJ .
