American terror suspect Jose Padilla was to appear in civil court Thursday to face criminal charges .,B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O,JJ NN NN NNP NNP VBD TO VB IN JJ NN NNP TO VB JJ NNS .
"Mr. Padilla had been held in a military prison for more than three years without being charged before his transfer Thursday to Miami , Florida .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O B-geo O,"NNP NNP VBD VBN VBN IN DT JJ NN IN JJR IN CD NNS IN VBG VBN IN PRP$ NN NNP TO NNP , NNP ."
"The Supreme Court agreed this week to let the Bush administration transfer Mr. Padilla , changing his status from what the White House calls "" an enemy combatant "" to a regular criminal suspect .",B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP VBD DT NN TO VB DT NNP NN VB NNP NNP , VBG PRP$ NN IN WP DT NNP NNP VBZ LQU DT NN NN RQU TO DT JJ JJ NN ."
Mr. Padilla 's case has been the subject of numerous court rulings and his detention without charge has been condemned by human and civil rights groups .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP POS NN VBZ VBN DT NN IN JJ NN NNS CC PRP$ NN IN NN VBZ VBN VBN IN JJ CC JJ NNS NNS .
"Mr. Padilla was arrested on suspicion of plotting to set off a radioactive "" dirty "" bomb within the United States .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP NNP VBD VBN IN NN IN VBG TO VB RP DT JJ LQU NN LQU NN IN DT NNP NNPS .
