Witnesses in southwestern Somalia say an explosion has killed four Ethiopian troops and triggered gunfire that killed two Somali civilians .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,NNS IN JJ NNP VBP DT NN VBZ VBN CD JJ NNS CC VBD NN WDT VBD CD JJ NNS .
Residents of Baidoa said Tuesday that a roadside bomb killed the Ethiopian soldiers late Monday .,O B-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-tim O,NNS IN NNP VBD NNP IN DT NN NN VBD DT JJ NNS JJ NNP .
"The witnesses said other troops responded to the attack by opening fire , killing two civilian bystanders .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS VBD JJ NNS VBD TO DT NN IN VBG NN , VBG CD JJ NNS ."
"Baidoa is about 250 kilometers west of the capital , Mogadishu , and is the seat of the Somali parliament .",B-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"NNP VBZ IN CD NNS JJS IN DT NN , NNP , CC VBZ DT NN IN DT JJ NN ."
Ethiopian troops supporting Somalia 's government come under frequent attack from Islamist insurgents .,B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O,JJ NNS VBG NNP POS NN VBD IN JJ NN IN NNP NNS .
A joint government-Ethiopian offensive drove Islamists from power in southern Somalia in late 2006 .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-tim O,DT JJ JJ NN VBD NNS IN NN IN JJ NNP IN JJ CD .
"Separately , officials said 10 people were killed and at least 11 wounded in a land dispute Monday in the southwestern Gedo region .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O,"RB , NNS VBD CD NNS VBD VBN CC IN JJS CD VBN IN DT NN NN NNP IN DT JJ NNP NN ."
"Disputes between rival clans over land and water are common in Somalia , which has not had a stable central government since 1991 .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"NNS IN JJ NNS IN NN CC NN VBP JJ IN NNP , WDT VBZ RB VBN DT JJ JJ NN IN CD ."
