"An Uzbek opposition leader says at least 745 people were killed by government troops suppressing widespread unrest , which began last week in the eastern city of Andijan .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT JJ NN NN VBZ IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN IN NN NNS VBG JJ NN , WDT VBD JJ NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
"The head of the Free Peasants party , Nigara Khidoyatova , said Tuesday her group arrived at the figure by speaking to relatives of those killed , and that the count is continuing .",O O O O B-org I-org O O B-per I-per O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NN , NNP NNP , VBD NNP PRP$ NN VBD IN DT NN IN VBG TO NNS IN DT VBN , CC IN DT NN VBZ VBG ."
"President Islam Karimov has denied that security forces opened fire on protesters , and blamed the violence on Islamic radicals trying to overthrow the government .",B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NN NNS VBD NN IN NNS , CC VBD DT NN IN NNP NNS VBG TO VB DT NN ."
The French News Agency says the Uzbek foreign ministry is planning a visit by journalists and diplomats to the affected areas Wednesday,O B-org I-org I-org O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ JJ NN VBZ VBG DT NN IN NNS CC NNS TO DT JJ NNS NNP
The United States has condemned the indiscriminate use of force against unarmed civilians in Uzbekistan .,O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNP NNPS VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN NN IN JJ NNS IN NNP .
"A State Department spokesman said Monday the United States also condemns violence by the demonstrators , who stormed a prison , freeing as many as two thousand inmates , including Muslim extremists convicted of terrorism .",O B-org I-org O O B-tim O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP NN VBD NNP DT NNP NNP RB VBZ NN IN DT NNS , WP VBD DT NN , VBG RB JJ IN CD CD NNS , VBG NNP NNS VBN IN NN ."
