International Olympic Committee President Jacques Rogge has urged North and South Korea to form a unified team for the 2008 Olympic Games .,O O B-org B-per I-per I-per O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNP CC NNP NNP TO VB DT JJ NN IN DT CD NNP NNPS .
"Rogge sent letters to the presidents of both Koreas on June 7 , to let them know he would do his best to help them field a single team for the Beijing Olympics .",B-per O O O O O O O B-org O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNP VBD NNS TO DT NNS IN DT NNP IN NNP CD , TO VB PRP VB PRP MD VB PRP$ JJS TO VB PRP VB DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNPS ."
It marks the first time the IOC president has asked the leaders of the two nations to cooperate in forming a unified team for the Games .,O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ DT JJ NN DT NNP NN VBZ VBN DT NNS IN DT CD NNS TO VB IN VBG DT JJ NN IN DT NNPS .
Inter-Korean sports leaders agreed in principle to field a single team for the 2008 Beijing Olympics in a meeting in March of 2003 .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim B-geo I-geo O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,JJ NNS NNS VBD IN NN TO VB DT JJ NN IN DT CD NNP NNPS IN DT NN IN NNP IN CD .
But the two sides have not yet worked out the details .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC DT CD NNS VBP RB RB VBN RP DT NNS .
Unification Minister Lee Jong-seok said Friday that North and South Korea will discuss the issue in the North Korean border city of Kaesong next Friday .,O O B-per I-per O B-tim I-tim B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-geo B-gpe O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP IN NNP CC NNP NNP MD VB DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NN NN IN NNP IN NNP .
