Thousands of Bangladeshi opposition activists have gathered in cities and urban centers to form a 900-kilometer human chain to demonstrate no-confidence in the government .,O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN JJ NN NNS VBP VBN IN NNS CC JJ NNS TO VB DT JJ JJ NN TO VB NN IN DT NN .
"The so-called "" human wall "" is planned to stretch hand-in-hand Saturday from Teknaf in the southeast to Tentulia in the northwest .",O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O B-geo O O O O,DT JJ LQU JJ NN LQU VBZ VBN TO VB JJ NNP IN NNP IN DT NN TO NNP IN DT NN .
The demonstration by the Awami League and its allies is calling for the resignation of the government and early elections .,O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN DT NNP NNP CC PRP$ NNS VBZ VBG IN DT NN IN DT NN CC JJ NNS .
"The government , which holds a strong parliamentary majority , has consistently rejected the opposition 's demands .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN , WDT VBZ DT JJ JJ NN , VBZ RB VBN DT NN POS NNS ."
"The Bangladeshi government has called out the country 's Rapid Action Battalion units , police and paramilitary forces to keep a watch on the demonstrators .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBZ VBN RP DT NN POS NNP NNP NNP NNS , NNS CC JJ NNS TO VB DT NN IN DT NNS ."
