Kyrgyzstan 's deposed President Askar Akayev says he fled the country two weeks ago in order to prevent civil war .,B-gpe O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS VBN NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBD DT NN CD NNS RB IN NN TO VB JJ NN .
"In a video-taped resignation speech , which was played in the Kyrgyz parliament Thursday , Mr. Akayev said he did not "" stain his hands with the blood of his countrymen "" and left office with a clear conscience .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-tim I-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN NN , WDT VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN NNP , NNP NNP VBD PRP VBD RB LQU VB PRP$ NNS IN DT NN IN PRP$ NNS RQU CC VBD NN IN DT JJ NN ."
"The video was recorded earlier this week in Moscow , where a delegation of Kyrgyz lawmakers negotiated Mr. Akayev 's resignation .",O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O,"DT NN VBD VBN RBR DT NN IN NNP , WRB DT NN IN JJ NNS VBD NNP NNP POS NN ."
"The Kyrgyz parliament is due to vote later today to accept the resignation , clearing the way for new presidential election set for June 26 .",O B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"DT JJ NN VBZ JJ TO VB RB NN TO VB DT NN , VBG DT NN IN JJ JJ NN VBN IN NNP CD ."
"Meanwhile , Kyrgyzstan 's Supreme Court annulled one of two criminal convictions against former opposition leader Felix Kulov , and agreed to consider a third conviction against him .",O O B-gpe O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , NNP POS NNP NNP VBD CD IN CD JJ NNS IN JJ NN NN NNP NNP , CC VBD TO VB DT JJ NN IN PRP ."
"If that verdict is also overturned , Mr. Kulov will be able to run for president .",O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN VBZ RB VBN , NNP NNP MD VB JJ TO VB IN NN ."
