Nigerian officials say gunmen kidnapped the principal of an ExxonMobil-sponsored school and killed her police escort and driver .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP NNS VBD DT NN IN DT JJ NN CC VBD PRP$ NN NN CC NN .
"The kidnap victim has been identified as Pegasus School Principal Lakshmi Tombush , an Indian national .",O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-gpe O O,"DT NN NN VBZ VBN VBN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP , DT JJ NN ."
Authorities have not indicated if any ransom demands have been made .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP RB VBN IN DT NN NNS VBP VBN VBN .
Police are investigating the abduction .,O O O O O O,NNS VBP VBG DT NN .
