The United Nations mission in Congo has confirmed that foreign troops crossed into the eastern part of the country last month .,O B-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NN IN NNP VBZ VBN IN JJ NNS VBD IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN JJ NN .
"The U.N. did not say if the troops were Rwandan forces , as the Congolese government alleges , or if the foreign troops are still in Congo .",O B-org O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NNP VBD RB VB IN DT NNS VBD JJ NNS , IN DT JJ NN VBZ , CC IN DT JJ NNS VBP RB IN NNP ."
"But in a statement issued late Friday , the mission said U.N. peacekeepers are convinced foreign troops entered Congo the day after Rwanda threatened to invade the country on November 23 .",O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"CC IN DT NN VBN JJ NNP , DT NN VBD NNP NNS VBP VBN JJ NNS VBD NNP DT NN IN NNP VBD TO VB DT NN IN NNP CD ."
The United Nations also said that mutinous soldiers in eastern Congo have received arms from outside the country .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP RB VBD IN JJ NNS IN JJ NNP VBP VBN NNS IN IN DT NN .
"Congo accuses Rwanda of backing the rebels , who began fighting with the Congolese army last week in the eastern town of Kanyabayonga .",B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP VBZ NNP IN VBG DT NNS , WP VBD VBG IN DT JJ NN JJ NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
"Rwanda has denied any involvement , but has repeatedly insisted it has the right to send troops into Congo to disarm Hutu fighters responsible for Rwanda 's 1994 genocide .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org O O O B-geo B-tim I-tim O O,"NNP VBZ VBN DT NN , CC VBZ RB VBN PRP VBZ DT NN TO VB NNS IN NNP TO VB NNP NNS JJ IN NNP POS CD NN ."
