"A leading Democratic U.S. Senator said the situation is getting worse in Iraq , where militants have continued to carry out deadly attacks despite Iraqi and U.S. military campaigns against them .",O O O B-org B-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-geo O O O O O,"DT VBG JJ NNP NNP VBD DT NN VBZ VBG JJR IN NNP , WRB NNS VBP VBN TO VB RP JJ NNS IN JJ CC NNP JJ NNS IN PRP ."
Senator Joe Biden told CBS Television on Sunday that Iraq is becoming a training ground for terrorists .,B-per I-per I-per O B-org I-org O B-tim I-tim B-geo O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP IN NNP IN NNP VBZ VBG DT NN NN IN NNS .
"His opinion was echoed by Republican Senator Chuck Hagel , who told U.S. News and World Report magazine the White House is , in his words , "" completely disconnected from reality "" about the situation in Iraq .",O O O O O B-org B-per I-per I-per O O O B-org I-org O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"PRP$ NN VBD VBN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP , WP VBD NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NN DT NNP NNP VBZ , IN PRP$ NNS , LQU RB VBN IN NN RQU IN DT NN IN NNP ."
"But Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice told Fox News Channel there has been "" a lot of progress "" in Iraq .",O O O B-org B-per I-per O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,CC NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP NNP EX VBZ VBN LQU DT NN IN NN LQU IN NNP .
"She pointed to the recent arrest of a suspected lieutenant of Abu Musab al-Zarqawi , who U.S. officials believe is leading al-Qaida in Iraq .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org B-per O O B-geo O O O O B-org O B-geo O,"PRP VBD TO DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP NNP , WP NNP NNS VBP VBZ VBG NNP IN NNP ."
Mr. Rice also said the growing strength and sophistication of Iraqi security forces will gradually lessen the burden of the U.S.-led coalition .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP RB VBD DT VBG NN CC NN IN JJ NN NNS MD RB VB DT NN IN DT JJ NN .
