The commander of U.S. troops in the Middle East has expressed concern about the performance of U.S.-trained Iraqi security forces .,O O O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O,DT NN IN NNP NNS IN DT NNP NNP VBZ VBN NN IN DT NN IN JJ JJ NN NNS .
"General John Abizaid says the Iraqi forces are "" not as mature as they need to be "" to ensure security for the country 's January 30 elections .",B-per I-per I-per O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O,NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ NNS VBP LQU RB RB JJ IN PRP VBP TO VB LQU TO VB NN IN DT NN POS NNP CD NNS .
"He expressed special concern about the city of Mosul , where he said foreign fighters and members of the banned Baathist party are cooperating in attacks on police .",O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD JJ NN IN DT NN IN NNP , WRB PRP VBD JJ NNS CC NNS IN DT VBN NN NN VBP VBG IN NNS IN NN ."
"The military has ordered another 12,000 U.S. troops to Iraq in a bid to increase security .",O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBN DT CD NNP NNS TO NNP IN DT NN TO VB NN .
General Abizaid made his comments Monday to reporters from the Blooomberg news service and the Washington Post newspaper .,B-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O O B-geo O O O O B-org I-org O O,NNP NNP VBD PRP$ NNS NNP TO NNS IN DT NNP NN NN CC DT NNP NNP NN .
"The Post quotes him as saying if the Iraqi forces improve , the United States can think about "" reshaping "" its own forces , which other officers say may lead to a lower U.S. troop level .",O B-org O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,"DT NNP VBZ PRP IN VBG IN DT JJ NNS VBP , DT NNP NNPS MD VB IN RQU VBG LQU PRP$ JJ NNS , WDT JJ NNS VBP MD VB TO DT JJR NNP NN NN ."
