"A Washington-based institute says half of the workforce in Los Angeles , California , is made up of immigrants , many of whom are unskilled and speak little English .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-art O,"DT JJ NN VBZ NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP , NNP , VBZ VBN IN IN NNS , NN IN WP VBP JJ CC VB JJ NNP ."
"The Migration Policy Institute ( MPI ) reports the immigrant workforce lacks the skills needed to replace a large bloc of U.S. workers nearing retirement age , known as the baby boomer generation .",O B-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP RRB VBZ DT NN NN VBZ DT NNS VBN TO VB DT JJ NN IN NNP NNS VBG NN NN , VBN IN DT NN NN NN ."
The group 's study also says Los Angeles is at the leading edge of a demographic trend taking place across the United States .,O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT NN POS NN RB VBZ NNP NNP VBZ IN DT VBG NN IN DT JJ NN VBG NN IN DT NNP NNPS .
MPI reports that more than one-third of the 9.9 million people who live in Los Angeles County are immigrants .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O O O,NNP VBZ IN JJR IN NN IN DT CD CD NNS WP VBP IN NNP NNP NNP VBP NNS .
"It recommends more resources be devoted to the integration of immigrants into U.S. classrooms , workplaces and civic life .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"PRP VBZ JJR NNS VB VBN TO DT NN IN NNS IN NNP NNS , NNS CC JJ NN ."
The institute says Los Angeles can serve as a policy laboratory for other U.S. communities .,O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,DT NN VBZ NNP NNP MD VB IN DT NN NN IN JJ NNP NNS .
