China has announced a double-digit increase in military spending and has issued a strong warning to Taiwan .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN JJ NN CC VBZ VBN DT JJ NN TO NNP .
Jamila Trindle reports from Beijing .,B-per I-per O O B-geo O,NNP NNP VBZ IN NNP .
"China has announced plans to increase military spending by almost 18 percent , to more than $ 58 billion dollars for 2008 .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"NNP VBZ VBN NNS TO VB JJ NN IN RB CD NN , TO JJR IN $ CD CD NNS IN CD ."
National People 's Congress spokesman Jiang Enzhu says most of the increase will cover higher prices and rising salaries .,B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP POS NNP NN NNP NNP VBZ JJS IN DT NN MD VB JJR NNS CC VBG NNS .
""" China 's military capability is solely for the purpose of safeguarding independence , sovereignty and territorial integrity , and it will not pose a threat to any country , "" he said .",O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"LQU NNP POS JJ NN VBZ RB IN DT NN IN VBG NN , NN CC JJ NN , CC PRP MD RB VB DT NN TO DT NN , RQU PRP VBD ."
"Jiang also warned Taiwan against holding a referendum on membership in the United Nations , saying Beijing sees that as a possible step toward independence .",B-per O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O,"NNP RB VBD NNP IN VBG DT NN IN NN IN DT NNP NNPS , VBG NNP VBZ DT IN DT JJ NN IN NN ."
