An Israeli official says Israel is considering plans to build a nuclear power station in its southern Negev desert .,O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,DT JJ NN VBZ NNP VBZ VBG NNS TO VB DT JJ NN NN IN PRP$ JJ NNP NN .
Israel Army Radio quoted Infrastructure Minister Binyamin Ben-Elizer as saying he has the support of Prime Minister Ehud Olmert and that the plan would be considered in coming months .,B-geo B-org I-org O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP NNP NNP IN VBG PRP VBZ DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP CC IN DT NN MD VB VBN IN VBG NNS .
The construction of a nuclear power plant could draw renewed attention to what is widely believed to be Israel 's nuclear weapons program .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,DT NN IN DT JJ NN NN MD VB VBN NN TO WP VBZ RB VBN TO VB NNP POS JJ NNS NN .
"Following a policy that it calls "" nuclear ambiguity , "" Israel has never admitted nor denied having a nuclear weapons program .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"VBG DT NN IN PRP VBZ LQU JJ NN , LQU NNP VBZ RB VBN CC VBN VBG DT JJ NNS NN ."
