Poor weather conditions have forced postponement of talks between top Georgian officials and representatives of the country 's breakaway region of Abkhazia .,O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NN NNS VBP VBN NN IN NNS IN JJ JJ NNS CC NNS IN DT NN POS JJ NN IN NNP .
Georgian State Minister for Conflict Resolution Giorgi Khaindrava had planned to travel to Abkhazia 's Gali district for talks with the breakaway region 's Interior Minister Sergei Khamba .,B-gpe O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O,JJ NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD VBN TO VB TO NNP POS NNP NN IN NNS IN DT JJ NN POS NNP NNP NNP NNP .
"The discussions , which had been expected to focus on security issues in the area , have been rescheduled for next week .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS , WDT VBD VBN VBN TO VB IN NN NNS IN DT NN , VBP VBN VBN IN JJ NN ."
