"Pakistan has issued new regulations ordering its controversial madrassas , or Islamic seminaries , to register with the authorities or face closure .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBN JJ NNS VBG PRP$ JJ NNS , CC NNP NNS , TO VB IN DT NNS CC NN NN ."
President Pervez Musharraf issued an ordinance in the capital Islamabad on Thursday ordering all madrassas to register with the government before December 31 and submit annual reports and accounts .,B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN DT NN NN IN NNP VBG DT NNS TO VB IN DT NN IN NNP CD CC VB JJ NNS CC NNS .
The new law also bars Islamic seminaries from teaching or publishing any literature which promotes militancy or spreads religious hatred .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN RB VBZ JJ NNS IN NN CC VBG DT NN WDT VBZ NN CC NNS JJ NN .
"President Musharraf has also promised to expel some 1,400 foreign students from these madrassas .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ RB VBN TO VB DT CD JJ NNS IN DT NNS .
General Musharraf came under international pressure after it was reported that at least two of the London suicide bombers had visited the Islamic country before the attacks last month and that one may have visited a madrassa .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD IN JJ NN IN PRP VBD VBN IN IN JJS CD IN DT NNP NN NNS VBD VBN DT JJ NN IN DT NNS JJ NN CC IN CD MD VB VBN DT NN .
