North Korea has issued a demand for the United States to treat it as a nuclear power awhile accusing Washington of hypocrisy for overlooking Israel 's presumed possession of nuclear weapons .,B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN DT NNP NNPS TO VB PRP IN DT JJ NN RB VBG NNP IN NN IN VBG NNP POS JJ NN IN JJ NNS .
An editorial published Sunday in the official newspaper Rodong Sinmun said the resolution of the nuclear standoff will be possible only when the United States gives up its unfair and prejudiced double standard .,O O O B-tim O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBN NNP IN DT JJ NN NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN DT JJ NN MD VB JJ RB WRB DT NNP NNPS VBZ RP PRP$ JJ CC JJ JJ NN .
"North Korea says it wants to be treated like Israel , a country widely believed to have nuclear weapons without having signed the Nuclear Non-Proliferation Treaty .",B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,"NNP NNP VBZ PRP VBZ TO VB VBN IN NNP , DT NN RB VBN TO VB JJ NNS IN VBG VBN DT NNP NNP NNP ."
"North Korea 's statement comes as the six party talks , including both Koreas , China , Russia , Japan and the United States , on Pyongyang 's nuclear program are about to resume .",B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP POS NN VBZ IN DT CD NN NNS , VBG DT NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP CC DT NNP NNPS , IN NNP POS JJ NN VBP RB TO VB ."
"While no date has been set , the talks are expected to begin in November .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"IN DT NN VBZ VBN VBN , DT NNS VBP VBN TO VB IN NNP ."
