"China 's President Hu Jintao received a royal welcome from Morocco on Monday , complete with a 21-gun salute and military bands .",B-geo O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NNP NNP NNP VBD DT JJ JJ IN NNP IN NNP , JJ IN DT JJ NN CC JJ NNS ."
Mr. Hu is on a short trip to Africa aimed at obtaining more oil for his country while increasing export opportunities for Chinese manufactured goods .,B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O,NNP NNP VBZ IN DT JJ NN TO NNP VBN IN VBG JJR NN IN PRP$ NN IN VBG NN NNS IN JJ JJ NNS .
"While in Rabat , the capital of Morocco , Mr. Hu and King Mohammed VI signed a package of accords covering trade , tourism , cultural and scientific cooperation .",O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O B-per I-per O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN IN NNP , DT NN IN NNP , NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN NNS VBG NN , NN , JJ CC JJ NN ."
"Morocco is a significant trading partner for China , worth about $ 150 billion in 2005 .",B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O,"NNP VBZ DT JJ NN NN IN NNP , JJ IN $ CD CD IN CD ."
"However , Morocco has expressed concern about a growing trade imbalance , and China 's textile exports have cut into Morocco 's own textile industry .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,"RB , NNP VBZ VBN NN IN DT VBG NN NN , CC NNP POS NN NNS VBP VBN IN NNP POS JJ NN NN ."
"Mr. Hu is scheduled to travel to Casablanca , Morocco 's commercial capital , on Tuesday before traveling on to Nigeria and Kenya .",B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB TO NNP , NNP POS JJ NN , IN NNP IN VBG IN TO NNP CC NNP ."
