Health officials in Asia are reporting that the deadly H5N1 bird flu virus is suspected in the deaths of two people .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS IN NNP VBP VBG IN DT JJ NNP NN NN NN VBZ VBN IN DT NNS IN CD NNS .
Hong Kong officials say a 32-year-old man who frequently visited markets where chickens were slaughtered died Thursday in Guangzhou on mainland China after showing symptoms of bird flu .,B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNS VBP DT JJ NN WP RB VBD NNS WRB NNS VBD VBN VBD NNP IN NNP IN NNP NNP IN VBG NNS IN NN NN .
"In Indonesia , officials said Saturday that local tests show a three-year-old boy has died of the deadly H5N1 virus in Central Java province .",O B-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O,"IN NNP , NNS VBD NNP IN JJ NNS VBP DT JJ NN VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NNP NN IN NNP NNP NN ."
Officials in both countries have sent samples to a World Health Organization-sanctioned laboratory in Hong Kong for confirmation that the pair had bird flu .,O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN DT NNS VBP VBN NNS TO DT NNP NNP NNP NN IN NNP NNP IN NN IN DT NN VBD VBN NN .
"China has already had eight known deaths from the disease , while 20 people have died from H5N1 in Indonesia .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP VBZ RB VBN CD VBN NNS IN DT NN , IN CD NNS VBP VBN IN NNP IN NNP ."
More than 90 people have died from the disease worldwide .,O O O O O O O O O O O,JJR IN CD NNS VBP VBN IN DT NN NN .
