U.S. Treasury Secretary Henry Paulson says U.S. financial regulations need modernization to match the growing size and complexity of financial institutions .,B-org I-org O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNP JJ NNS VBP NN TO VB DT VBG NN CC NN IN JJ NNS .
"In a speech in Washington Monday , he suggested giving the U.S. central bank ( known as the Federal Reserve ) a larger role in stabilizing the economy , and more authority to demand information from banks and other institutions in exchange for government help during a crisis .",O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN IN NNP NNP , PRP VBD VBG DT NNP JJ NN LRB VBN IN DT NNP NNP RRB DT JJR NN IN VBG DT NN , CC JJR NN TO VB NN IN NNS CC JJ NNS IN NN IN NN NN IN DT NN ."
"He also proposed a "" prudential financial regulator "" to watch over banks and insurance firms , and a "" conduct of business "" regulator to protect investors and consumers .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP RB VBD DT RQU JJ JJ NN LQU TO VB IN NNS CC NN NNS , CC DT LQU NN IN NN LQU NN TO VB NNS CC NNS ."
Paulson 's plan calls for consolidating regulatory agencies with the goal of simplifying and improving oversight of the financial system .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NN VBZ IN VBG JJ NNS IN DT NN IN VBG CC VBG NN IN DT JJ NN .
The proposals come as that system faces its most severe credit crisis in decades .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP IN DT NN VBZ PRP$ RBS JJ NN NN IN NNS .
"The new rules must be approved by Congress , and Paulson says they will generate "" controversy and healthy debate . """,O O O O O O O B-org O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNS MD VB VBN IN NNP , CC NNP VBZ PRP MD VB LQU NN CC JJ NN . LQU"
