A French official says one of two mail bombs sent from Yemen last week to addresses in the United States was defused just 17 minutes before it was set to explode .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBZ CD IN CD NN NNS VBN IN NNP JJ NN TO NNS IN DT NNP NNPS VBD VBN RB CD NNS IN PRP VBD VBN TO VB .
"Interior Minister Brice Hortefeux , speaking Thursday on French television , provided no further details , nor did he say where he got the information about the timing .",O B-per I-per I-per O O B-tim O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP , VBG NNP IN JJ NN , VBD DT JJ NNS , CC VBD PRP VB WRB PRP VBD DT NN IN DT NN ."
"But investigators who pulled Chicago-bound packages off cargo planes in Britain and the United Arab Emirates on Friday found bombs that were wired to cell phones , with the communication cards removed .",O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"CC NNS WP VBD JJ NNS IN NN NNS IN NNP CC DT NNP NNP NNPS IN NNP VBD NNS WDT VBD VBN TO NN NNS , IN DT NN NNS VBD ."
"Separately Thursday , police in the Greek capital conducted a controlled explosion of a parcel bomb addressed to the French embassy .",O B-tim O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"RB NNP , NN IN DT JJ NN VBN DT JJ NN IN DT NN NN VBD TO DT JJ NN ."
No injuries were reported .,O O O O O,DT NNS VBD VBN .
