"The Philippine military says government troops have captured two camps belonging to the Islamist Moro National Liberation Front , killing eight Muslim rebels .",O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O B-org O O,"DT JJ NN VBZ NN NNS VBP VBN CD NNS VBG TO DT NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP , VBG CD NNP NNS ."
"Military officials say the raid took place on the southern island of Jolo in retaliation for an attack on a marine outpost near the town of Panamao Friday night , which left two soldiers and a child dead .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP DT NN VBD NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP IN NN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP NN , WDT VBD CD NNS CC DT NN NN ."
The officials say Sunday 's raid aimed to capture the Front 's commander Habier Malik and his followers .,O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-org O O B-per I-per O O O O,DT NNS VBP NNP POS NN VBD TO VB DT NNP POS NN NNP NNP CC PRP$ NNS .
"Malik escaped to the jungles , but the military says he is now isolated and on his own .",B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD TO DT NNS , CC DT NN VBZ PRP VBZ RB JJ CC IN PRP$ NN ."
Malik embarrassed the army in February when he held government and military leaders hostage .,B-per O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,NNP JJ DT NN IN NNP WRB PRP VBD NN CC JJ NNS NN .
The hostages were released unharmed .,O O O O O O,DT NNS VBD VBN JJ .
"The MNLF signed a truce with the government in 1996 , but relations have remained tense .",O B-org O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O,"DT NNP VBD DT NN IN DT NN IN CD , CC NNS VBP VBN JJ ."
"Some members of the MNLF are considered sympathetic to Abu Sayyaf , an al-Qaida-linked group active on Jolo island .",O O O O B-org O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O,"DT NNS IN DT NNP VBP VBN JJ TO NNP NNP , DT JJ NN JJ IN NNP NN ."
