U.S. and Iraqi troops met sporadic resistance Saturday at the start of a new offensive against insurgents in western Iraq .,B-gpe O B-gpe O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP CC JJ NNS VBD JJ NN NNP IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNS IN JJ NNP .
"The U.S. military says 2,500 U.S. service members and a thousand Iraqi soldiers are participating in the operation , dubbed "" Steel Curtain . """,O B-gpe O O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NN VBZ CD NNP NN NNS CC DT CD JJ NNS VBP VBG IN DT NN , VBN LQU NNP NNP . RQU"
"U.S. jets have carried out nine airstrikes on insurgent strong holds , killing an unconfirmed number of suspected al-Qaida in Iraq militants .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-geo O O,"NNP NNS VBP VBN RP CD NNS IN JJ JJ VBZ , VBG DT JJ NN IN VBN NNP IN NNP NNS ."
There have been no reports of Iraqi or American fatalities .,O O O O O O B-gpe O B-gpe O O,EX VBP VBN DT NNS IN JJ CC JJ NNS .
"The military says it is providing temporary shelter , food and security to about 400 displaced residents from the Husaybah area , affected by the offensive .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"DT JJ VBZ PRP VBZ VBG JJ NN , NN CC NN TO IN CD VBD NNS IN DT NNP NN , VBN IN DT NN ."
