"U.S. military officials say five more American troops have died in Iraq , raising the number of U.S. troops killed in Iraq this month to 18 .",B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O B-tim I-tim O,"NNP JJ NNS VBP CD JJR JJ NNS VBP VBN IN NNP , VBG DT NN IN NNP NNS VBN IN NNP DT NN TO CD ."
"U.S. officials in Baghdad said Monday that an American helicopter crashed in northern Iraq , killing two soldiers on board .",B-geo O O B-geo O B-tim O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"NNP NNS IN NNP VBD NNP IN DT JJ NN VBD IN JJ NNP , VBG CD NNS IN NN ."
A military statement said no enemy fire was observed when the helicopter went down in Salaheddin province .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,DT JJ NN VBD DT NN NN VBD VBN WRB DT NN VBD RB IN NNP NN .
An investigation into the crash is under way .,O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN DT NN VBZ IN NN .
The military also reported another three American troops were killed in combat in western Iraq 's Anbar province .,O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O,DT NN RB VBD DT CD JJ NNS VBD VBN IN NN IN JJ NNP POS NNP NN .
The three Americans - two Marines and one Army soldier - were fatally wounded during fighting Saturday and Sunday .,O O B-gpe O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,DT CD NNS IN CD NNS CC CD NNP NN : VBD RB VBN IN VBG NNP CC NNP .
"In other news , the U.S. military says coalition ground troops south of Baghdad Sunday killed an insurgent with links to a senior al-Qaida in Iraq leader .",O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O B-org O B-geo O O,"IN JJ NN , DT NNP NN VBZ NN NN NNS RB IN NNP NNP VBD DT JJ IN NNS TO DT JJ NNP IN NNP NN ."
