U.S. President Barack Obama is calling on Congress to pass legislation that will reform the credit card industry and make it more fair and transparent to consumers .,B-org B-per I-per I-per O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBG IN NNP TO VB NN WDT MD VB DT NN NN NN CC VB PRP RBR JJ CC JJ TO NNS .
"In his weekly address Saturday , Mr. Obama said consumers too often get "" ripped off "" by credit card companies that impose sudden rate hikes , unfair penalties and hidden fees .",O O O O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN PRP$ JJ NN NNP , NNP NNP VBD NNS RB RB VB LQU VBN RP RQU IN NN NN NNS WDT VB JJ NN NNS , JJ NNS CC JJ NNS ."
The president says consumers also should not have to fear that any new credit card is going to come with strings attached and need a magnifying glass and reference book to read an application .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ NNS RB MD RB VB TO VB IN DT JJ NN NN VBZ VBG TO VB IN NNS VBN CC VBP DT JJ NN CC NN NN TO VB DT NN .
"President Obama called for lawmakers in Washington to craft a bill that will address what he described as the credit card industry 's "" anything goes approach . """,B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD IN NNS IN NNP TO VB DT NN WDT MD VB WP PRP VBD IN DT NN NN NN POS LQU DT VBZ NN . LQU
Mr. Obama urged lawmakers to have a bill ready for him to sign by Memorial Day on May 25 .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim I-tim O,NNP NNP VBD NNS TO VB DT NN JJ IN PRP TO VB IN NNP NNP IN NNP CD .
