President George Bush is urging Congress to work together with him and approve new proposals to reduce America 's dependence on foreign oil and diversify its energy supply .,B-per I-per I-per O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBG NNP TO VB RB IN PRP CC VB JJ NNS TO VB NNP POS NN IN JJ NN CC VB PRP$ NN NN .
"In his weekly radio address Saturday , Mr. Bush said energy policy was an area of great potential for bipartisan cooperation .",O O O O O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN PRP$ JJ NN NN NNP , NNP NNP VBD NN NN VBD DT NN IN JJ NN IN JJ NN ."
"Mr. Bush called on Democrats to approve the budget he submitted to Congress earlier this week , which proposes $ 2.7 billion in spending for alternative energy research .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD IN NNS TO VB DT NN PRP VBD TO NNP RBR DT NN , WDT VBZ $ CD CD IN NN IN JJ NN NN ."
Mr. Bush says the budget is a key step toward reaching his national goal to reduce America 's gasoline consumption by 20 percent over the next 10 years .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-tim O O B-tim O O,NNP NNP VBZ DT NN VBZ DT JJ NN IN VBG PRP$ JJ NN TO VB NNP POS NN NN IN CD NN IN DT JJ CD NNS .
"On the supply side , Mr. Bush proposes raising mandatory fuel standards to require an increased use of renewable and alternative fuels .",O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN NN , NNP NNP VBZ VBG JJ NN NNS TO VB DT VBN NN IN JJ CC JJ NNS ."
"On the demand side , he says he wants to raise fuel economy standards to make cars more energy efficient .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN NN , PRP VBZ PRP VBZ TO VB NN NN NNS TO VB NNS JJR NN NN ."
