Lawyers for two jailed Hamas Cabinet ministers and a Palestinian legislator Monday said an Israeli military court has ordered the three men held without trial for six months .,O O O O B-org I-org O O O B-gpe O B-tim O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,NNS IN CD JJ NNP NNP NNS CC DT JJ NN NNP VBD DT JJ JJ NN VBZ VBN DT CD NNS VBN IN NN IN CD NNS .
"An Israeli military spokesman says the three men , Minister of State Wasfi Kabha , Education Minister Naser al-Deen al-Shaer and legislator Abdel-Rahman Zeidan , were ordered held until December fourth because their release would pose a "" clear and present danger "" to Israel .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-per O B-org B-per I-per O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT JJ NN NN VBZ DT CD NNS , NNP IN NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP CC NN NNP NNP , VBD VBN VBN IN NNP NN IN PRP$ NN MD VB DT RQU JJ CC JJ NN LQU TO NNP ."
"The military court did not release the specific charges against the three men , who were detained last month along with more than 30 others .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBD RB VB DT JJ NNS IN DT CD NNS , WP VBD VBN JJ NN IN IN JJR IN CD NNS ."
"Israel 's use of lengthy administrative detention without specific charges being filed has prompted criticism from Palestinian officials , the U.S. State Department and some human rights groups .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O,"NNP POS NN IN JJ JJ NN IN JJ NNS VBG VBN VBZ VBN NN IN JJ NNS , DT NNP NNP NNP CC DT JJ NNS NNS ."
