Ukraine 's Supreme Court is still hearing a legal challenge to last month 's presidential election even after clearing the way for Viktor Yushchenko 's inauguration .,B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O,NNP POS NNP NNP VBZ RB VBG DT JJ NN TO JJ NN POS JJ NN RB IN VBG DT NN IN NNP NNP POS NN .
"The court Tuesday ruled that the December 26 election results can be printed in two government newspapers on Thursday , making it official .",O O B-tim O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O,"DT NN NNP VBD IN DT NNP CD NN NNS MD VB VBN IN CD NN NNS IN NNP , VBG PRP JJ ."
The decision allows Mr. Yushchenko to be sworn in as president as soon as parliament sets a date .,O O O B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ NNP NNP TO VB VBN IN RB NN RB RB IN NN VBZ DT NN .
Yushchenko aides say they expect the lawmakers to set the inauguration for Saturday .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP NNS VBP PRP VBP DT NNS TO VB DT NN IN NNP .
But the court will continue hearing former Prime Minister Viktor Yanukovych 's claim that the election was fraudulent .,O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O,CC DT NN MD VB VBG JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP POS NN IN DT NN VBD JJ .
It has already dismissed a number of other Yanukovych challenges .,O O O O O O O O B-per O O,PRP VBZ RB VBN DT NN IN JJ NNP NNS .
