"Arabic broadcaster Al-Jazeera has aired a new video in which al-Qaida 's deputy leader , Ayman al-Zawahri , says U.S. plans to reduce the number of troops in Iraq means victory for Islam .",O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O,"JJ NN NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN WDT NNP POS NN NN , NNP NNP , VBZ NNP NNS TO VB DT NN IN NNS IN NNP VBZ NN IN NNP ."
This is an apparent reference to the recent remarks by U.S. Defense Secretary Donald Rumsfeld that the military will soon begin reducing its troop strength in Iraq .,O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT VBZ DT JJ NN TO DT JJ NNS IN NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP IN DT NN MD RB VB VBG PRP$ NN NN IN NNP .
"The al-Qaida leader also says the United States will soon be defeated in Palestine , too .",O B-org O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O,"DT NNP NN RB VBZ DT NNP NNPS MD RB VB VBN IN NNP , RB ."
"The most recent videotape from al-Zawahri , aired by Al-Jazeera last October , called on Muslims to aid victims of the massive earthquake in Pakistan .",O O O O O B-per O O O O O B-tim O O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT RBS JJ NN IN NNP , VBN IN NNP JJ NNP , VBD IN NNP TO VB NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
