Mediators at peace talks between Sudan 's government and southern rebels say the two sides will sign a permanent cease-fire on Friday .,O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNS IN NN NNS IN NNP POS NN CC JJ NNS VBP DT CD NNS MD VB DT JJ NN IN NNP .
"Negotiators say the deal will be signed at 1200 GMT ( 3:00 p.m. local time ) in the Kenyan town of Naivasha , where peace talks have yielded several partial agreements .",O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim I-tim O B-tim O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP DT NN MD VB VBN IN CD NNP LRB CD RB JJ NN RRB IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , WRB NN NNS VBP VBN JJ JJ NNS ."
"However , mediators say the permanent truce will not be a final deal to end 21 years of civil war .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O,"RB , NNS VBP DT JJ NN MD RB VB DT JJ NN TO VB CD NNS IN JJ NN ."
They say a comprehensive accord will likely be signed in early January .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,PRP VBP DT JJ NN MD RB VB VBN IN JJ NNP .
"Meanwhile , South Africa 's President Thabo Mbeki arrived in the Sudanese capital , Khartoum , Thursday .",O O B-geo I-geo O B-per I-per I-per O O O B-gpe O O B-org O B-tim O,"RB , NNP NNP POS NNP NNP NNP VBD IN DT JJ NN , NNP , NNP ."
He is expected to hold talks with Sudanese President Omar al-Bashir on the peace negotiations .,O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O,PRP VBZ VBN TO VB NNS IN JJ NNP NNP NNP IN DT NN NNS .
