The U.S. military says coalition forces have killed six suspected terrorists and detained 22 others during operations to disrupt terrorist networks in central and northern Iraq .,O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNP NN VBZ NN NNS VBP VBN CD JJ NNS CC VBD CD NNS IN NNS TO VB JJ NNS IN JJ CC JJ NNP .
A statement says coalition troops southwest of Mosul killed four suspects Friday in an operation targeting a man believed responsible for al-Qaida in Iraq security functions .,O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-geo O O O,DT NN VBZ NN NNS JJS IN NNP VBD CD NNS NNP IN DT NN VBG DT NN VBN JJ IN NNP IN NNP NN NNS .
It says troops discovered grenades and other weapons in a vehicle used by the suspects .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ NNS VBD NNS CC JJ NNS IN DT NN VBN IN DT NNS .
"In another operation , the military says coalition forces killed two suspected terrorists and wounded another in Mosul Thursday .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O,"IN DT NN , DT NN VBZ NN NNS VBD CD JJ NNS CC VBD DT IN NNP NNP ."
"Separately , the military says one U.S. soldier was killed and another four wounded when their convoy in southern Baghdad was struck Thursday by an armor-piercing bomb .",O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O O O O,"RB , DT JJ VBZ CD NNP NN VBD VBN CC DT CD VBN WRB PRP$ NN IN JJ NNP VBD VBN NNP IN DT JJ NN ."
"Elsewhere , Iraqi police say a roadside bomb killed two policemen and wounded three others north of the city of Diwaniya .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"RB , JJ NNS VBP DT NN NN VBD CD NNS CC VBD CD NNS RB IN DT NN IN NNP ."
