Leaders at a summit of more than 50 Muslim nations have promised to fight religious extremism and crack down on terrorist financing .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN DT NN IN JJR IN CD NNP NNS VBP VBN TO VB JJ NN CC VB RP IN JJ NN .
The Organization of the Islamic Conference made the pledges in a statement at the end of a two-day summit in the Saudi city of Mecca .,O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNP IN DT NNP NNP VBD DT NNS IN DT NN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
"The statement called on Muslim schools to reject extremist ideas , and warned that fatwas , or religious edicts , should not be issued by unauthorized people .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD IN NNP NNS TO VB NN NNS , CC VBD IN NNS , CC JJ NNS , MD RB VB VBN IN JJ NNS ."
The group also expressed concern at rising hatred against Muslims and Islam around the world .,O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O,DT NN RB VBD NN IN VBG NN IN NNPS CC NNP IN DT NN .
"Founded in 1969 , the conference is based in Saudi Arabia .",O O B-tim O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"VBN IN CD , DT NN VBZ VBN IN NNP NNP ."
