"James Brown 's body was placed in a crypt March 10 at the Beech Island , South Carolina home of one of his daughters .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-geo I-geo I-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP POS NN VBD VBN IN DT NN NNP CD IN DT NNP NNP , NNP NNP NN IN CD IN PRP$ NNS ."
"The soul great 's friends and family sang and released white balloons at the ceremony , presided over by the Rev. Al Sharpton .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O,"DT NN JJ POS NNS CC NN VBD CC VBD JJ NNS IN DT NN , VBN RP IN DT NNP NNP NNP ."
"It will not be the final resting place for "" The Godfather Of Soul , "" who died December 25 at age 73 .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O B-tim O,"PRP MD RB VB DT JJ VBG NN IN LQU DT NNP IN NNP , LQU WP VBD NNP CD IN NN CD ."
"Family members said a public mausoleum is being built , and its location will be announced once it is finished .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NN NNS VBD DT JJ NN VBZ VBG VBN , CC PRP$ NN MD VB VBN RB PRP VBZ VBN ."
"Brown 's children used their own money to erect the structure , as his estate has yet to be settled in court .",B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NNS VBD PRP$ JJ NN TO VB DT NN , IN PRP$ NN VBZ RB TO VB VBN IN NN ."
