President Bush called Afghan President Hamid Karzai from the White House earlier Thursday to reaffirm the strong relationship shared between the two countries .,B-per I-per O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O B-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD JJ NNP NNP NNP IN DT NNP NNP RB NNP TO VB DT JJ NN VBN IN DT CD NNS .
"According to the White House , the two leaders discussed ongoing security operations against extremist elements .",O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,"VBG TO DT NNP NNP , DT CD NNS VBD JJ NN NNS IN NN NNS ."
"They also spoke about efforts to implement security , governance , and economic development and reconstruction in war-shattered Afghanistan .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O,"PRP RB VBD IN NNS TO VB NN , NN , CC JJ NN CC NN IN JJ NNP ."
The White House says the issue of counter-narcotics efforts was also raised .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ DT NN IN NNS NNS VBD RB VBN .
Afghanistan is the world 's number one producer of opium .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ DT NN POS NN CD NN IN NN .
The White House said both presidents will continue to work together to build a prosperous Afghanistan and fight the global war on terror .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBD DT NNS MD VB TO VB RB TO VB DT JJ NNP CC VB DT JJ NN IN NN .
Mr. Karzai is considered a key ally in the U.S. war against terrorism .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NN IN NN .
"There are some 26,000 U.S. troops currently deployed in Afghanistan , helping NATO fight Taleban militants and work on reconstruction projects .",O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O B-org O B-org O O O O O O O,"EX VBP DT CD NNP NNS RB VBN IN NNP , VBG NNP VB NNP NNS CC VB IN NN NNS ."
