The United Nations mission in Haiti has condemned the kidnapping and murder of a journalist in Port-au-Prince .,O B-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNP NNP NN IN NNP VBZ VBN DT NN CC NN IN DT NN IN NNP .
"In a statement issued Friday , the mission called the murder of reporter Jacques Roche a "" brutal and vile "" act and an attack on freedom of the press .",O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN VBN NNP , DT NN VBD DT NN IN NN NNP NNP DT LQU JJ CC JJ RQU NN CC DT NN IN NN IN DT NN ."
"Haitian authorities discovered Mr. Roche 's body Thursday , four days after he was abducted at gunpoint .",B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBD NNP NNP POS NN NNP , CD NNS IN PRP VBD VBN IN NN ."
They said he was burned and tortured and then shot several times .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD PRP VBD VBN CC VBN CC RB VBD JJ NNS .
The journalist worked for Le Matin newspaper and was a commentator at Radio Ibo in the capital .,O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O,DT NN VBD IN NNP NNP NN CC VBD DT NN IN NNP NNP IN DT NN .
He also hosted a television show for dozens of civic groups that contributed to President Jean-Bertrand Aristide 's ouster in February of last year .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O B-tim I-tim O O O,PRP RB VBD DT NN NN IN NNS IN JJ NNS WDT VBD TO NNP NNP NNP POS NN IN NNP IN JJ NN .
