"In an interview with Newsweek Magazine published Sunday , Mr. Sharon said he will meet Mr. Abbas when Palestinian leaders are ready .",O O O O B-org I-org O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O B-per I-per O B-per O O O O,"IN DT NN IN NNP NNP VBD NNP , NNP NNP VBD PRP MD VB NNP NNP WRB JJ NNS VBP JJ ."
"In a separate Newsweek interview , Mr. Abbas said he would be willing to meet the Israeli leader after the January ninth Palestinian presidential election .",O O O B-org O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O,"IN DT JJ NNP NN , NNP NNP VBD PRP MD VB JJ TO VB DT JJ NN IN DT NNP JJ JJ JJ NN ."
Mr. Sharon also said he will work with the Palestinians to coordinate Israel 's planned withdrawal from the Gaza Strip .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP NNP RB VBD PRP MD VB IN DT NNS TO VB NNP POS VBN NN IN DT NNP NNP .
"Mr. Abbas said Palestinians are rebuilding their security forces ahead of the Gaza withdrawal , which is slated for next year .",B-per I-per O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD NNS VBP VBG PRP$ NN NNS RB IN DT NNP NN , WDT VBZ VBN IN JJ NN ."
Mr. Abbas is backed by the powerful Fatah political faction and is viewed as a front-runner for the Palestinian presidency .,B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NNP JJ NN CC VBZ VBN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN .
