British authorities have started arresting thousands of failed Iraqi asylum seekers with plans to return them to Iraq .,B-gpe O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNS VBP VBN VBG NNS IN JJ JJ NN NNS IN NNS TO VB PRP TO NNP .
The Home Office in London Tuesday said it is beginning to enforce a policy that was announced last year .,O B-org I-org O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP IN NNP NNP VBD PRP VBZ VBG TO VB DT NN WDT VBD VBN JJ NN .
"Officials say each deportation will take place on a case-by-case basis , and that no one will be sent back to areas of Iraq that are unstable or where they could face persecution .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP DT NN MD VB NN IN DT JJ NN , CC IN DT NN MD VB VBN RB TO NNS IN NNP WDT VBP JJ CC WRB PRP MD VB NN ."
Refugee groups say at least 43 Iraqis have been rounded up so far .,O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,NN NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBP VBN VBN RP RB RB .
The groups say they are appalled at the British policy .,O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT NNS VBP PRP VBP VBN IN DT JJ NN .
They say all of Iraq is unsafe .,O O O O B-geo O O O,PRP VBP DT IN NNP VBZ JJ .
