"Gunners Football Club has moved to the top of Zimbabwe 's Premier Soccer League , displacing Dynamos which had headed the league table for some seeks .",B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo O B-org I-org I-org O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,"NNPS NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO DT NN IN NNP POS NNP NNP NNP , VBG NNP WDT VBD VBN DT NN NN IN DT VBZ ."
But Gunners with 41 points is just one up on Dynamos with 40 .,O B-org O O O O O O O O B-org O B-tim O,CC NNPS IN CD NNS VBZ RB CD RP IN NNS IN CD .
Gunners Coach Moses “ Bambo ” Chunga told reporter Marvellous Mhlanga-Nyahuye of VOA 's Studio 7 for Zimbabwe that his team will do all it can to capture the title .,B-org O B-per O B-per O B-per O O B-per I-per O B-org O O B-org O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNPS NN NNPS LQU NNP RQU NNP VBD NN NNP NNP IN NNP POS NNP NNP IN NNP IN PRP$ NN MD VB DT PRP MD TO VB DT NN .
More reports from VOA 's Studio 7 for Zimbabwe ...,O O O B-org O O O O B-org O,JJR NNS IN NNP POS NNP CD IN NNP .
