The White House is denying Albanian media reports that an enthusiastic souvenir hunter stole President Bush 's watch from his wrist during a sea of handshaking Sunday near Tirana .,O B-org I-org O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O,DT NNP NNP VBZ VBG JJ NNS NNS IN DT JJ NN NN VBZ NNP NNP POS NN IN PRP$ NN IN DT NN IN VBG NNP IN NNP .
Dozens of Albanians shook the president 's hands and grabbed his arms during a stop in a town north of the capital .,O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNS VBD DT NN POS NNS CC VBD PRP$ NNS IN DT NN IN DT NN NN IN DT NN .
Albanian television pictures show Mr. Bush wearing his watch as one man grasped his arm and seemed to grab at the timepiece .,B-gpe O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN NNS VBP NNP NNP VBG PRP$ NN IN CD NN VBD PRP$ NN CC VBD TO VB IN DT NN .
"Seconds later , the watch was gone .",O O O O O O O O,"NNS RB , DT NN VBD VBN ."
Albanian newspapers and other media reports say the watch was stolen .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS CC JJ NNS NNS VBP DT NN VBD VBN .
But the White House says the president paused for a moment to slip the watch in his pocket before plunging his hands back into the crowd .,O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC DT NNP NNP VBZ DT NN VBD IN DT NN TO VB DT NN IN PRP$ NN IN VBG PRP$ NNS RB IN DT NN .
