"The head of ASEAN says a draft version of the group 's first charter of standards - set to be released next week - will "" pressure "" military-ruled Burma to improve its human rights record .",O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN NNP VBZ DT NN NN IN DT NN POS JJ NN IN NNS : VBN TO VB VBN JJ NN : MD LQU VB RQU JJ NN TO VB PRP$ JJ NNS NN .
"Speaking with reporters in Singapore on Monday , Secretary-General Ong Keng Yong said the charter will stress "" responsibility and obligation "" of membership in the Association for South East Asian Nations .",O O O O B-org O B-tim O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-geo I-geo B-per B-org O,"VBG IN NNS IN NNP IN NNP , JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN MD VB LQU NN CC NN RQU IN NN IN DT NNP IN NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
"Burma has long been a problem for the 10-nation group because of its poor human rights record and its detention of activists , including Nobel peace laureate Aung San Suu Kyi .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O,"NNP VBZ RB VBN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN IN PRP$ JJ JJ NNS NN CC PRP$ NN IN NNS , VBG NNP NN NN NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
A draft of the new charter will be presented to ASEAN members next week when they meet in the Philippines .,O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NN IN DT JJ NN MD VB VBN TO NNP NNS JJ NN WRB PRP VBP IN DT NNPS .
