Attorney General Michael Mukasey announced Wednesday that he is appointing federal prosecutor John Durham to conduct the investigation .,O B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP IN PRP VBZ VBG JJ NN NNP NNP TO VB DT NN .
Critics of the move accuse the CIA of destroying evidence of torture .,O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O,NNS IN DT NN VBP DT NNP IN VBG NN IN NN .
"Also Wednesday , Thomas Keane and Lee Hamilton , heads of the U.S. commission that investigated the September 11 , 2001 attacks on the United States , published an editorial in the New York Times saying CIA officials unlawfully obstructed their investigation by failing to notify them that the videotapes existed .",O B-tim O B-per I-per O B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB NNP , NNP NNP CC NNP NNP , NNS IN DT NNP NN WDT VBD DT NNP CD , CD NNS IN DT NNP NNPS , VBD DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP VBG NNP NNS RB VBD PRP$ NN IN VBG TO VB PRP IN DT NNS VBD ."
