"The Pakistani government has imposed a ban on protests in the capital , Islamabad , ahead of a planned demonstration on Sunday against cartoons lampooning the Prophet Muhammad .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-org I-org O,"DT JJ NN VBZ VBN DT NN IN NNS IN DT NN , NNP , RB IN DT JJ NN IN NNP IN NNS VBG DT NNP NNP ."
The announcement of the ban by Information Minister Sheikh Rashid Ahmed follows a violent week of demonstrations in Pakistan .,O O O O O O B-org O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN NNS IN NNP .
"Five people were killed this week , and at least four people were wounded Saturday when shots were fired during a protest in the town of Cheniot , in central Punjab province .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O,"CD NNS VBD VBN DT NN , CC IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN NNP WRB NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP , IN JJ NNP NN ."
"In a separate demonstration Saturday , thousands of Pakistani women rallied peacefully in Karachi .",O O O O B-tim O O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O,"IN DT JJ NN NNP , NNS IN JJ NNS VBD RB IN NNP ."
"In London , at least 10,000 Muslims converged on London 's Trafalgar Square .",O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O,"IN NNP , IN JJS CD NNPS VBD IN NNP POS NNP NNP ."
The Muslim Action Committee organized Saturday 's protest in the British capital .,O B-org I-org I-org O B-tim O O O O B-gpe O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP POS NN IN DT JJ NN .
The uproar over the satirical cartoons also resulted in the deaths Friday of at least 11 people in Libya and the burning of the Italian consulate in Benghazi .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O,DT NN IN DT JJ NNS RB VBD IN DT NNS NNP IN IN JJS CD NNS IN NNP CC DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
