Serbian prosecutors say authorities have detained four new suspects in connection with the killing of three American brothers of ethnic Albanian origin during the Kosovo conflict .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O O B-org O O,JJ NNS VBP NNS VBP VBN CD JJ NNS IN NN IN DT NN IN CD JJ NNS IN JJ JJ NN IN DT NNP NN .
"Serbian news media identify the suspects as former and serving policemen , including the deputy commander of an elite police unit .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN NNS VBP DT NNS IN JJ CC VBG NNS , VBG DT NN NN IN DT JJ NN NN ."
"Prosecutors linked the men to the executions of the three Bytyqi brothers ( Illy , Mehmet and Agron ) , American citizens who went to Kosovo in 1999 to help ethnic Albanians fighting Yugoslav and Serbian forces in the province .",O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org O B-org O B-org O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O B-gpe O B-gpe O B-gpe O O O O O,"NNS VBD DT NNS TO DT NNS IN DT CD NNP NNS LRB NNP , NNP CC NNP RRB , JJ NNS WP VBD TO NNP IN CD TO VB JJ NNS VBG JJ CC JJ NNS IN DT NN ."
Serbian authorities arrested the three on charges of illegally entering the country .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBN DT CD IN NNS IN RB VBG DT NN .
"Prosecutors say Serbian police later took the brothers away and executed them , dumping their bodies into a mass grave with other ethnic Albanians .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O,"NNS VBP JJ NNS RB VBD DT NNS RB CC VBD PRP , VBG PRP$ NNS IN DT NN NN IN JJ JJ NNS ."
The remains were found in 2001 .,O O O O O B-tim O,DT NNS VBD VBN IN CD .
Two former Serbian policemen are currently on trial for the killings .,O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O,CD JJ JJ NNS VBP RB IN NN IN DT NNS .
U.S. authorities have called on Serbia to punish those responsible .,B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O,NNP NNS VBP VBN IN NNP TO VB DT JJ .
