The World Health Organization is still waiting for China to hand over tissue samples from bird flu outbreaks in poultry .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ RB VBG IN NNP TO VB IN NN NNS IN NN NN NNS IN NN .
WHO officials say getting information on China 's 26 reported outbreaks in animals this year could help formulate effective vaccines and other prevention measures .,B-org O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBP VBG NN IN NNP POS CD JJ NNS IN NNS DT NN MD VB VB JJ NNS CC JJ NN NNS .
China has given no clear explanation of why it has not sent WHO the samples .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O,NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN WRB PRP VBZ RB VBN NNP DT NNS .
Foreign Ministry spokesman Qin Gang told reporters Tuesday that China believes in international cooperation to deal with the threat of bird flu .,B-org I-org O B-per I-per O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NN NNP NNP VBD NNS NNP IN NNP VBZ IN JJ NN TO VB IN DT NN IN NN NN .
"WHO 's regional director for the Western Pacific , Shigeru Omi says that seeing the tissue samples would allow researchers to know what changes the virus is undergoing , which would be crucial to developing an effective vaccine to contain the spread of the disease .",B-org O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP , NNP NNP VBZ IN VBG DT NN NNS MD VB NNS TO VB WP VBZ DT NN VBZ VBG , WDT MD VB JJ TO VBG DT JJ NN TO VB DT NN IN DT NN ."
"Tuesday , Turkey and Romania announced new bird flu outbreaks .",B-tim O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O,"NNP , NNP CC NNP VBD JJ NN NN NNS ."
