The leader of the U.S. opposition Democratic party says he believes the Republicans are going to make illegal immigration an issue in the 2006 midterm elections .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,DT NN IN DT NNP NN JJ NN VBZ PRP VBZ DT NNPS VBP VBG TO VB JJ NN DT NN IN DT CD NN NNS .
"Howard Dean spoke Saturday in Phoenix , Arizona at a Democratic National Committee meeting , where he criticized President Bush 's approach to the issue .",B-per I-per O B-tim O B-geo O B-geo O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD NNP IN NNP , NNP IN DT JJ NNP NNP NN , WRB PRP VBD NNP NNP POS NN TO DT NN ."
"A spokesman for the Republican National Committee , Tucker Bounds , responded by saying the Democrats are out of touch with voters on border security .",O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNPS , VBN IN VBG DT NNPS VBP IN IN NN IN NNS IN NN NN ."
President Bush this past week addressed the issue of illegal immigration .,B-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP DT JJ NN VBD DT NN IN JJ NN .
"Mr. Bush said that while immigrants are important to the United States , the country must control its borders and enforce immigration law .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD IN IN NNS VBP JJ TO DT NNP NNPS , DT NN MD VB PRP$ NNS CC VB NN NN ."
