Venezuelan President Hugo Chavez travels to Cuba late Thursday to accept an award for the preservation of native culture .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ TO NNP JJ NNP TO VB DT NN IN DT NN IN JJ NN .
"Mr. Chavez is accepting an award from UNESCO , the United Nations educational and cultural organization .",B-per I-per O O O O O B-org O O B-org I-org O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBG DT NN IN NNP , DT NNP NNPS JJ CC JJ NN ."
"The Jose Marti International Award , named for the Cuban writer and patriot , is awarded annually to a person or group for their work preserving and promoting Latin American and Caribbean culture .",O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-geo O O,"DT NNP NNP NNP NNP , VBN IN DT JJ NN CC NN , VBZ VBN RB TO DT NN CC NN IN PRP$ NN VBG CC VBG JJ JJ CC JJ NN ."
"While in Cuba , the Venezuelan leader will attend Cuba 's annual International Book Fair , which focuses this year on Venezuela .",O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo O,"IN IN NNP , DT JJ NN MD VB NNP POS JJ NNP NNP NNP , WDT VBZ DT NN IN NNP ."
"President Chavez and Cuban President Fidel Castro are close allies , and often denounce the United States and its policies in the hemisphere .",B-per I-per O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP CC JJ NNP NNP NNP VBP JJ NNS , CC RB VBP DT NNP NNPS CC PRP$ NNS IN DT NN ."
Cuban state media said the visit will strengthen ties between the two governments .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN NNS VBD DT NN MD VB NNS IN DT CD NNS .
