Haiti 's highest court has ruled a Haitian-American businessman may run for president .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS JJS NN VBZ VBN DT JJ NN MD VB IN NN .
Five Supreme Court judges Tuesday unanimously ruled that Dumarsais Simeus could be included on a list of presidential candidates .,O B-org I-org I-org B-tim O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O,CD NNP NNP NNS NNP RB VBD IN NNP NNP MD VB VBN IN DT NN IN JJ NNS .
This overruled a decision by electoral authorities in September to bar his election run on the grounds that he holds U.S. citizenship .,O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,DT VBD DT NN IN JJ NNS IN NNP TO VB PRP$ NN NN IN DT NNS IN PRP VBZ NNP NN .
Mr. Simeus argued that he was born in Haiti and his citizenship should not be an issue .,B-per B-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD IN PRP VBD VBN IN NNP CC PRP$ NN MD RB VB DT NN .
"In an exclusive interview with VOA , Mr. Simeus heralded the Supreme Court 's ruling as a great decision for Haitian people around the world .",O O O O O B-org I-org B-per B-org O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , NNP NNP VBD DT NNP NNP POS NN IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS IN DT NN ."
He added he was not surprised by the outcome .,O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD PRP VBD RB VBN IN DT NN .
"Mr. Simeus has lived in the United States for more than 40 years and owns one of the country 's largest black-owned businesses , Texas-based Simeus Foods International .",B-per B-org O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN DT NNP NNPS IN JJR IN CD NNS CC VBZ CD IN DT NN POS JJS JJ NNS , JJ NNP NNP NNP ."
