They say the unidentified assailant tried to enter by force the office of Erdogan Tezic .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,PRP VBP DT JJ NN VBD TO VB IN NN DT NN IN NNP NNP .
"The man fled the scene , and there were no reports of injuries .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD DT NN , CC EX VBD DT NNS IN NNS ."
"Tezic , a strict secularist , has been highly critical of Turkey 's ruling AK Party .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-org I-org O,"NNP , DT JJ NN , VBZ VBN RB JJ IN NNP POS NN NNP NNP ."
The Islamist-rooted party announced Foreign Minister Adbullah Gul as their presidential candidate Tuesday .,O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-tim O,DT JJ NN VBD NNP NNP NNP NNP IN PRP$ JJ NN NNP .
