"With U.S. legislative elections scheduled for November seventh , both Republicans and Democrats used their weekly radio addresses Saturday to highlight major points in their campaign platforms .",O B-geo O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP JJ NNS VBN IN NNP JJ , DT NNPS CC NNPS VBD PRP$ JJ NN VBZ NNP TO VB JJ NNS IN PRP$ NN NNS ."
President Bush said the tax cuts put in place by his administration are contributing to the growth of the U.S. economy .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,NNP NNP VBD DT NN NNS VBN IN NN IN PRP$ NN VBP VBG TO DT NN IN DT NNP NN .
He said Democrats will raise taxes if they gain control of Congress in the upcoming mid-term legislative elections .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,PRP VBD NNP MD VB NNS IN PRP VBP NN IN NNP IN DT JJ JJ JJ NNS .
"Democrat Jim Webb , who is in a tight race for one of Virginia 's U.S. Senate seats , said President Bush 's decisions in Iraq have undercut the fight against terrorism .",B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-org I-org O O O B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP , WP VBZ IN DT JJ NN IN CD IN NNP POS NNP NNP NNS , VBD NNP NNP POS NNS IN NNP VBP VBN DT NN IN NN ."
"He said a Democratic Congress would demand that the president find what he called "" the real way forward "" in Iraq .",O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,PRP VBD DT JJ NNP MD VB IN DT NN VBP WP PRP VBD LQU DT JJ NN RB RQU IN NNP .
Democrats hope to regain ground in both the House of Representatives and the Senate .,O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-org O,NNPS VBP TO VB NN IN DT DT NNP IN NNPS CC DT NNP .
Currently the Republicans control both .,O O O O O O,RB DT NNPS VBP DT .
