Somalia 's transitional parliament has fired its former speaker and 30 other lawmakers for failing to attend sessions in recent months .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS JJ NN VBZ VBN PRP$ JJ NN CC CD JJ NNS IN VBG TO VB NNS IN JJ NNS .
The parliament had warned absent lawmakers in March that they would lose their seats if they did not begin showing up for meetings .,O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD VBN JJ NNS IN NNP IN PRP MD VB PRP$ NNS IN PRP VBD RB VB VBG RP IN NNS .
"Those fired Tuesday include Sharif Hassan Sheik Aden , who was removed as speaker in January for holding unauthorized negotiations with the government 's Islamist rivals .",O O B-tim O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT VBN NNP VBP NNP NNP NNP NNP , WP VBD VBN IN NN IN NNP IN VBG JJ NNS IN DT NN POS NN NNS ."
Witnesses say about 150 lawmakers approved Tuesday 's decision .,O O O O O O B-tim O O O,NNS VBP IN CD NNS VBD NNP POS NN .
There was no immediate word on how many opposed it .,O O O O O O O O O O O,EX VBD DT JJ NN IN WRB JJ VBD PRP .
The parliament has 275 members in all .,O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ CD NNS IN DT .
It was formed in Kenya in 2004 as part of efforts to establish a new central Somali government .,O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,PRP VBD VBN IN NNP IN CD IN NN IN NNS TO VB DT JJ JJ JJ NN .
That government has struggled to assert authority despite the intervention of Ethiopian troops who helped defeat the Islamists late last year .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBN TO VB NN IN DT NN IN JJ NNS WP VBD VB DT NNPS RB JJ NN .
Somalia has lacked an effective central government since warlords overthrew dictator Mohamed Siad Barre in 1991 .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O,NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNS JJ NN NNP NNP NNP IN CD .
