"Presidential candidate Barack Obama has addressed issues important to women , as he tries to appeal to a critical voting bloc .",O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNS JJ TO NNS , IN PRP VBZ TO VB TO DT JJ NN NN ."
The Democratic senator told a crowd in Florida on Saturday that it is an outrage that women still make 77 cents for every dollar that men make in the United States .,O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT JJ NN VBD DT NN IN NNP IN NNP IN PRP VBZ DT NN IN NNS RB VBP CD NNS IN DT NN IN NNS VBP IN DT NNP NNPS .
"He said his Republican opponent , John McCain , has opposed legislation to help women get equal pay .",O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD PRP$ JJ NN , NNP NNP , VBZ VBN NN TO VB NNS VB JJ NN ."
"He also outlined his support for abortion rights , and promised a plan to provide health insurance for all Americans .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O,"PRP RB VBD PRP$ NN IN NN NNS , CC VBD DT NN TO VB NN NN IN DT NNS ."
"Both Obama and McCain are trying to appeal to women voters , particularly those who supported Senator Hillary Clinton during her run for the Democratic Party presidential nomination .",O B-per O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-org I-org O O O,"DT NNP CC NNP VBP VBG TO VB TO NNS NNS , RB DT WP VBD NNP NNP NNP IN PRP$ NN IN DT NNP NNP JJ NN ."
