"Cuban leader Fidel Castro , who has not been seen in public in more than 16 months because of ill health , says that he will not obstruct the rise of a new generation of leaders .",B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN NNP NNP , WP VBZ RB VBN VBN IN NN IN JJR IN CD NNS IN IN JJ NN , VBZ IN PRP MD RB VB DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNS ."
"In a letter read on Cuban television Monday , Mr. Castro said his elemental duty is not to hold onto positions , or stand in the way of younger people .",O O O O O B-gpe O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN VBN IN JJ NN NNP , NNP NNP VBD PRP$ JJ NN VBZ RB TO VB IN NNS , CC NN IN DT NN IN JJR NNS ."
It was the first suggestion from the 81-year-old Castro that he might step down permanently from the presidency .,O O O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NNP IN PRP MD VB RB RB IN DT NN .
"He handed over power to his brother , Raul , in July 2006 to undergo surgery , but said the move was temporary .",O O O O O O O O B-per O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD RP NN TO PRP$ NN , NNP , IN NNP CD TO JJ NN , CC VBD DT NN VBD JJ ."
He has yet to reclaim presidential powers .,O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ RB TO VB JJ NNS .
Fidel Castro has since appeared in official photographs and videos and regularly is credited with essays on international themes .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ IN VBN IN JJ NNS CC NNS CC RB VBZ VBN IN NNS IN JJ NNS .
Details of his health have been kept secret by the Cuban government .,O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,NNS IN PRP$ NN VBP VBN VBN JJ IN DT JJ NN .
The Cuban leader seized power in a 1959 revolution .,O B-gpe O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT JJ NN VBD NN IN DT CD NN .
