"Nepal says its soldiers backed by helicopters have raided a rebel camp in the remote western part of the country , killing at least 30 Maoist insurgents .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ PRP$ NNS VBN IN NNS VBP VBN DT NN NN IN DT JJ JJ NN IN DT NN , VBG IN JJS CD NNP NNS ."
"The military says the fighting erupted Wednesday in the mountainous Kailali district after the army , acting on a tip , ambushed the hideout .",O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ VBZ DT NN VBD NNP IN DT JJ NNP NN IN DT NN , VBG IN DT NN , VBD DT NN ."
Officials say they believe the rebels were about to launch an attack on an army post .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP PRP VBP DT NNS VBD RB TO VB DT NN IN DT NN NN .
"They say at least two soldiers were wounded in the clash , which lasted several hours .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN , WDT VBD JJ NNS ."
