"The Iranian embassy in Lebanon says four Iranians , including three diplomats , who disappeared in Beirut in 1982 are still alive and are being held in Israel .",O B-gpe O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT JJ NN IN NNP VBZ CD NNS , VBG CD NNS , WP VBD IN NNP IN CD VBP RB JJ CC VBP VBG VBN IN NNP ."
An embassy statement called for their release in a statement Thursday marking the 26th anniversary of their disappearance .,O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-tim O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBN IN PRP$ NN IN DT NN NNP VBG DT JJ NN IN PRP$ NN .
It says Iran has information indicating Israel has detained the four .,O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O,PRP VBZ NNP VBZ NN VBG NNP VBZ VBN DT CD .
The son of one of the missing Iranians Thursday said former prisoners in Israel have confirmed seeing the four alive in Israeli jails .,O O O O O O O B-gpe B-tim O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT NN IN CD IN DT VBG NNS NNP VBD JJ NNS IN NNP VBP VBN VBG DT CD JJ IN JJ NNS .
Tehran says militants from the Christian Lebanese Forces kidnapped the four in Beirut during the 1982 Israeli invasion of Lebanon .,B-org O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim B-gpe O O B-geo O,NNP VBZ NNS IN DT NNP JJ NNP VBD DT CD IN NNP IN DT CD JJ NN IN NNP .
The militant group has said they died in Lebanon .,O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT JJ NN VBZ VBN PRP VBD IN NNP .
"The embassy statement comes a day after the leader of Lebanon 's Hezbollah opposition , Hassan Nasrallah , said Israel would provide the group with information on the fate of the four Iranians as part of a prisoner exchange deal .",O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-org I-org O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBZ DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP POS NNP NN , NNP NNP , VBD NNP MD VB DT NN IN NN IN DT NN IN DT CD NNS IN NN IN DT NN NN NN ."
