The former Hurricane Otis has weakened to a tropical storm as it drifts toward the west coast of Mexico .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT JJ NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO DT JJ NN IN PRP VBZ IN DT JJS NN IN NNP .
The U.S. National Hurricane Center says the center of Otis was 195 kilometers southwest of the Baja California peninsula early Sunday .,O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-tim O,DT NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT NN IN NNP VBD CD NNS JJS IN DT NNP NNP NN RB NNP .
"The storm is moving north slowly , with sustained winds of 115 kilometers per hour .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ VBG RB RB , IN JJ NNS IN CD NNS IN NN ."
"Heavy rains fell in parts of Baja California Saturday , leading authorities to issue evacuation orders for the Cabo San Lucas resort and nearby low-lying areas .",O O O O O O B-geo I-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-org B-geo B-org O O O O O O,"NNP NNS VBD IN NNS IN NNP NNP NNP , VBG NNS TO VB NN NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP NN CC JJ JJ NNS ."
"Meanwhile , Tropical Storm Stan has made landfall over eastern Mexico 's Yucatan peninsula .",O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O,"RB , NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN NN IN JJ NNP POS NNP NN ."
Maximum sustained winds are 65 kilometers per hour .,O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD NNS VBP CD NNS IN NN .
"Weather forecasters say Stan will likely weaken to a tropical depression as it passes over Yucatan , but could regain strength when it moves over the Gulf Of Mexico Monday .",O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo B-tim O,"NNP NNS VBP NNP MD RB VB TO DT JJ NN IN PRP VBZ IN NNP , CC MD VB NN WRB PRP VBZ IN DT NNP IN NNP NNP ."
