Felipe Calderon is a career politician who served as energy secretary under Mexican President Vicente Fox .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O,NNP NNP VBZ DT NN NN WP VBD IN NN NN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP .
"Like his father Luis , who helped found the National Action Party , Calderon has been an influential member of the party , serving as its president .",O O O B-per O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN PRP$ NN NNP , WP VBD VBN DT NNP NNP NNP , NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN DT NN , VBG IN PRP$ NN ."
"During this year 's presidential election campaign , Calderon won the support of Mexico 's business leaders .",B-tim O O O O O O O B-per O O O O B-geo O O O O,"IN DT NN POS JJ NN NN , NNP VBD DT NN IN NNP POS NN NNS ."
"A Harvard-educated lawyer , he has pledged to continue Mr. Fox 's conservative economic policies .",O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O,"DT JJ NN , PRP VBZ VBN TO VB NNP NNP POS JJ JJ NNS ."
He also has pledged to battle crime and attract new investments that would create jobs and help resolve social issues .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP RB VBZ VBN TO VB NN CC VB JJ NNS WDT MD VB NNS CC VB VB JJ NNS .
"During the campaign , he criticized political rival Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador , accusing him of having ties to leftist Venezuelan President Hugo Chavez .",O O O O O O O O B-org I-org B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O,"IN DT NN , PRP VBD JJ JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP , VBG PRP IN VBG NNS TO JJ JJ NNP NNP NNP ."
"Although election officials banned Calderon 's advertisements describing Lopez Obrador as a danger to Mexico , the allegations still dogged his rival .",O O O O B-per O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"IN NN NNS VBD NNP POS NNS VBG NNP NNP IN DT NN TO NNP , DT NNS RB VBD PRP$ NN ."
