Afghan officials say Afghan and NATO forces killed or wounded more than 50 Taliban insurgents in a large operation in southern Afghanistan Sunday .,B-gpe O O B-gpe O B-org O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O,JJ NNS VBP JJ CC NNP NNS VBD CC VBD JJR IN CD NNP NNS IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NNP NNP .
"The Afghan Defense Ministry said in a statement Monday , that the NATO-led International Security Assistance Force backed up the Afghan National Army during the battle in Baluch village in Uruzgan province .",O B-gpe B-org I-org O O O O B-tim O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O B-gpe B-org I-org O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O,"DT JJ NNP NNP VBD IN DT NN NNP , IN DT JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD RP DT JJ NNP NNP IN DT NN IN NNP NN IN NNP NN ."
The ministry said 13 other militants were captured .,O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD CD JJ NNS VBD VBN .
"In southern Afghanistan , officials say a suicide bomber killed three people Monday , when he detonated himself near a police convoy .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,"IN JJ NNP , NNS VBP DT NN NN VBD CD NNS NNP , WRB PRP VBD PRP IN DT NN NN ."
"Police say the attack took place in Lashkar Gah , capital of troubled Helmand Province .",O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNS VBP DT NN VBD NN IN NNP NNP , NN IN JJ NNP NNP ."
A police official said at least five people were wounded in the attack .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN NN VBD IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN .
"Helmand province , the biggest opium producing region of Afghanistan , has endured a wave of Taliban-led violence this year .",B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NN , DT JJS NN VBG NN IN NNP , VBZ VBN DT NN IN JJ NN DT NN ."
