Nigerian authorities say four American hostages were released Wednesday after three weeks in captivity .,B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O O B-tim O B-tim O B-tim I-tim O,JJ NNS VBP CD JJ NNS VBD VBN NNP IN CD NNS IN NN .
Gunmen captured the four contractors on May 9 in the country 's oil-producing Niger Delta region .,O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O B-gpe O O O,NNS VBD DT CD NNS IN NNP CD IN DT NN POS JJ NNP NNP NN .
"The men are employed by the U.S. oil company Chevron , which operates in the area .",O O O O O O B-geo O O B-per O O O O O O O,"DT NNS VBP VBN IN DT NNP NN NN NNP , WDT VBZ IN DT NN ."
"Earlier this week , kidnappers released a Polish oil worker who was abducted near the southern Nigerian city of Warri .",O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O,"RBR DT NN , NNS VBD DT JJ NN NN WP VBD VBN IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP ."
Nearly 20 other foreigners remain in captivity in the Niger Delta .,O O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-org O,RB CD JJ NNS VBP IN NN IN DT NNP NNP .
"Most have been released unharmed , often after their employers paid a ransom .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJS VBP VBN VBN JJ , RB IN PRP$ NNS VBD DT NN ."
Nigeria 's oil exports are down nearly 25 percent since last February because of the unrest .,B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-tim O O O O O,NNP POS NN NNS VBP RB RB CD NN IN JJ NNP IN IN DT NN .
