"Polish parliament has honored a 97-year-old Warsaw woman for saving the lives of 2,500 Jews during the Holocaust .",B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-org O O B-eve O,JJ NN VBZ VBN DT JJ NNP NN IN VBG DT NNS IN CD NNPS IN DT NNP .
Polish senators Wednesday unanimously approved a resolution honoring Irena Sendler and the Polish Underground Council for assisting Jews .,B-gpe O B-tim O O O O O B-per I-per O O B-gpe B-org I-org O O B-org O,JJ NNS NNP RB VBD DT NN VBG NNP NNP CC DT JJ NNP NNP IN VBG NNPS .
President Lech Kaczynski told senators that Sendler was a great hero deserving of the Nobel Prize .,B-per I-per I-per O O O B-per O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,NNP NNP NNP VBD NNS IN NNP VBD DT JJ NN NN IN DT NNP NNP .
Sendler led a group that smuggled Jewish children out of the Warsaw Ghetto to safety until the Nazis arrested her in 1943 .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-org O O O B-tim O,NNP VBD DT NN WDT VBD JJ NNS IN IN DT NNP NNP TO VB IN DT NNPS VBN PRP IN CD .
Israel 's Yad Vashem Holocaust Remembrance authority honored Sendler in 1965 awarding her one of its first medals for people who saved Jews During World War II .,B-geo O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-eve O,NNP POS NNP NNP NNP NNP NN VBD NNP IN CD VBG PRP$ NN IN PRP$ JJ NNS IN NNS WP VBD NNPS IN NNP NNP NNP .
The Nazis forced hundreds of thousands of Jews into the Warsaw Ghetto after they invaded Poland in 1939 .,O O O O O O O B-org O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-geo O B-tim O,DT NNPS VBD NNS IN NNS IN NNPS IN DT NNP NNP IN PRP VBD NNP IN CD .
They summarily executed people who were caught helping those held there .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP RB VBD NNS WP VBD VBN VBG DT VBN RB .
