South Korea 's president says Tokyo must follow up on apologies for its wartime atrocities in the past with actions that reflect true contrition .,B-geo I-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP POS NN VBZ NNP MD VB RP IN NNS IN PRP$ NN NNS IN DT NN IN NNS WDT VBP JJ NN .
"In a meeting with visiting Japanese members of Parliament Friday , President Roh Moo-hyun said Japan has "" nullified "" its previous apologies for World War II era atrocities by its recent actions .",O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo B-tim O B-per I-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-eve O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN IN VBG JJ NNS IN NNP NNP , NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP VBZ LQU VBN RQU PRP$ JJ NNS IN NNP NNP NNP NN NNS IN PRP$ JJ NNS ."
"His comments referred to Tokyo 's approval of a school textbook that minimizes Japan 's record of wartime aggression , as well as controversial visits by Mr. Koizumi and other political figures to the Yasukuni Shrine in Tokyo , widely seen as a symbol of Japanese militarism .",O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per B-geo O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"PRP$ NNS VBD TO NNP POS NN IN DT NN NN WDT VBZ NNP POS NN IN NN NN , RB RB IN JJ NNS IN NNP NNP CC JJ JJ NNS TO DT NNP NNP IN NNP , RB VBN IN DT NN IN JJ NN ."
"As long as such actions recur , Mr. Roh says , Seoul will find it hard to accept the sincerity of Japan 's words .",O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O B-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,"RB RB IN JJ NNS NN , NNP NNP VBZ , NNP MD VB PRP JJ TO VB DT NN IN NNP POS NNS ."
