Researchers say a gel or a cream that allows women to protect themselves from the AIDS virus may be available within the next few years .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O B-tim O O,NNS VBP DT NN CC DT NN WDT VBZ NNS TO VB PRP IN DT NNP NN MD VB JJ IN DT JJ JJ NNS .
"Scientists are discussing the possible breakthrough at a conference in Cape Town , South Africa that began Sunday .",O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo I-geo O O B-tim O,"NNS VBP VBG DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP , NNP NNP WDT VBD NNP ."
"The gel or cream would contain microbicides , a product with an ingredient designed to kill the HIV virus during sexual intercourse .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O,"DT NN CC NN MD VB NNS , DT NN IN DT NN VBN TO VB DT NNP NN IN JJ NN ."
More than a thousand scientists have gathered at the conference to study the progress being made .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJR IN DT CD NNS VBP VBN IN DT NN TO VB DT NN VBG VBN .
Southern Africa has some of the world 's highest HIV infection rates .,B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ DT IN DT NN POS JJS NN NN NNS .
"The United Nations says HIV infection rates among pregnant women are 20 percent or higher in six southern African countries , including South Africa .",O B-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo I-geo O,"DT NNP NNP VBZ NNP NN NNS IN JJ NNS VBP CD NN CC JJR IN CD JJ JJ NNS , VBG NNP NNP ."
"The others are Botswana , Lesotho , Namibia , Swaziland , and Zimbabwe .",O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O B-geo O,"DT NNS VBP NNP , NNP , NNP , NNP , CC NNP ."
