Iran 's constitutional overseers have disqualified nearly all pro-reform candidates in next month 's presidential election .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS JJ NNS VBP VBN RB DT JJ NNS IN JJ NN POS JJ NN .
"Members of the hardline Guardian Council rejected more than 1,000 candidates who had registered to run in the June 17 election .",O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,NNS IN DT JJ NNP NNP VBD JJR IN CD NNS WP VBD VBN TO VB IN DT NNP CD NN .
"The only pro-reform candidate to receive the council 's approval is Mehdi Karroubi , a former speaker of parliament .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O,"DT JJ JJ NN TO VB DT NN POS NN VBZ NNP NNP , DT JJ NN IN NN ."
"Among those rejected was Mustafa Moin , the only candidate of Iran 's largest reformist party , the Islamic Iran Participation Front .",O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O,"IN DT VBN VBD NNP NNP , DT JJ NN IN NNP POS JJS NN NN , DT NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
Iran 's Guardian Council is a group of 12 individuals that supervises elections and makes sure the laws passed by parliament conform to Islamic doctrine .,B-geo O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,NNP POS NNP NNP VBZ DT NN IN CD NNS WDT VBZ NNS CC VBZ JJ DT NNS VBN IN NN VBP TO JJ NN .
