Security officials say two Turkish soldiers have died in clashes with Kurdish fighters in southeastern Turkey .,O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NN NNS VBP CD JJ NNS VBP VBN IN NNS IN NNP NNS IN JJ NNP .
The officials did not release more detail about the fighting in Kurdish-populated areas near the border with Iraq .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNS VBD RB VB JJR NN IN DT NN IN JJ NNS IN DT NN IN NNP .
Fighting between Turkish soldiers and the Kurdistan Workers Party or PKK has increased in recent months .,O O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O,VBG IN JJ NNS CC DT NNP NNP NNP CC NNP VBZ VBN IN JJ NNS .
"In July , Kurdish rebels killed at least 15 Turkish troops in southeastern Turkey .",O B-tim O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo O,"IN NNP , NNP NNS VBD IN JJS CD JJ NNS IN JJ NNP ."
Turkish Prime Minister Recep Tayyip Erdogan said then that Turkey had the right to mount an offensive against PKK bases in northern Iraq .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-org O O O B-geo O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD RB IN NNP VBD DT NN TO VB DT NN IN NNP NNS IN JJ NNP .
The United States opposes a Turkish raid into Iraq and has urged Turkey to work with the U.S. to address the PKK threat .,O B-geo I-geo O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O B-org O O,DT NNP NNPS VBZ DT JJ NN IN NNP CC VBZ VBN NNP TO VB IN DT NNP TO VB DT NNP NN .
The PKK began its battle for autonomy in 1984 .,O B-org O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NNP VBD PRP$ NN IN NN IN CD .
