U.S. Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice says the new U.S. human rights envoy for North Korea will have the opportunity to highlight the communist country 's pressing rights issues .,B-org O O B-org B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ NNP JJ NNS NN IN NNP NNP MD VB DT NN TO VB DT NN NN POS JJ NNS NNS .
Ms. Rice said envoy Jay Lefkowitz will also be able to find out what the United States can do with the rest of the world to improve humanitarian conditions and the rights situation in North Korea .,B-per I-per O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP NNP VBD JJ NNP NNP MD RB VB JJ TO VB RP WP DT NNP NNPS MD VB IN DT NN IN DT NN TO VB JJ NNS CC DT NNS NN IN NNP NNP .
Ms. Rice made the comments in Washington before meeting with the U.S. envoy .,B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O,NNP NNP VBD DT NNS IN NNP IN VBG IN DT NNP NN .
"Also Tuesday , British Foreign Secretary Jack Straw met in London with a former North Korean labor camp prisoner and accused Pyongyang of "" despicable "" human rights abuses .",O B-tim O B-org I-org O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O B-geo B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"RB NNP , NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD IN NNP IN DT JJ JJ JJ NN NN NN CC VBD NNP IN LQU JJ RQU JJ NNS NNS ."
"Mr. Straw said former prisoner Kang Cheol Hwan 's eyewitness accounts of forced labor , public executions , and near-starvation rations show what he called the "" outrages "" committed by the regime .",B-per I-per O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD JJ NN NNP NNP NNP POS NN NNS IN VBN NN , JJ NNS , CC NN NNS VBP WP PRP VBD DT LQU NNS RQU VBN IN DT NN ."
Reaction from Pyongyang was not immediately available .,O O B-geo O O O O O,NN IN NNP VBD RB RB JJ .
