"Iran 's new hard-line President Mahmoud Ahmadinejad has presented his proposed cabinet to parliament , triggering what is expected to be lengthy debate over the qualifications of the 21 nominees .",B-geo O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP$ JJ NN TO NN , VBG WP VBZ VBN TO VB JJ NN IN DT NNS IN DT CD NNS ."
"In an address Sunday , the president said he has nominated "" strong , brave and expert "" people .",O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN NNP , DT NN VBD PRP VBZ VBN LQU JJ , JJ CC JJ LQU NNS ."
"However , some analysts have questioned whether acting Tehran Mayor Ali Saeedlou has the experience to manage Iran 's Oil Ministry .",O O O O O O O O B-geo B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O B-org I-org O,"RB , DT NNS VBP VBN IN VBG NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT NN TO VB NNP POS NNP NNP ."
Debate is expected to last through much of the week .,O O O O O O O O O O O,NN VBZ VBN TO VB IN NN IN DT NN .
Mr. Ahmadinejad also lashed out at Western governments that maintain economic ties with Iran while opposing its nuclear program .,B-per I-per O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,NNP NNP RB VBD RP IN JJ NNS WDT VBP JJ NNS IN NNP IN VBG PRP$ JJ NN .
"It is widely assumed the president was referring to Britain , France and Germany - key trading partners who called an emergency session of the International Atomic Energy Agency earlier this month over Iran 's plans to restart its nuclear fuel program .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBZ RB VBN DT NN VBD VBG TO NNP , NNP CC NNP : JJ NN NNS WP VBD DT NN NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP RBR DT NN IN NNP POS NNS TO VB PRP$ JJ NN NN ."
