The Democratic party used its weekly radio address to praise the accomplishments of the Democratic-led Congress in its first 100 working hours .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBD PRP$ JJ NN NN TO VB DT NNS IN DT JJ NNP IN PRP$ JJ CD VBG NNS .
"A leading member of the House of Representatives , Majority Whip Jim Clyburn , Saturday outlined the measures House members have approved - which include raising the federal minimum wage , lowering interest rates on student loans and expanding stem cell research .",O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org B-per I-per O B-tim O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT VBG NN IN DT NNP IN NNP , NNP NNP NNP NNP , NNP VBD DT NNS NNP NNS VBP VBN : WDT VBP VBG DT JJ NN NN , VBG NN NNS IN NN NNS CC VBG NN NN NN ."
"Clyburn said the Democratic leadership in Congress , in his words , "" reflects the diverse vision , experience and values of the American people . """,B-per O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O,"NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN NNP , IN PRP$ NNS , LQU VBZ DT JJ NN , NN CC NNS IN DT JJ NNS . LQU"
"According to Clyburn , Democrats plan to address the Iraq war , global warming and the budget deficit in coming weeks .",O O B-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"VBG TO NNP , NNPS VBP TO VB DT NNP NN , JJ NN CC DT NN NN IN VBG NNS ."
The president urged Congress to enact wide-ranging reforms to boost the American economy and balance the budget .,O O O B-org O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,DT NN VBD NNP TO VB JJ NNS TO VB DT JJ NN CC VB DT NN .
