Syrian officials say an Islamic militant blew himself up after being stopped at a crossing on the Lebanese border .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,JJ NNS VBP DT JJ NN VBD PRP RP IN VBG VBN IN DT VBG IN DT JJ NN .
"They say the man , Omar Hamra , was the leader of the Islamic militant group al-Tawhid Wal Jihad .",O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O,"PRP VBP DT NN , NNP NNP , VBD DT NN IN DT NNP JJ NN JJ NNP NNP ."
"Syrian security officials say they stopped him at the Jdaydet Yabous border point , which he was trying to cross with fake documents .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN NNS VBP PRP VBD PRP IN DT NNP NNP NN NN , WDT PRP VBD VBG TO VB IN JJ NNS ."
They say the militant shot at police before blowing himself up .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBP DT NN VBD IN NN IN VBG PRP RP .
The incident comes at a time of increased tension between Lebanon 's pro- and anti-Syrian politicians .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ IN DT NN IN VBN NN IN NNP POS JJ CC JJ NNS .
The pro-Syrian Shi'ite militant group Hezbollah says it is planning massive demonstrations this week against the country 's government .,O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNP JJ NN NNP VBZ PRP VBZ VBG JJ NNS DT NN IN DT NN POS NN .
Hezbollah postponed the protests last week following Thursday 's assassination of anti-Syrian politician Pierre Gemayel .,B-org O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-per I-per O,NNP VBD DT NNS JJ NN VBG NNP POS NN IN JJ NN NNP NNP .
