German lawmakers questioned Wednesday government ministers about the CIA abduction of a German citizen who was suspected of being a terrorist .,B-gpe O O B-tim O O O O B-org O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBD NNP NN NNS IN DT NNP NN IN DT JJ NN WP VBD VBN IN VBG DT JJ .
"Lawmakers discussed the case behind closed doors with the Justice , Interior , and Foreign ministers , seeking to determine what the government knew about the incident .",O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBD DT NN IN JJ NNS IN DT NNP , NNP , CC JJ NNS , VBG TO VB WP DT NN VBD IN DT NN ."
The ministers have denied a German role in the abduction .,O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,DT NNS VBP VBN DT JJ NN IN DT NN .
Khaled al-Masri says CIA agents kidnapped him in Macedonia in December of 2003 and took him to Afghanistan for questioning .,B-per I-per O B-org O O O O B-geo O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O B-geo O O O,NNP NNP VBZ NNP NNS VBD PRP IN NNP IN NNP IN CD CC VBD PRP TO NNP IN VBG .
He says he was tortured there during his five month detention and is suing the CIA .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,PRP VBZ PRP VBD VBN RB IN PRP$ CD NN NN CC VBZ VBG DT NNP .
"The CIA is under fire in Europe over reports that it secretly flew terror suspects across the continent , and operated secret prisons in Eastern Europe to house and question the suspects .",O B-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O,"DT NNP VBZ IN NN IN NNP IN NNS IN PRP RB VBD NN NNS IN DT NN , CC VBD JJ NNS IN NNP NNP TO VB CC VB DT NNS ."
