A Yemeni government Web site says the leader of Yemen 's Zaidi Shi'ite rebels may have been fatally wounded in a recent government airstrike .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN NN NN VBZ DT NN IN NNP POS NNP NNP NNS MD VB VBN RB VBN IN DT JJ NN NN .
A message on a Defense Ministry Web site Sunday says there are increasing reports about the death of Abdul-Malik al-Houthi .,O O O O B-org I-org O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O,DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NN NN NNP VBZ EX VBP VBG NNS IN DT NN IN NNP NNP .
The Web site says there are reports that he was severely wounded and died from his injuries and has already been buried in Jabel Tolan in the northern Malaheeth area .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-geo O O,DT NN NN VBZ EX VBP NNS IN PRP VBD RB VBN CC VBN IN PRP$ NNS CC VBZ RB VBN VBN IN NNP NNP IN DT JJ NNP NN .
The rebels did not immediately comment on the report .,O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBD RB RB VB IN DT NN .
"Yemen has been intensifying its operations against rebels and suspected al-Qaida terrorists , conducting a series of airstrikes and other raids that it says resulted in militant deaths and arrests .",B-org O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBN VBG PRP$ NNS IN NNS CC VBN NNP NNS , VBG DT NN IN NNS CC JJ NNS IN PRP VBZ VBN IN NN NNS CC NNS ."
Yemen 's government and Houthi rebels have been battling sporadically since 2004 .,B-org O O O B-org O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP POS NN CC NNP NNS VBP VBN VBG RB IN CD .
