Australian counter-terrorism officers have raided several homes after an investigation revealed that Islamic extremists were planning attacks in Sydney and Melbourne .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,JJ NN NNS VBP VBN JJ NNS IN DT NN VBD IN NNP NNS VBD VBG NNS IN NNP CC NNP .
Police officials say security forces conducted raids Wednesday in the two cities .,O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O,NN NNS VBP NN NNS VBN NNS NNP IN DT CD NNS .
They gave no other details .,O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT JJ NNS .
Australian media reports said police raided four houses in Melbourne and two in Sydney after the government 's spy agency uncovered a plot to attack the famed Sydney Opera House and Harbor Bridge .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-geo I-geo O,JJ NNS NNS VBD NNS VBD CD NNS IN NNP CC CD IN NNP IN DT NN POS NN NN VBD DT NN TO VB DT JJ NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP .
The reports said six people were detained for questioning .,O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBD CD NNS VBD VBN IN VBG .
"Australia has had no major terrorist attacks on its soil , but 88 Australians were among the 202 victims of the Bali bombings in Indonesia in 2002 .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O B-tim O,"NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ JJ NNS IN PRP$ NN , CC CD NNS VBD IN DT CD NNS IN DT NNP NNS IN NNP IN CD ."
