"On Thursday , June 5 , President Bush is scheduled to speak at the groundbreaking of the U.S. Institute of Peace .",O B-tim O B-tim I-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,"IN NNP , NNP CD , NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB IN DT NN IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP ."
Thursday is also the 61st anniversary of the day that then U.S. Secretary of State George Marshall laid out a plan to return a devastated continent to economic health after World War II .,B-tim O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O B-tim I-tim I-tim B-org O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-eve O,NNP VBZ RB DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN RB NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBD RP DT NN TO VB DT JJ NN TO JJ NN IN NNP NNP NNP .
There is no word on what Mr. Bush will say on Thursday .,O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O B-tim O,EX VBZ DT NN IN WP NNP NNP MD VB IN NNP .
But the president last week spoke of the reconstruction of Iraq in the context of the Marshall Plan .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-org I-org O,CC DT NN JJ NN VBD IN DT NN IN NNP IN DT NN IN DT NNP NNP .
"Next week , Mr. Bush will travel to Europe , where he will commemorate the anniversary of the Marshall plan and the Berlin Airlift .",O O O B-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O B-org I-org O,"JJ NN , NNP NNP MD VB TO NNP , WRB PRP MD VB DT NN IN DT NNP NN CC DT NNP NNP ."
"VOA 's George Lewinski remembers the devastation of Europe at that time , and the four-year foreign aid program that was launched in a speech 61 years ago this week .",B-org O B-org I-org O O O O B-geo O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O,"NNP POS NNP NNP VBZ DT NN IN NNP IN DT NN , CC DT JJ JJ NN NN WDT VBD VBN IN DT NN CD NNS RB DT NN ."
