Three of America 's top female rowers work at the same high tech company just outside Washington .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,CD IN NNP POS JJ NN NNS VBP IN DT JJ JJ NN NN RB IN NNP .
The result is a flexible work schedule that allows the young athletes to train for this year 's Olympic games in Beijing .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NN VBZ DT JJ NN NN WDT VBZ DT JJ NNS TO VB IN DT NN POS NNP NNS IN NNP .
"For producer Yi Suli , Elaine Lu has more .",O O B-per I-per O B-per I-per O O O,"IN NN NNP NNP , NNP NNP VBZ RBR ."
