"Hundreds of people in northwest Pakistan watched a public execution Tuesday , after a Taliban court found a man guilty of killing two brothers .",O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-tim O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS IN NNS IN JJ NNP VBD DT JJ NN NNP , IN DT NNP NN VBD DT NN NN IN VBG CD NNS ."
"The execution highlights the influence the Taliban still wields in the North Waziristan tribal region , which borders Afghanistan .",O O O O O O B-org O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NN VBZ DT NN DT NNP RB VBZ IN DT NNP NNP JJ NN , WDT VBZ NNP ."
"Taliban members tied the man 's hands , blindfolded him and brought him out to be shot in public in the town of Miran Shah .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNP NNS VBD DT NN POS NNS , VBD PRP CC VBD PRP RP TO VB VBN IN NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP ."
"A relative of the slain brothers shot and killed the man , after the Taliban court decided that Islamic law called for relatives of the deceased to take their revenge for the murders .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN DT NN NNS VBD CC VBD DT NN , IN DT NNP NN VBD IN NNP NN VBD IN NNS IN DT JJ TO VB PRP$ NN IN DT NNS ."
"Pakistan has carried out multiple offensives against Taliban militants in the northwest tribal belt , most recently in South Waziristan , but troops have yet to launch an assault in North Waziristan .",B-geo O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNP VBZ VBN RP JJ NNS IN NNP NNS IN DT JJS JJ NN , RBS RB IN NNP NNP , CC NNS VBP RB TO VB DT NN IN NNP NNP ."
