"Investigators Monday said soldiers uncovered the remains recently , but that it was not clear who was buried in the graves .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS NNP VBD NNS VBD DT NNS RB , CC IN PRP VBD RB JJ WP VBD VBN IN DT NNS ."
"Word of the discovery came as a woman police chief , Hermila Garcia was ambushed and shot dead on a highway near the town of Meoqui , which is in Chihuahua .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O,"NNP IN DT NN VBD IN DT NN NN NN , NNP NNP VBD VBN CC VBN NN IN DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP , WDT VBZ IN NNP ."
Garcia had served as Meoqui 's police chief since October .,B-per O O O B-geo O O O B-tim I-tim O,NNP VBD VBN IN NNP POS NN NN IN NNP .
