A U.N. official says the World Food Program ( WFP ) plans to stop emergency food shipments to North Korea by January .,O B-org O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-tim O,DT NNP NN VBZ DT NNP NNP NNP LRB NNP RRB VBZ TO VB NN NN NNS TO NNP NNP IN NNP .
"The head of the WFP office in Pyongyang , Richard Ragan , told the Associated Press that the agency plans to shift its focus to development programs .",O O O O B-org O O B-geo O B-per I-per O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN DT NNP NN IN NNP , NNP NNP , VBD DT NNP NNP IN DT NN VBZ TO VB PRP$ NN TO NN NNS ."
He says North Korea requested the shift and the government says it has enough food to meet its peoples ' needs .,O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ NNP NNP VBD DT NN CC DT NN VBZ PRP VBZ JJ NN TO VB PRP$ NNS POS NNS .
But Mr. Ragan says he still believes there are large numbers of North Koreans who are struggling to meet their basic food needs .,O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,CC NNP NNP VBZ PRP RB VBZ EX VBP JJ NNS IN NNP NNS WP VBP VBG TO VB PRP$ JJ NN NNS .
"The World Food Program started emergency food aid to North Korea in 1995 , and has so far distributed $ 1.5 billion worth of food there .",O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP NNP VBD NN NN NN TO NNP NNP IN CD , CC VBZ RB RB VBN $ CD CD NN IN NN RB ."
