A New York jury Wednesday found Vladimir Kuznetsov guilty of helping to launder hundreds of thousands of dollars in bribes by foreign companies seeking U.N. contracts .,O B-geo I-geo O B-tim O B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O,DT NNP NNP NN NNP VBD NNP NNP NN IN VBG TO VB NNS IN NNS IN NNS IN NNS IN JJ NNS VBG NNP NNS .
Kuznetsov faces as much as 20 years in prison when he is sentenced in June .,B-org O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP VBZ RB JJ IN CD NNS IN NN WRB PRP VBZ VBN IN NNP .
"The employee , Alexander Yakovlev , pleaded guilty in 2005 and testified against Kuznetsov .",O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-tim O O O B-org O,"DT NN , NNP NNP , VBD JJ IN CD CC VBD IN NNP ."
