Residents of one New Orleans ' neighborhood began returning home Monday despite federal warnings that the hurricane-ravaged city still has health and safety problems .,O O O B-org I-org O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN CD NNP NNP POS NN VBD VBG NN NNP IN JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN RB VBZ NN CC NN NNS .
"The most urgent warning came today from President Bush , who said there is "" deep concern "" that Tropical Storm Rita will hit New Orleans and cause more flooding .",O O O O O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-nat I-nat I-nat O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O,"DT RBS JJ NN VBD NN IN NNP NNP , WP VBD EX VBZ LQU JJ NN RQU WDT NNP NNP NNP MD VB NNP NNP CC VB JJR NN ."
"Mr. Bush said he shares the dream of Mayor Ray Nagin to get New Orleans up and running but said authorities must be what he called "" realistic "" about bringing people home .",B-per I-per O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD PRP VBZ DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP TO VB NNP NNP IN CC VBG CC VBD NNS MD VB WP PRP VBD LQU JJ RQU IN VBG NNS NN .
"Mr. Nagin has stood by his plan for evacuees to return one neighborhood at a time , starting with the relatively undamaged Algiers district Monday .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo B-tim O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN PRP$ NN IN NNS TO VB CD NN IN DT NN , VBG IN DT RB JJ NNP NN NNP ."
The head of the federal relief effort insists New Orleans is not ready to be re-populated .,O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O,DT NN IN DT JJ NN NN VBZ NNP NNP VBZ RB JJ TO VB JJ .
Concerns raised by Coast Guard Vice Admiral Thad Allen include the city 's lack of clean drinking water and the weakened state of levees damaged by Hurricane Katrina .,O O O B-org I-org O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBP DT NN POS NN IN JJ NN NN CC DT JJ NN IN NNS VBN IN NNP NNP .
