"Thousands of people in London 's Trafalgar Square protested Israel 's actions , while counter-protesters stationed themselves nearby to call out support for Israel .",O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNS IN NNS IN NNP POS NNP NNP VBD NNP POS NNS , IN NNS VBD PRP JJ TO VB RP NN IN NNP ."
"Thousands also marched in Brussels , Belgium , and in Madrid , Spain .",O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O B-geo O B-geo O,"NNS RB VBD IN NNP , NNP , CC IN NNP , NNP ."
The rallies were a continuation of the protests that took place a day earlier in cities worldwide .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O,DT NNS VBD DT NN IN DT NNS WDT VBD NN DT NN RBR IN NNS JJ .
"Saturday , several thousand demonstrators in Washington gathered in a park across the street from the White House to protest Israel 's offensive against Gaza .",B-tim O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O O O B-geo O,"NNP , JJ CD NNS IN NNP VBD IN DT NN IN DT NN IN DT NNP NNP TO VB NNP POS NN IN NNP ."
The protesters carried Palestinian flags and shouted slogans in support of the Palestinians in Gaza .,O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-geo O,DT NNS VBD JJ NNS CC VBD NNS IN NN IN DT NNS IN NNP .
"In France , tens of thousands of people took to the streets of the capital , Paris .",O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"IN NNP , NNS IN NNS IN NNS VBD TO DT NNS IN DT NN , NNP ."
Protests were also held in smaller cities around the country .,O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBD RB VBN IN JJR NNS IN DT NN .
