"A German-born Turkish citizen held for more than four years at the U.S. terrorism detention center at the American naval base in Guantanamo Bay , Cuba has been released and returned to Germany .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT JJ JJ NN VBD IN JJR IN CD NNS IN DT NNP NN NN NN IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP NNP , NNP VBZ VBN VBN CC VBN TO NNP ."
"Attorney Bernhard Docke said his client , Murat Kurnaz , was flown to a U.S. Air Force base in Germany and released Thursday .",O B-per I-per O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-geo O O B-tim O,"NNP NNP NNP VBD PRP$ NN , NNP NNP , VBD VBN TO DT NNP NNP NNP NN IN NNP CC VBN NNP ."
Kurnaz was released after long negotiations between U.S. and German officials .,B-per O O O O O O B-geo O B-gpe O O,NNP VBD VBN IN JJ NNS IN NNP CC JJ NNS .
Docke said his client will undergo a medical examination and will refuse interviews as he adjusts to his newfound freedom .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD PRP$ NN MD VB DT JJ NN CC MD VB NNS IN PRP VBZ TO PRP$ JJ NN .
"Kurnaz was arrested in Pakistan in 2001 and transferred to Guantanamo Bay , where he remained for more than four years .",B-per O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD VBN IN NNP IN CD CC VBN TO NNP NNP , WRB PRP VBD IN JJR IN CD NNS ."
"Docke said his client suffered abuse in the U.S. military prison , including sexual humiliation .",B-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD PRP$ NN VBD NN IN DT NNP JJ NN , VBG JJ NN ."
