"U.S. President Barack Obama made his first official visit to the Federal Bureau of Investigation , calling on FBI employees to remain committed to the values of liberty , integrity and the rule of law no matter what challenges they face .",B-geo B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD PRP$ JJ JJ NN TO DT NNP NNP IN NNP , VBG IN NNP NNS TO VB JJ TO DT NNS IN NN , NN CC DT NN IN NN DT NN WP VBZ PRP VBP ."
"Speaking at FBI headquarters in Washington , President Obama said Tuesday that "" living "" such values means maintaining higher standards than enemies of the United States .",O O B-org O O B-geo O B-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"VBG IN NNP NN IN NNP , NNP NNP VBD NNP IN LQU VBG RQU JJ NNS VBZ VBG JJR NNS IN NNS IN DT NNP NNPS ."
"Using al-Qaida as an example , Mr. Obama noted many changes in recent years in the threats facing the U.S. But he said what makes the country "" so special "" is that Americans are willing to uphold their own values even when it is difficult to do so .",O B-org O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"VBG NNP IN DT NN , NNP NNP VBD JJ NNS IN JJ NNS IN DT NNS VBG DT NNP CC PRP VBD WP VBZ DT NN RQU RB JJ LQU VBZ IN NNS VBP JJ TO VB PRP$ JJ NNS RB WRB PRP VBZ JJ TO VB RB ."
"Mr. Obama praised the FBI for its ability to adapt to new dangers in an ever-changing world , while calling for a rejection of the notion that the U.S. must ever choose between its security and its ideals .",B-per I-per O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD DT NNP IN PRP$ NN TO VB TO JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN , IN VBG IN DT NN IN DT NN IN DT NNP MD RB VB IN PRP$ NN CC PRP$ NNS ."
