The U.S. government is warning Americans in the Middle East and North Africa to be extra vigilant following the death of Palestinian leader Yasser Arafat .,O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-org I-org O,DT NNP NN VBZ VBG NNS IN DT NNP NNP CC NNP NNP TO VB JJ NN VBG DT NN IN JJ NN NNP NNP .
"In a travel alert issued Thursday , the State Department said Mr. Arafat 's death has the potential to produce demonstrations and unrest throughout the region .",O O O O O B-tim O O B-org I-org O B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN NN VBN NNP , DT NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP POS NN VBZ DT NN TO VB NNS CC NN IN DT NN ."
The department expressed concern that extremists may be planning attacks against Westerners and oil workers in the Persian Gulf area .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O,DT NN VBD NN IN NNS MD VB VBG NNS IN NNS CC NN NNS IN DT NNP NNP NN .
"The U.S. Embassy in Egypt says Americans in that country should be especially vigilant on Friday , when Mr. Arafat 's funeral takes place in Cairo .",O B-org I-org O B-geo O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-per B-org O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NNP NNP IN NNP VBZ NNS IN DT NN MD VB RB NN IN NNP , WRB NNP NNP POS NN VBZ NN IN NNP ."
The embassy has advised Americans to avoid parts of Cairo where demonstrations could take place .,O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBN NNS TO VB NNS IN NNP WRB NNS MD VB NN .
It said those sites include Cairo 's Tahrir Square and the areas around mosques and universities .,O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT NNS VBP NNP POS NNP NNP CC DT NNS IN NNS CC NNS .
