"The U.N. human rights chief in Haiti says the situation in the Caribbean nation is , "" catastrophic . """,O B-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NN NNS NN IN NNP VBZ DT NN IN DT JJ NN VBZ , LQU JJ . LQU"
"In a news conference in the capital Port-au-Prince Friday , Thierry Fagart said there were multiple instances of summary executions , mob violence , torture and arbitrary arrests .",O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN NN IN DT NN NN NNP , NNP NNP VBD EX VBD JJ NNS IN NN NNS , NN NN , NN CC JJ NNS ."
He noted that police and civilians were responsible for committing grave violations in the poor Caribbean nation .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,PRP VBD IN NNS CC NNS VBD JJ IN VBG JJ NNS IN DT JJ NNP NN .
"The comments come just days after a U.N. report said the security situation in Haiti was improving , but still fragile .",O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"DT NNS VBP RB NNS IN DT NNP NN VBD DT NN NN IN NNP VBD VBG , CC RB JJ ."
"Earlier this week , Haiti 's Police Chief Mario Andresol said 15 police officers are facing prosecution for criminal activities .",O O O O B-geo O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,"RBR DT NN , NNP POS NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD CD NNS NNS VBP VBG NN IN JJ NNS ."
