Britain 's Deputy Prime Minister John Prescott has condemned the manner in which Iraq 's former leader Saddam Hussein was put to death .,B-geo O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-per I-per O O O O O,NNP POS NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN WDT NNP POS JJ NN NNP NNP VBD VBN TO NN .
"Mr. Prescott said Tuesday the taunting and baiting that accompanied Saddam 's execution was "" deplorable . """,B-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O O B-per O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD NNP DT NN CC NN WDT VBD NNP POS NN VBD RQU JJ . LQU
He said those responsible should be punished .,O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT JJ MD VB VBN .
"The British official said regardless of what views one holds of capital punishment , no one can endorse the manner in which the former Iraqi dictator was executed .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBD RB IN WP NNS CD VBZ IN NN NN , DT NN MD VB DT NN IN WDT DT JJ JJ NN VBD VBN ."
Mr. Prescott was referring to leaked video footage showing witnesses chanting and telling the former Iraqi leader to go to hell as he was about to be hanged .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD VBG TO JJ NN NN VBG NNS VBG CC VBG DT JJ JJ NN TO VB TO NN IN PRP VBD RB TO VB VBN .
"Brtitish Prime Minister Tony Blair , on vacation in Florida , has not spoken publicly about Saddam Hussein 's execution .",O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP , IN NN IN NNP , VBZ RB VBN RB IN NNP NNP POS NN ."
