"The Indian Ocean provides major sea routes connecting the Middle East , Africa , and East Asia with Europe and the Americas .",O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O,"DT NNP NNP VBZ JJ NN NNS VBG DT NNP NNP , NNP , CC NNP NNP IN NNP CC DT NNPS ."
It carries a particularly heavy traffic of petroleum and petroleum products from the oilfields of the Persian Gulf and Indonesia .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O,PRP VBZ DT RB JJ NN IN NN CC NN NNS IN DT NNS IN DT NNP NNP CC NNP .
Its fish are of great and growing importance to the bordering countries for domestic consumption and export .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP$ NN VBP IN JJ CC VBG NN TO DT VBG NNS IN JJ NN CC NN .
"Fishing fleets from Russia , Japan , South Korea , and Taiwan also exploit the Indian Ocean , mainly for shrimp and tuna .",O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O,"VBG NNS IN NNP , NNP , NNP NNP , CC NNP RB VBP DT NNP NNP , RB IN NN CC NN ."
"Large reserves of hydrocarbons are being tapped in the offshore areas of Saudi Arabia , Iran , India , and western Australia .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O B-geo O,"JJ NNS IN NNS VBP VBG VBN IN DT JJ NNS IN NNP NNP , NNP , NNP , CC JJ NNP ."
An estimated 40 % of the world 's offshore oil production comes from the Indian Ocean .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT VBN CD NN IN DT NN POS JJ NN NN VBZ IN DT NNP NNP .
"Beach sands rich in heavy minerals and offshore placer deposits are actively exploited by bordering countries , particularly India , South Africa , Indonesia , Sri Lanka , and Thailand .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O B-per B-gpe O O B-geo O,"NN NNS JJ IN JJ NNS CC JJ NN NNS VBP RB VBN IN VBG NNS , RB NNP , NNP NNP , NNP , NNP NNP , CC NNP ."
