"Dozens of people took to the streets in Bangladesh 's capital of Dhaka Tuesday , to protest military rule in Burma .",O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNS IN NNS VBD TO DT NNS IN NNP POS NN IN NNP NNP , TO VB JJ NN IN NNP ."
"The group , mostly made up of Burmese nationals , demonstrated outside Burma 's embassy among tight police security .",O O O O O O O B-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"DT NN , RB VBN IN IN JJ NNS , VBD IN NNP POS NN IN JJ NNS NN ."
Protesters called for an end to military rule and pledged their support for pro-democracy leader Aung San Suu Kyi .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O,NNS VBD IN DT NN TO JJ NN CC VBD PRP$ NN IN JJ NN NNP NNP NNP NNP .
The group also demanded the international community do more to stop the violence and restore democracy to Burma .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NN RB VBD DT JJ NN VBP JJR TO VB DT NN CC VB NN TO NNP .
"Several thousand Burmese refugees , mostly Muslims known as Rohingyas , have fled to neighboring Bangladesh after alleged persecution by the Burmese government .",O O B-org O O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O,"JJ CD JJ NNS , RB NNPS VBN IN NNP , VBP VBN TO VBG NNP IN VBN NN IN DT JJ NN ."
