"The United Nations Security Council has called on Lebanon 's parliament to hold presidential elections as scheduled next month in "" an atmosphere free of violence , fear , and intimidation . """,O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NNP POS NN TO VB JJ NNS IN VBN JJ NN IN LQU DT NN NN IN NN , NN , CC NN . LQU"
"The council said in a statement Thursday that there should be no "" foreign interference "" in the election .",O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD IN DT NN NNP IN EX MD VB DT RQU JJ NN LQU IN DT NN .
"Tuesday , Lebanon 's parliament speaker postponed a session to elect a new president until October 23 after lawmakers failed to reach a consensus on a presidential candidate .",B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP , NNP POS NN NN VBD DT NN TO VB DT JJ NN IN NNP CD IN NNS VBD TO VB DT NN IN DT JJ NN ."
"The Hezbollah-led pro-Syrian opposition stayed away from parliament , preventing a two-thirds quorum required for a vote .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ JJ NN VBD RB IN NN , VBG DT NNS NN VBN IN DT NN ."
The opposition has vowed to prevent Lebanon 's anti-Syrian government from electing one of its members as president .,O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBN TO VB NNP POS JJ NN IN VBG CD IN PRP$ NNS IN NN .
Outgoing pro-Syrian President Emile Lahoud ends his term on November 24 .,O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-tim I-tim O,VBG JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP$ NN IN NNP CD .
A series of anti-Syrian figures have been killed in Lebanon in recent years .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O,DT NN IN JJ NNS VBP VBN VBN IN NNP IN JJ NNS .
