"Ivory Coast 's ruling party is calling for 4,000 French peacekeepers in the country to leave .",B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,NNP NNP POS NN NN VBZ VBG IN CD JJ NNS IN DT NN TO VB .
"The head of the Ivorian Popular Front , Pascal Affi N'Guessan , said that peace in Ivory Coast can only be achieved when French forces withdraw .",O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O B-gpe O O O,"DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP NNP , VBD IN NN IN NNP NNP MD RB VB VBN WRB JJ NNS VB ."
"He also called late Friday , for the dissolution of a group of foreign mediators overseeing the country 's struggling peace process .",O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP RB VBD JJ NNP , IN DT NN IN DT NN IN JJ NNS VBG DT NN POS VBG NN NN ."
French troops helped to end a civil war which erupted in 2002 after rebels tried to out President Laurent Gbagbo .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O,JJ NNS VBD TO VB DT JJ NN WDT VBD IN CD IN NNS VBD TO IN NNP NNP NNP .
Supporters of the president have accused the former colonial power of showing bias towards the rebels .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN DT NN VBP VBN DT JJ NN NN IN VBG NN IN DT NNS .
"Earlier this month , President Gbagbo said that U.N. and French peacekeepers are free to leave Ivory Coast because the peace process has failed .",O O O O B-per I-per O O B-geo O B-gpe O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O,"RBR DT NN , NNP NNP VBD IN NNP CC JJ NNS VBP JJ TO VB NNP NNP IN DT NN NN VBZ VBN ."
