"The Futuna island group was discovered by the Dutch in 1616 and Wallis by the British in 1767 , but it was the French who declared a protectorate over the islands in 1842 , and took official control of them between 1886 and 1888 .",O B-gpe O O O O O O B-gpe O B-tim O B-geo O O B-gpe O B-tim O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,"DT NNP NN NN VBD VBN IN DT NNS IN CD CC NNP IN DT NNS IN CD , CC PRP VBD DT NNS WP VBD DT NN IN DT NNS IN CD , CC VBD JJ NN IN PRP IN CD CC CD ."
"Notably , Wallis and Futuna was the only French colony to side with the Vichy regime during World War II , a phase that ended in May of 1942 with the arrival of 2,000 American troops .",O O B-per O B-org O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-org O O O O B-eve O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O B-gpe O O,"RB , NNP CC NNP VBD DT JJ JJ NN TO NN IN DT NNP NN IN NNP NNP NNP , DT NN WDT VBD IN NNP IN CD IN DT NN IN CD JJ NNS ."
"In 1959 , the inhabitants of the islands voted to become a French overseas territory and officially assumed this status in July 1961 .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"IN CD , DT NNS IN DT NNS VBD TO VB DT JJ JJ NN CC RB VBD DT NN IN NNP CD ."
