World number-two tennis player Rafael Nadal of Spain has pulled out of next month 's Chennai Open tournament in India because he still has not fully recovered from a foot injury .,O O O O B-per I-per O B-geo O O O O O O O B-eve I-eve O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,NN JJ NN NN NNP NNP IN NNP VBZ VBN IN IN JJ NN POS NNP NNP NN IN NNP IN PRP RB VBZ RB RB VBN IN DT NN NN .
Organizers say the 2005 French Open champion will be replaced in the draw by Croatia 's Ivan Ljubicic .,O O O O B-eve I-eve O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-per I-per O,NNS VBP DT CD JJ NNP NN MD VB VBN IN DT NN IN NNP POS NNP NNP .
"Ljubicic is ranked ninth in the world and got a wild card entry into the event , which begins January second in Chennai , also known as Madras .",B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-geo O O O O B-geo O,"NNP VBZ VBN JJ IN DT NN CC VBD DT JJ NN NN IN DT NN , WDT VBZ NNP JJ IN NNP , RB VBN IN NNP ."
"The loss of Nadal is a big blow to the tournament , which is also raising funds for tsunami victims in southern India .",O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"DT NN IN NNP VBZ DT JJ NN TO DT NN , WDT VBZ RB VBG NNS IN NN NNS IN JJ NNP ."
"However , Nadal says he is donating $ 25,000 to the Tamil Nadu state government 's main relief fund .",O O B-per O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O,"RB , NNP VBZ PRP VBZ VBG $ CD TO DT NNP NNP NN NN POS JJ NN NN ."
