"Iran has denied as "" baseless "" U.S. charges that it is pursuing nuclear weapons , sponsoring terrorism and depriving its citizens of freedom .",B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBN IN RQU JJ RQU NNP NNS IN PRP VBZ VBG JJ NNS , VBG NN CC VBG PRP$ NNS IN NN ."
"Foreign Ministry spokesman Hamid Reza Asefi said Thursday that the accusations made in President Bush 's State of the Union address show Mr. Bush is , in his words , "" closing his eyes to the realities of the Islamic Republic with its deep-rooted freedom and democracy . """,B-org I-org O B-per I-per I-per O B-tim O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O B-per B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NN NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP IN DT NNS VBN IN NNP NNP POS NN IN DT NNP NN VBP NNP NNP VBZ , IN PRP$ NNS , LQU VBG PRP$ NNS TO DT NNS IN DT NNP NNP IN PRP$ JJ NN CC NN . LQU"
"Referring to the 1979 Islamic Revolution , Mr. Asefi said his country "" 26 years ago put an end to the dominant influence and presence of the United States in Iran . """,O O O B-tim B-geo I-geo O B-per I-per O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O,"VBG TO DT CD NNP NNP , NNP NNP VBD PRP$ NN LQU CD NNS RB VBD DT NN TO DT JJ NN CC NN IN DT NNP NNPS IN NNP . LQU"
"In his speech Wednesday night , Mr. Bush said the United States stands with the Iranian people as they seek liberty .",O O O B-tim I-tim O B-per B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,"IN PRP$ NN NNP NN , NNP NNP VBD DT NNP NNPS VBZ IN DT JJ NNS IN PRP VBP NN ."
"He also said Iran is the world 's primary state sponsor of terror , and is pursuing nuclear weapons .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP RB VBD NNP VBZ DT NN POS JJ NN NN IN NN , CC VBZ VBG JJ NNS ."
