Iraqi Prime Minister Nouri al-Maliki says his critics in U.S. Congress do not appreciate his government 's achievements .,B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP$ NNS IN NNP NNP VBP RB VB PRP$ NN POS NNS .
Mr. Maliki told reporters Sunday in Baghdad that some criticism from Washington is encouraging people trying to destabilize Iraq .,B-per I-per O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP VBD NNS NNP IN NNP IN DT NN IN NNP VBZ JJ NNS VBG TO VB NNP .
U.S. Democratic Party presidential candidate Senator Hillary Rodham Clinton and some other U.S. lawmakers have called for Iraq 's parliament to replace Mr. Maliki .,B-org I-org I-org O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O B-per I-per O,NNP NNP NNP JJ NN NNP NNP NNP NNP CC DT JJ NNP NNS VBP VBN IN NNP POS NN TO VB NNP NNP .
"The Iraqi leader says U.S. critics may not know "" the size of the destruction that Iraq passed through , "" and do not appreciate "" the big role of the Iraqi government and its achievements , such as stopping the civil and sectarian war . """,O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBZ NNP NNS MD RB VB LQU DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP VBD IN , RQU CC VBP RB VB LQU DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN CC PRP$ NNS , JJ IN VBG DT JJ CC JJ NN . RQU"
"The remarks came as U.S. Ambassador Ryan Crocker and the top American military commander , General David Petraeus , prepare to deliver reports to Congress next week on the progress achieved since President Bush ordered nearly 30 thousand more troops to Iraq .",O O O O B-org I-org B-per I-per O O O B-gpe O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NNS VBD IN NNP NNP NNP NNP CC DT JJ JJ JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP , VBP TO VB NNS TO NNP JJ NN IN DT NN VBN IN NNP NNP VBD RB CD CD JJR NNS TO NNP ."
