A South African-led delegation is set to arrive in Ivory Coast Sunday to advise its government on legal changes needed to satisfy a 2003 peace deal .,O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,DT NNP JJ NN VBZ VBN TO VB IN NNP NNP NNP TO VB PRP$ NN IN JJ NNS VBN TO VB DT CD NN NN .
"South Africa 's Defense Minister Mosiuoa Lekota is leading the team , which includes lawyers and judges from South Africa , Burundi and Rwanda .",B-geo I-geo O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O B-geo O,"NNP NNP POS NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBG DT NN , WDT VBZ NNS CC NNS IN NNP NNP , NNP CC NNP ."
South African spokesman Bheki Khumalo says the team will present its findings on whether new laws passed in Ivory Coast comply with the Linas-Marcoussis peace accord .,B-geo I-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NN NNP NNP VBZ DT NN MD VB PRP$ NNS IN IN JJ NNS VBN IN NNP NNP VB IN DT NNP NN NN .
The French-brokered deal calls for reforming citizenship requirements on candidates for Ivorian president .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT JJ NN VBZ IN VBG NN NNS IN NNS IN JJ NN .
Ivorian rebels have criticized President Laurent Gbagbo for failing to change the citizenship rule ahead of elections in October .,B-gpe O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,JJ NNS VBP VBN NNP NNP NNP IN VBG TO VB DT NN NN RB IN NNS IN NNP .
