Pakistani authorities say three more men arrested in connection with a car bomb attack outside an American fast food restaurant in Karachi Tuesday have confessed to the crime .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP CD JJR NNS VBN IN NN IN DT NN NN NN IN DT JJ JJ NN NN IN NNP NNP VBP VBN TO DT NN .
"A senior police official , Deputy Inspector General Mazoor Mughal , told reporters the suspects were arrested Thursday in an eastern part of the city .",O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN NN , NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP , VBD NNS DT NNS VBD VBN NNP IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN ."
"He identified the suspects as members of a little-known separatist group from the troubled southwestern province of Baluchistan , the Baluchistan Liberation Army .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org I-org O,"PRP VBD DT NNS IN NNS IN DT JJ NN NN IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP , DT NNP NNP NNP ."
"On Wednesday , President Pervez Musharraf announced the arrest of one man , also a Baluch , in connection with the bombing that killed three people and injured 22 others .",O B-tim O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN CD NN , RB DT NN , IN NN IN DT NN WDT VBD CD NNS CC VBD CD NNS ."
"Baluch tribesmen have been waging a low-level insurgency for years , demanding more jobs and higher royalties from the Islamabad government for the region 's natural resources .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNS VBP VBN VBG DT JJ NN IN NNS , VBG JJR NNS CC JJR NNS IN DT NNP NN IN DT NN POS JJ NNS ."
