The International Olympic Committee has expelled Bulgarian member Ivan Slavkov for ethical misconduct connected to London 's hosting the 2012 Summer Games .,O O O B-org O O B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim B-eve I-eve O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN JJ NN NNP NNP IN JJ NN VBN TO NNP POS VBG DT CD NNPS NNPS .
The vote was 82-12 with five abstentions during a special hearing in Singapore .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,DT NN VBD JJ IN CD NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
Slavkov was expelled for bringing the IOC into disrepute .,B-per O O O O O B-org O O O,NNP VBD VBN IN VBG DT NNP IN NN .
"The Bulgarian spoke in his own defense , but was not able to persuade the hearing .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD IN PRP$ JJ NN , CC VBD RB JJ TO VB DT NN ."
Slavkov will lose his position as head of the Bulgarian National Olympic Committee .,B-per O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,NNP MD VB PRP$ NN IN NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP .
The Bulgarian was suspended last year at the Athens Olympics after being videotaped in a television program indicating that IOC members were willing to accept bribes to secure their votes for London 's bid to host the 2012 Olympics .,O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT NN VBD VBN JJ NN IN DT NNP NNPS IN VBG VBN IN DT NN NN VBG IN NNP NNS VBD JJ TO VB NNS TO VB PRP$ NNS IN NNP POS NN TO VB DT CD NNS .
London won the right to host the Games Wednesday by a vote of 54-50 .,B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O,NNP VBD DT NN TO VB DT NNPS NNP IN DT NN IN CD .
