The head of the U.S. Central Intelligence Agency said the United States is no longer using secret prisons overseas to detain and interrogate terror suspects .,O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NNP NNPS VBZ RB RB VBG JJ NNS RB TO VB CC VB NN NNS .
CIA Director Leon Panetta said in a letter to employees Thursday that the spy agency plans to permanently shut down the facilities .,B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD IN DT NN TO NNS NNP IN DT NN NN VBZ TO RB VB RP DT NNS .
"The administration of former President George W. Bush was criticized for using the secret prisons in the war on terrorism , with critics saying that detainees could be tortured outside the reach of U.S. judicial system .",O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,"DT NN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD VBN IN VBG DT JJ NNS IN DT NN IN NN , IN NNS VBG IN NNS MD VB VBN IN DT NN IN NNP JJ NN ."
The Bush administration had said the United States does not condone or conduct torture .,O B-per O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBD VBN DT NNP NNPS VBZ RB VB CC VB NN .
President Barack Obama has stipulated that all U.S. interrogations will be guided by the U.S. Army Field Manual - which forbids harsh techniques like waterboarding that were used during the Bush administration .,B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O,NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN DT NNP NNS MD VB VBN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP : WDT VBZ JJ NNS IN NN WDT VBD VBN IN DT NNP NN .
