"North Korea 's nuclear weapons program dominated the two-day meeting of Asia and European foreign ministers in Kyoto , Japan .",B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,"NNP NNP POS JJ NNS NN VBD DT JJ NN IN NNP CC JJ JJ NNS IN NNP , NNP ."
"In a closing statement , the ministers strongly urged North Korea to make a strategic decision to denuclearize the Korean Peninsula and to return to negotiations without delay .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-gpe B-org O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN NN , DT NNS RB VBD NNP NNP TO VB DT JJ NN TO VB DT JJ NNP CC TO VB TO NNS IN NN ."
"North Korea has boycotted talks with China , South Korea , Russia , Japan and the United States since June .",B-geo I-geo O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo B-tim I-tim O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNS IN NNP , NNP NNP , NNP , NNP CC DT NNP NNPS IN NNP ."
"Friday , Japan hardened its stance , saying it will consider referring North Korea to the U.N. Security Council for action unless talks resume .",B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O,"NNP , NNP VBD PRP$ NN , VBG PRP MD VB VBG NNP NNP TO DT NNP NNP NNP IN NN IN NNS VBP ."
""" They have the Security Council in their minds , as well as five-party talks , six minus North Korea , "" Foreign Ministry spokesman Hatsuhisa Takashima said .",O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-org I-org I-org O B-per I-per O O,"LQU PRP VBP DT NNP NNP IN PRP$ NNS , RB RB IN JJ NNS , CD CC NNP NNP , LQU NNP NNP NN NNP NNP VBD ."
"North Korea is insisting on massive aid and specific security guarantees , before it will consider honoring its agreements to be nuclear free .",B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBG IN JJ NN CC JJ NN NNS , IN PRP MD VB VBG PRP$ NNS TO VB JJ JJ ."
