A U.S.-owned luxury cruise ship attacked by pirates off the coast of Somalia has docked in the Seychelles after experts removed parts of a grenade shell embedded in a passenger cabin .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN NN NN VBN IN NNS IN DT NN IN NNP VBZ VBN IN DT NNS IN NNS VBD NNS IN DT NN NN VBN IN DT NN NN .
"The ship , its crew and 151 passengers - mostly from the United States , Australia and Europe - arrived in the Seychelles late on Sunday .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O,"DT NN , PRP$ NN CC CD NNS : RB IN DT NNP NNPS , NNP CC NNP : VBD IN DT NNS RB IN NNP ."
"The Seaborne Spirit was sailing to Mombasa , Kenya , Saturday , when attackers on two speedboats pulled alongside and opened fire with assault rifles and rocket-propelled grenades .",O B-org I-org O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP VBD VBG TO NNP , NNP , NNP , WRB NNS IN CD NNS VBD RB CC VBD NN IN NN NNS CC JJ NNS ."
The cruise ship changed course and escaped without any serious injuries among the passengers .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN NN VBD NN CC VBD IN DT JJ NNS IN DT NNS .
One crew member suffered minor injuries .,O O O O O O O,CD NN NN VBD JJ NNS .
"Pirates have launched around 25 attacks off Somalia since March -- in some cases , targeting ships carrying food aid .",O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP VBN IN CD NNS IN NNP IN NNP : IN DT NNS , VBG NNS VBG NN NN ."
A British maritime union has called for the waters to be declared a war zone .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN NN VBZ VBN IN DT NNS TO VB VBN DT NN NN .
