The United Nations peacekeeping force in Lebanon says Israel has lifted it two-month-long sea blockade of the country .,O B-org I-org O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBG NN IN NNP VBZ NNP VBZ VBN PRP JJ NN NN IN DT NN .
The commander of the U.N. force said Israel Friday lifted the sea blockade as an international naval force began patrolling the Lebanese coastline .,O O O O B-org O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT NN IN DT NNP NN VBD NNP NNP VBD DT NN NN IN DT JJ JJ NN VBD VBG DT JJ NN .
Israel lifted its air blockade of Lebanon on Thursday .,B-geo O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O,NNP VBD PRP$ NN NN IN NNP IN NNP .
Israel imposed the blockade at the start of its war against Hezbollah to prevent the guerrilla group from getting arms supplies from Iran through Syria .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,NNP VBD DT NN IN DT NN IN PRP$ NN IN NNP TO VB DT NN NN IN VBG NNS NNS IN NNP IN NNP .
A U.N.-mandated ceasefire ended the war last month .,O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBD DT NN JJ NN .
"In other developments , Israeli media say Prime Minister Ehud Olmert has indicated he would be prepared to discuss the status of the disputed Shebaa Farms region if Lebanon disarms Hezbollah and fulfills its obligations under U.N. resolutions ( 1701 and 1559 ) .",O O O O B-gpe O O B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo O B-org O O O O O B-org O O O O B-tim O O,"IN JJ NNS , JJ NNS VBP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP MD VB VBN TO VB DT NN IN DT JJ NNP NNPS NN IN NNP VBZ NNP CC VBZ PRP$ NNS IN NNP NNS LRB CD CC CD RRB ."
The reports say Mr. Olmert made the remark during talks with visiting Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov .,O O O B-per B-org O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O,DT NNS VBP NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN NNS IN VBG JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP .
