European space agency officials say the Huygens space probe has successfully entered the atmosphere of Saturn 's moon Titan in the final stage of a seven-year journey .,O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,JJ NN NN NNS VBP DT NNP NN NN VBZ RB VBN DT NN IN NNP POS NN NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN .
"The probe , operated jointly by NASA , the European Space Agency and the Italian Space Agency , deployed a huge parachute Friday for a descent toward the surface .",O O O O O O B-org O O B-org I-org I-org O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O,"DT NN , VBP RB IN NNP , DT NNP NNP NNP CC DT NNP NNP NNP , VBD DT JJ NN NNP IN DT NN IN DT NN ."
Titan is the only moon in the solar system known to have a significant atmosphere .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN VBN TO VB DT JJ NN .
