"Sirens wailed across Israel Monday morning , as Israelis stood in silence in memory of the six million Jews who perished in the Holocaust .",O O O B-geo B-tim I-tim O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNS VBD IN NNP NNP NN , IN NNS VBD IN NN IN NN IN DT CD CD NNPS WP VBD IN DT NNP ."
"Israeli officials , Holocaust survivors and foreign dignitaries are in Jerusalem for solemn ceremonies in observance of Holocaust Remembrance Day .",B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo B-tim I-tim O,"JJ NNS , NNP NNS CC JJ NNS VBP IN NNP IN JJ NNS IN NN IN NNP NNP NNP ."
"This year 's theme at the Yad Vashem Holocaust Memorial is the "" Voices of the Survivors . """,O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O,DT NN POS NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT RQU NNS IN DT NNS . LQU
"All across Israel , flags are flying at half-staff , places of entertainment are closed , and radio and television broadcasts are dedicated to remembering the Holocaust .",O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,"DT IN NNP , NNS VBP VBG IN NN , NNS IN NN VBP VBN , CC NN CC NN NNS VBP VBN TO VBG DT NNP ."
"More than 200,000 Holocaust survivors currently live in Israel .",O O O B-org O O O O B-geo O,JJR IN CD NNP NNS RB VBP IN NNP .
Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu said at the opening ceremonies Sunday evening that free societies should have learned from the Holocaust the danger of remaining quiet in the face of evil .,B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD IN DT NN VBZ NNP NN IN JJ NNS MD VB VBN IN DT NNP DT NN IN VBG JJ IN DT NN IN NN .
"U.S. President Barack Obama recognized Holocaust Remembrance Day by saying the "" hateful stereotypes and prejudice "" against Jewish people must not be tolerated .",B-geo B-per I-per I-per O B-org I-org B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP NNP IN VBG DT LQU JJ NNS CC NN RQU IN JJ NNS MD RB VB VBN .
