"India 's prime minister has called the Iraqi elections "" a historic day for the people of Iraq , "" saying New Delhi will do everything possible to assist Baghdad in its efforts to rebuild the country .",B-geo O B-per O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ NN VBZ VBN DT JJ NNS LQU DT JJ NN IN DT NNS IN NNP , LQU VBG NNP NNP MD VB DT JJ TO VB NNP IN PRP$ NNS TO VB DT NN ."
Prime Minister Manmohan Singh also expressed hope for warm relations with the future democratic government of Iraq .,B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP NNP NNP RB VBD NN IN JJ NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP .
"Meanwhile , Pakistan said it hopes the Iraqi elections will lead to stability and the country will regain full control over its rich oil reserves .",O O B-per O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , NNP VBD PRP VBZ DT JJ NNS MD VB TO NN CC DT NN MD VB JJ NN IN PRP$ JJ NN NNS ."
"Foreign office spokesman Masood Khan said Pakistan also hopes the election process culminates in a stable , unified , sovereign and independent Iraq .",O O O B-per I-per O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"JJ NN NN NNP NNP VBD NNP RB VBZ DT NN NN VBZ IN DT JJ , JJ , JJ CC JJ NNP ."
"In Kabul , Afghan President Hamid Karzai said he was encouraged by reports of higher than expected voter turnout .",O B-geo O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD PRP VBD VBN IN NNS IN JJR IN VBN NN NN ."
