"A United Nations agency says that while Burma responded quickly to outbreaks of bird flu last month , it needs more help to continue its fight against the disease in the long term .",O B-org I-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNPS NN VBZ IN IN NNP VBD RB TO NNS IN NN NN JJ NN , PRP VBZ JJR NN TO VB PRP$ NN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN ."
"The Food and Agriculture Organization , FAO , says that the source of an outbreak that spread to four townships around Rangoon in late February is still unknown .",B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O O O,"DT NNP CC NNP NNP , NNP , VBZ IN DT NN IN DT NN WDT VBD TO CD NNS IN NNP IN JJ NNP VBZ RB JJ ."
"To help prevent further outbreaks , the FAO says that more intensive surveillance was needed around Rangoon .",O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"TO VB VB JJ NNS , DT NNP VBZ IN JJR JJ NN VBD VBN IN NNP ."
"It is also recommending that the military-ruled country strengthen its lab capabilities , animal health services and public awareness campaigns .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBZ RB VBG IN DT JJ NN VB PRP$ NN NNS , JJ NN NNS CC JJ NN NNS ."
The FAO is providing Burma with $ 1.4 million in emergency assistance to help fight the disease .,B-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP VBZ VBG NNP IN $ CD CD IN NN NN TO VB VB DT NN .
