"The U.S. Defense Department has ordered 1,500 additional U.S. troops to Iraq to provide security ahead of elections in October and December .",O B-org I-org I-org O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN CD JJ NNP NNS TO NNP TO VB NN RB IN NNS IN NNP CC NNP .
A Defense Department statement said Wednesday that two battalions from the 82nd Airborne Division will deploy to Iraq for about 120 days to support security efforts during the election period .,O B-org I-org O O B-tim O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O B-geo O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NN VBD NNP IN CD NNS IN DT CD NNP NNP MD VB TO NNP IN RB CD NNS TO VB NN NNS IN DT NN NN .
"The statement said they will join 180,000 Iraqi security forces and 138,000 coalition forces and that additional adjustments to troop levels for the elections are possible .",O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD PRP MD VB CD JJ NN NNS CC CD NN NNS CC IN JJ NNS TO NN NNS IN DT NNS VBP JJ .
A referendum on the constitution is scheduled for mid-October and parliamentary elections are due in December .,O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NN IN DT NN VBZ VBN IN NNP CC JJ NNS VBP JJ IN NNP .
"Earlier , President Bush reiterated in a speech to military families in Idaho that U.S. forces will not stage an early withdrawal from Iraq .",O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"RB , NNP NNP VBD IN DT NN TO JJ NNS IN NNP IN NNP NNS MD RB VB DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
He said an early withdrawal would embolden the terrorists and create a staging ground to launch more attacks against Americans .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O,PRP VBD DT JJ NN MD VB DT NNS CC VB DT NN NN TO VB JJR NNS IN NNS .
