"A U.S. military statement from Iraq says operations at Baghdad 's notorious Abu Ghraib prison will end within months , and that prisoners there will be transferred to a new facility now under construction .",O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP JJ NN IN NNP VBZ NNS IN NNP POS JJ NNP NNP NN MD VB IN NNS , CC IN NNS EX MD VB VBN TO DT JJ NN RB IN NN ."
"Military spokesman , Lieutenant-Colonel Barry Johnson said no precise dates have yet been set for the transfer .",O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NN , NNP NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NNS VBP RB VBN VBN IN DT NN ."
But he said said the plan is to complete the changeover within two or three months .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O,CC PRP VBD VBD DT NN VBZ TO VB DT NN IN CD CC CD NNS .
"In Washington , the Pentagon confirmed the timetable for completion of the new facility , Camp Cropper .",O B-geo O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O,"IN NNP , DT NNP VBD DT NN IN NN IN DT JJ NN , NNP NNP ."
But a spokesman said it has not been determined whether opening the new facility will lead to the closing of Abu Ghraib .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O,CC DT NN VBD PRP VBZ RB VBN VBN IN VBG DT JJ NN MD VB TO DT NN IN NNP NNP .
"Pentagon spokesman , Bryan Whitman also said talk of a timetable for closing Abu Ghraib is premature .",B-org O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O,"NNP NN , NNP NNP RB VBD NN IN DT NN IN VBG NNP NNP VBZ JJ ."
"He said it is not clear whether U.S. forces , which operate the facility , will stop using it as others become available .",O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD PRP VBZ RB JJ IN NNP NNS , WDT VBP DT NN , MD VB VBG PRP IN NNS VBP JJ ."
