Russia 's President says the country will stop following the World Trade Organization 's rules if Moscow is not admitted to the trade group .,B-geo O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NNP VBZ DT NN MD VB VBG DT NNP NNP NNP POS NNS IN NNP VBZ RB VBN TO DT NN NN .
Vladimir Putin made the comments Tuesday to a business group in Moscow .,B-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP VBD DT NNS NNP TO DT NN NN IN NNP .
"Over the past decade , Russia has made agreements with numerous WTO members , but ca n't join unless it gets an agreement with one last nation - the United States .",O O B-tim I-tim O B-geo O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"IN DT JJ NN , NNP VBZ VBN NNS IN JJ NNP NNS , CC MD RB VB IN PRP VBZ DT NN IN CD JJ NN IN DT NNP NNPS ."
"Washington and Moscow have been haggling over protection for intellectual property , access to Russia 's banking sector , and other issues .",B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"NNP CC NNP VBP VBN VBG IN NN IN JJ NN , NN TO NNP POS NN NN , CC JJ NNS ."
A news report on Bloomberg says Russia is the largest economy still outside the WTO .,O O O O B-org O B-geo O O O O O O O B-org O,DT NN NN IN NNP VBZ NNP VBZ DT JJS NN RB IN DT NNP .
Moscow is pressing to join before the G8 summit meeting that begins July 15 in Russia .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-geo O,NNP VBZ VBG TO VB IN DT NNP NN NN WDT VBZ NNP CD IN NNP .
