"Israeli Prime Minister Ariel Sharon has returned to work , a week after suffering a mild stroke .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NN , DT NN IN VBG DT JJ NN ."
Mr. Sharon held his weekly meeting with his Cabinet Sunday .,B-per I-per O O O O O O B-org B-tim O,NNP NNP VBD PRP$ JJ NN IN PRP$ NNP NNP .
"The severely overweight and self-admitted food lover joked with Cabinet members about his health scare , warning them about the dangers of eating fried foods during the Jewish Hanukkah holiday , which begins Sunday .",O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"DT RB JJ CC JJ NN NN VBN IN NNP NNS IN PRP$ NN NN , VBG PRP IN DT NNS IN VBG JJ NNS IN DT JJ NNP NN , WDT VBZ NNP ."
Mr. Sharon spent most of last week resting after being hospitalized for a mild stroke .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD JJS IN JJ NN VBG IN VBG VBN IN DT JJ NN .
Doctors say the illness has not caused any permanent damage .,O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP DT NN VBZ RB VBN DT JJ NN .
Public opinion surveys show the Israeli prime minister is expected to win a third term as leader of a new centrist party in a March 28 general election .,O O O O O B-gpe B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O,JJ NN NNS VBP DT JJ JJ NN VBZ VBN TO VB DT JJ NN IN NN IN DT JJ NN NN IN DT NNP CD JJ NN .
