The Israeli army has banned citizens from moving to Jewish settlements in the Gaza Strip over fears their presence could complicate Israel 's planned withdrawal from the area .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBZ VBN NNS IN VBG TO JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNP IN NNS PRP$ NN MD VB NNP POS VBN NN IN DT NN .
In recent days supporters have vowed to swell the Gaza settler population to resist the army 's planned July evacuation .,O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,IN JJ NNS NNS VBP VBN TO VB DT NNP NN NN TO VB DT NN POS JJ NNP NN .
"The army said Friday no relocations to Gaza will be approved , but it was unclear how it would enforce the ban .",O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD NNP DT NNS TO NNP MD VB VBN , CC PRP VBD JJ WRB PRP MD VB DT NN ."
The army also said it will start removing some equipment from the Gaza Strip over the next two weeks in preparation for the evacuation .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O O O,DT NN RB VBD PRP MD VB VBG DT NN IN DT NNP NNP IN DT JJ CD NNS IN NN IN DT NN .
"Thursday , 13 Palestinian militant groups pledged to extend an informal truce through the end of this year , in exchange for some Israeli concessions .",B-tim O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"NNP , CD JJ JJ NNS VBD TO VB DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN DT NN , IN NN IN DT JJ NNS ."
"Israel welcomed the move , but said Palestinians must also disarm the militants .",B-org O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,"NNP VBD DT NN , CC VBD NNS MD RB VB DT NNS ."
