An appeals court has voted to strip former Chilean dictator Augusto Pinochet of his immunity from prosecution in a human rights case involving the infamous Villa Grimaldi prison .,O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O,DT NNS NN VBZ VBN TO VB JJ JJ NN NNP NNP IN PRP$ NN IN NN IN DT JJ NNS NN VBG DT JJ NNP NNP NN .
Friday 's ruling must be upheld by the Supreme Court before Pinochet can be tried .,B-tim O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-per O O O O,NNP POS NN MD VB VBN IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP MD VB VBN .
"The case against Pinochet would charge him with 23 cases of torturing political prisoners , and 36 disappearances of people who were imprisoned .",O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN NNP MD VB PRP IN CD NNS IN VBG JJ NNS , CC CD NNS IN NNS WP VBD VBN ."
"Chile 's president-elect Michelle Bachelet was among the political dissidents held at the Santiago prison in the mid-1970s , although she is not involved in the case .",B-geo O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ NNP NNP VBD IN DT JJ NNS VBN IN DT NNP NN IN DT NNS , IN PRP VBZ RB VBN IN DT NN ."
"Pinochet , who seized power in a 1973 military coup against a socialist government and ruled for 17 years , faces trial in several other human rights cases .",B-per O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP , WP VBD NN IN DT CD JJ NN IN DT JJ NN CC VBD IN CD NNS , VBZ NN IN JJ JJ JJ NNS NNS ."
His immunity from prosecution is decided on a case-by-case basis .,O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP$ NN IN NN VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NN .
