A Russian contractor for the United Nations and an Indian businessman are the latest kidnap victims in Haiti 's recent rash of ransom abductions .,O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNPS CC DT JJ NN VBP DT JJS NN NNS IN NNP POS JJ NN IN NN NNS .
Officials said Thursday the men were snatched in separate incidents this week in Haiti 's capital and kidnappers later demanded ransoms for their release .,O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBD NNP DT NNS VBD VBN IN JJ NNS DT NN IN NNP POS NN CC NNS RB VBD NNS IN PRP$ NN .
"The Associated Press reports that the U.N. estimates some 130 people , mostly affluent businessmen , were kidnapped last month alone in Port-au-Prince .",B-org I-org I-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NNP NNP VBZ IN DT NNP VBZ DT CD NNS , RB JJ NNS , VBD VBN JJ NN RB IN NNP ."
