Officials in Yemen say a suicide bomber has killed a policeman and wounded 20 others in the eastern part of the country .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNP VBP DT NN NN VBZ VBN DT NN CC VBD CD NNS IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN .
Officials say the bomber rammed his car into a police station in Yemen 's Hadramut province Friday .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-tim O,NNS VBP DT NN VBD PRP$ NN IN DT NN NN IN NNP POS NNP NN NNP .
The blast also caused damage to several nearby buildings .,O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN RB VBD NN TO JJ JJ NNS .
There has been no claim of responsibility .,O O O O O O O O,EX VBZ VBN DT NN IN NN .
"In January , gunmen in Hadramut province opened fire on tourists , killing two Belgians and wounding four others .",O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,"IN NNP , NNS IN NNP NN VBD NN IN NNS , VBG CD NNS CC VBG CD NNS ."
Yemen in the ancestral home of Osama bin Laden .,B-geo O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O,NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP NNP .
Several recent attacks have been blamed on al-Qaida terrorists .,O O O O O O O B-org O O,JJ JJ NNS VBP VBN VBN IN NNP NNS .
The government has also been battling Shi'ite insurgents in the northwest of the country since 2004 .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT NN VBZ RB VBN VBG NNP NNS IN DT JJS IN DT NN IN CD .
The conflict has killed thousands of people .,O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBN NNS IN NNS .
