A published report says a top United Nations envoy will tell Syrian President Bashar al-Assad that his country will face political and economic isolation if Syria does not quickly and completely withdraw troops from Lebanon .,O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT JJ NN VBZ DT JJ NNP NNPS NN MD VB JJ NNP NNP NNP IN PRP$ NN MD VB JJ CC JJ NN IN NNP VBZ RB RB CC RB VB NNS IN NNP .
The Washington Post says U.N. envoy Terje Roed-Larsen plans to deliver the message to Syria at a meeting Saturday in Damascus .,B-org I-org I-org O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O B-geo O,DT NNP NNP VBZ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ TO VB DT NN TO NNP IN DT NN NNP IN NNP .
The newspaper quotes U.N. officials as saying the international community is united in insisting that Damascus comply with U.N. resolution 1559 calling for an end to Syria 's 15-year military intervention in Lebanon .,O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O,DT NN VBZ NNP NNS IN VBG DT JJ NN VBZ VBN IN VBG DT NNP VB IN NNP NN CD NN IN DT NN TO NNP POS JJ JJ NN IN NNP .
Syrian troops there were continuing a redeployment that began earlier this week after Mr. Assad announced plans to move Syrian forces in a phased pullback to the country 's border with Lebanon .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per B-tim O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNS EX VBD VBG DT NN WDT VBD RBR DT NN IN NNP NNP VBD NNS TO VB JJ NNS IN DT VBN NN TO DT NN POS NN IN NNP .
