The Paris club of creditors is reported near agreement on a deal to waive billions of dollars in Iraqi debt owed member nations .,O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,DT NNP NN IN NNS VBZ VBN IN NN IN DT NN TO VB NNS IN NNS IN JJ NN VBN NN NNS .
"The United States , Germany , France and 16 other industrialized nations agreed early Sunday to write off up to $ 33 billion .",O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"DT NNP NNPS , NNP , NNP CC CD JJ JJ NNS VBD JJ NNP TO VB RP RB TO $ CD CD ."
Officials say only Russia has not signed off on the deal .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP RB NNP VBZ RB VBN RP IN DT NN .
Russian negotiators in Paris are reported awaiting Moscow 's final approval of the agreement .,B-gpe O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,JJ NNS IN NNP VBP VBN VBG NNP POS JJ NN IN DT NN .
"In other developments , the Iraqi government says its first democratic national elections in decades will take place January 30 .",O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"IN JJ NNS , DT JJ NN VBZ PRP$ JJ JJ JJ NNS IN NNS MD VB NN NNP CD ."
"An Iraqi elections spokesman , Farid Ayar , says ballots for a new national assembly , provincial councils and a Kurdish regional parliament will be cast nationwide , including areas now gripped by insurgency .",O B-gpe O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNS NN , NNP NNP , VBZ NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN , JJ NNS CC DT JJ JJ NN MD VB VBN JJ , VBG NNS RB VBN IN NN ."
He did not say why the polls were moved from the earlier date of January 27 .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,PRP VBD RB VB WRB DT NNS VBD VBN IN DT JJR NN IN NNP CD .
There were no U.S. reports of major combat operations today .,O O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim O,EX VBD DT NNP NNS IN JJ NN NNS NN .
