A court in Britain has convicted three men on terrorism charges - including one that was only 16 when he was arrested .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN NNP VBZ VBN CD NNS IN NN NNS : VBG CD WDT VBD RB CD WRB PRP VBD VBN .
"London 's Blackfriars Crown Court Monday found Hammaad Munshi , Sultan Muhammad , and Aabid Khan guilty of possessing documents useful to terrorists .",B-geo O B-org I-org I-org B-tim O B-geo I-geo O B-per I-per O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP , NNP NNP , CC NNP NNP NN IN VBG NNS JJ TO NNS ."
"The men used the Internet to recruit followers , disseminate propaganda , and spread information about use of weapons and manufacture of bombs .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS VBD DT NN TO VB NNS , VB NN , CC VB NN IN NN IN NNS CC NN IN NNS ."
"Prosecutors said Munshi , now 18 , is the youngest person ever convicted of a terrorism offense in Britain .",O O B-geo O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNS VBD NNP , RB CD , VBZ DT JJS NN RB VBN IN DT NN NN IN NNP ."
He is the grandson of a leading Islamic scholar .,O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ DT NN IN DT VBG JJ NN .
Sentencing has been set for Tuesday .,O O O O O B-tim O,NN VBZ VBN VBN IN NNP .
