Western diplomats say Iran has agreed to let the International Atomic Energy Agency have greater overview of a uranium-enriching site in Iran .,O O O B-geo O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O,JJ NNS VBP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB DT NNP NNP NNP NNP VBP JJR NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
"The officials , speaking on condition of anonymity , made the announcement to news agencies Friday .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"DT NNS , VBG IN NN IN NN , VBD DT NN TO NN NNS NNP ."
There was no immediate confirmation from Iran .,O O O O O O B-geo O,EX VBD DT JJ NN IN NNP .
"On Thursday , U.S. Vice President Joe Biden said he expected the United Nations will impose a new round of sanctions against Iran by the beginning of next month over its nuclear program .",O B-tim O B-geo B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD PRP VBD DT NNP NNP MD VB DT JJ NN IN NNS IN NNP IN DT NN IN JJ NN IN PRP$ JJ NN ."
"The United States and its allies believe Iran is secretly trying to develop nuclear weapons , but Tehran has insisted its nuclear program is for peaceful , civilian purposes .",O B-org I-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNPS CC PRP$ NNS VBP NNP VBZ RB VBG TO VB JJ NNS , CC NNP VBZ VBN PRP$ JJ NN VBZ IN JJ , JJ NNS ."
