Officials in the Philippines say Muslim separatists in the southern part of the country have pledged not to attack U.S. troops when they hold an exercise on the island of Jolo next month .,O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,NNS IN DT NNPS VBP NNP NNS IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN VBP VBN RB TO VB NNP NNS WRB PRP VBP DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP JJ NN .
"In a personal message , Muslim rebel leader Nur Misuari - who has been in detention for four years - ordered his followers to stay in their camps and avoid what he called "" untoward "" incidents while the American troops are in the region .",O O O O O B-geo O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ NN , NNP JJ NN NNP NNP : WP VBZ VBN IN NN IN CD NNS IN VBD PRP$ NNS TO VB IN PRP$ NNS CC VB WP PRP VBD RQU JJ LQU NNS IN DT JJ NNS VBP IN DT NN ."
"Local military commander Brigadier-General Mohammad Ben Dolorfino delivered the letter Friday to Habier Malik , spiritual leader of Misuari 's followers .",O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O B-per O O O,"JJ JJ NN JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN NNP TO NNP NNP , JJ NN IN NNP POS NNS ."
Misuari issued the directive after meeting with government officials in his cell south of Manila earlier in the week .,B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,NNP VBD DT NN IN VBG IN NN NNS IN PRP$ NN NN IN NNP RBR IN DT NN .
The United States has been sending small units of military advisers to the Philippines to provide humanitarian assistance and counter-terrorism training to Filipino troops .,O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT NNP NNPS VBZ VBN VBG JJ NNS IN JJ NNS TO DT NNPS TO VB JJ NN CC NN NN TO JJ NNS .
