The U.S. military in Iraq says coalition forces have killed 14 suspected terrorists and rescued a kidnapped Iraqi policeman in two separate operations .,O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,DT NNP NN IN NNP VBZ NN NNS VBP VBN CD JJ NNS CC VBN DT VBN JJ NN IN CD JJ NNS .
"A statement said 10 terrorists believed linked to al-Qaida were killed Wednesday , when coalition troops raided their hideout near the town of Muqdadiyah north of Baghdad .",O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O,"DT NN VBD CD NNS VBN VBN IN NNP VBD VBN NNP , WRB NN NNS VBD PRP$ NN IN DT NN IN NNP NN IN NNP ."
It said the Iraqi policeman was found blindfolded and shackled to the floor inside the building .,O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT JJ NN VBD VBN JJ CC JJ TO DT NN IN DT NN .
The military said four terrorists were killed and 48 others detained in a separate operation in the restive town of Ramadi late Tuesday .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O,DT NN VBD CD NNS VBD VBN CC CD NNS VBN IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP JJ NNP .
"In a separate statement , the military said a U.S. Marine died today from wounds sustained while operating in Al Anbar province , west of Baghdad .",O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-geo O,"IN DT JJ NN , DT NN VBD DT NNP NN VBD NN IN NNS VBN IN VBG IN NNP NNP NN , NN IN NNP ."
"Tuesday , an explosion in a coffee shop in a Shi'ite district of Baghdad killed at least 14 people and wounded 16 others .",B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP , DT NN IN DT NN NN IN DT NNP NN IN NNP VBD IN JJS CD NNS CC VBD CD NNS ."
There were conflicting reports on whether the explosion was caused by a suicide bomber or mortar rounds .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,EX VBD VBG NNS IN IN DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NN NN CC NN NNS .
