A lawyer for one of Saddam Hussein 's top aides in U.S. custody says a detained Iraqi female scientist is dying of cancer and should be freed immediately .,O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN CD IN NNP NNP POS JJ NNS IN NNP NN VBZ DT JJ JJ NN NN VBZ VBG IN NN CC MD VB VBN RB .
"Badee Izzat Aref , representing former Deputy Prime Minister Tariq Aziz says Mr. Aziz told him of Huda Ammash 's deteriorating condition .",B-org I-org I-org O O O O B-per O B-per I-per O B-per I-per O O O B-org I-org O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP , VBG JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNP NNP VBD PRP IN NNP NNP POS JJ NN ."
He called on international humanitarian agencies to intervene for her release .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD IN JJ JJ NNS TO VB IN PRP$ NN .
"It is not clear how Mr. Aziz knew about Mrs. Ammash 's condition , or if she indeed has cancer .",O O O O O B-per I-per O O B-per B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBZ RB JJ WRB NNP NNP VBD IN NNP NNP POS NN , CC IN PRP RB VBZ NN ."
"Mrs. Ammash , who is also known as "" Mrs. Anthrax , "" has been in U.S. custody since May 2003 .",B-per B-geo O O O O O O O B-per B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim I-tim O,"NNP NNP , WP VBZ RB VBN IN LQU NNP NNP , LQU VBZ VBN IN NNP NN IN NNP CD ."
She was the only woman among 55 most-wanted members of Saddam 's regime .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,PRP VBD DT JJ NN IN CD JJ NNS IN NNP POS NN .
"Officials hope she may provide information about Saddam 's alleged weapons of mass destruction , a key reason the U.S. launched its invasion of Iraq in April 2003 .",O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O B-tim I-tim O,"NNS VBP PRP MD VB NN IN NNP POS JJ NNS IN NN NN , DT JJ NN DT NNP VBD PRP$ NN IN NNP IN NNP CD ."
