Iraqi authorities say gunmen have kidnapped a top Iraqi army officer - the latest insurgent abduction of a senior Iraqi official .,B-gpe O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,JJ NNS VBP NNS VBP VBN DT JJ JJ NN NN IN DT JJS JJ NN IN DT JJ JJ NN .
Police said Brigadier General Jalal Mohammed Saleh was pulled out of his car in western Baghdad Tuesday and taken away .,O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O,NNP VBD NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD VBN IN IN PRP$ NN IN JJ NNP NNP CC VBN RB .
He was the commander of a special armored division .,O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NN .
Insurgents have kidnapped several senior Iraqi civilian and military officials .,O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,NNS VBP VBN JJ JJ JJ JJ CC JJ NNS .
Some of them have been killed .,O O O O O O O,DT IN PRP VBP VBN VBN .
"Meanwhile , the U.S. military says one American Marine was killed by an explosion in Al Anbar province Monday .",O O O B-geo O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-tim O,"RB , DT NNP NN VBZ CD NNP NNP VBD VBN IN DT NN IN NNP NNP NN NNP ."
"In another development , the military says a riot erupted at Camp Bucca prison in southern Iraq last week , when some unruly prisoners were being transferred to a different compound .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN , DT NN VBZ DT NN VBD IN NNP NNP NN IN JJ NNP JJ NN , WRB DT JJ NNS VBD VBG VBN TO DT JJ NN ."
It says the situation was quickly brought under control and four prison guards and 12 inmates suffered minor injuries .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ DT NN VBD RB VBN IN NN CC CD NN NNS CC CD NNS VBD JJ NNS .
