North Korea says joint military exercises between South Korea and the United States are a prelude to a U.S. attack on North Korea .,B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP NNP VBZ JJ JJ NNS IN NNP NNP CC DT NNP NNPS VBP DT NN TO DT NNP NN IN NNP NNP .
"In a statement Saturday , an unnamed North Korean military spokesman said the drills , which begin later this month , are designed to compel North Korea to end its nuclear program .",O O O B-tim O O O B-geo B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O,"IN DT NN NNP , DT JJ JJ JJ JJ NN VBD DT NNS , WDT VBP RB DT NN , VBP VBN TO VB NNP NNP TO VB PRP$ JJ NN ."
North Korea 's nuclear capability was the key issue at six-party disarmament talks held in Beijing in recent weeks .,B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O,NNP NNP POS JJ NN VBD DT JJ NN IN JJ NN NNS VBN IN NNP IN JJ NNS .
Disagreement led negotiators to call for a three-week recess of the talks .,O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O,NN VBD NNS TO VB IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNS .
"At the beginning of discussions in July , chief U.S. negotiator Christopher Hill repeated the assurance that Washington has absolutely no intention of attacking North Korea .",O O O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"IN DT NN IN NNS IN NNP , JJ NNP NN NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN NNP VBZ RB DT NN IN VBG NNP NNP ."
