An Iranian official says his country will not stop developing its nuclear program even if the United Nations imposes a third set of sanctions .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBZ PRP$ NN MD RB VB VBG PRP$ JJ NN RB IN DT NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN NNS .
Iranian Foreign Ministry spokesman Mohammad Ali Hosseini Sunday told reporters that Iran will ignore continued U.S. and U.N. pressure to stop enriching uranium as part of its nuclear program .,B-gpe B-org I-org O B-per I-per I-per B-tim O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NN NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNS IN NNP MD VB JJ NNP CC NNP NN TO VB VBG NN IN NN IN PRP$ JJ NN .
"Just three days ago Thursday , Iran 's top nuclear negotiator Ali Larijani met with the European Union 's foreign policy chief Javier Solana .",O B-tim O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O B-per I-per O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-per I-per O,"RB CD NNS IN NNP , NNP POS JJ JJ NN NNP NNP VBD IN DT NNP NNP POS JJ NN NN NNP NNP ."
"Those talks produced no breakthrough in the nuclear standoff , and the two men will meet again in two weeks .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"DT NNS VBD DT NN IN DT JJ NN , CC DT CD NNS MD VB RB IN CD NNS ."
"Since December , the U.N. Security Council has approved two sets of sanctions against Iran to pressure the nation to halt uranium enrichment .",B-tim I-tim O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN CD NNS IN NNS IN NNP TO VB DT NN TO VB NN NN ."
"Tehran says its program is for peaceful , civilian uses .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ PRP$ NN VBZ IN JJ , JJ NNS ."
