British police have released video footage showing the London subway suicide bombers on a reconnaissance trip less than two weeks before the July 7 blasts that killed 56 people .,B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-tim O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN NN NN VBG DT NNP NN NN NNS IN DT NN NN JJR IN CD NNS IN DT NNP CD NNS WDT VBD CD NNS .
"Scotland Yard says the closed circuit television recordings show three of the four bombers traveling through London on June 28 , making the same journey they did on the day of the bombings .",B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ NN NN NNS VBP CD IN DT CD NNS VBG IN NNP IN NNP CD , VBG DT JJ NN PRP VBD IN DT NN IN DT NNS ."
Officials believe they were checking out potential targets on the London transport system and checking how long the journey would take on the day of the attack .,O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP PRP VBD VBG RP JJ NNS IN DT NNP NN NN CC VBG WRB RB DT NN MD VB IN DT NN IN DT NN .
"The development comes one day after al-Qaida 's number two leader , Ayman al-Zawahri , said the terror network was behind the bombings .",O O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ CD NN IN NNP POS NN CD NN , NNP NNP , VBD DT NN NN VBD IN DT NNS ."
"In a video broadcast on Arabic language al-Jazeera television , he said the bombings were aimed against what he termed as British aggression against Muslims and its part in creating Israel .",O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O,"IN DT NN NN IN JJ NN NNP NN , PRP VBD DT NNS VBD VBN IN WP PRP VBD IN JJ NN IN NNPS CC PRP$ NN IN VBG NNP ."
