U.S. Defense Secretary Robert Gates and European defense ministers and diplomats are set to begin their second day of talks Friday regarding NATO 's mission in Afghanistan .,B-org I-org B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-org O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP CC JJ NN NNS CC NNS VBP VBN TO VB PRP$ JJ NN IN NNS NNP VBG NNP POS NN IN NNP .
"Gates arrived in Edinburgh , Scotland , Thursday to promote a master document that would better explain exactly what NATO is doing in Afghanistan , and why countries should support its mission .",B-per O O B-geo O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD IN NNP , NNP , NNP TO VB DT NN NN WDT MD RB VB RB WP NNP VBZ VBG IN NNP , CC WRB NNS MD VB PRP$ NN ."
"Earlier this week , Gates briefed members of the U.S. Congress on the situation in Afghanistan .",O O O O B-per O O O O B-org I-org O O O O B-geo O,"RBR DT NN , NNP VBD NNS IN DT NNP NNP IN DT NN IN NNP ."
He said there are serious shortfalls in equipment and training to help the Afghan police and army fight militants .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,PRP VBD EX VBP JJ NNS IN NN CC NN TO VB DT JJ NN CC NN VB NNS .
"Over the past two years , remnants of the Taliban government have been waging fierce battles against the Afghan government , NATO and U.S. soldiers - resorting to suicide attacks , roadside bombings and kidnappings .",O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-org O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT JJ CD NNS , NNS IN DT NNP NN VBP VBN VBG JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN , NNP CC NNP NNS IN VBG TO NN NNS , NN NNS CC NNS ."
