"A bomb blast in southern Beirut has killed three people , including at least two members of the Palestinian militant group Hamas .",O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-org O,"DT NN NN IN JJ NNP VBZ VBN CD NNS , VBG IN JJS CD NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN NNP ."
A Hamas spokesman confirmed two of his group 's members were among those killed in the explosion late Saturday .,O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NNP NN VBD CD IN PRP$ NN POS NNS VBD IN DT VBN IN DT NN JJ NNP .
He said the cause of the blast was still unclear .,O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT NN IN DT NN VBD RB JJ .
The blast happened near an office of a senior Hamas official in a southern Beirut neighborhood controlled by the Lebanese militant group Hezbollah .,O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-gpe O O B-org O,DT NN VBD IN DT NN IN DT JJ NNP NN IN DT JJ NNP NN VBN IN DT JJ JJ NN NNP .
"Hezbollah fighters sealed off streets around the site of the bombing , preventing journalists from getting close .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNS VBD RP NNS IN DT NN IN DT NN , VBG NNS IN VBG RB ."
"Hamas and Hezbollah , listed by the U.S. as terrorist organizations , have fought separate wars against Israel in recent years .",B-org O B-org O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O,"NNP CC NNP , VBN IN DT NNP IN JJ NNS , VBP VBN JJ NNS IN NNP IN JJ NNS ."
