"Egypt 's election commission has declared President Hosni Mubarak the winner of the country 's first multi-candidate presidential election , with 88 percent of the vote .",B-geo O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NN NN VBZ VBN NNP NNP NNP DT NN IN DT NN POS JJ JJ JJ NN , IN CD NN IN DT NN ."
There are 32 million registered voters in a country of 77 million people .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,EX VBP CD CD JJ NNS IN DT NN IN CD CD NNS .
The commission reported only 23 percent of them cast ballots in Wednesday 's historic poll -- an even lower turnout than earlier estimated .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD RB CD NN IN PRP VBD NNS IN NNP POS JJ NN IN DT RB JJR NN IN RBR VBN .
State television reported that Mr. Mubarak won over six million votes .,O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O,NNP NN VBD IN NNP NNP VBD RP CD CD NNS .
"Mr. Mubarak was widely expected to win a fifth term , despite competition for the first time .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD RB VBN TO VB DT JJ NN , IN NN IN DT JJ NN ."
