"Prior to the arrival of the Spanish in the 16th century , the Inca ruled northern Chile while the indigenous Mapuche inhabited central and southern Chile .",O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-tim I-tim O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O,"RB TO DT NN IN DT JJ IN DT JJ NN , DT NNP VBD JJ NNP IN DT JJ NNP VBD JJ CC JJ NNP ."
"Although Chile declared its independence in 1810 , decisive victory over the Spanish was not achieved until 1818 .",O B-geo O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-tim O,"IN NNP VBD PRP$ NN IN CD , JJ NN IN DT JJ VBD RB VBN IN CD ."
"In the War of the Pacific ( 1879 - 83 ) , Chile defeated Peru and Bolivia and won its present northern regions .",O O B-org O O B-org O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O,"IN DT NNP IN DT NNP LRB CD IN CD RRB , NNP VBD NNP CC NNP CC VBD PRP$ JJ JJ NNS ."
It was not until the 1880s that the Mapuche Indians were completely subjugated .,O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-geo B-gpe O O O O,PRP VBD RB IN DT NNS IN DT NNP NNS VBD RB VBN .
"After a series of elected governments , the three-year-old Marxist government of Salvador ALLENDE was overthrown in 1973 by a military coup led by Augusto PINOCHET , who ruled until a freely elected president was installed in 1990 .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"IN DT NN IN JJ NNS , DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP NNP VBD VBN IN CD IN DT JJ NN VBN IN NNP NNP , WP VBD IN DT RB VBN NN VBD VBN IN CD ."
"Sound economic policies , maintained consistently since the 1980s , have contributed to steady growth , reduced poverty rates by over half , and have helped secure the country 's commitment to democratic and representative government .",O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ JJ NNS , VBD RB IN DT NNS , VBP VBN TO JJ NN , VBN NN NNS IN IN NN , CC VBP VBN VB DT NN POS NN TO JJ CC JJ NN ."
"Chile has increasingly assumed regional and international leadership roles befitting its status as a stable , democratic nation .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ RB VBN JJ CC JJ NN NNS VBG PRP$ NN IN DT JJ , JJ NN ."
