President Bush has extended his greetings to all who are celebrating the 105th anniversary of Cuba 's independence .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP$ NNS TO DT WP VBP VBG DT JJ NN IN NNP POS NN .
"In a statement released Sunday by the White House , Mr. Bush said the United States remains committed to extending the full blessings of liberty around the world .",O O O O B-tim O O B-org I-org O B-per I-per O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN VBN NNP IN DT NNP NNP , NNP NNP VBD DT NNP NNPS VBZ JJ TO VBG DT JJ NNS IN NN IN DT NN ."
"He said the U.S. stands with all freedom-loving people in the conviction that Cuba 's future must be one of dignity , liberty and opportunity .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD DT NNP VBZ IN DT JJ NNS IN DT NN IN NNP POS NN MD VB CD IN NN , NN CC NN ."
The president said the anniversary of Cuba 's independance is also a day to recognize the contributions of generations of Cuban Americans .,O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe I-gpe O,DT NN VBD DT NN IN NNP POS NN VBZ RB DT NN TO VB DT NNS IN NNS IN JJ NNS .
"On May 20 , 1902 , the Cuban republic was inaugurated .",O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O B-gpe O O O O,"IN NNP CD , CD , DT JJ NN VBD VBN ."
"On that date , the United States ended its occupation of the island following the Spanish-American war .",O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN , DT NNP NNPS VBD PRP$ NN IN DT NN VBG DT JJ NN ."
