The Ukrainian government has canceled a planned meeting at its headquarters in Kiev after hundreds of protesters massed outside to prevent Prime Minister Viktor Yanukovych from entering .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O,DT JJ NN VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN PRP$ NN IN NNP IN NNS IN NNS VBN IN TO VB NNP NNP NNP NNP IN VBG .
"Government officials told reporters Wednesday the cabinet meeting would not take place , as planned .",O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,"NN NNS VBD NNS NNP DT NN NN MD RB VB NN , IN VBN ."
No explanation was given .,O O O O O,DT NN VBD VBN .
"Earlier , opposition leader Viktor Yushchenko , the apparent winner of Sunday 's presidential runoff election , urged supporters to stage a blockade to stop Mr. Yanukovych from convening the meeting .",O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per B-org O O O O O,"RB , NN NN NNP NNP , DT JJ NN IN NNP POS JJ NN NN , VBD NNS TO VB DT NN TO VB NNP NNP IN VBG DT NN ."
"Meanwhile , officials say Mr. Yanukovych has filed a formal complaint with the Central Election Commission challenging Sunday 's runoff , claiming widespread fraud .",O O O O B-per B-org O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O O,"RB , NNS VBP NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP VBG NNP POS NN , VBG JJ NN ."
Official results show Mr. Yushchenko won 52 percent of the vote .,O O O B-per B-org O B-tim O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP NNP NNP VBD CD NN IN DT NN .
