The high court in Georgia 's breakaway region of Abkhazia has annulled a disputed presidential election -- hours after declaring the opposition candidate the winner .,O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN IN NNP POS JJ NN IN NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ JJ NN : NNS IN VBG DT NN NN DT NN .
But Supreme Court Justice Georgiy Akaba said the action can not be considered legal because it was made under intense pressure after backers of losing candidate Prime Minister Raul Khadjimba stormed the court building .,O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O,CC NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN MD RB VB VBN JJ IN PRP VBD VBN IN JJ NN IN NNS IN VBG NN NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN NN .
"However , outgoing Abkhaz President Vladislav Ardzinba ordered new elections within two months .",O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O B-tim I-tim O O,"RB , VBG NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD JJ NNS IN CD NNS ."
Broadcasters complained that they were taken off the air .,O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBD IN PRP VBD VBN RP DT NN .
"Thursday , the court declared opposition candidate Sergei Bagapsh the winner of the October 3 vote .",B-tim O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,"NNP , DT NN VBD NN NN NNP NNP DT NN IN DT NNP CD NN ."
"Abkhazia , a pro-Russian enclave , has run its own affairs since driving out Georgian troops and civilians in the early 1990's .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim O,"NNP , DT JJ NN , VBZ VBN PRP$ JJ NNS IN VBG RP JJ NNS CC NNS IN DT JJ NNS ."
The central Georgian government says the election was illegal and insists it will bring Abkhazia under its control .,O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,DT JJ JJ NN VBZ DT NN VBD JJ CC VBZ PRP MD VB NNP IN PRP$ NN .
