"Sporadic gunfire has been reported in Andijon and other border areas of Uzbekistan , where security forces fired on protesters last week , reportedly killing as many as 500 people .",O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN VBZ VBN VBN IN NNP CC JJ NN NNS IN NNP , WRB NN NNS VBN IN NNS JJ NN , RB VBG RB JJ IN CD NNS ."
"President Islam Karimov has denied security forces opened fire on demonstrators , as witnesses claimed .",B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN NN NNS VBD NN IN NNS , IN NNS VBD ."
But the authoritarian government has sought to restrict access for reporters in the affected areas .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC DT JJ NN VBZ VBN TO VB NN IN NNS IN DT JJ NNS .
The Associated Press quotes a local doctor as saying that about 500 bodies had been laid out at a school for collection by relatives .,B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN VBG IN IN CD NNS VBD VBN VBN RP IN DT NN IN NN IN NNS .
There was no independent confirmation .,O O O O O O,EX VBD DT JJ NN .
