"The Ukrainian parliament has overwhelmingly voted for a presidential election October 25th , in a move that President Viktor Yushchenko says he will challenge as unconstitutional .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBZ RB VBN IN DT JJ NN NNP CD , IN DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP MD VB IN JJ ."
A parliamentary resolution setting a date earlier than expected won the backing of 401 deputies in the 450-member parliament .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBG DT NN RBR IN VBN VBD DT NN IN CD NNS IN DT JJ NN .
"The legislative body and its leader , Prime Minister Yulia Tymoshenko , have grown increasingly hostile to the Yushchenko presidency over the past two years .",O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-per O O O B-tim I-tim O O,"DT JJ NN CC PRP$ NN , NNP NNP NNP NNP , VBP VBN RB JJ TO DT NNP NN IN DT JJ CD NNS ."
"Analysts say the vote Wednesday was a maneuver to prevent the president from dissolving the chamber , which is illegal in the last six months of his mandate .",O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,"NNS VBP DT NN NNP VBD DT NN TO VB DT NN IN VBG DT NN , WDT VBZ JJ IN DT JJ CD NNS IN PRP$ NN ."
"A short while after the vote , the deputy head of Mr. Yushchenko 's administration , Maryna Stavniychuk , said the president would appeal to the country 's Constitutional Court .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-per B-org O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"DT JJ NN IN DT NN , DT NN NN IN NNP NNP POS NN , NNP NNP , VBD DT NN MD VB TO DT NN POS NNP NNP ."
No one has yet announced plans to contest the election .,O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ RB VBN NNS TO NN DT NN .
