A senior U.S. defense official says elements of al-Qaida still remain in Pakistan and unless more is done to stop the flow of recruits into militant groups the war on terror will never be won .,O O B-geo O O O O O B-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNP NN NN VBZ NNS IN NNP RB VBP IN NNP CC IN JJR VBZ VBN TO VB DT NN IN NNS IN JJ NNS DT NN IN NN MD RB VB VBN .
Visiting U.S. Undersecretary for Defense Douglas Feith told a news conference in Pakistan that disrupting and destroying terrorist networks is not enough .,O B-org I-org I-org I-org B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,VBG NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN NN IN NNP IN VBG CC VBG JJ NNS VBZ RB RB .
He said the war on terror can not be won without stopping the flow of people into the ranks of terrorist groups .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT NN IN NN MD RB VB VBN IN VBG DT NN IN NNS IN DT NNS IN JJ NNS .
He also said terrorists must be denied what they need to survive and operate .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP RB VBD NNS MD VB VBN WP PRP VBP TO VB CC VB .
Pakistan is a key U.S. ally and has handed over more than 500 militants to the United States .,B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP VBZ DT JJ NNP NN CC VBZ VBN RP JJR IN CD NNS TO DT NNP NNPS .
But hundreds of al-Qaida militants are still hiding in the Pakistan-Afghan border region .,O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,CC NNS IN NNP NNS VBP RB VBG IN DT JJ NN NN .
