Iraqi police in the northern town of Mosul say gunmen have killed a cameraman working for the Associated Press .,B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,JJ NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP VBP NNS VBP VBN DT NN VBG IN DT NNP NNP .
He went to film the clash and was apparently deliberately shot by gunmen .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD TO NN DT NN CC VBD RB RB VBN IN NNS .
Lutfalla is the second AP Television News cameraman to be killed in Mosul in the last two years .,B-org O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O O,NNP VBZ DT JJ NNP NNP NNP NN TO VB VBN IN NNP IN DT JJ CD NNS .
"Last week , a U.S. press advocacy group , The Committee to Protect Journalists , said 89 journalists have been killed in Iraq since the U.S.-led invasion in March 2003 .",O O O O B-geo O O O O B-org I-org O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"JJ NN , DT NNP NN NN NN , DT NNP TO VB NNS , VBD CD NNS VBP VBN VBN IN NNP IN DT JJ NN IN NNP CD ."
