Switzerland has reported its first case of bird flu .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN PRP$ JJ NN IN NN NN .
A dead wild duck found in central Geneva tested positive Sunday for the H5 virus .,O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O B-org O O,DT JJ NN NN VBN IN JJ NNP VBD JJ NNP IN DT NNP NN .
"Tests are underway to determine if the duck had the H5N1 strain , which has killed 92 people since 2003 , mostly in Asia .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O B-geo O,"NNS VBP JJ TO VB IN DT NN VBD DT NNP NN , WDT VBZ VBN CD NNS IN CD , RB IN NNP ."
"Meanwhile , Hong Kong has joined Japan in banning poultry imports from France , where bird flu has struck a turkey farm near the eastern city of Lyon .",O O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"RB , NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNP IN VBG JJ NNS IN NNP , WRB NN NN VBZ VBN DT NN NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
France is Europe 's biggest poultry producer .,B-geo O B-geo O O O O O,NNP VBZ NNP POS JJS NN NN .
French President Jacques Chirac says there is absolutely no danger in eating properly cooked chickens and eggs .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ EX VBZ RB DT NN IN VBG RB VBN NNS CC NNS .
The agriculture ministry said Sunday 15 more wild swans infected with bird flu were found in the area near the turkey farm .,O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN NN VBD NNP CD JJR JJ NNS VBN IN NN NN VBD VBN IN DT NN IN DT NN NN .
"Elsewhere , Chinese media report that the agriculture minister is calling on authorities to go on high alert for what he says could be a massive bird flu outbreak in the coming months .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , JJ NNS NN IN DT NN NN VBZ VBG IN NNS TO VB IN JJ NN IN WP PRP VBZ MD VB DT JJ NN NN NN IN DT JJ NNS ."
