Internationally acclaimed jazz pianist Oscar Peterson has died .,O O O O B-per I-per O O O,RB VBN NN NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN .
The Canadian Broadcasting Corporation says the legendary musician died Sunday from kidney failure at his home near Toronto .,O B-gpe B-org I-org O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT JJ NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ NN VBD NNP IN NN NN IN PRP$ NN IN NNP .
"In a career spanning decades , Peterson performed at Carnegie Hall in New York and with musical greats such as Nat King Cole , Ella Fitzgerald and Dizzy Gillespie .",O O O O O O B-per O O B-per I-per O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,"IN DT NN VBG NNS , NNP VBD IN NNP NNP IN NNP NNP CC IN JJ NNS JJ IN NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP CC NNP NNP ."
His honors include a Grammy for Lifetime Achievement in 1997 and an International Jazz Hall of Fame Award .,O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-tim O O B-org I-org B-per O B-org I-org O,PRP$ NNS VBP DT NNP IN NNP NNP IN CD CC DT NNP NNP NNP IN NNP NNP .
"Canada had also named him a Companion of the Order of Canada , bestowing on him his country 's highest civilian award .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD RB VBN PRP DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP , VBG IN PRP PRP$ NN POS JJS JJ NN ."
