Italy 's highest sports authority - CONI - has suspended all competition Saturday and Sunday as a sign of respect for Pope John Paul II .,B-gpe O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O,NNP POS JJS NNS NN : NNP : VBZ VBN DT NN NNP CC NNP IN DT NN IN NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP .
"CONI President Gianni Petrucci said the decision affects Serie-A football ( soccer ) matches , a playoff to decide the Italian ice hockey title , basketball and volleyball league matches , and amateur sports .",B-org B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN VBZ NNP NN LRB NN RRB NNS , DT NN TO VB DT JJ NN NN NN , NN CC NN NN NNS , CC JJ NNS ."
"On Friday , the heads of Serie-A powerhouses AC Milan and Juventus had called for the suspension of play as Pope John Paul 's condition worsened .",O B-tim O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O,"IN NNP , DT NNS IN NNP VBZ NNP NNP CC NNP VBD VBN IN DT NN IN NN IN NNP NNP NNP POS NN VBD ."
Several crucial Italian league matches were scheduled for Saturday and Sunday .,O O B-gpe O O O O O B-tim O B-tim O,JJ JJ JJ NN NNS VBD VBN IN NNP CC NNP .
"Some Formula One drivers preparing to start in Sunday 's Bahrain Grand Prix expressed their sympathy for the pope , but ruled out postponing the race .",O B-org I-org O O O O O B-tim O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP CD NNS VBG TO VB IN NNP POS NNP NNP NNP VBD PRP$ NN IN DT NN , CC VBD RP VBG DT NN ."
Giancarlo Fisichella said that he did not think Formula One should be stopped despite the drivers ' sympathies with the pontiff .,B-per I-per O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD IN PRP VBD RB VB NNP CD MD VB VBN IN DT NNS POS NNS IN DT NN .
