"The U.S. military says Marines have cleared more than half the houses in the Iraqi city of Fallujah of weapons , after mounting an offensive to crush the city 's rebels .",O B-geo O O B-org O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NN VBZ NNPS VBP VBN JJR IN PDT DT NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NNP IN NNS , IN VBG DT NN TO VB DT NN POS NNS ."
Military officials say the Marines will search every house in Fallujah to deprive Iraq 's guerrillas of a main base and weapons point and pave the way for rebuilding the city ahead of elections scheduled in January .,O O O O B-org O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,JJ NNS VBP DT NNPS MD VB DT NN IN NNP TO VB NNP POS NNS IN DT JJ NN CC NNS NN CC VB DT NN IN VBG DT NN RB IN NNS VBN IN NNP .
A Marine spokesman says two Marines were killed during the clearing operations when insurgents threw grenades at them as they entered a house Thursday .,O B-org O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NNP NN VBZ CD NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN NNS WRB NNS VBD NNS IN PRP IN PRP VBD DT NN NNP .
He says three insurgents were killed in return fire .,O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ CD NNS VBD VBN IN NN NN .
