Spain 's Prince of Asturias Foundation has announced that the scientific journals Science and Nature will receive its annual award for helping explain some of the world 's most important discoveries .,B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NNP IN NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NNS NN CC NN MD VB PRP$ JJ NN IN VBG VB DT IN DT NN POS RBS JJ NNS .
Organizers said Wednesday that the jury meeting in the Spanish city of Oviedo selected the U.S. and the British scientific publications to receive the Asturias communication prize .,O O B-tim O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O O O O B-org O O O,NNP VBD NNP IN DT NN NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP VBD DT NNP CC DT JJ JJ NNS TO VB DT NNP NN NN .
The jury praised the journals as indispensable sources of universal reference material and a vanguard of scientific information .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD DT NNS IN JJ NNS IN JJ NN NN CC DT NN IN JJ NN .
Science magazine is an American weekly that first appeared in New York in 1880 .,O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-tim O,NNP NN VBZ DT JJ NN WDT RB VBD IN NNP NNP IN CD .
The British journal Nature was first published in 1869 .,O B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim O,DT JJ NN NN VBD JJ VBN IN CD .
"The $ 67,000 prize will be presented at a formal ceremony in October .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT $ CD NN MD VB VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
"The Asturias Foundation , headed by Spanish Crown Prince Filipe , awards eight prizes every year in the fields including the arts , science , and sports .",O B-org I-org O O O B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP , VBN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP , RB CD NNS DT NN IN DT NNS VBG DT NNS , NN , CC NNS ."
