Two new public opinion polls show President Bush 's approval ratings remaining at an all-time low .,O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,CD JJ JJ NN NNS VBP NNP NNP POS NN NNS VBG IN DT JJ NN .
"In the surveys , conducted by Fox News television and Newsweek magazine , 36 percent of Americans said they approve of the president 's job performance .",O O O O O O B-org I-org O O B-org O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NNS , VBN IN NNP NNP NN CC NNP NN , CD NN IN NNS VBD PRP VBP IN DT NN POS NN NN ."
Newsweek also asked respondents whether they think the president and Vice President Dick Cheney are honest and ethical .,B-org O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O O,NNP RB VBD NNS IN PRP VBP DT NN CC NNP NNP NNP NNP VBP JJ CC JJ .
"Forty-two percent said that phrase applies to Mr. Bush , while 29 percent said it describes Mr. Cheney .",O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-per I-per O,"CD NN VBD IN NN VBZ TO NNP NNP , IN CD NN VBD PRP VBZ NNP NNP ."
Mr. Cheney 's former top aide Lewis Libby was indicted last month on five criminal charges related to the leak of a covert CIA officer 's identity to the media .,B-per I-per O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,NNP NNP POS JJ JJ NN NNP NNP VBD VBN JJ NN IN CD JJ NNS VBN TO DT NN IN DT JJ NNP NN POS NN TO DT NNS .
The president has also faced continued criticism for his handling of Iraq and the failed Supreme Court nomination of White House counsel Harriet Miers .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O B-per I-per O,DT NN VBZ RB VBN JJ NN IN PRP$ NN IN NNP CC DT VBN NNP NNP NN IN NNP NNP NN NNP NNP .
