The United States says Syria needs to get out of Lebanon and let the people there decide their political future through free and fair elections .,O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBZ NNP VBZ TO VB IN IN NNP CC VB DT NNS RB VB PRP$ JJ NN IN JJ CC JJ NNS .
Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice has discussed Lebanon with French Foreign Minister Michel Barnier on the sidelines of a London conference on Palestinian reforms .,O O B-org B-per I-per O O B-geo O B-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O,NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN NNP IN NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP IN DT NNS IN DT NNP NN IN JJ NNS .
"Afterward , Secretary Rice said Syria needs to leave Lebanon and let elections proceed .",O O O B-per O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O,"RB , NNP NNP VBD NNP VBZ TO VB NNP CC VB NNS VB ."
""" The Syrians are out of step with the way the region is going and out of step with the aspirations of the people of the Middle East , "" said Ms. Rice .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-per I-per O,"LQU DT NNS VBP IN IN NN IN DT NN DT NN VBZ VBG CC IN IN NN IN DT NNS IN DT NNS IN DT NNP NNP , RQU VBD NNP NNP ."
"She says Syria also must end its political meddling in Lebanon , where the pro-Syrian government has just resigned , and she pledges U.S. material support for free and fair elections in Lebanon .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"PRP VBZ NNP RB MD VB PRP$ JJ NN IN NNP , WRB DT JJ NN VBZ RB VBN , CC PRP VBZ NNP NN NN IN JJ CC JJ NNS IN NNP ."
"Mr. Barnier said France agrees that the Lebanese should be , as he put it , "" the masters of their own fate "" .",B-per I-per O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD NNP VBZ IN DT NNS MD VB , IN PRP VBD PRP , LQU DT NNS IN PRP$ JJ NN RQU ."
