Officials in Saudi Arabia say the number of Ramadan visas issued for foreign pilgrims has jumped by 16 percent .,O O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNP NNP VBP DT NN IN NNP NNS VBN IN JJ NNS VBZ VBN IN CD NN .
"Saudi Arabia 's Ministry of Hajj said it initially planned to issue 792,000 visas during the Muslim fasting month of Ramadan .",B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-org O,NNP NNP POS NNP IN NNP VBD PRP RB VBD TO VB CD NNS IN DT NNP JJ NN IN NNP .
"But it says that number was raised to 911,000 due to high demand from abroad and more space being available at hotels in the holy cities of Mecca and Medina .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,CC PRP VBZ IN NN VBD VBN TO CD JJ TO JJ NN IN RB CC JJR NN VBG JJ IN NNS IN DT JJ NNS IN NNP CC NNP .
Thousands of Muslims from around the world make pilgrimages to Saudi Arabia 's holy cities during Ramadan .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O B-org O,NNS IN NNPS IN IN DT NN VBP NNS TO NNP NNP POS JJ NNS IN NNP .
