Russian officials say the two leaders spoke by phone on Saturday and said it was possible to talk about a firm date for signing at treaty to reduce their arsenals of nuclear weapons .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP DT CD NNS VBD IN NN IN NNP CC VBD PRP VBD JJ TO VB IN DT NN NN IN NN IN NN TO VB PRP$ NNS IN JJ NNS .
"Russia and the United States have been negotiating a replacement to the 1991 Strategic Arms Limitation Treaty , which expired in December .",B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"NNP CC DT NNP NNPS VBP VBN VBG DT NN TO DT CD NNP NNP NNP NNP , WDT VBD IN NNP ."
The talks had been hung up on how to verify the arms cuts and U.S. plans for a missile defense system in Europe .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNS VBD VBN VBG RP IN WRB TO VB DT NNS NNS CC NNP NNS IN DT NN NN NN IN NNP .
Russia opposes the missile plan .,B-geo O O O O O,NNP VBZ DT NN NN .
