It was the retelling of a decades old popular Indian opera Sultana Daku .,O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O B-art I-art O,PRP VBD DT NN IN DT NNS JJ JJ JJ NN NNP NNP .
VOA 's Savita Patel was on hand for one of the performances .,B-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NNP NNP VBD IN NN IN CD IN DT NNS .
Jim Bertel narrates .,B-per I-per O O,NNP NNP VBZ .
