A U.S. diplomatic cable released by WikiLeaks says Israeli officials charged extremely high fees to allow goods to enter into Gaza .,O B-geo O O O O B-org O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,DT NNP JJ NN VBN IN NNP VBZ JJ NNS VBD RB JJ NNS TO VB NNS TO VB IN NNP .
The diplomatic cable from 2006 says American companies complained they had to pay fees up to 75 times higher than normal .,O O O O B-tim O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN IN CD VBZ JJ NNS VBD PRP VBD TO VB NNS IN TO CD NNS JJR IN JJ .
The diplomatic cable was published Thursday in Norway 's Aftenposten newspaper .,O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O B-org O O,DT JJ NN VBD VBN NNP IN NNP POS NNP NN .
"The alleged corruption took place at the Karni crossing , a major entry point into Gaza .",O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT JJ NN VBD NN IN DT NNP VBG , DT JJ NN NN IN NNP ."
"The document says U.S. companies who made the charges included Coca-Cola , Caterpillar , Phillip Morris , Hewlett Packard and Motorola .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O B-per I-per O B-per O,"DT NN VBZ NNP NNS WP VBD DT NNS VBD NNP , NNP , NNP NNP , NNP NNP CC NNP ."
"The cable says a Coca-Cola distributor said he was asked to pay as much as $ 3,300 per truckload passing through the Karni crossing .",O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,DT NN VBZ DT NNP NN VBD PRP VBD VBN TO VB RB JJ IN $ CD IN NN VBG IN DT NNP VBG .
The document was based on information provided by the U.S. Embassy in Tel Aviv .,O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-org I-org O,DT NN VBD VBN IN NN VBN IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP NNP .
