"Zimbabwe is inviting new bidders to take over its collapsed state steelmaker , after rejecting offers from two foreign companies .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBG JJ NNS TO VB RP PRP$ JJ NN NN , IN VBG NNS IN CD JJ NNS ."
"In a statement Wednesday , Zimbabwe 's Industry and Commerce Minister Welshman Ncube said the bidding process is now open .",O O O B-tim O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN NNP , NNP POS NN CC NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN NN VBZ RB JJ ."
He said offers must be submitted to the government by September 24 .,O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,PRP VBD NNS MD VB VBN TO DT NN IN NNP CD .
"In May , Zimbabwe 's government rejected bids by South Africa 's ArcelorMittal and India 's Jindal Steel to take over the Zimbabwe Iron and Steel Company , or ZISCO .",O B-tim O B-org I-org O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-org O,"IN NNP , NNP POS NN VBD NNS IN NNP NNP POS JJ CC NNP POS NNP NNP TO VB RP DT NNP NNP CC NNP NNP , CC NNP ."
President Robert Mugabe said those companies were too big .,B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NNS VBD RB JJ .
ZISCO stopped operations in 2008 at the height of Zimbabwe 's economic crisis due to a lack of funding .,B-org O O O B-tim O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD NNS IN CD IN DT NN IN NNP POS JJ NN JJ TO DT NN IN NN .
