"Security officials say the victims were on a bus that was returning from the Dead Sea to the capital Amman , late Thursday .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-geo O O B-tim O,"NN NNS VBP DT NNS VBD IN DT NN WDT VBD VBG IN DT NNP NNP TO DT NN NNP , JJ NNP ."
Authorities say two British women and four Iraqis were killed .,O O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O O,NNS VBP CD JJ NNS CC CD NNS VBD VBN .
"Iraqi Minister of Science and Technology Raed Fahmi was hospitalized , with injuries .",B-gpe O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O,"JJ NNP IN NNP CC NNP NNP NNP VBD VBN , IN NNS ."
The bus passengers were taking part in a United Nations Development Program training course for Iraqis .,O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O B-gpe O,DT NN NNS VBD VBG NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP NN NN IN NNS .
