"When first the Fox saw the Lion he was terribly frightened , and ran away and hid himself in the wood .",O O O B-org O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"WRB RB DT NNP VBD DT NNP PRP VBD RB JJ , CC VBD RB CC VBD PRP IN DT NN ."
Next time however he came near the King of Beasts he stopped at a safe distance and watched him pass by .,O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NN RB PRP VBD IN DT NNP IN NNPS PRP VBD IN DT JJ NN CC VBD PRP VB IN .
"The third time they came near one another the Fox went straight up to the Lion and passed the time of day with him , asking him how his family were , and when he should have the pleasure of seeing him again ; then turning his tail , he parted from the Lion without much ceremony .",O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"DT JJ NN PRP VBD IN CD DT DT NNP VBD RB RB TO DT NNP CC VBD DT NN IN NN IN PRP , VBG PRP WRB PRP$ NN VBD , CC WRB PRP MD VB DT NN IN VBG PRP RB ; RB VBG PRP$ NN , PRP VBD IN DT NNP IN JJ NN ."
Familiarity breeds contempt .,O O O O,NNP NNS VBP .
