"Israeli police say they have arrested two Israeli Arabs , including a Muslim cleric , on suspicion of supporting terror organizations .",B-gpe O O O O O O B-gpe I-gpe O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP PRP VBP VBN CD JJ NNS , VBG DT NNP NN , IN NN IN VBG NN NNS ."
Police issued a gag order on details of the case .,O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBD DT NN NN IN NNS IN DT NN .
But Israeli media have identified the detained men as Sheikh Nazem Abu Salim and Mohammed Zohadi Naarani .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,CC JJ NNS VBP VBN DT JJ NNS IN NNP NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP .
"The two are residents of the northern city of Nazareth , and reports say Abu Salim was trying to encourage worshippers at his mosque to join al-Qaida .",O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,"DT CD VBP NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NNP , CC NNS VBP NNP NNP VBD VBG TO VB NNS IN PRP$ NN TO VB NNP ."
The cleric has spoken out against Israel and the United States and is known for his protest against the pope 's visit to Nazareth in 2009 .,O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O,DT NN VBZ VBN RP IN NNP CC DT NNP NNPS CC VBZ VBN IN PRP$ NN IN DT NN POS NN TO NNP IN CD .
"Israel has arrested several other of its Arab citizens this year on charges of working with anti-Israeli militant groups , including Hamas and Hezbollah .",B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,"NNP VBZ VBN JJ NN IN PRP$ JJ NNS DT NN IN NNS IN VBG IN JJ JJ NNS , VBG NNP CC NNP ."
