"The United States and France have urged Iran to restart negotiations on its nuclear program , warning that referring the issue to the United Nations Security Council for sanctions is still a possibility .",B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNPS CC NNP VBP VBN NNP TO VB NNS IN PRP$ JJ NN , VBG IN VBG DT NN TO DT NNP NNP NNP NNP IN NNS VBZ RB DT NN ."
"U.S. Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice and French officials made the comment Friday in Paris , after the secretary 's talks with French President Jacques Chirac .",B-org O O B-org B-per I-per O B-gpe O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O,"NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP CC JJ NNS VBD DT NN NNP IN NNP , IN DT NN POS NNS IN JJ NNP NNP NNP ."
Iran 's refusal to grant full access to International Atomic Energy Agency inspectors contributed to an IAEA vote last month that found Iran in violation of the Nuclear Non-Proliferation Treaty .,B-geo O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O B-org B-tim O O O O B-geo O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,NNP POS NN TO VB JJ NN TO NNP NNP NNP NNP NNS VBD TO DT NNP NN JJ NN WDT VBD NNP IN NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP .
"Secretary Rice has arrived in Moscow , where she is expected to discuss the Iran nuclear issue with Russian officials Saturday .",O B-per O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O B-tim O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NNP , WRB PRP VBZ VBN TO VB DT NNP JJ NN IN JJ NNS NNP ."
"Meanwhile , Iran 's official IRNA news agency quotes Iranian Foreign Minister Manouchehr Mottaki as saying during talks in Beijing that his country is ready to resume negotiations on the nuclear issue .",O O B-geo O O B-org O O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , NNP POS JJ NNP NN NN VBZ JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP IN VBG IN NNS IN NNP IN PRP$ NN VBZ JJ TO VB NNS IN DT JJ NN ."
