A U.S. Marine charged with deserting his unit while serving in Iraq has been labeled a deserter for a second time .,O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBN IN VBG PRP$ NN IN VBG IN NNP VBZ VBN VBN DT NN IN DT JJ NN .
"The Marines Corps said in a statement Wednesday that Corporal Wassef Ali Hassoun failed to return to his base at Camp Lejeune , North Carolina Tuesday , after an authorized leave .",O B-org I-org O O O O B-tim O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo I-geo B-tim O O O O O O,"DT NNPS NNP VBD IN DT NN NNP IN NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD TO VB TO PRP$ NN IN NNP NNP , NNP NNP NNP , IN DT JJ NN ."
The statement said civilian law enforcement officials have been authorized to apprehend the corporal and return him to military control .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD JJ NN NN NNS VBP VBN VBN TO VB DT JJ CC VB PRP TO JJ NN .
Corporal Hassoun was serving as an Arabic interpreter when he disappeared from his brigade last June .,B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP NNP VBD VBG IN DT JJ NN WRB PRP VBD IN PRP$ NN JJ NNP .
"A videotape was aired on the Arab TV network al-Jazeera , showing him blindfolded and apparently being held hostage .",O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN NN NNP , VBG PRP JJ CC RB VBG VBN NN ."
Corporal Hassoun turned up unharmed several weeks later at the U.S. Embassy in Beirut .,B-org I-org O O O B-tim O B-tim O O B-org I-org O B-geo O,NNP NNP VBD RP JJ JJ NNS RB IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP .
