Officials in Yemen say they will hold peace talks in the coming days with Shi'ite rebel leaders to strengthen a fragile 2007 peace deal .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNS VBP PRP MD VB NN NNS IN DT VBG NNS IN JJ NN NNS TO VB DT JJ CD NN NN .
Qatari officials will mediate the talks between the two sides in Doha .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNS MD VB DT NNS IN DT CD NNS IN NNP .
Qatar also oversaw negotiations for the agreement three years ago .,B-org O O O O O O B-tim O O O,NNP RB VBD NNS IN DT NN CD NNS RB .
The meeting was planned when Qatar 's Prime Minister Hamad bin Jasim bin Jabir Al Thani made a trip to Yemen last month .,O O O O O B-org O B-per O B-per I-per I-per I-per I-per I-per I-per O O O O B-geo O O O,DT NN VBD VBN WRB NNP POS NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN NNP JJ NN .
Six years of fighting between the northern rebels and government forces ended earlier this year in a ceasefire .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CD NNS IN VBG IN DT JJ NNS CC NN NNS VBD RBR DT NN IN DT NN .
Both sides have since been accusing the other of violating the peace deal signed at the time .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP IN VBN VBG DT NN IN VBG DT NN NN VBD IN DT NN .
The talks come only a few days after rebels tried to take over two government buildings in the northern al-Jawf province .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP RB DT JJ NNS IN NNS VBD TO VB RP CD NN NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN .
Yemen 's western-backed government has also been trying to confront an al-Qaida insurgency as well as violent protests by separatists in the south .,B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS JJ NN VBZ RB VBN VBG TO VB DT NNP NN RB RB IN JJ NNS IN NNS IN DT NN .
