"Residents say Ethiopian troops allied to Somalia 's transitional government entered a neighborhood in the north of the city early Saturday , sparking fierce clashes with insurgents .",O O B-gpe O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP JJ NNS VBN IN NNP POS JJ NN VBD DT NN IN DT NN IN DT NN JJ NNP , VBG JJ NNS IN NNS ."
They say at least two Ethiopian soldiers are among those killed .,O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,PRP VBP IN JJS CD JJ NNS VBP IN DT VBN .
Witnesses say at least five civilians were killed when a stray artillery shell struck a small restaurant in the city 's Fagah neighborhood .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O,NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN WRB DT NN NN NN VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NN POS NNP NN .
"The Somali government has the backing of Ethiopian troops , who in 2006 helped drive a militant Islamist movement from power in southern Somalia .",O B-gpe O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-tim O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O,"DT JJ NN VBZ DT NN IN JJ NNS , WP IN CD VBD VB DT JJ NN NN IN NN IN JJ NNP ."
The conflict has intensified the country 's already dire humanitarian crisis .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBN DT NN POS RB JJ JJ NN .
