An Iraqi woman who confessed to participating in the triple suicide bombing attacks in Jordan 's capital last week had three brothers killed by U.S. forces in Iraq .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O,DT JJ NN WP VBD TO VBG IN DT JJ NN VBG NNS IN NNP POS NN JJ NN VBD CD NNS VBN IN NNP NNS IN NNP .
"Jordanian officials and friends of Sajida al-Rishawi said Tuesday that one of her brothers was a top aide of Iraq 's most wanted terrorist , Abu Musab al-Zarqawi , and was killed in Fallujah during a U.S.-led offensive last year .",O O O O O B-org I-org O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS CC NNS IN NNP NNP VBD NNP IN CD IN PRP$ NNS VBD DT JJ NN IN NNP POS RBS JJ JJ , NNP NNP NNP , CC VBD VBN IN NNP IN DT JJ NN JJ NN ."
"Two other brothers , also insurgents , were killed in the western city of Ramadi .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"CD JJ NNS , RB NNS , VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
"Sajida al-Rishawi confessed to trying to blow herself up at a wedding party in the Radisson hotel , but said her explosives belt malfunctioned .",B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP VBD TO VBG TO VB PRP RP IN DT VBG NN IN DT NNP NN , CC VBD PRP$ NNS NN VBD ."
"Her husband , one of three successful bombers , died in the attacks that killed 57 people .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP$ NN , CD IN CD JJ NNS , VBD IN DT NNS WDT VBD CD NNS ."
"Meanwhile , Jordan 's official news agency reports that U.S. National Intelligence Director John Negroponte met with Jordan 's foreign minister Farouk Qasrawi in Amman today .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org B-per B-org O O B-gpe O O O B-per I-per O B-geo B-tim O,"RB , NNP POS JJ NN NN NNS IN NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD IN NNP POS JJ NN NNP NNP IN NNP NN ."
