Palestinian hospital officials say Israeli soldiers have shot a young Palestinian boy in the northern West Bank town of Jenin .,B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-org I-org O O B-geo O,JJ NN NNS VBP JJ NNS VBP VBN DT JJ JJ NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP NN IN NNP .
Hospital officials say a bullet struck the boy in the head Thursday when Israeli soldiers fired on a group of Palestinians throwing rocks at them .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-gpe O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,NN NNS VBP DT NN VBD DT NN IN DT NN NNP WRB JJ NNS VBD IN DT NN IN NNS VBG NNS IN PRP .
Associated Press reports the boy has been put on life support .,B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ DT NN VBZ VBN VBN IN NN NN .
Residents say the Israeli soldiers were in the town pursuing an Islamic Jihad fugitive .,O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP DT JJ NNS VBD IN DT NN VBG DT JJ NN NN .
"Meanwhile , Hamas militants who had threatened not to renew a de~facto truce with Israel when it expires at the end of this year backed off Thursday , saying they would extend it if Israel stops its "" aggression "" and releases Palestinian prisoners .",O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"RB , NNP NNS WP VBD VBN RB TO VB DT JJ NN IN NNP WRB PRP VBZ IN DT NN IN DT NN VBD RP NNP , VBG PRP MD VB PRP IN NNP VBZ PRP$ LQU NN LQU CC VBZ JJ NNS ."
"Mahmoud Zahar , a Hamas leader in the Gaza Strip said the Palestinian Authority must also hold parliamentary elections as scheduled in January and reform what he called its corrupt government .",B-per I-per O O B-org O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP , DT NNP NN IN DT NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NNP MD RB VB JJ NNS IN VBN IN NNP CC VB WP PRP VBD PRP$ JJ NN ."
