"Upon independence in 1960 , the former French region of Middle Congo became the Republic of the Congo .",O O O B-tim O O O B-gpe O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O,"IN NN IN CD , DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP NNP VBD DT NNP IN DT NNP ."
A quarter century of experimentation with Marxism was abandoned in 1990 and a democratically elected government took office in 1992 .,O O O O O O B-org O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NN NN IN NN IN NNP VBD VBN IN CD CC DT RB VBN NN VBD NN IN CD .
"A brief civil war in 1997 restored former Marxist President Denis SASSOU-Nguesso , and ushered in a period of ethnic and political unrest .",O O O O O B-tim O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ JJ NN IN CD VBD JJ JJ NNP NNP NNP , CC VBD IN DT NN IN JJ CC JJ NN ."
"Southern-based rebel groups agreed to a final peace accord in March 2003 , but the calm is tenuous and refugees continue to present a humanitarian crisis .",O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NN NNS VBD TO DT JJ NN NN IN NNP CD , CC DT NN VBZ JJ CC NNS VBP TO VB DT JJ NN ."
"The Republic of Congo was once one of Africa 's largest petroleum producers , but with declining production it will need new offshore oil finds to sustain its oil earnings over the long term .",O B-geo O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP IN NNP VBD RB CD IN NNP POS JJS NN NNS , CC IN VBG NN PRP MD VB JJ JJ NN NNS TO VB PRP$ NN NNS IN DT JJ NN ."
