The U.S. Department of Defense says it will begin blocking the use of its computers and networks to access some popular websites on the Internet .,O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP IN NNP VBZ PRP MD VB VBG DT NN IN PRP$ NNS CC NNS TO VB DT JJ NNS IN DT NN .
"A memo from the U.S. forces commander in Korea , General B.B. Bell , says the Pentagon will block access to sites like YouTube and MySpace , along with some other video and photo-sharing services and social networking sites .",O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O B-org I-org I-org O O O B-org O O O O O O B-org O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN DT NNP NNS VBP IN NNP , NNP NNP NNP , VBZ DT NNP MD VB NN TO NNS IN NNP CC NNP , IN IN DT JJ NN CC JJ NNS CC JJ NN NNS ."
The Pentagon says the ban is needed because recreational traffic to the websites slows down official Defense Department networks and poses a significant security challenge .,O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O,DT NNP VBZ DT NN VBZ VBN IN JJ NN TO DT NNS VBZ RP JJ NNP NNP NNS CC VBZ DT JJ NN NN .
The access restrictions will only affect Defense Department equipment .,O O O O O O B-org I-org O O,DT NN NNS MD RB VB NNP NNP NN .
"Members of the U.S. military can still access the websites on their own computers and networks , although Pentagon computers are the only ones available to many troops serving in Iraq and Afghanistan .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,"NNS IN DT NNP NN MD RB VB DT NNS IN PRP$ JJ NNS CC NNS , IN NNP NNS VBP DT JJ NNS JJ TO JJ NNS VBG IN NNP CC NNP ."
