An Afghan court has sentenced a former senior police officer to 10 years in prison for helping traffickers smuggle drugs from Afghanistan to Iran .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O,DT JJ NN VBZ VBN DT JJ JJ NN NN TO CD NNS IN NN IN VBG NNS VBP NNS IN NNP TO NNP .
The jury found Commander General Malham Khan guilty Tuesday of cooperating with drug dealers and receiving bribes .,O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per B-tim O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD NNP NNP NNP NNP JJ NNP IN VBG IN NN NNS CC VBG NNS .
"He was also fined $ 14,000 .",O O O O O O O,PRP VBD RB VBN $ CD .
"Authorities arrested the general , who was in charge of Afghan provinces bordering Turkmenistan and Iran , earlier this year .",O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O,"NNS VBN DT JJ , WP VBD IN NN IN JJ NNS VBG NNP CC NNP , RBR DT NN ."
Khan has denied all charges against him .,B-per O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN DT NNS IN PRP .
The prosecution 's evidence was based on the testimony of two police officers who worked with the general .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN POS NN VBD VBN IN DT NN IN CD NNS NNS WP VBD IN DT NN .
"Afghanistan is the world 's leading producer of poppies , the raw material for opium and heroin .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ DT NN POS VBG NN IN NNS , DT JJ NN IN NN CC NN ."
The country 's multi-million- dollar drug trade is seen to be aiding the Taliban-led insurgency and encouraging corruption .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN POS JJ NN NN NN VBZ VBN TO VB VBG DT JJ NN CC JJ NN .
