At least 17 people have been reported killed and more than 60 hurt in clashes between rival ethnic and political groups in the Pakistani city of Karachi over the past two days .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O B-tim I-tim O O,IN JJS CD NNS VBP VBN VBN VBN CC JJR IN CD NN IN NNS IN JJ JJ CC JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN IN NNP IN DT JJ CD NNS .
"Security forces are patrolling Karachi Sunday to prevent further violence between members of a political party that represents Urdu speakers , Muttahida Qaumi Movement , and another that represents Pashtuns , Awami National Party .",O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,"NN NNS VBP VBG NNP NNP TO VB JJ NN IN NNS IN DT JJ NN WDT VBZ NNP NNS , NNP NNP NNP , CC DT WDT VBZ NNPS , NNP NNP NNP ."
Troops have been given orders to use their guns if necessary .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP VBN VBN NNS TO VB PRP$ NNS IN JJ .
"Since Saturday , angry mobs have rampaged in parts of the city , firing guns and setting fire to cars .",B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , JJ NNS VBP VBN IN NNS IN DT NN , VBG NNS CC VBG NN TO NNS ."
"Today in northwest Pakistan , police say militants attacked a security post in the town of Bannu , close to the Afghan border , killing three police .",B-tim O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O,"NN IN JJ NNP , NNS VBP NNS VBD DT NN NN IN DT NN IN NNP , RB TO DT JJ NN , VBG CD NNS ."
Three militants were killed in the fighting .,O O O O O O O O,CD NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN .
"In nearby Lakki Marwat , another three policemen were killed when Taliban insurgents launched rockets at a security checkpoint .",O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O,"IN JJ NNP NNP , DT CD NNS VBD VBN WRB NNP VBZ VBD NNS IN DT NN NN ."
