Pakistani officials say a suspected U.S. missile strike has killed at least four militants in the country 's northwestern tribal region .,B-gpe O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP DT JJ NNP NN NN VBZ VBN IN JJS CD NNS IN DT NN POS JJ JJ NN .
"Elsewhere in the tribal region , officials say Pakistani troops used mortars and artillery to target militant hide-outs near Khar , the main town in Bajaur .",O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O,"RB IN DT JJ NN , NNS VBP JJ NNS VBD NNS CC NN TO VB NN NNS IN NNP , DT JJ NN IN NNP ."
They say at least 18 militants were killed .,O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN .
"In Orakzai tribal agency , local officials say 11 militants and two soldiers were killed during clashes Monday .",O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"IN NNP JJ NN , JJ NNS VBP CD NNS CC CD NNS VBD VBN IN NNS NNP ."
