"The head of the Democratic Republic of Congo 's electoral commission says nationwide elections set for June this year may be delayed , but added they must take place by November .",O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,"DT NN IN DT JJ NNP IN NNP POS JJ NN VBZ JJ NNS VBN IN NNP DT NN MD VB VBN , CC VBD PRP MD VB NN IN NNP ."
"Apolinaire Malu Malu says postponing elections is in line with Congo 's peace accord , which allows for two delays of up to six months .",B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBG NNS VBZ IN NN IN NNP POS NN NN , WDT VBZ IN CD NNS IN RB IN CD NNS ."
The elections will mark the first time Congolese voters will go to the polls since independence in 1960 .,O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NNS MD VB DT JJ NN JJ NNS MD VB TO DT NNS IN NN IN CD .
Most of the fighting that drew in six foreign armies and several rebel groups has stopped and Congo 's former fighters have joined a transitional government .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,JJS IN DT NN WDT VBD IN CD JJ NNS CC JJ NN NNS VBZ VBN CC NNP POS JJ NNS VBP VBN DT JJ NN .
But progress in unifying the vast Central African country has been hampered by political infighting and continued lawlessness and sporadic violence in the east .,O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC NN IN VBG DT JJ JJ JJ NN VBZ VBN VBN IN JJ NN CC JJ NN CC JJ NN IN DT NN .
