Thousands of Sudanese gathered at Khartoum airport Saturday to show their support for a new peace deal between the government and southern rebels .,O O B-gpe O O B-geo I-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS IN NNS VBD IN NNP NN NNP TO VB PRP$ NN IN DT JJ NN NN IN DT NN CC JJ NNS .
"Crowds sang , danced , and cheered the arrival of the government negotiators headed by Sudan 's First Vice President Ali Osman Taha .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O,"NNS VBD , VBD , CC VBD DT NN IN DT NN NNS VBN IN NNP POS NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
"Later , Mr. Taha told another crowd at the headquarters of the ruling party that the deal is complete , with no differences remaining .",O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , NNP NNP VBD DT NN IN DT NN IN DT VBG NN IN DT NN VBZ JJ , IN DT NNS VBG ."
"Meanwhile , Sudan 's opposition Popular Congress Party welcomed the deal .",O O B-gpe O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O,"RB , NNP POS NN NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN ."
"On Friday in Kenya , the government and the rebel Sudan 's People 's Liberation Army signed the last remaining agreements to bring an end to 21 years of civil war .",O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O,"IN NNP IN NNP , DT NN CC DT NN NNP POS NNS POS NNP NNP VBD DT JJ VBG NNS TO VB DT NN TO CD NNS IN JJ NN ."
The latest accords call for a permanent cease-fire and lay out the details of how to implement a final agreement .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJS NNS VBP IN DT JJ NN CC VBD RP DT NNS IN WRB TO VB DT JJ NN .
A document that includes all previous agreements is expected to be signed on January 9 .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,DT NN WDT VBZ DT JJ NNS VBZ VBN TO VB VBN IN NNP CD .
