U.S. President Barack Obama and Russian counterpart Dmitri Medvedev say they still plan to have a replacement nuclear arms reduction treaty ready by the end of the year .,B-geo B-per I-per I-per O B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP CC JJ NN NNP NNP VBP PRP RB VBP TO VB DT NN JJ NNS NN NN JJ IN DT NN IN DT NN .
The two presidents met in Singapore Sunday after the close of the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation forum .,O O O O O B-org B-tim O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O,DT CD NNS VBD IN NNP NNP IN DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NN .
"The two leading nuclear powers have committed to a replacement for their Strategic Arms Reduction Treaty , which expires on December 5 .",O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"DT CD VBG JJ NNS VBP VBN TO DT NN IN PRP$ NNP NNPS NNP NNP , WDT VBZ IN NNP CD ."
"Earlier this year , Mr. Obama and Mr. Medvedev agreed to reduce Cold War-era stockpiles from 2,200 warheads to somewhere between 1,500 and 1,650 .",O O O O B-per I-per O B-per I-per O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O,"RBR DT NN , NNP NNP CC NNP NNP VBD TO VB NNP NNP NNS IN CD NNS TO RB IN CD CC CD ."
That agreement is part of a commitment from both leaders to reset bilateral relations strained in recent years by differences over NATO expansion and the brief Russian-Georgian war of 2008 .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NN VBZ NN IN DT NN IN DT NNS TO VB JJ NNS VBN IN JJ NNS IN NNS IN NNP NN CC DT JJ JJ NN IN CD .
