"Switzerland has scored a surprise win over the Czech Republic , while Finland blanked host country Italy in the men 's Olympic ice hockey tournament in Turin .",B-geo O O O O O O O B-gpe B-geo O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP VBZ VBN DT NN NN IN DT JJ NNP , IN NNP VBD NN NN NNP IN DT NNS POS NNP NN NN NN IN NNP ."
"David Aebischer of the Colorado Avalanche made 40 saves for the Swiss as they stunned the 1998 Olympic champion Czech team , 3-2 .",B-per I-per O O B-org I-org O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-tim O O B-gpe O O O O,"NNP NNP IN DT NNP NNP VBD CD NNS IN DT NNS IN PRP VBD DT CD NNP NN JJ NN , CD ."
"The Swiss team has only two National ice Hockey League players in its lineup , while the Czech Republic boasts such stars as Jaromir Jagr , Tomas Vokun , Marek Zidlicky and Dominik Hasek .",O B-gpe O O O O B-org O B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-gpe B-geo O O O O B-org I-org O B-org I-org O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,"DT JJ NN VBZ RB CD NNP NN NNP NNP NNS IN PRP$ NN , IN DT JJ NNP VBZ JJ NNS IN NNP NNP , NNP NNP , NNP NNP CC NNP NNP ."
"Earlier , Finland blanked host country Italy , 6-0 , with Anaheim Mighty Ducks star Teemu Selanne scoring twice for the Finns .",O O B-geo O O O B-geo O B-geo O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O B-gpe O,"RB , NNP VBD NN NN NNP , CD , IN NNP NNP NNP NN NNP NNP VBG RB IN DT NNS ."
Other games Thursday have Sweden taking on Russia and Slovakia facing Latvia .,O O B-tim O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo O,JJ NNS NNP VBP NNP VBG IN NNP CC NNP VBG NNP .
Reigning champion Canada plays Germany and the U.S. team plays Kazakhstan .,O O B-geo O B-geo O O B-geo O O B-geo O,VBG NN NNP VBZ NNP CC DT NNP NN VBZ NNP .
