Italy says it will extradite a key suspect in the failed July 21 London bombings to Britain within 35 days so Italian authorities have time to complete their investigations .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim B-geo O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ PRP MD VB DT JJ NN IN DT VBN NNP CD NNP NNS TO NNP IN CD NNS RB JJ NNS VBP NN TO VB PRP$ NNS .
"An Italian judge made the announcement Wednesday in Rome following an extradition hearing for suspect Hamdi Issac , also known as Osman Hussain .",O B-gpe O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-per I-per O,"DT JJ NN VBD DT NN NNP IN NNP VBG DT NN NN IN JJ NNP NNP , RB VBN IN NNP NNP ."
The decision came after an Italian prosecutor asked for a delay in any decision until authorities properly analyze materials the suspect allegedly carried on the day of the failed bombings .,O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD IN DT JJ NN VBD IN DT NN IN DT NN IN NNS RB VBP NNS DT NN RB VBD IN DT NN IN DT VBN NNS .
"British authorities have charged that Mr. Issac , a British citizen of Ethiopian descent , fled to Italy after he and three other men allegedly tried to set off bombs on three London subway trains and a bus .",B-gpe O O O O B-per B-geo O O B-gpe O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP VBN IN NNP NNP , DT JJ NN IN JJ NN , VBD TO NNP IN PRP CC CD JJ NNS RB VBD TO VB RP NNS IN CD NNP NN NNS CC DT NN ."
The other suspects are in British custody .,O O O O O B-gpe O O,DT JJ NNS VBP IN JJ NN .
"The failed attacks came two weeks after the July seventh London bombings , which killed 56 people , including four suicide bombers .",O O O O B-tim O O O B-tim I-tim B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNS VBD CD NNS IN DT NNP JJ NNP NNS , WDT VBD CD NNS , VBG CD NN NNS ."
