"Former President Jimmy Carter says he will head an independent observer mission for the upcoming Palestinian elections , but he says he will not participate in the Iraqi polls set for January 30 .",O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-tim I-tim O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ PRP MD VB DT JJ NN NN IN DT JJ JJ NNS , CC PRP VBZ PRP MD RB VB IN DT JJ NNS VBN IN NNP CD ."
"In an interview with Reuters news agency , Mr. Carter - who has monitored more than 50 elections around the world - said the Iraqi situation is "" a debacle - a very costly one . """,O O O O B-org O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN IN NNP NN NN , NNP NNP : WP VBZ VBN JJR IN CD NNS IN DT NN : VBD DT JJ NN VBZ LQU DT NN IN DT RB JJ NN . LQU"
He said there is not enough security in that country to have a fair and safe election .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD EX VBZ RB JJ NN IN DT NN TO VB DT JJ CC JJ NN .
The former U.S. president also said Palestinian leaders have invited him to monitor January ninth polls called to replace the late Yasser Arafat .,O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O B-org I-org O,DT JJ NNP NN RB VBD JJ NNS VBP VBN PRP TO VB NNP JJ NNS VBN TO VB DT JJ NNP NNP .
"He said he is optimistic about those polls , and will utilize 80 to 90 observers from his Atlanta-based Carter Center .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,"PRP VBD PRP VBZ JJ IN DT NNS , CC MD VB CD TO CD NNS IN PRP$ JJ NNP NNP ."
President Carter helped broker the historic 1979 peace treaty between Egypt and Israel .,B-per I-per O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O B-geo O,NNP NNP VBD NN DT JJ CD NN NN IN NNP CC NNP .
