"A spill of up to 150,000 liters of diesel oil from a broken pipeline in northern China has reached the Yellow River , the drinking water source for millions of people .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN RB TO CD NNS IN JJ NN IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NNP VBZ VBN DT NNP NNP , DT NN NN NN IN NNS IN NNS ."
State media say the spill in an upstream tributary reached the massive river Monday .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP NNS VBP DT NN IN DT NN NN VBD DT JJ NN NNP .
Thousands of people in northern China have been told to stop using water from the Yellow River .,O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,NNS IN NNS IN JJ NNP VBP VBN VBN TO VB VBG NN IN DT NNP NNP .
The diesel oil spilled last Wednesday from a ruptured pipeline into the Wei River .,O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,DT JJ NN VBN JJ NNP IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP .
That pipeline in Shaanxi province is owned by China National Petroleum Corporation .,O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O,DT NN IN NNP NN VBZ VBN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP .
"China 's official news agency , Xinhua , says the company immediately closed the pipeline when the leak was discovered , but not before about 150,000 liters had spilled out .",B-geo O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ NN NN , NNP , VBZ DT NN RB VBD DT NN WRB DT NN VBD VBN , CC RB IN IN CD NNS VBD VBN RP ."
"Hundreds of workers dug diversion channels and built floating dams on Sunday , in what turned out to be a failed attempt to keep the leak from reaching the Yellow River .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"NNS IN NNS JJ NN NNS CC VBN VBG NNS IN NNP , IN WP VBD RP TO VB DT JJ NN TO VB DT NN IN VBG DT NNP NNP ."
