North Korea has proposed a resumption of talks involving Red Cross officials from both countries .,B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN NNS VBG NNP NNP NNS IN DT NNS .
"South Korean Red Cross officials say their Northern counterparts telephoned Friday , with an offer to host a meeting later this month at the Mount Kumgang resort near the Demilitarized Zone separating the two countries .",B-org B-gpe B-org I-org O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP JJ NNP NNP NNS VBP PRP$ JJ NNS VBN NNP , IN DT NN TO VB DT NN RBR DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NN IN DT VBN NNP VBG DT CD NNS ."
The two sides have been discussing the construction of facilities at Mount Kumgang for the reunions of separated families .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O,DT CD NNS VBP VBN VBG DT NN IN NNS IN NNP NNP IN DT NNS IN JJ NNS .
"The North Korean offer came two days after Seoul sent the first shipment of a promised 100,000 tons of fertilizer to the north .",O B-geo B-gpe O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ JJ NN VBD CD NNS IN NNP VBD DT JJ NN IN DT VBN CD NNS IN NN TO DT NN .
"The last Red Cross talks took place in July , prior to a deterioration in bilateral ties triggered by a mass defection of North Koreans to the South .",O O B-org I-org O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-gpe O B-geo I-geo O,"DT JJ NNP NNP NNS VBD NN IN NNP , RB TO DT NN IN JJ NNS VBN IN DT NN NN IN NNP NNS TO DT NNP ."
