Syrian intelligence agents have abandoned their headquarters in Lebanon 's Bekaa Valley town of Anjar and returned home .,B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O,JJ NN NNS VBP VBN PRP$ NN IN NNP POS NNP NNP NN IN NNP CC VBD NN .
Their departure Monday virtually completes a pullout that ends 29 years of Syrian dominance in Lebanese political life .,O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-gpe O O O,PRP$ NN NNP RB VBZ DT NN WDT VBZ CD NNS IN JJ NN IN JJ JJ NN .
Witnesses say a Syrian convoy left Anjar and crossed the border into Syria at Masnaa early this evening .,O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O B-geo B-tim I-tim I-tim O,NNS VBP DT JJ NN VBD NNP CC VBD DT NN IN NNP IN NNP RB DT NN .
"The head of Syrian military intelligence , Major-General Rustom Ghazale , was seen in one of the vehicles .",O O O B-gpe O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN JJ JJ NN , JJ NNP NNP , VBD VBN IN CD IN DT NNS ."
He is expected to return to Lebanon briefly Tuesday to take part in a farewell ceremony .,O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ VBN TO VB IN NNP RB NNP TO VB NN IN DT JJ NN .
"Earlier Monday , Lebanon 's pro-Syrian security chief resigned .",O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O,"RBR NNP , NNP POS JJ NN NN VBD ."
The Syrian withdrawal comes two months after opposition leaders blamed the Beirut government and its Syrian sponsors for the assassination of former Lebanese Prime Minister Rafik Hariri .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O,DT JJ NN VBZ CD NNS IN NN NNS VBD DT NNP NN CC PRP$ JJ NNS IN DT NN IN JJ JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP .
"Despite denials from both governments , hundreds of thousands of protesters took to the streets of Beirut to demand that all Syrian forces leave the country .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O O O O,"IN NNS IN DT NNS , NNS IN NNS IN NNS VBD TO DT NNS IN NNP TO VB IN DT JJ NNS VBP DT NN ."
