Renewed protests have erupted in Bolivia 's capital as demonstrators massed in the streets and set up roadblocks to press for the nationalization of the energy sector .,O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,VBN NNS VBP VBN IN NNP POS NN IN NNS VBD IN DT NNS CC VBN RP NNS TO VB IN DT NN IN DT NN NN .
"As the protesters crowded the streets of La Paz Thursday , President Carlos Mesa 's government rejected suggestions that international mediation could be needed to resolve the crisis .",O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo B-tim O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NNS VBD DT NNS IN NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP NNP POS NN VBD NNS IN JJ NN MD VB VBN TO VB DT NN ."
The remark came one day after the U.S. State Department said Bolivia will be discussed at a meeting in Florida next week of the Organization of American States General Assembly .,O O O B-tim I-tim O O B-org I-org I-org O B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O B-tim O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,DT NN VBD CD NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP MD VB VBN IN DT NN IN NNP JJ NN IN DT NNP IN NNP NNP NNP NNP .
"Bolivia 's Congress recently passed a bill to increase taxes on foreign oil companies , but opponents say it does not go far enough .",B-geo O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NNP RB VBD DT NN TO VB NNS IN JJ NN NNS , CC NNS VBP PRP VBZ RB VB RB RB ."
"The measure calls for the firms to pay a 32 percent tax on production , in addition to an 18 percent royalty tax they already pay .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ IN DT NNS TO VB DT CD NN NN IN NN , IN NN TO DT CD NN NN NN PRP RB VBP ."
