Washington D.C. has moved a step closer to formally returning Major League Baseball to the U.S. capital .,B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN RBR TO RB VBG NNP NNP NN TO DT NNP NN .
The D.C. City Council initially approved Tuesday a debt and tax-backed financing plan to build a new stadium .,O B-geo I-geo B-org O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP RB VBD NNP DT NN CC JJ NN NN TO VB DT JJ NN .
"Under the proposal , Washington would sell about $ 500 million in bonds along with an increased stadium sales tax and a new tax on large businesses in the city .",O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN , NNP MD VB IN $ CD CD IN NNS IN IN DT VBN NN NNS NN CC DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS IN DT NN ."
The financing needs final approval by December 31 under Mayor Anthony Williams ' agreement with Major League Baseball .,O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ JJ NN IN NNP CD IN NNP NNP NNP POS NN IN NNP NNP NNP .
The mayor has said a new stadium would cost about $ 440 million .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ VBN DT JJ NN MD VB IN $ CD CD .
But other estimates boost the total by more than $ 140 million .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,CC JJ NNS VBP DT NN IN JJR IN $ CD CD .
The league announced in September the Montreal Expos would move to Washington .,O O O O B-tim O B-org I-org O O O B-geo O,DT NN VBD IN NNP DT NNP NNP MD VB TO NNP .
The team was later renamed the Nationals .,O O O O O O B-org O,DT NN VBD RB VBN DT NNPS .
