"Australia 's Sydney Harbor went dark as lights were turned off at the iconic Sydney Opera House and Harbor Bridge as part of Earth Hour , a global event calling attention to climate change .",B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-geo I-geo O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NNP NNP VBD JJ IN NNS VBD VBN RP IN DT JJ NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP IN NN IN NNP NNP , DT JJ NN VBG NN TO NN NN ."
"First organized in Sydney in 2007 , at least 3,929 communities around the world are shutting off lights this year in the event rolling through the world 's time zones .",O O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB VBN IN NNP IN CD , IN JJS CD NNS IN DT NN VBP VBG RP NNS DT NN IN DT NN VBG IN DT NN POS NN NNS ."
Hundreds of landmarks around the world are expected to go dark for an hour as nightfall circles the globe Saturday night .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,NNS IN NNS IN DT NN VBP VBN TO VB NN IN DT NN IN JJ NNS DT NN NNP NN .
This year 's Earth Hour officially started in the remote Chatham Island chain about 800 kilometers southeast of New Zealand .,O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O B-org I-org O,DT NN POS NNP NNP RB VBD IN DT JJ NNP NNP NN IN CD NNS NN IN NNP NNP .
"Organizers hope up to a billion people from small villages in Namibia to sprawling cities in Asia will participate in an international effort to cut greenhouse gas emissions , which many scientists blame for a warming climate .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP RP TO DT CD NNS IN JJ NNS IN NNP TO VBG NNS IN NNP MD VB IN DT JJ NN TO VB NN NN NNS , WDT JJ NNS VBP IN DT NN NN ."
