"The economy of Benin remains underdeveloped and dependent on subsistence agriculture , cotton production , and regional trade .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN NNP VBZ JJ CC JJ IN NN NN , NN NN , CC JJ NN ."
"Growth in real output had averaged about 4 % before the global recession , but fell to 2.7 % in 2009 and 3 % in 2010 .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-tim O,"NN IN JJ NN VBD VBN RB CD NN IN DT JJ NN , CC VBD TO CD NN IN CD CC CD NN IN CD ."
Inflation has subsided over the past several years .,O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O,NN VBZ VBN IN DT JJ JJ NNS .
"In order to raise growth , Benin plans to attract more foreign investment , place more emphasis on tourism , facilitate the development of new food processing systems and agricultural products , and encourage new information and communication technology .",O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NN TO VB NN , NNP VBZ TO VB JJR JJ NN , NN JJR NN IN NN , VB DT NN IN JJ NN NN NNS CC JJ NNS , CC VB JJ NN CC NN NN ."
"Specific projects to improve the business climate by reforms to the land tenure system , the commercial justice system , and the financial sector were included in Benin 's $ 307 million Millennium Challenge Account grant signed in February 2006 .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O B-tim I-tim O,"JJ NNS TO VB DT NN NN IN NNS TO DT NN NN NN , DT JJ NN NN , CC DT JJ NN VBD VBN IN NNP POS $ CD CD NNP NNP NNP NN VBN IN NNP CD ."
"The 2001 privatization policy continues in telecommunications , water , electricity , and agriculture .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT CD NN NN VBZ IN NNS , NN , NN , CC NN ."
"As result of these reforms , Benin has become the most competitive country in the West African Economic and Monetary Union , according to the World Economic Forum .",O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-org I-org I-org O,"IN NN IN DT NNS , NNP VBZ VBN DT RBS JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP , VBG TO DT NNP NNP NNP ."
"The Paris Club and bilateral creditors have eased the external debt situation , with Benin benefiting from a G-8 debt reduction announced in July 2005 , while pressing for more rapid structural reforms .",O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-org O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP CC JJ NNS VBP VBN DT JJ NN NN , IN NNP VBG IN DT NNP NN NN VBN IN NNP CD , IN VBG IN RBR JJ JJ NNS ."
An insufficient electrical supply continues to adversely affect Benin 's economic growth though the government recently has taken steps to increase domestic power production .,O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ JJ NN VBZ TO RB VB NNP POS JJ NN IN DT NN RB VBZ VBN NNS TO VB JJ NN NN .
