German prosecutors say Polish authorities have arrested a suspected Israeli intelligence agent wanted in connection with the assassination of a Palestinian militant in Dubai .,B-gpe O O B-gpe O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O,JJ NNS VBP JJ NNS VBP VBN DT JJ JJ NN NN VBN IN NN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP .
"A spokesman for the German federal prosecutor 's office said Saturday that the suspect , Uri Brodsky , was arrested in early June upon his arrival in Poland .",O O O O B-gpe O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-geo O,"DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NN POS NN VBD NNP IN DT NN , NNP NNP , VBD VBN IN JJ NNP IN PRP$ NN IN NNP ."
He was accused of obtaining an illegal German passport .,O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,PRP VBD VBN IN VBG DT JJ JJ NN .
"Police in Dubai have said a team of assassins used forged passports to conduct an operation in January to kill a senior Hamas commander , Mahmoud al-Mabhou .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-org O O B-per I-per O,"NNS IN NNP VBP VBN DT NN IN NNS VBN VBD NNS TO VB DT NN IN NNP TO VB DT JJ NNP NN , NNP NNP ."
Dubai has accused Israel 's Mossad spy agency of being behind the killing .,B-geo O O B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN NNP POS NNP NN NN IN VBG IN DT NN .
Israel has said there is no proof to back that claim .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN EX VBZ DT NN TO VB DT NN .
