A Somali teenager accused of leading last month 's hijacking of an American cargo ship has pleaded not guilty to piracy charges .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBN IN VBG JJ NN POS NN IN DT JJ NN NN VBZ VBN RB JJ TO NN NNS .
Abdiwali Abdiqadir Muse entered his plea Thursday during a short appearance in U.S. District Court in New York .,B-org I-org I-org O O O B-tim O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O B-geo I-geo O,NNP NNP NNP VBD PRP$ NN NNP IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP NNP IN NNP NNP .
"Earlier this week , Muse was indicted on 10 counts that include piracy , hostage-taking , kidnapping , and possession of a machine gun while seizing a ship by force .",O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RBR DT NN , NNP VBD VBN IN CD NNS WDT VBP NN , NN , NN , CC NN IN DT NN NN IN VBG DT NN IN NN ."
Prosecutors said Muse led the band of pirates that briefly hijacked the U.S.-flagged Maersk Alabama near Somalia last month .,O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O,NNS VBD NNP VBD DT NN IN NNS IN RB VBD DT JJ NNP NNP IN NNP JJ NN .
The U.S. Navy took him into custody April 12 during operations that freed captain Richard Phillips and killed the three other pirates .,O B-org I-org O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP VBD PRP IN NN NNP CD IN NNS WDT VBD NN NNP NNP CC VBD DT CD JJ NNS .
"U.S. authorities believe Muse to be at least 18 , old enough to be tried as an adult , though his parents have said he is younger .",B-geo O O B-org O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNS VBP NN TO VB IN JJS CD , JJ NN TO VB VBN IN DT NN , IN PRP$ NNS VBP VBN PRP VBZ JJR ."
He faces a maximum sentence of life in prison if convicted .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ DT JJ NN IN NN IN NN IN VBN .
