Health officials in Indonesia say tests show that a girl who died on Thursday was infected with bird flu .,O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O,NNP NNS IN NNP VBP NNS VBP IN DT NN WP VBD IN NNP VBD VBN IN NN NN .
The World Health Organization has yet to confirm the cause of death .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ RB TO VB DT NN IN NN .
Authorities say the girl lived in a city on the outskirts of Jakarta .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNS VBP DT NN VBD IN DT NN IN DT NNS IN NNP .
"Meanwhile , WHO officials say 54 people under quarantine in Indonesia are receiving daily medical exams and the anti-viral drug Tamiflu as a precaution .",O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"RB , WP NNS VBP CD NNS IN NN IN NNP VBP VBG JJ JJ NNS CC DT JJ NN NNP IN DT NN ."
All came in contact with seven family members who died from the virus last month .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT VBD IN NN IN CD NN NNS WP VBD IN DT NN JJ NN .
"In Europe , the European Union is expanding an import ban on Romanian poultry because of spreading instances of the deadly H5N1 strain of bird flu .",O B-geo O O B-org I-org O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , DT NNP NNP VBZ VBG DT NN NN IN JJ NN IN IN VBG NNS IN DT JJ NNP NN IN NN NN ."
The EU restrictions now apply to the entire country .,O B-org O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNS RB VBP TO DT JJ NN .
They previously applied only to parts of Romania .,O O O O O O O B-geo O,PRP RB VBD RB TO NNS IN NNP .
