U.S. Defense Secretary Robert Gates has ordered top military officials to inform the Pentagon before giving interviews to news media .,B-org I-org B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN JJ NN NNS TO VB DT NNP IN VBG NNS TO NN NNS .
"The new policy announced Friday comes little more than a week after the top U.S. commander in Afghanistan , General Stanley McChrystal , was forced to resign because of a published article .",O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBN NNP VBZ RB JJR IN DT NN IN DT JJ NNP NN IN NNP , NNP NNP NNP , VBD VBN TO VB IN IN DT VBN NN ."
The U.S. magazine Rolling Stone last month published mocking comments McChrystal and his staff made about the Obama administration .,O B-geo O B-per I-per O O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-per O O,DT NNP NN NNP NNP JJ NN VBD VBG NNS NNP CC PRP$ NN VBD IN DT NNP NN .
Pentagon officials say Secretary Gates was working on the new policy before that scandal .,B-org O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBP NNP NNP VBD VBG IN DT JJ NN IN DT NN .
They added that the policy was not intended to restrict information or media access to officials .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD IN DT NN VBD RB VBN TO VB NN CC NNS NN TO NNS .
Some reporters have expressed concern after the McChrystal episode that military officials will be wary of communicating with them .,O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBP VBN NN IN DT NNP NN IN JJ NNS MD VB JJ IN VBG IN PRP .
