Peru has canceled planned talks with Chile at an Asia-Pacific summit and is leaving the meeting a day early over an espionage dispute .,B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN JJ NNS IN NNP IN DT JJ NN CC VBZ VBG DT NN DT NN RB IN DT NN NN .
"Peru 's foreign minister , Jose Garcia Belaunde , says President Alan Garcia is leaving the meeting in Singapore , following the recall of Peru 's envoy to Chile over charges a Peruvian military officer has been spying for Chile .",B-geo O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNP POS JJ NN , NNP NNP NNP , VBZ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBG DT NN IN NNP , VBG DT NN IN NNP POS NN TO NNP IN NNS DT JJ JJ NN VBZ VBN VBG IN NNP ."
Mr. Garcia and his Chilean counterpart Michelle Bachelet had been scheduled to meet at the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation forum .,B-per I-per O O B-gpe O B-per I-per O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O,NNP NNP CC PRP$ JJ NN NNP NNP VBD VBN VBN TO VB IN DT NNP NNP NNP NN .
Peruvian officials say they are returning to Lima to investigate the charges against the air force officer who was arrested several days ago .,B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O,JJ NNS VBP PRP VBP VBG TO NNP TO VB DT NNS IN DT NN NN NN WP VBD VBN JJ NNS RB .
"The neighboring South American countries maintain close trade ties , but have a long-standing maritime border dispute .",O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ JJ JJ NNS VBP JJ NN NNS , CC VBP DT JJ NN NN NN ."
