"Three Muslim men , believed to be closely linked to al-Qaida , have pleaded guilty in London to using the Internet to incite terrorism .",O B-org O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"CD NNP NNS , VBN TO VB RB VBN TO NNP , VBP VBN JJ IN NNP TO VBG DT NN TO VB NN ."
"Authorities say Younes Tsouli , Waseem Mughal and Tariq al-Daour pleaded guilty to charges of inciting acts of terrorism wholly or partly outside Britain via Web sites that encouraged the killing of non-Muslims .",O O B-org I-org O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP NNP NNP , NNP NNP CC NNP NNP VBD JJ TO NNS IN JJ NNS IN NN RB CC RB JJ NNP IN NNP NNS WDT VBD DT NN IN JJ ."
Police say the three men financed their activities using stolen credit cards .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP DT CD NNS VBD PRP$ NNS VBG JJ NN NNS .
Officials say they believe the case is the first time in Britain that anyone has been convicted on such charges .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP PRP VBP DT NN VBZ DT JJ NN IN NNP IN DT VBZ VBN VBN IN JJ NNS .
The three changed their not-guilty pleas several months into their trial .,O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT CD VBD PRP$ JJ NNS JJ NNS IN PRP$ NN .
Authorities said they found manuals for putting together car bombs and suicide vests in the possession of the three men .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBD PRP VBD NNS IN VBG RB NN NNS CC NN NNS IN DT NN IN DT CD NNS .
