Egypt 's leading human rights group has called for an investigation into the violent death of a jailed suspected terrorist .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS VBG JJ NNS NN VBZ VBN IN DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ JJ NN .
Officials said Ashraf Saeed Youssef died in prison last Thursday after intentionally smashing his head against a wall .,O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBD NNP NNP NNP VBD IN NN JJ NNP IN RB VBG PRP$ NN IN DT NN .
The Egyptian Organization for Human Rights says he may have been tortured while in detention .,O B-gpe B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNP IN NNP NNP VBZ PRP MD VB VBN VBN IN IN NN .
Prosecutors accused him of leading a group responsible for several recent attacks on foreigners .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBD PRP IN VBG DT NN JJ IN JJ JJ NNS IN NNS .
They say he organized the April 7 suicide bombing in Cairo that killed three foreigners and the April 30 attacks on the Egyptian Museum and a tourist bus that wounded seven people .,O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O B-gpe B-org O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBP PRP VBD DT NNP CD NN NN IN NNP WDT VBD CD NNS CC DT NNP CD NNS IN DT JJ NNP CC DT NN NN WDT VBD CD NNS .
The human rights group said Ashraf Saeed Youssef 's cousin also died in police custody earlier this month .,O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NNS NN VBD NNP NNP NNP POS NN RB VBD IN NN NN RBR DT NN .
There were no details available on his death .,O O O O O O O O O,EX VBD DT NNS JJ IN PRP$ NN .
