The rights group Amnesty International has accused Nigerian authorities of forcibly evicting 1.2 million people from their homes over the last five years .,O O O B-org I-org O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,DT NNS NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN JJ NNS IN RB VBG CD CD NNS IN PRP$ NNS IN DT JJ CD NNS .
"Amnesty has released a report on the evictions compiled with a Nigerian group , the Social and Economic Rights Action Center .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,"NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN DT NNS VBN IN DT JJ NN , DT NNP CC NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
"In the most recent instance cited in the report , Amnesty says government forces seized and demolished homes , churches and a mosque in a Lagos neighborhood last April , leaving 3,000 people homeless .",O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-tim O O O O O O,"IN DT RBS JJ NN VBN IN DT NN , NNP VBZ NN NNS VBN CC VBN NNS , NNS CC DT NN IN DT NNP NN JJ NNP , VBG CD NNS JJ ."
"It says nine months later , hundreds of people from the Makoko neighborhood are still sleeping out in the open .",O O B-tim O B-tim O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBZ CD NNS RB , NNS IN NNS IN DT NNP NN VBP RB VBG RP IN DT JJ ."
"Amnesty says the evictions amount to a "" grave violation of human rights , "" and has called on the Nigerian government to immediately make sure they stop .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ DT NNS NN TO DT LQU JJ NN IN JJ NNS , LQU CC VBZ VBN IN DT JJ NN TO RB VB JJ PRP VBP ."
Nigerian officials have not yet commented on the report .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP RB RB VBN IN DT NN .
