Iran has launched an English satellite television news channel in hopes of giving what Tehran says is an alternate view to Western media coverage .,B-geo O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ VBN DT JJ NN NN NN NN IN NNS IN VBG WP NNP VBZ VBZ DT JJ NN TO JJ NNS NN .
"Iranian President Mahmoud Ahmadinejad spoke at a ceremony Monday marking the inauguration of the channel , which will focus on Middle East news .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD IN DT NN NNP VBG DT NN IN DT NN , WDT MD VB IN NNP NNP NN ."
He said the network should stand behind oppressed nations but not make up news in their favor .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD DT NN MD VB IN JJ NNS CC RB VB RP NN IN PRP$ NN .
"The state-owned channel , called Press TV , says on its Web site that it aims to "" break the global media stranglehold of Western outlets . """,O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN , VBD NNP NNP , VBZ IN PRP$ NNP NN IN PRP VBZ TO LQU VB DT JJ NNS NN IN JJ NNS . RQU"
The channel also says it is the first international Iran-based news network to broadcast in English on a 24-hour cycle .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-art O O O O O,DT NN RB VBZ PRP VBZ DT JJ JJ JJ NN NN TO VB IN NNP IN DT JJ NN .
"Press TV has bureaus and staff around the world , including in the Middle East and the United States .",B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNP NNP VBZ NN CC NN IN DT NN , VBG IN DT NNP NNP CC DT NNP NNPS ."
