"China plans to relocate more than 100,000 people this year to make way for the Three Gorges Dam .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,NNP VBZ TO VB JJR IN CD NNS DT NN TO VB NN IN DT CD NNP NNP .
State media report that this year 's relocations will bring to nearly one million the number of people that have been resettled due to the controversial project .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS NN IN DT NN POS NNS MD VB TO RB CD CD DT NN IN NNS WDT VBP VBN VBN JJ TO DT JJ NN .
"By the time the dam is completed in 2009 , 1.1 million people , mostly residents of the Chongqing area , will have been moved .",O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,"IN DT NN DT NN VBZ VBN IN CD , CD CD NNS , RB NNS IN DT NNP NN , MD VB VBN VBN ."
The Three Gorges Dam hydroelectric project is considered the world 's largest .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT CD VBZ NNP JJ NN VBZ VBN DT NN POS JJS .
Chinese leaders say the dam will control chronic flooding on the Yangtze River and will generate much-needed electricity to drive economic growth in China 's interior .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,JJ NNS VBP DT NN MD VB JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP CC MD VB JJ NN TO VB JJ NN IN NNP POS NN .
The project 's critics say a series of smaller dams could have produced the same effect at a lower cost .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN POS NNS VBP DT NN IN JJR NNS MD VB VBN DT JJ NN IN DT JJR NN .
