Israeli Prime Minister Ariel Sharon has asked his cabinet to approve a range of measures meant to ensure next month 's Palestinian elections are conducted in a free and fair atmosphere .,B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN PRP$ NN TO VB DT NN IN NNS VBN TO VB JJ NN POS JJ NNS VBP VBN IN DT JJ CC JJ NN .
"The arrangements include granting Palestinians freedom of movement , and allowing candidates to campaign in disputed East Jerusalem .",O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"DT NNS VBP VBG NNS NN IN NN , CC VBG NNS TO NN IN JJ NNP NNP ."
Israeli troops would also pull out of Palestinian population centers immediately before the vote .,B-gpe O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,JJ NNS MD RB VB IN IN JJ NN NNS RB IN DT NN .
"Israel has long limited Palestinian activity in East Jerusalem , which it captured and annexed after the 1967 Mideast War .",B-geo O O O B-gpe O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,"NNP VBZ RB VBN JJ NN IN NNP NNP , WDT PRP VBD CC VBD IN DT CD NNP NNP ."
Both sides want Jerusalem for a capital .,O O O B-geo O O O O,DT NNS VBP NNP IN DT NN .
"At today 's cabinet meeting , Mr. Sharon told the ministers it was important to show "" the whole world that Israel allowed free , fair and efficient elections . """,O B-tim O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,"IN NN POS NN NN , NNP NNP VBD DT NNS PRP VBD JJ TO VB LQU DT JJ NN IN NNP VBD JJ , JJ CC JJ NNS . LQU"
The January 9 poll comes in the wake of the death on November 11 of longtime Palestinian leader Yasser Arafat .,O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O B-gpe O B-per I-per O,DT NNP CD NN VBZ IN DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP CD IN JJ JJ NN NNP NNP .
