Lebanese military officials say the army is making significant progress against militants barricaded inside a Palestinian refugee camp in northern Lebanon .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O B-geo O,JJ JJ NNS VBP DT NN VBZ VBG JJ NN IN NNS VBD IN DT JJ NN NN IN JJ NNP .
Officials say at least one Lebanese soldier was killed Tuesday as fighting continued in the eight-week standoff .,O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-tim O O O O O B-tim O O,NNS VBP IN JJS CD JJ NN VBD VBN NNP IN NN VBD IN DT JJ NN .
The military says it has forced the remaining Fatah al-Islam militants into a small area and is pressuring them to surrender .,O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ VBZ PRP VBZ VBN DT VBG NNP NNP NNS IN DT JJ NN CC VBZ VBG PRP TO VB .
"In combat on Monday , troops unleashed artillery shells and exchanged machine gun fire with militants .",O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NN IN NNP , NNS VBD NN NNS CC VBD NN NN NN IN NNS ."
The militants also launched at least five Katyusha rockets that landed in areas outside of the Nahr al-Bared camp .,O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-org O O O,DT NNS RB VBD IN JJS CD NNP NNS WDT VBD IN NNS IN IN DT NNP JJ NN .
More than 200 people have been killed since the standoff began May 20 .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,JJR IN CD NNS VBP VBN VBN IN DT NN VBD NNP CD .
That includes about 100 Lebanese soldiers and at least 60 militants .,O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,DT VBZ IN CD JJ NNS CC IN JJS CD NNS .
