"U.S. and Colombian officials have arrested 22 Colombians for smuggling heroin into the United States using a wide variety of methods , including having the drug surgically implanted into puppies .",B-geo O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP CC JJ NNS VBP VBN CD NNS IN VBG NN IN DT NNP NNPS VBG DT JJ NN IN NNS , VBG VBG DT NN RB VBD IN NNS ."
U.S. Drug Enforcement Administration officials said Wednesday that a two-year investigation led to the arrests in Colombia and the United States .,B-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP NNP NNP NNP NNS VBD NNP IN DT JJ NN VBD TO DT NNS IN NNP CC DT NNP NNPS .
"Officials said that in one instance , three kilograms of liquid heroin packets had been implanted into six puppies .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBD IN IN CD NN , CD NNS IN JJ NN NNS VBD VBN VBN IN CD NNS ."
Three of the dogs later died of infection .,O O O O O O O O O,CD IN DT NNS RB VBD IN NN .
"DEA officials also say smugglers frequently use human couriers , known as "" swallowers , "" who typically ingest drug-packed pellets before boarding flights for the United States .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNP NNS RB VBP NNS RB VBP JJ NNS , VBN IN LQU NNS , RQU WP RB VBP JJ NNS IN VBG NNS IN DT NNP NNPS ."
"The drugs are also frequently concealed in body creams and aerosol cans , and sewn into purses and luggage .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS VBP RB RB VBN IN NN NNS CC NN NNS , CC VBN IN NNS CC NN ."
