"Haiti 's new president Rene Preval is an advocate of the poor , a former president , and a former ally of ex-president Jean-Bertrand Aristide .",B-geo O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ NN NNP NNP VBZ DT NN IN DT NN , DT JJ NN , CC DT JJ NN IN JJ JJ NN ."
"Haitians once referred to Preval and Aristide as "" the twins "" because of their similarities and political alliance .",B-gpe O O O B-per O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS RB VBD TO NNP CC NNP IN LQU DT NNS RQU IN IN PRP$ NNS CC JJ NN .
Both were popular for their interest in helping Haiti 's poor .,O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,DT VBD JJ IN PRP$ NN IN VBG NNP POS NN .
"Preval served his first presidential term from 1996 to 2001 , between Aristide 's two terms in office .",B-per O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O B-per O O O O O O,"NNP VBD PRP$ JJ JJ NN IN CD TO CD , IN NNP POS CD NNS IN NN ."
Critics said Preval was no more than a placeholder for his colleague .,O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBD NNP VBD DT JJR IN DT NN IN PRP$ NN .
But the two men broke over the corruption scandal that brought down Aristide 's presidency in 2004 .,O O O O O O O O O O O O B-per O O O B-tim O,CC DT CD NNS VBD IN DT NN NN WDT VBD RP NNP POS NN IN CD .
"As Haiti 's first elected president since Aristide 's departure , Preval says he wants to improve social conditions and education for his homeland , which is known as the poorest nation in the Americas .",O B-geo O O O O O B-per O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"IN NNP POS JJ VBN NN IN NNP POS NN , NNP VBZ PRP VBZ TO VB JJ NNS CC NN IN PRP$ NN , WDT VBZ VBN IN DT JJS NN IN DT NNPS ."
