"The head of Iran 's nuclear agency says his country will resume enrichment activities , but not during nuclear talks with the international community .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN NNP POS JJ NN VBZ PRP$ NN MD VB NN NNS , CC RB IN JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN ."
Gholamreza Aghazadeh told reporters in Tehran Saturday that he has no doubt Iran will carry out nuclear fuel production some day .,B-org I-org O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD NNS IN NNP NNP IN PRP VBZ DT NN NNP MD VB RP JJ NN NN DT NN .
He added that the government has approved funds to build a 360-megawatt nuclear power plant .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBD IN DT NN VBZ VBN NNS TO VB DT JJ JJ NN NN .
But he said it will take seven years to complete the facility in the town of Darkhoein in southern Khuzestan province .,O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O,CC PRP VBD PRP MD VB CD NNS TO VB DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP IN JJ NNP NN .
"Meanwhile , in Vienna , the U.S. ambassador to the International Atomic Energy Agency , Gregory Schulte , told the Associated Press the announcement by Tehran underscores that Iran is today 's greatest threat to efforts aimed at stopping the spread of nuclear weapons .",O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O B-org I-org O O O B-tim O O B-geo O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"RB , IN NNP , DT NNP NN TO DT NNP NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP , VBD DT NNP NNP DT NN IN NNP VBZ IN NNP VBZ NN POS JJS NN TO NNS VBN IN VBG DT NN IN JJ NNS ."
