U.S. Undersecretary of State Nicholas Burns begins talks in New Delhi Friday on a civilian nuclear deal offered to India by President Bush during Prime Minister Manmohan Singh 's July visit to Washington .,B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O B-geo I-geo B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O B-per I-per O B-per O O O O B-tim O O B-geo O,NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP VBZ NNS IN NNP NNP NNP IN DT JJ JJ NN VBN TO NNP IN NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP NNP POS NNP NN TO NNP .
"Under the deal , the United States would help India 's civilian nuclear program to boost growth in Asia 's third-largest economy .",O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"IN DT NN , DT NNP NNPS MD VB NNP POS JJ JJ NN TO VB NN IN NNP POS JJ NN ."
"In return , India promised to separate its civilian and military nuclear facilities and place the civilian ones under international safeguards .",O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NN , NNP VBD TO VB PRP$ JJ CC JJ JJ NNS CC NN DT JJ NNS IN JJ NNS ."
"Speaking at the Asia Society in New York before his departure for New Delhi , Mr. Burns said India must draft a plan to separate civil and military nuclear sectors so Washington can keep its side of the agreement .",O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-per B-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"VBG IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP NNP IN PRP$ NN IN NNP NNP , NNP NNP VBD NNP MD VB DT NN TO VB JJ CC JJ JJ NNS IN NNP MD VB PRP$ NN IN DT NN ."
"Several U.S. lawmakers have expressed concern about the deal , saying it goes against the nuclear non-proliferation regime .",O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNP NNS VBP VBN NN IN DT NN , VBG PRP VBZ IN DT JJ JJ NN ."
