Chinese President Hu Jintao has met and shaken hands with AIDS patients at a Beijing hospital .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN CC VBN NNS IN NNP NNS IN DT NNP NN .
State media say Mr. Hu told the patients Tuesday that China must end all discrimination and estrangement towards those suffering from HIV and AIDS .,O O O B-per I-per O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O,NNP NNS VBP NNP NNP VBD DT NNS NNP IN NNP MD VB DT NN CC NN IN DT VBG IN NNP CC NNP .
The hospital visit is believed to be the first time Mr. Hu has met publicly with AIDS patients since becoming president last year .,O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN NN VBZ VBN TO VB DT JJ NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN RB IN NNP NNS IN VBG NN JJ NN .
"China estimates it has 840,000 people living with HIV or AIDS on the mainland , although some experts believe there are many more .",B-geo O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ PRP VBZ CD NNS VBG IN NNP CC NNP IN DT NN , IN DT NNS VBP EX VBP JJ JJR ."
The World Health Organization has warned that China could face as many as 10-million patients by 2010 unless Beijing strengthens efforts to address the epidemic .,O B-org I-org I-org O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN NNP MD VB RB JJ IN JJ NNS IN CD IN NNP VBZ NNS TO VB DT NN .
