"Officials in Pakistan say the government will begin monitoring major websites , including Google and Yahoo , for material it deems offensive to Islam .",O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O B-geo O,"NNS IN NNP VBP DT NN MD VB VBG JJ NNS , VBG NNP CC NNP , IN NN PRP VBZ JJ TO NNP ."
"The Pakistan Telecommunications Authority also said it will block 17 lesser-known sites for containing blasphemous content , in response to a court order .",O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP NNP RB VBD PRP MD VB CD JJ NNS IN VBG JJ NN , IN NN TO DT NN NN ."
"Among the websites that will be monitored are Amazon , MSN , Hotmail and Bing .",O O O O O O O O B-art O B-art O B-art B-org B-art O,"IN DT NNS WDT MD VB VBN VBP NNP , NNP , NNP CC NNP ."
"Friday 's move follows the temporary blocking last month of the social networking site Facebook , after someone using the site sought to collect images of the Prophet Muhammad .",B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-art O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"NNP POS NN VBZ DT JJ VBG JJ NN IN DT JJ NN NN NNP , IN DT VBG DT NN VBD TO VB NNS IN DT NNP NNP ."
The Pakistani government also temporarily banned the video website YouTube for distributing allegedly sacrilegious or profane material .,O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN RB RB VBD DT NN JJ NN IN VBG RB JJ CC JJ NN .
"In recent years , Western newspapers ' publication of caricatures of the prophet have triggered violent protests in majority-Muslim countries including Pakistan .",O B-tim O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O,"IN JJ NNS , JJ NNS POS NN IN NNS IN DT NN VBP VBN JJ NNS IN JJ NNS VBG NNP ."
Islam forbids any depiction of the prophet .,B-geo O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ DT NN IN DT NN .
