Russian police have detained about 20 human rights activists who demonstrated in Moscow Wednesday against what they called an official campaign against non-governmental organizations .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP VBN IN CD JJ NNS NNS WP VBD IN NNP NNP IN WP PRP VBD DT JJ NN IN JJ NNS .
"Those detained were among a group of 60 protesters who had received permission to demonstrate in Lubyanka Square , but later moved to the front of the headquarters of the Federal Security Service , the successor to the KGB The detainees include the leader of the movement For Human Rights , Lev Ponomaryov ; the head of the Memorial Human Rights Center , Oleg Orlov ; and Human Rights Institute Director Valentin Gefter .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo I-geo O B-geo I-geo O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O,"DT VBN VBD IN DT NN IN CD NNS WP VBD VBN NN TO VB IN NNP NNP , CC RB VBD TO DT NN IN DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP , DT NN TO DT NNP DT NNS VBP DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP NNPS , NNP NNP ; DT NN IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP , NNP NNP ; CC NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP NNP ."
"The activists were protesting recently adopted legislation restricting the rights of non-governmental groups in Russia , and television documentaries attempting to portray group members as maintaining close ties with foreign intelligence services .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS VBD VBG RB VBN NN VBG DT NNS IN JJ NNS IN NNP , CC NN NNS VBG TO VB NN NNS IN VBG JJ NNS IN JJ NN NNS ."
