Montenegro 's government and opposition leaders have agreed to hold a referendum on May 21 on the republic 's independence .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O,NNP POS NN CC NN NNS VBP VBN TO VB DT NN IN NNP CD IN DT NN POS NN .
Officials announced the decision Tuesday following talks with European Union envoy Miroslav Lajcak .,O O O O B-tim O O O B-org I-org O B-per I-per O,NNS VBD DT NN NNP VBG NNS IN NNP NNP NN NNP NNP .
Montenegro 's parliament is to meet Wednesday to consider the referendum plan .,B-geo O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O,NNP POS NN VBZ TO VB NNP TO VB DT NN NN .
"Officials say the agreement calls for postponing local elections , originally set for March , to coincide with a parliamentary vote later in the year .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP DT NN VBZ IN VBG JJ NNS , RB VBN IN NNP , TO VB IN DT JJ NN RB IN DT NN ."
The two sides accepted an EU proposal that 55 percent of those casting ballots must back independence for the referendum to be approved .,O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT CD NNS VBD DT NNP NN IN CD NN IN DT VBG NNS MD VB NN IN DT NN TO VB VBN .
The 2003 agreement that transformed the former Yugoslavia into Serbia and Montenegro allows the Montenegrins to move towards independence this year .,O B-tim O O O O O B-gpe O B-gpe O B-gpe O O B-gpe O O O O O O O,DT CD NN WDT VBD DT JJ NNP IN NNP CC NNP VBZ DT NNS TO VB IN NN DT NN .
Montenegro was the only republic to remain with Serbia after the break-up of Yugoslavia in the early 1990s .,B-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim O,NNP VBD DT JJ NN TO VB IN NNP IN DT NN IN NNP IN DT JJ NNS .
