Five bomb attacks in the northern Iraqi city of Kirkuk have killed at least 17 people .,O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O,CD NN NNS IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP VBP VBN IN JJS CD NNS .
"Authorities say many of Tuesday 's nearly simultaneous explosions were aimed at police , and several policemen are among the dead .",O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP NN IN NNP POS RB JJ NNS VBD VBN IN NN , CC JJ NNS VBP IN DT NN ."
"The bombings came a day after the terror group al-Qaida in Iraq named Abu Hamza al-Muhajer as its new leader , following the death of Abu Musab al-Zarqawi in a U.S. airstrike .",O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-geo O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org B-per O O B-geo O O,"DT NNS VBD DT NN IN DT NN NN NNP IN NNP VBD NNP NNP NNP IN PRP$ JJ NN , VBG DT NN IN NNP NNP NNP IN DT NNP NN ."
"In an Internet posting Tuesday , the new insurgent leader vowed to continue attacks on U.S. forces in Iraq and their Iraqi allies .",O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O,"IN DT NN VBG NNP , DT JJ JJ NN VBD TO VB NNS IN NNP NNS IN NNP CC PRP$ JJ NNS ."
"The Iraqi government has announced plans for a security crackdown Wednesday in Baghdad that will involve at least 40,000 Iraqi and U.S. troops .",O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O B-gpe O B-geo O O,DT JJ NN VBZ VBN NNS IN DT NN NN NNP IN NNP WDT MD VB IN JJS CD JJ CC NNP NNS .
The plan will include a curfew .,O O O O O O O,DT NN MD VB DT NN .
"Also Tuesday , the chief judge in the trial of former President Saddam Hussein said he had heard the last defense witnesses .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O,"RB NNP , DT NN NN IN DT NN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD PRP VBD VBN DT JJ NN NNS ."
