"The lights came up , the music started , and Heather Mills danced divinely .",O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O,"DT NNS VBD RP , DT NN VBD , CC NNP NNP VBD RB ."
"The animal rights crusader - who wears a prosthetic lower left leg - emerged unscathed in the first round of ABC televsion 's popular show , Dancing With The Stars .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN NNS NN : WP VBZ DT JJ JJR NN NN : VBD JJ IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NN POS JJ NN , VBG IN DT NNS ."
The 39-year-old activist created worldwide interest after becoming the first amputee to compete in the televised U.S. dance contest .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,DT JJ NN VBD JJ NN IN VBG DT JJ NN TO VB IN DT JJ NNP NN NN .
"The victim of a 1993 motorcycle accident , Heather says she has placed a brace over the limb to prevent it detaching .",O O O O B-tim O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN IN DT CD NN NN , NNP VBZ PRP VBZ VBN DT NN IN DT NN TO VB PRP VBG ."
She says she hopes her efforts will cheer and encourage other young amputees .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ PRP VBZ PRP$ NNS MD VB CC VB JJ JJ NNS .
"The three judges praised her footwork , but told her to work on her upper body movement .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT CD NNS VBD PRP$ NN , CC VBD PRP TO VB IN PRP$ JJ NN NN ."
"Little-known in the United States , Heather Mills is a major public figure in Britain , largely due to her bitter divorce from former Beatle Paul McCartney .",O O O B-geo I-geo O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo I-geo O,"JJ IN DT NNP NNPS , NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP , RB JJ TO PRP$ JJ NN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP ."
The two separated last May .,O O O O B-tim O,DT CD VBD JJ NNP .
