Chinese officials say the cabinet will ask top lawmakers to settle a dispute over how many years Hong Kong 's next leader will serve .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP DT NN MD VB JJ NNS TO VB DT NN IN WRB JJ NNS NNP NNP POS JJ NN MD VB .
"China 's official Xinhua news agency says the State Council , China 's cabinet , decided Sunday to request that the Standing Committee of the National People 's Congress interpret Hong Kong 's constitution and resolve the disagreement .",B-geo O O B-org O O O O B-org I-org O B-geo O O O O B-tim O O O O B-org I-org O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O,"NNP POS JJ NNP NN NN VBZ DT NNP NNP , NNP POS NN , VBD NNP TO VB IN DT NNP NNP IN DT NNP NNP POS NNP VB NNP NNP POS NN CC VB DT NN ."
The dispute began last month when Hong Kong Chief Executive announced he was retiring because of ill health .,O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBD JJ NN WRB NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD PRP VBD VBG IN IN JJ NN .
"Hong Kong pro-democracy lawmakers and legal experts have argued that the Basic Law , the territory 's mini constitution , says that Mr. Tung 's successor should serve a full , five-year term .",B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-per B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP JJ NNS CC JJ NNS VBP VBN IN DT NNP NNP , DT NN POS NN NN , VBZ IN NNP NNP POS NN MD VB DT JJ , JJ NN ."
But the government and mainland legal experts insist that the next leader should finish the remaining two years in Mr. Tung 's term .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O B-per B-geo O O O,CC DT NN CC JJ JJ NNS VBP IN DT JJ NN MD VB DT VBG CD NNS IN NNP NNP POS NN .
