The chairman of the committee drafting Iraq 's constitution says a compromise has been reached and that a new draft document will be sent to the parliament on Sunday .,O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,DT NN IN DT NN VBG NNP POS NN VBZ DT NN VBZ VBN VBN CC IN DT JJ NN NN MD VB VBN TO DT NN IN NNP .
"Shi'ite Sheik Humam Hammoudi made the announcement early Saturday ( local time ) , shortly after the latest negotiation deadline expired .",B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT NN JJ NNP LRB JJ NN RRB , RB IN DT JJS NN NN VBD ."
"But Sunni Arab negotiators said no agreement has been reached , and one prominent Sunni Arab , Saleh al-Mutlaq , told Arab television that he urged all Iraqis to reject the document when it is put to a national referendum October 15 .",O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-per I-per O B-per I-per O O B-gpe O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"CC NNP NNP NNS VBD DT NN VBZ VBN VBN , CC CD JJ NNP NNP , NNP NNP , VBD JJ NN IN PRP VBD DT NNS TO VB DT NN WRB PRP VBZ VBN TO DT JJ NN NNP CD ."
Talks had been extended for an extra day so that Sunni Arab concerns regarding federalism and the exclusion of former Ba'athists from the government could be further discussed .,O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBD VBN VBN IN DT JJ NN RB IN NNP NNP NNS VBG NN CC DT NN IN JJ NNS IN DT NN MD VB RB VBN .
No casualty figures were released .,O O O O O O,DT NN NNS VBD VBN .
