"Several hundred people , mostly youths of African descent , have marched to the French parliament in Paris to protest laws they say discriminate against immigrants and minorities .",O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ CD NNS , RB NNS IN JJ NN , VBP VBN TO DT JJ NN IN NNP TO VB NNS PRP VBP NN IN NNS CC NNS ."
Wednesday 's march comes two days before the first anniversary of fiery suburban riots that shook France last year .,B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,NNP POS NN VBZ CD NNS IN DT JJ NN IN JJ JJ NNS WDT VBD NNP JJ NN .
"The youths , representing poor and minority neighborhoods , carried banners and lists of their complaints .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS , VBG JJ CC NN NNS , VBD NNS CC NNS IN PRP$ NNS ."
"Police and security forces lined their route , barring close approach to public buildings .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS CC NN NNS VBD PRP$ NN , VBG JJ NN TO JJ NNS ."
"A grass-roots movement , AC - Le Feu , founded in Clichy-sous-Bois , a northern suburb of Paris , says it has collected some 20,000 complaints and will publish them in a Book of Grievances ahead of next year 's elections .",O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O B-org O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN , NNP IN NNP NNP , VBN IN NNP , DT JJ NN IN NNP , VBZ PRP VBZ VBN DT CD NNS CC MD VB PRP IN DT NN IN NNP RB IN JJ NN POS NNS ."
The group says there have been no improvements in poor neighborhoods since the riots .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ EX VBP VBN DT NNS IN JJ NNS IN DT NNS .
