Colombia 's biggest leftist rebel group has rejected the latest call from the government for talks about exchanging hostages for jailed rebels .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS JJS JJ NN NN VBZ VBN DT JJS NN IN DT NN IN NNS IN VBG NNS IN JJ NNS .
"In a statement issued Thursday , the Revolutionary Armed Forces of Colombia , or FARC , said it would not agree to talks until government forces withdraw from the area where the two sides are set to meet for a period of 30 days .",O O O O B-tim O O B-org I-org I-org I-org B-geo O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O,"IN DT NN VBN NNP , DT NNP NNP NNS IN NNP , CC NNP , VBD PRP MD RB VB TO NNS IN NN NNS VB IN DT NN WRB DT CD NNS VBP VBN TO VB IN DT NN IN CD NNS ."
President Alvaro Uribe has refused earlier demands to create a demilitarized zone .,B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN JJR NNS TO VB DT JJ NN .
His government has promised to ensure safe passage for any FARC negotiators to attend the proposed talks in southwestern Pradera county .,O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,PRP$ NN VBZ VBN TO VB JJ NN IN DT NNP NNS TO VB DT VBN NNS IN JJ NNP NN .
"Colombia 's government is offering to exchange some 500 jailed rebels for dozens of hostages , including politicians , military personnel and three U.S. defense contractors .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O,"NNP POS NN VBZ VBG TO VB DT CD JJ NNS IN NNS IN NNS , VBG NNS , JJ NNS CC CD NNP NN NNS ."
FARC rebels have been battling government forces and right-wing paramilitaries in a 40-year-old conflict .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNS VBP VBN VBG NN NNS CC JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN .
Some of information in the story provided by AP .,O O O O O O O O B-org O,DT IN NN IN DT NN VBN IN NNP .
