Thousands of Palestinians celebrated Israel 's impending withdrawal from the Gaza Strip at a rally Friday along a tiny stretch of waterfront in Gaza .,O B-org B-gpe O B-geo O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNS IN NNS VBD NNP POS JJ NN IN DT NNP NNP IN DT NN NNP IN DT JJ NN IN NN IN NNP .
"Palestinian Prime Minister Mahmoud Abbas addressed the joyous crowd , telling them "" today Gaza , tomorrow Jerusalem . """,B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O B-tim I-tim O O,"JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN , VBG PRP LQU NN NNP , NN NNP . LQU"
He was referring to Palestinian dreams of having Jerusalem as the capital of an independent Palestinian state .,O O O O B-gpe O O O B-tim O O O O O O B-gpe O O,PRP VBD VBG TO JJ NNS IN VBG NNP IN DT NN IN DT JJ JJ NN .
"Meanwhile , Israeli Prime Minister Ariel Sharon told an Israeli newspaper , Yediot Ahronot that his government could eventually remove more settlements in the West Bank than originally planned .",O O B-gpe B-per O B-per I-per O O B-gpe O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O O O O,"RB , JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN , NNP NNP IN PRP$ NN MD RB VB JJR NNS IN DT NNP NNP IN RB VBN ."
Israel is to begin a full withdrawal Wednesday from its 21 settlements in Gaza .,B-geo O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-tim O,NNP VBZ TO VB DT JJ NN NNP IN PRP$ CD NNS IN NNP .
