"Afghanistan 's Defense Ministry says its troops have killed four Taliban near Musa Qala , in the first fighting since the militants were ousted from the southern town .",B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-org O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NNP NNP VBZ PRP$ NNS VBP VBN CD NNP IN NNP NNP , IN DT JJ NN IN DT NNS VBD VBN IN DT JJ NN ."
In a statement Sunday the ministry said Afghan national forces engaged with the enemy as they moved to expand the area under government control .,O O O B-tim O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,IN DT NN NNP DT NN VBD JJ JJ NNS VBN IN DT NN IN PRP VBD TO VB DT NN IN NN NN .
"Afghan and NATO forces regained control of the area last week , in a battle that left hundreds of Taliban insurgents killed , wounded or detained .",B-gpe O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O,"JJ CC NNP NNS VBD NN IN DT NN JJ NN , IN DT NN WDT VBD NNS IN NNP NNS VBN , VBN CC VBN ."
Hundreds of troops continued to patrol the streets on Saturday .,O O O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNS IN NNS VBD TO VB DT NNS IN NNP .
British military officials also said Saturday two rockets were fired into Musa Qala from the outskirts where some Taliban had escaped .,B-gpe O O O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-org O O O,JJ NN NNS RB VBD NNP CD NNS VBD VBN IN NNP NNP IN DT NNS WRB DT NNP VBD VBN .
No injuries were reported .,O O O O O,DT NNS VBD VBN .
"The Taliban had seized Musa Qala , in Helmand province about eight months ago .",O B-org O O B-geo I-geo O O B-geo O O B-tim O O O,"DT NNP VBD VBN NNP NNP , IN NNP NN IN CD NNS RB ."
