"An Australian archaeology team has located an ancient Egyptian city used by foreign occupiers some 3,500 years ago .",O B-gpe O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim O O O,DT JJ NN NN VBZ VBN DT JJ JJ NN VBN IN JJ NNS DT CD NNS RB .
"Egypt 's antiquities department says pictures taken by radar show an underground city complete with streets , houses and temples .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP POS NNS NN VBZ NNS VBN IN NN VBP DT JJ NN JJ IN NNS , NNS CC NNS ."
It is located in an area in Egypt 's Nile Delta .,O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O,PRP VBZ VBN IN DT NN IN NNP POS NNP NNP .
"Antiquities Chief Zahi Hawass says the ancient city could be part of Avaris , the capital used by the Hyksos , an Asiatic group that ruled Egypt from 1664 through 1569 BC .",O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-org O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ NN MD VB NN IN NNP , DT NN VBN IN DT NNP , DT JJ NN WDT VBD NNP IN CD IN CD NNP ."
