Nigeria 's Securities and Exchange Commission has fired the head of the country 's stock exchange after allegations of financial mismanagement and poor oversight .,B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP POS NNP CC NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN IN DT NN POS NN NN IN NNS IN JJ NN CC JJ NN .
A spokesman for the regulator said Director-General Ndi Okereke-Onyiuke was removed late Wednesday along with the exchange president and members of its council .,O O O O O O O B-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN IN DT NN VBD JJ NNP NNP VBD VBN JJ NNP IN IN DT NN NN CC NNS IN PRP$ NN .
"The SEC says the move was aimed at restoring confidence because of worries of inadequate oversight of the exchange , governance challenges and ongoing litigation .",O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP VBZ DT NN VBD VBN IN VBG NN IN IN NNS IN JJ NN IN DT NN , NN NNS CC JJ NN ."
Okereke-Onyiuke was scheduled to retire in November .,B-per O O O O O B-tim O,NNP VBD VBN TO VB IN NNP .
"Emmanuel Ikazoboh , a former executive at financial consulting firm Deloitte in West and Central Africa , has been named the interim administrator of the stock exchange .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP , DT JJ NN IN JJ NN NN NNP IN NNP CC NNP NNP , VBZ VBN VBN DT JJ NN IN DT NN NN ."
