Palestine Liberation Organization leader Mahmoud Abbas has received a hero 's welcome on a campaign trip to the Gaza Strip .,B-org I-org I-org O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,NNP NNP NNP NN NNP NNP VBZ VBN DT NN POS JJ IN DT NN NN TO DT NNP NNP .
Armed militants hoisted Mr. Abbas on their shoulders as thousands of Palestinians greeted him Saturday at a refugee camp in Rafah on the Egyptian border .,O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O,JJ NNS VBD NNP NNP IN PRP$ NNS IN NNS IN NNS VBD PRP NNP IN DT NN NN IN NNP IN DT JJ NN .
Mr. Abbas is the front-running candidate in this month 's election to choose a leader for the Palestinian Authority .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN DT NN POS NN TO VB DT NN IN DT JJ NNP .
"He has denounced violence , but also has won crucial support from militants by promising to insist on a total Israeli withdrawal from occupied Palestinian land .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O,"PRP VBZ VBN NN , CC RB VBZ VBN JJ NN IN NNS IN VBG TO VB IN DT JJ JJ NN IN JJ JJ NN ."
"Meanwhile , a 10-year-old Palestinian girl was killed Saturday when an explosion ripped through her home in the northern Gaza Strip .",O O O O B-gpe O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"RB , DT JJ JJ NN VBD VBN NNP WRB DT NN VBN IN PRP$ NN IN DT JJ NNP NNP ."
Neighbors said the explosion appeared to have been caused by a Palestinian rocket that militants had aimed at Israel .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-geo O,NNS VBD DT NN VBD TO VB VBN VBN IN DT JJ NN IN NNS VBD VBN IN NNP .
