"Iranian President Mahmoud Ahmadinejad says the Holocaust is a "" myth "" and has repeated his widely-condemned suggestion that the Jewish state of Israel be moved to Europe or North America .",B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O B-eve O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ DT NNP VBZ DT LQU NN RQU CC VBZ VBN PRP$ JJ NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP VB VBN TO NNP CC NNP NNP .
"Addressing a gathering in the Iranian city of Zahedan Wednesday , Mr. Ahmadinejad said the West has "" fabricated a legend "" which it holds "" above God "" of the systematic killing of millions of Jews by Nazi Germany during World War II .",O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo B-tim O B-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O B-org I-org O B-eve I-eve I-eve O,"VBG DT NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP NNP , NNP NNP VBD DT NNP VBZ LQU VBN DT NN RQU WDT PRP VBZ LQU IN NNP RQU IN DT JJ NN IN NNS IN NNPS IN NNP NNP IN NNP NNP NNP ."
His speech was broadcast on Iran 's state television .,O O O O O B-geo O O O O,PRP$ NN VBD VBN IN NNP POS NN NN .
"Similar remarks earlier by the Iranian president caused an uproar and drew rebukes from Israel , the United States , and the United Nations .",O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-org I-org O,"JJ NNS RBR IN DT JJ NN VBD DT NN CC VBD NNS IN NNP , DT NNP NNPS , CC DT NNP NNPS ."
The White House Wednesday said Mr. Ahmadinejad 's comments underscore why it is so important the international community continue to work together to keep Iran from developing nuclear weapons .,O B-org I-org B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,DT NNP NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP POS NNS VBP WRB PRP VBZ RB JJ DT JJ NN VBP TO VB RB TO VB NNP IN VBG JJ NNS .
