A U.S. official says Vice President Dick Cheney and Saudi King Abdullah have discussed how to deal with the rise in oil prices .,O B-geo O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBZ NNP NNP NNP NNP CC NNP NNP NNP VBP VBN WRB TO VB IN DT NN IN NN NNS .
The two men held talks Friday after Cheney arrived in Saudi Arabia from a visit to Afghanistan .,O O O O O B-tim O B-per O O B-per I-per O O O O B-geo O,DT CD NNS VBD NNS NNP IN NNP VBD IN NNP NNP IN DT NN TO NNP .
"The official says Cheney and the king discussed how to stabilize the markets now , and what is needed for the future .",O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ NNP CC DT NN VBD WRB TO VB DT NNS RB , CC WP VBZ VBN IN DT NN ."
President Bush urged Saudi Arabia and other members of OPEC during a trip in January to boost production .,B-per I-per O B-per I-per O O O O B-org O O O O B-tim O O O O,NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP CC JJ NNS IN NNP IN DT NN IN NNP TO VB NN .
Oil has risen in recent weeks to more than $ 100 a barrel .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NN VBZ VBN IN JJ NNS TO JJR IN $ CD DT NN .
"The official says Cheney and King Abdullah discussed various issues during their meeting , including the Israeli-Palestinian stalemate , other Middle East concerns , Pakistan , and bilateral issues .",O O O B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O B-per O O O O O,"DT NN VBZ NNP CC NNP NNP VBD JJ NNS IN PRP$ NN , VBG DT JJ NN , JJ NNP NNP NNS , NNP , CC JJ NNS ."
