Iraqi authorities say unidentified gunmen killed three Iraqi soldiers and two policemen during an attack at a security checkpoint in western Baghdad .,B-gpe O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,JJ NNS VBP JJ NNS VBD CD JJ NNS CC CD NNS IN DT NN IN DT NN NN IN JJ NNP .
Officials say the attack took place late Sunday night .,O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O,NNS VBP DT NN VBD NN JJ NNP NN .
"In other violence , police say a car bomb in the northern city of Mosul has wounded at least eight people .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O,"IN JJ NN , NNS VBP DT NN NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP VBZ VBN IN JJS CD NNS ."
"U.S. troops pulled out of Iraqi cities last week and deployed to their bases , leaving Iraqi police and soldiers in control of security in residential areas .",B-geo O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNS VBD IN IN JJ NNS JJ NN CC VBN TO PRP$ NNS , VBG JJ NNS CC NNS IN NN IN NN IN JJ NNS ."
"U.S. President Barack Obama has pledged to withdraw all combat troops from Iraq by September 2010 , leaving only advisors and trainers .",B-geo B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN TO VB DT NN NNS IN NNP IN NNP CD , VBG RB NNS CC NNS ."
"At present , about 130,000 U.S. troops remain in Iraq to conduct combat duties outside urban areas .",O O O O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,"IN JJ , IN CD NNP NNS VBP IN NNP TO VB NN NNS IN JJ NNS ."
