"NATO says militants surrounded the outpost , firing from all directions with rocket-propelled grenades , small arms and mortars .",B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ NNS VBN DT NN , VBG IN DT NNS IN JJ NNS , JJ NNS CC NNS ."
Coalition officials said the embattled troops on the ground called in air support to help repel the attack .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NN NNS VBD DT JJ NNS IN DT NN VBN IN NN NN TO VB VB DT NN .
"At least five coalition service members were wounded during the firefight , but NATO says none were killed .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O O,"IN JJS CD NN NN NNS VBD VBN IN DT NN , CC NNP VBZ NN VBD VBN ."
