"The International Red Cross has called on the United States to grant access to all al-Qaida suspects it is holding , including those reported to be in secret prisons in undisclosed locations .",O B-org I-org I-org O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN DT NNP NNPS TO VB NN TO DT NNP NNS PRP VBZ VBG , VBG DT VBN TO VB IN JJ NNS IN JJ NNS ."
A spokeswoman says the agency is concerned about the fate of those held .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NN VBZ DT NN VBZ VBN IN DT NN IN DT VBN .
"Wednesday , the Washington Post newspaper and NBC television reported that the CIA has been holding and interrogating top al-Qaida suspects at secret locations outside the United States .",B-tim O O B-org I-org O O B-org O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-org O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNP , DT NNP NNP NN CC NNP NN VBD IN DT NNP VBZ VBN VBG CC VBG JJ NNP NNS IN JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNPS ."
"The reports say more than 100 prisoners have been questioned at facilities in at least two eastern European countries , Thailand and other locations .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"DT NNS VBP JJR IN CD NNS VBP VBN VBN IN NNS IN IN JJS CD JJ JJ NNS , NNP CC JJ NNS ."
"Thailand has denied having secret detention centers , as have officials in many eastern European states .",B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBN VBG JJ NN NNS , RB VBP NNS IN JJ JJ JJ NNS ."
"Earlier Thursday , a European Union spokesman said the European Commission will investigate the reports of the possible use of secret detention facilities in eastern Europe .",O B-tim O O B-org I-org O O O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"RBR NNP , DT NNP NNP NN VBD DT JJ NNP MD VB DT NNS IN DT JJ NN IN JJ NN NNS IN JJ NNP ."
