"A mild earthquake has shaken northern Pakistan , without any reports of serious damage or casualties .",O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN VBZ VBN JJ NNP , IN DT NNS IN JJ NN CC NNS ."
"Police say the tremor rocked office buildings in the capital , Islamabad , and people ran out of their homes in Muzaffarabad and Balakot - the two towns that were badly damaged in the October 8th quake that killed more than 73,000 people .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP DT NN VBD NN NNS IN DT NN , NNP , CC NNS VBD IN IN PRP$ NNS IN NNP CC NNP IN DT CD NNS WDT VBD RB VBN IN DT NNP CD NN WDT VBD JJR IN CD NNS ."
"Pakistani Meteorological Department officials said the intensity was 5.2 , and the epicenter of the tremor was in the Hazara area of North West Frontier Province , about 100 kilometers northwest of Islamabad .",B-gpe B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org I-org I-org O O O O O O B-geo O,"JJ NNP NNP NNS VBD DT NN VBD CD , CC DT NN IN DT NN VBD IN DT NNP NN IN NNP NNP NNP NNP , IN CD NNS JJS IN NNP ."
The last such aftershock occurred on December 21 and officials are expecting more aftershocks for at least another two months .,O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O,DT JJ JJ NN VBD IN NNP CD CC NNS VBP VBG JJR NNS IN IN JJS DT CD NNS .
