"A United nations-backed report says many Afghan refugees who return home have limited access to jobs , health care , education , water and housing .",O B-org O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP JJ NN VBZ JJ JJ NNS WP VBP NN VBP VBN NN TO NNS , NN NN , NN , NN CC NN ."
"The Afghan Independent Human Rights Commission and the U.N. refugee agency recently surveyed 11,000 Afghans , including refugees and internally displaced persons .",B-org B-gpe B-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NNP NNP NNP NNP CC DT NNP NN NN RB VBD CD NNS , VBG NNS CC RB JJ NNS ."
"More than half of those interviewed said they do not have access to safe drinking water , and one-third said their children are not enrolled in school .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJR IN NN IN DT VBN VBD PRP VBP RB VB NN TO JJ NN NN , CC NN VBD PRP$ NNS VBP RB VBN IN NN ."
"Many parents said there were schools nearby , but they did not send their children because of security concerns or because the children work .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBD EX VBD NNS RB , CC PRP VBD RB VB PRP$ NNS IN IN NN NNS CC IN DT NNS VBP ."
"About 85 percent of those surveyed say their top priorities include finding employment or gaining access to clean water , schools or medical clinics .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN CD NN IN DT VBN VBP PRP$ JJ NNS VBP VBG NN CC VBG NN TO JJ NN , NNS CC JJ NNS ."
Only three to four percent cited security or justice as a top concern .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,RB CD CC CD NN VBD NN CC NN IN DT JJ NN .
