Afghan officials say security forces have found the dead body of a Turkish engineer who was abducted by suspected militants Tuesday .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-tim O,JJ NNS VBP NN NNS VBP VBN DT JJ NN IN DT JJ NN WP VBD VBN IN JJ NNS NNP .
"Interior Ministry official Jamil Jumbesh said the body was found in eastern Afghanistan Wednesday , and appeared to have been shot several times .",B-org I-org O B-org I-org O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP NNP NN NNP NNP VBD DT NN VBD VBN IN JJ NNP NNP , CC VBD TO VB VBN VBN JJ NNS ."
Also abducted were his driver and a translator .,O O O O O O O O O,RB VBN VBD PRP$ NN CC DT NN .
Both Afghan nationals were freed hours later .,O B-gpe O O O O O O,DT JJ NNS VBD VBN NNS RB .
