"Hurricane Tomas is gaining strength as it moves deeper into the Caribbean Sunday , after tearing off roofs , downing powerlines and dropping up to 15 centimeters of rain across Barbados , St. Vincent and St. Lucia .",O B-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo I-geo O B-geo I-geo O,"NNP NNP VBZ VBG NN IN PRP VBZ JJR IN DT NNP NNP , IN VBG RP NNS , VBG NNS CC VBG RP TO CD NNS IN NN IN NNP , NNP NNP CC NNP NNP ."
"No deaths have been reported on those islands , but hundreds of people took refuge in shelters as 150 kilometer per hour winds tore at buildings and rain-soaked hillsides slid across roads .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNS VBP VBN VBN IN DT NNS , CC NNS IN NNS VBD NN IN NNS IN CD NN IN NN NNS VBD IN NNS CC JJ NNS VBD IN NNS ."
"Forecasters at the U.S. National Hurricane Center say Tomas has the potential to strengthen into a major storm as it moves westward toward Jamaica , Haiti and the Dominican Republic .",O O O B-org I-org O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-geo O O B-geo I-geo O,"NNS IN DT NNP NNP NNP NNP VBP NNP VBZ DT JJ TO VB IN DT JJ NN IN PRP VBZ RB IN NNP , NNP CC DT NNP NNP ."
Winds are now at 160 kilometers per hour .,O O O O O O O O O,NNS VBP RB IN CD NNS IN NN .
"Tomas could bring heavy rains across the southern parts of the Dominican Republic and Haiti , which is struggling to recover from a devastating earthquake and cope with a recent cholera outbreak .",B-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP MD VB JJ NNS IN DT JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNP CC NNP , WDT VBZ VBG TO VB IN DT JJ NN CC VB IN DT JJ NN NN ."
