"China plans its second manned space launch later this week , with reports suggesting a Wednesday or Thursday blast-off from Inner Mongolia .",B-geo O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O B-tim O B-tim O O B-org I-org O,"NNP VBZ PRP$ JJ JJ NN NN RB DT NN , IN NNS VBG DT NNP CC NNP NN IN NNP NNP ."
"Chinese space agency officials have not confirmed a date , but short-listed astronauts for the two-man mission have already arrived at the Gobi desert launch site .",B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O,"JJ NN NN NNS VBP RB VBN DT NN , CC JJ NNS IN DT JJ NN VBP RB VBN IN DT NNP NN NN NN ."
"China launched its first manned space flight two years ago , in October 2003 .",B-geo O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-tim I-tim O,"NNP VBD PRP$ JJ JJ NN NN CD NNS RB , IN NNP CD ."
The secretive space program is closely affiliated with the military and is considered a source of national prestige .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN NN VBZ RB VBN IN DT JJ CC VBZ VBN DT NN IN JJ NN .
