Afghan President Hamid Karzai has expressed support for the Pakistani government 's decision to raid a radical mosque in Islamabad on Tuesday .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN NN IN DT JJ NN POS NN TO VB DT JJ NN IN NNP IN NNP .
Mr. Karzai told reporters Wednesday that his nation fully supports Pakistan 's campaign against extremists .,B-per I-per O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD NNS NNP IN PRP$ NN RB VBZ NNP POS NN IN NNS .
He also called on Pakistan to take an equally decisive stand against militants who are crossing the border into neighboring Afghanistan and killing Afghan civilians .,O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-gpe O O,PRP RB VBD IN NNP TO VB DT RB JJ NN IN NNS WP VBP VBG DT NN IN VBG NNP CC VBG JJ NNS .
Pakistani officials say their government is bracing for a possible militant backlash after Tuesday 's raid at the Red Mosque compound .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O B-org I-org O O,JJ NNS VBP PRP$ NN VBZ VBG IN DT JJ JJ NN IN NNP POS NN IN DT NNP NNP NN .
"Officials warn there could be an uprising along the border with Afghanistan , where the mosque 's pro-Taleban leaders had many supporters .",O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP EX MD VB DT NN IN DT NN IN NNP , WRB DT NN POS JJ NNS VBD JJ NNS ."
