"Canada 's next prime minister , Stephen Harper , is a trained economist who united two right-of-center political factions under a Conservative Party banner three years ago .",B-geo O O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O B-tim O O O,"NNP POS JJ JJ NN , NNP NNP , VBZ DT JJ NN WP VBD CD JJ JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNP NN CD NNS RB ."
"Born in Toronto in 1959 , Mr. Harper began working as a computer analyst for an oil company in western Alberta province when he was 18 .",O O B-geo O B-tim O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O,"VBN IN NNP IN CD , NNP NNP VBD VBG IN DT NN NN IN DT NN NN IN JJ NNP NN WRB PRP VBD CD ."
"He was first elected to Parliament in 1993 , but left four years later to head a conservative lobbying group .",O O O O O B-org O B-tim O O O B-tim O B-tim O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD JJ VBN TO NNP IN CD , CC VBD CD NNS RB TO VB DT JJ NN NN ."
"He was re-elected in 2002 , but lost the 2004 elections after Prime Minister Paul Martin painted him as a hard-line , right-wing opponent of same-sex marriage and abortion rights .",O O O O B-tim O O O O B-tim O O B-per O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD VBN IN CD , CC VBD DT CD NNS IN NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD PRP IN DT JJ , JJ NN IN JJ NN CC NN NNS ."
Mr. Harper is a married father of two .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBZ DT JJ NN IN CD .
"He describes himself as a cautious politician who believes "" it is better to light one candle than to promise a million lightbulbs . """,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP VBZ PRP IN DT JJ NN WP VBZ LQU PRP VBZ JJR TO VB CD NN IN TO VB DT CD NNS . LQU
"An avid ice hockey fan , he has been writing a book on the history of the sport .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT JJ NN NN NN , PRP VBZ VBN VBG DT NN IN DT NN IN DT NN ."
