Rescuers in Pakistan have pulled a five-year old girl to safety after she was trapped in the quake rubble for 100 hours .,O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,NNS IN NNP VBP VBN DT JJ JJ NN TO NN IN PRP VBD VBN IN DT NN NN IN CD NNS .
Zarabe Shah was trapped under the stairwell in the rubble of her quake-hit home in Muzaffarabad .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP NNP VBD VBN IN DT NN IN DT NN IN PRP$ JJ NN IN NNP .
"On Wednesday , Russian rescuers pulled the dazed girl from the debris .",O B-tim O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , JJ NNS VBD DT JJ NN IN DT NN ."
"She asked for a glass of water , but said she was n't hungry .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD IN DT NN IN NN , CC VBD PRP VBD RB JJ ."
"A day earlier , neighbors had recovered the bodies of her father and two of her sisters from the debris .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NN RB , NNS VBD VBN DT NNS IN PRP$ NN CC CD IN PRP$ NNS IN DT NN ."
Her mother and another two sisters survived .,O O O O O O O O,PRP$ NN CC DT CD NNS VBD .
"The mother had given Zarabe up for dead and had left for the city of Abbotabad , a town north of Islamabad that suffered far less damage than Muzaffarabad .",O O O O B-per O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O,"DT NN VBD VBN NNP IN IN JJ CC VBD VBN IN DT NN IN NNP , DT NN NN IN NNP WDT VBD RB JJR NN IN NNP ."
Her uncle held her tight as she told reporters how the stairwell shielded her from the debris above .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,PRP$ NN VBD PRP JJ IN PRP VBD NNS WRB DT NN VBD PRP IN DT NN IN .
