A prominent Cuban dissident has denied reports that she sought refuge at the Argentine embassy in Havana after spending the night there earlier this week .,O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O B-geo O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O,DT JJ JJ NN VBZ VBN NNS IN PRP VBD NN IN DT JJ NN IN NNP IN VBG DT NN RB RBR DT NN .
Renown brain surgueon Hilda Molina told reporters late Thursday that she had gone to the embassy with her mother Wednesday in an effort to have a telephone conversation with her son who lives in Buenos Aires .,O O O B-per I-per O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O,JJ NN NN NNP NNP VBD NNS RB NNP IN PRP VBD VBN TO DT NN IN PRP$ NN NNP IN DT NN TO VB DT NN NN IN PRP$ NN WP VBZ IN NNP NNP .
"She said while there , her mother became ill and embassy staff offered to let the two women spend the night .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"PRP VBD IN RB , PRP$ NN VBD JJ CC JJ NN VBN TO VB DT CD NNS VBP DT NN ."
An Argentine newspaper had reported that Ms. Molina was seeking asylum in the embassy .,O B-gpe O O O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O,DT JJ NN VBD VBN IN NNP NNP VBD VBG NN IN DT NN .
"For ten years , Cuba has denied Ms. Molina a visa to visit her son and grandchildren in Argentina .",O O O O B-geo O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"IN CD NNS , NNP VBZ VBN NNP NNP DT NN TO VB PRP$ NN CC NNS IN NNP ."
Argentine President Nestor Kirchner wrote to Cuban President on her behalf earlier this month .,B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O B-gpe B-per O O O O O O O,JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD TO JJ NNP IN PRP$ NN RBR DT NN .
