Britain oversaw foreign relations and defense for the ruling Kuwaiti AL-SABAH dynasty from 1899 until independence in 1961 .,B-geo O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-tim O,NNP VBD JJ NNS CC NN IN DT NN JJ NNP NN IN CD IN NN IN CD .
Kuwait was attacked and overrun by Iraq on 2 August 1990 .,B-gpe O O O O O B-geo O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,NNP VBD VBN CC VBN IN NNP IN CD NNP CD .
"Following several weeks of aerial bombardment , a US-led , UN coalition began a ground assault on 23 February 1991 that liberated Kuwait in four days .",O B-tim O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O B-gpe O B-tim O O,"VBG JJ NNS IN JJ NN , DT JJ , JJ NN VBD DT NN NN IN CD NNP CD WDT VBD NNP IN CD NNS ."
Kuwait spent more than $ 5 billion to repair oil infrastructure damaged during 1990 - 91 .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O,NNP VBD JJR IN $ CD CD TO VB NN NN VBN IN CD IN CD .
The AL-SABAH family has ruled since returning to power in 1991 and reestablished an elected legislature that in recent years has become increasingly assertive .,O B-org O O O O O O O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,DT NNP NN VBZ VBN IN VBG TO NN IN CD CC VBD DT JJ NN IN IN JJ NNS VBZ VBN RB JJ .
The country witnessed the historic election in May 2009 of four women to its National Assembly .,O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O B-org I-org O,DT NN VBD DT JJ NN IN NNP CD IN CD NNS TO PRP$ NNP NNP .
"Amid the 2010 - 11 uprisings and protests across the Arab world , stateless Arabs , known as bidoon , staged small protests in February and March 2011 demanding citizenship , jobs , and other benefits available to Kuwaiti nationals .",O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O B-gpe O O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O,"IN DT CD IN CD NNS CC NNS IN DT JJ NN , JJ NNS , VBN IN NN , VBD JJ NNS IN NNP CC NNP CD VBG NN , NNS , CC JJ NNS JJ TO JJ NNS ."
Youth activist groups - supported by opposition legislators and the prime minister 's rivals within the ruling family - in March of 2011 rallied for an end to corruption and the prime minister 's ouster .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim I-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NN NNS : VBN IN NN NNS CC DT JJ NN POS NNS IN DT NN NN : IN NNP IN CD VBD IN DT NN TO NN CC DT JJ NN POS NN .
