The Palestinian Islamic militant group Hamas has banned public prayers in the Gaza Strip after the rival Fatah movement used the services to protest Hamas ' rule in Gaza .,O B-gpe O O O B-org O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-org O O O B-geo O,DT JJ NNP JJ NN NNP VBZ VBN JJ NNS IN DT NNP NNP IN DT JJ NNP NN VBD DT NNS TO VB NNP POS NN IN NNP .
"In a statement Tuesday , the Hamas-led government in Gaza said it decided to ban all gatherings held under the guise of Friday prayers .",O O O B-tim O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-tim O O,"IN DT NN NNP , DT JJ NN IN NNP VBD PRP VBD TO VB DT NNS VBN IN DT NN IN NNP NNS ."
"Hamas accused Fatah of using the past weeks ' outdoor services to incite chaos , trouble and terrorist acts .",B-org O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBD NNP IN VBG DT JJ NNS POS NN NNS TO JJ NN , NN CC JJ NNS ."
"Fatah , headed by Palestinian President Mahmoud Abbas , organized the outdoor prayer sessions , accusing Hamas of driving Fatah members out of Gaza 's mosques .",B-geo O O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O B-org O O B-geo O O O B-geo O O O,"NNP , VBN IN JJ NNP NNP NNP , VBD DT JJ NN NNS , VBG NNP IN VBG NNP NNS IN IN NNP POS NNS ."
"During last week 's Friday prayers , Hamas forces fired shots into the air and beat and arrested Fatah protesters .",B-tim O O B-tim I-tim O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O,"IN JJ NN POS NNP NNS , NNP NNS VBD NNS IN DT NN CC VBN CC VBN NNP NNS ."
"President Abbas dismissed the Hamas-led government and named another administration , based in the West Bank .",B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org O,"NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN CC VBD DT NN , VBN IN DT NNP NNP ."
