Afghanistan 's President Hamid Karzai has fired at least 24 top police officials days after anti-U.S. riots in Kabul .,B-geo O B-per I-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,NNP POS NNP NNP NNP VBZ VBN IN JJS CD JJ NN NNS NNS IN JJ NNS IN NNP .
"Officials said Saturday the shake-up includes Kabul 's police chief , whose forces failed to prevent rioters from looting stores and setting fire to offices and cars in the capital .",O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBD NNP DT NN VBZ NNP POS NN NN , WP$ NNS VBD TO VB NNS IN VBG NNS CC VBG NN TO NNS CC NNS IN DT NN ."
The riots erupted Monday after a U.S. military truck accidentally crashed into civilian vehicles .,O O O B-tim O O B-geo O O O O O O O O,DT NNS VBD NNP IN DT NNP JJ NN RB VBD IN JJ NNS .
"U.S. military spokesman Tom Collins said an initial probe shows that mobs threw stones and fired shots after the accident , and that U.S. troops fired back in self-defense .",B-geo O O B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O B-tim O,"NNP JJ NN NNP NNP VBD DT JJ NN VBZ IN NNS VBD NNS CC VBD NNS IN DT NN , CC IN NNP NNS VBD RB IN NN ."
Afghan police say at least 20 people were killed and 160 wounded in the accident and subsequent unrest .,B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,JJ NNS VBP IN JJS CD NNS VBD VBN CC CD VBN IN DT NN CC JJ NN .
White House spokesman Tony Snow said President Bush spoke to Mr. Karzai and pledged an investigation .,B-org I-org O B-per I-per O B-per I-per O O B-per I-per O O O O O,NNP NNP NN NNP NNP VBD NNP NNP VBD TO NNP NNP CC VBD DT NN .
