"At least 16 bodies of people apparently killed execution-style have been found in a Sunni Muslim insurgent stronghold , Qaim in western Iraq .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O B-org O B-geo I-geo O,"IN JJS CD NNS IN NNS RB VBN NN VBP VBN VBN IN DT NNP NNP JJ NN , NNP IN JJ NNP ."
"Witnesses say many of the bodies were blindfolded , bound and clad in civilian clothes .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS VBP NN IN DT NNS VBD VBN , VBN CC VBN IN JJ NNS ."
It was unclear if the bodies were related to some 20 Iraqi soldiers that disappeared from the area Tuesday .,O O O O O O O O O O O B-gpe O O O O O O B-tim O,PRP VBD JJ IN DT NNS VBD VBN TO DT CD JJ NNS WDT VBD IN DT NN NNP .
"Separately , Iraqi authorities say gunmen shot dead two senior police officials in Kirkuk and another two police officers in Basra .",O O B-gpe O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O O B-geo O,"RB , JJ NNS VBP NNS VBD JJ CD JJ NN NNS IN NNP CC DT CD NN NNS IN NNP ."
The U.S. army said Friday it is launching a criminal investigation into the killing of two army officers at a base north of Baghdad on Tuesday .,O B-geo O O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O B-tim O,DT NNP NN VBD NNP PRP VBZ VBG DT JJ NN IN DT NN IN CD NN NNS IN DT NN NN IN NNP IN NNP .
"Officials first reported they had been killed by mortar fire , but say a later investigation ruled that out .",O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"NNS RB VBD PRP VBD VBN VBN IN NN NN , CC VBP DT JJ NN VBD DT RP ."
