"Israeli warplanes continued to pound targets in the Gaza Strip on Monday as Israel 's Defense Minister declared an "" all out war "" against the Islamic militant group Hamas and its Gaza government .",B-gpe O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O B-tim O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O B-org O O B-geo O O,JJ NNS VBD TO VB NNS IN DT NNP NNP IN NNP IN NNP POS NNP NNP VBD DT RQU DT IN NN LQU IN DT NNP JJ NN NNP CC PRP$ NNP NN .
"Palestinian officials say Israeli airstrikes have killed more than 300 people since Saturday , some of them civilians .",B-gpe O O B-gpe O O O O O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O,"JJ NNS VBP JJ NNS VBP VBN JJR IN CD NNS IN NNP , DT IN PRP NNS ."
Israel says rockets launched from Gaza against Israeli towns provoked the conflict .,B-geo O O O O B-geo O B-gpe O O O O O,NNP VBZ NNS VBN IN NNP IN JJ NNS VBD DT NN .
But some say the response has been disproportionate and may be an attempt by Israel to restore its image .,O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O O O O O,CC DT VBP DT NN VBZ VBN JJ CC MD VB DT NN IN NNP TO VB PRP$ NN .
