India says it is searching for the best technology on the market to set up an early warning system to prevent disasters like the recent Asian tsunamis .,B-org O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ PRP VBZ VBG IN DT JJS NN IN DT NN TO VB RP DT JJ NN NN TO VB NNS IN DT JJ JJ NNS .
Defense Minister Pranab Mukherjee told reporters in New Delhi the decision was made at a meeting Sunday between leaders of India 's major political parties and Prime Minister Manmohan Singh .,O B-per I-per I-per O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-tim O O O B-geo O O O O O B-per I-per I-per I-per O,NNP NNP NNP NNP VBD NNS IN NNP NNP DT NN VBD VBN IN DT NN NNP IN NNS IN NNP POS JJ JJ NNS CC NNP NNP NNP NNP .
Mr. Mukherjee said the participants also agreed to set up a disaster management authority that would be responsible for finding the best technology available .,B-per I-per O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O,NNP NNP VBD DT NNS RB VBD TO VB RP DT NN NN NN WDT MD VB JJ IN VBG DT JJS NN JJ .
"Currently , no such system exists for the Indian Ocean where a strong earthquake and tsunami off Indonesia 's coast on December 26 killed more than 153,000 people .",O O O O O O O O B-geo I-geo O O O O O O O B-geo O O O B-tim I-tim O O O O O O,"RB , DT JJ NN VBZ IN DT NNP NNP WRB DT JJ NN CC NN IN NNP POS NN IN NNP CD VBD JJR IN CD NNS ."
"Last Thursday , leaders of the affected nations agreed to set up a regional tsunami warning system at an emergency meeting in Jakarta .",O B-tim O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O O B-geo O,"JJ NNP , NNS IN DT JJ NNS VBD TO VB RP DT JJ NN NN NN IN DT NN NN IN NNP ."
