"Iran has asked to meet British , French and German negotiators Monday to discuss the stand-off over its nuclear program .",B-geo O O O O B-gpe O B-gpe O B-gpe O B-tim O O O O O O O O O,"NNP VBZ VBN TO VB JJ , JJ CC JJ NNS NNP TO VB DT NN IN PRP$ JJ NN ."
Iran requested the talks in Brussels for the same day delegates from those countries plus the United States and European Union meet in London to discuss whether to refer Iran to the U.N. Security Council .,B-geo O O O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O B-org I-org I-org I-org I-org O O B-geo O O O O O B-geo O O B-org I-org I-org O,NNP VBD DT NNS IN NNP IN DT JJ NN NNS IN DT NNS CC DT NNP NNPS CC NNP NNP VB IN NNP TO VB IN TO VB NNP TO DT NNP NNP NNP .
"The United States accuses Tehran of secretly trying to build an atomic bomb , and wants the Council to impose sanctions on Tehran for violating provisions of a key global nuclear treaty .",O B-org I-org O B-org I-org O O O O O O O O O O O B-org O O O O B-org O O O O O O O O O O,"DT NNP NNPS VBZ NNP IN RB VBG TO VB DT JJ NN , CC VBZ DT NNP TO VB NNS IN NNP IN VBG NNS IN DT JJ JJ JJ NN ."
Iran says its nuclear program is for developing electricity .,B-geo O O O O O O O O O,NNP VBZ PRP$ JJ NN VBZ IN VBG NN .
"In Jerusalem , visiting German Chancellor Angela Merkel said that Iran and its nuclear program pose a threat to the entire democratic world .",O B-geo O O B-gpe B-per I-per I-per O O B-geo O O O O O O O O O O O O O,"IN NNP , VBG JJ NNP NNP NNP VBD IN NNP CC PRP$ JJ NN VBP DT NN TO DT JJ JJ NN ."
